Chapter 1561: View At The Peak

This was one of the greatest pursuits of refinement path — combining all kinds of killer moves into one Gu worm!

For instance, mortal killer move self strength.

This move was a strength path killer move which Northern Plains Gu Immortal Su Xian Er had created for her daughter Hei Lou Lan. Its core was strength path, but it treaded on soul path and qi path, once it was activated, it could produce a human phantom, the phantom's appearance was lifelike and was a portrayal of the Gu Master's inner consciousness.

Moreover, this strength path phantom could act on its own and chase its enemies.

There were altogether fifty Gu worms used in forming this killer move.

According to Fang Yuan's current comprehension of the refinement path maxim: any killer move, be it of mortal or immortal level, could be considered as an incomplete recipe.

That was to say, self strength killer move's contents could be altered by taking out and adding in various kinds of Gu materials, continuously improving it until it becomes a Gu recipe for self strength Gu.

When the Gu recipe is perfected and self strength Gu is refined, activating just this Gu worm could produce a strength path phantom!

The benefits of this were clear as day.

A killer move condensed into a Gu worm reduced the amount of Gu worms used to only one. When the Gu Master activates it, not only would it be extremely convenient and fast, the primeval essence expended would also be much less than activating the killer move.

Another example was immortal killer move myriad self.

This move was Fang Yuan's unique creation, it combined enslavement and strength path, made from the merging of killer moves like dragon horse spirit, three heads six arms, rat epidemic, thunder explosion. leopard rush, horse barrage, three hearts combination soul, beast phantoms, six arm heavenly zombie king, and so on.

The core Immortal Gu were Self Strength, Pulling Mountain, Pulling Water, and Cleanse Soul. The supplementary Gu worms were all-out effort Gu, bitter strength Gu, borrow strength Gu, self-reliance Gu, refine essence spirit Gu, earth strength Gu, water strength Gu, wind strength Gu, lightning strength Gu, fire strength Gu, heavenly essence treasure king lotus Gu, lurking soul coat Gu, breath concealment Gu, group strength Gu, as well as all kinds of soul path mortal Gu.

This killer move clearly had lots of contents, it was extremely troublesome to activate.

It was because Fang Yuan had practised it frequently to the point where it had become a kind of instinct that he was able to use it freely in battle.

But in fact, it contained countless extremely complex steps.

What if this killer move was elevated and refined into a Gu?

Myriad self Immortal Gu!

It would clearly be extremely convenient and usable!

Fang Yuan would only need to transfer immortal essence and activate this Gu worm to produce tens of thousands of strength path phantoms, quickly and conveniently.

Fang Yuan did not have qualifications to do this before, but now with his quasi-supreme refinement path attainment, he had the ability to reach this level!

All kinds of killer moves refined into Gu worms!

Fang Yuan's heart thumped with excitement, but he did not lose his calm as he continued to ponder.

"I now have the ability to elevate killer moves into Gu worms."

"However, even though there are killer moves that can be refined into a Gu worm like myriad self, some killer moves cannot, like purple blood river formation or ignited thought flying rock. If these killer moves are condensed to their limit, they will comprise multiple Immortal Gu. Later on, I will need to coordinate and activate these multiple Immortal Gu to use the killer move."

"This method has benefits and demerits as well."

"The benefits are that it will be much more convenient and quick, the exhaustion of mind is also sharply reduced. But there are disadvantages, first, when myriad self killer move is condensed into a myriad self Immortal Gu, other Immortal Gu might be required to be used as Gu materials to refine it. Moreover, the power of just myriad self Immortal Gu might not be as strong as myriad self killer move."

Myriad self killer move used so many Immortal Gu and supplementary mortal Gu, while myriad self Gu would only be one Gu, if its rank was just rank six or rank seven, it would have limited dao marks, thus not enough power.

"Another thing is that when only a Gu worm is used, it will be easy to counter. Killer moves are complicated but they are also much more difficult for others to deduce and decipher."

Killer moves could also be continuously adjusted and elevated. For instance, myriad self killer move had the variation moves strength path giant hand and reverse flow protection seal.

But myriad self Gu itself would not have the potential to be elevated further.

"Of course, the overall benefits in elevating killer moves to a Gu worm is still much higher. Simply because the Gu could be used as the core of the original killer move anyway, raising its power and also preventing it from being deduced easily."

"Even if some Immortal Gu have to be used as Gu materials during the refinement process, I can refine them again!"

This ability would be extremely helpful to Fang Yuan.

Look at myriad self first, Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal was a variation move of this killer move. Since the start, it was extremely troublesome for Fang Yuan to activate reverse flow protection seal, he needed time to prepare for it because of the complicated procedures, and if there was even a slight mistake, the killer move would fail and inflict backlash to himself.

But if he had myriad self Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan could modify reverse flow protection seal, greatly simplifying its steps and activating it much faster.

With this, his battle strength would rise by another level!

Fang Yuan possessed a lot of killer moves, but the ones he used frequently were few.

Myriad self could be condensed and elevated, purple thought perception starlight could be condensed into multiple Immortal Gu, ancient sword dragon transformation could also be condensed into one Gu worm. By then, with myriad self Immortal Gu and ancient sword dragon Immortal Gu, he could use just two Immortal Gu to unleash the killer move myriad dragon!

Divination tortoise transformation, self cleansing killer move, hundred and eighty slaves, enslavement after victorious fight, and so on could also be condensed and elevated.

As Fang Yuan continued to ponder deep into this subject, he suddenly had another insight.

"Wait, be it killer moves or refining Gu, they are both basically the utilization of Dao."

"Isn't my reverse flow protection seal using Reverse Flow River? And didn't Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's orderly well use City Well?"

"City Well and Reverse Flow River are not Gu worms, why could they be used? Isn't it because they are secluded domains of heaven and earth, containing a huge amount of dao marks which are then used by us?"

Fang Yuan thought about it again, the nurture, use, and refinement of Gu worms were in essence, Dao.

There were too many Gu cultivation paths[1], fire path, water path, metal path, wood path, strength path, wisdom path, soul path, rule path, poison path, theft path…

"These paths all involve the nurture, use, and refinement of Gu, all involving Dao, this is in fact a kind of Dao that connects us to heaven and earth!"

Suddenly, the most classic phrase of the Gu cultivation world appeared in Fang Yuan's mind.

Man is the spirit of all beings, Gu are the essence of heaven and earth!

Never had Fang Yuan's understanding of this phrase been as profound as this moment.

"I want to condense and elevate killer moves into Gu worms, I need to take out Gu worms, add in Gu materials, and merge them into one."

"Immortal Gu are the fragments of the Great Dao, Gu materials are the accumulation of dao marks, as long as the path is the same, they can be substituted with each other."

"The reason why killer moves like reverse flow protection seal and orderly well can be activated is because Reverse Flow River and City Well have an abundant amount of dao marks that can take the place of Gu worms. From this point of view, these two killer moves have actually progressed from killer moves to Gu recipes!"

As Fang Yuan continued to ponder, many of his questions from before were being clearly solved.

Refinement path was actually rather special, although it was one path, it was related to every path. The comprehension gained from becoming a quasi-supreme grandmaster was much broader and deeper than any of Fang Yuan's accomplishments in other paths.

"Thinking about it, I am using landscape as before Immortal Gu to restore Dang Hun Mountain, it looks like I am using a Gu worm on the surface, but it can also be seen as using the killer move landscape as before. Any killer moves can be seen as an incomplete Gu recipe, thus from another angle, this is also Gu refinement."

"Only that what I am trying to refine is not a Gu worm, but a rank nine immortal material — Dang Hun Mountain!"

Fang Yuan was only rank seven, but he could refine rank nine immortal material?

The important thing here was the orderly well killer move, which was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's method. And back then, the orderly well killer move that Spectral Soul Demon Venerable used on Dang Hun Mountain was of rank nine level.

Realizing this point, Fang Yuan immediately got many new ideas for the restoration of Dang Hun Mountain.

"Dang Hun Mountain can be restored, it can also be used as a core like Reverse Flow River and form an immortal killer move!"

"Oh! I understand! The peak of soul cultivation recorded in Spectral Soul's true inheritance —the Three Headed Thousand Arms Demon Soul, isn't it an artificial secluded domain of heaven and earth?"

"Also, the rank nine killer move ghostly concealment of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable has countless dao marks working together and can function endlessly without adding any immortal essence, this is also an artificial secluded domain of heaven and earth!"

All along, Fang Yuan did not understand why ghostly concealment did not need immortal essence and could continue working all the time.

But now, he came to a realization.

Did Dang Hun Mountain require immortal essence? No.

Did Luo Po Valley require immortal essence? Also no.

Spectral Soul forcibly resisted the calamities and tribulations, although he used immortal essence to activate killer moves, in essence, he did not require immortal essence to possess his extremely powerful battle strength.

But this did not mean all kinds of dao marks could be casually piled together with enough quantity to form a secluded domain of heaven and earth, or form a killer move like ghostly concealment.

Dao marks needed to coordinate together.

Wasn't this coordination just Gu refinement? The required Gu materials needed to be selectively chosen.

Wasn't it nurturing Gu? The required food materials needed to be of a certain standard.

Wasn't it using Gu? The coordination between Gu worms was the coordination between dao marks.

Fang Yuan continued to ponder deeply for a long time before slowly opening his eyes.

Three days and three nights had passed.

He had absorbed the refinement path true meaning in a few hours, but his comprehension used up three days and three nights!

Fang Yuan's black eyes shone brightly, he looked even more unfathomable now.

"You…" Looking at Fang Yuan's eyes, Lang Ya land spirit became uncertain with shock.

"What's wrong?" Fang Yuan asked.

Lang Ya land spirit sighed: "The air you gave off a moment ago made me feel like I was looking at Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable!"

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable… any Gu Venerable was publicly recognized as a supreme grandmaster of their own path.

Fang Yuan was already able to reach their boundary with his refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment.

He was no longer looking up at the towering mountains, from the level below, he was able to observe the scenery!

This was the view at the peak of Gu cultivation!

[1] Path is also read as Dao in Chinese. Back

Chapter 1562: Emperor Yama!

"Slumbering lightning python!" Lang Ya land spirit gave a loud shout.

At the next moment, lightning bolts flashed and interwove together, forming a huge dragon-like lightning python.

Lightning was yang, python was yin. The lightning python contained yin and yang, not only was the wild nature of the lightning curbed, it even showed some gentleness.

As a result, the lightning python was not ferocious, but graceful and lovely.

It moved in a zigzag pattern, slowly coiling around a mountain-like elephant shaped rock. The python constantly crushed the rocks into the finest powder.

Refinement path had four publicly recognized strongest immortal killer moves to deal with immortal materials. One of them was slumbering lightning python.

Lang Ya land spirit originated from Long Hair Ancestor, he naturally had extreme proficiency in them.

This killer move was elevated to rank eight by using rank eight refinement path Immortal Gu.

They could not process this rank eight immortal material elephant armor mountain without the rank eight slumbering lightning python.

This was an immemorial immortal material of information path.

Lang Ya land spirit had already been processing immortal materials for several hours now, over ten rank eight immortal materials had already been processed, these immortal materials were divided into various categories and were all of information path.

Slumbering lightning python gradually dissipated, elephant armor mountain had completely been turned into fine powder. The powder gathered with other immortal materials, and under Lang Ya land spirit's methods, they all formed a constantly rotating multicolored whirlpool.

"It is done, you can stop the immortal formation." Lang Ya land spirit let out a breath of relief, extremely exhausted.

Immediately, a hairy man Gu Immortal removed the refinement path immortal formation.

With the immortal formation gone, the aura of the multicolored whirlpool immediately started to spread, the distant wisdom Gu was like a kitten that had smelled fish as it flew over and jumped right into the whirlpool, looking drunk.

"So wisdom Gu had such a trait." Fang Yuan said with a moved expression.

"According to legends, wisdom Gu's recipe contains a large amount of information path immortal materials. In nature, a wild wisdom Gu can only complete its advancement in areas that are full of information path dao marks." Lang Ya land spirit said.

Fang Yuan immediately understood.

Wisdom Gu's Gu recipe was not recorded in both Spectral Soul's true inheritance and Lang Ya true inheritance. Only Heavenly Court had some records.

Fang Yuan could not control wisdom Gu, but he could move this lump of multicolored whirlpool from afar.

As for those over four thousand years of lifespan Gu, he had already collected them after refinement path true meaning.

"I had to trouble first supreme elder to personally act, I will gradually repay this debt." Fang Yuan spoke in a sincere way to Lang Ya land spirit.

Although the method of moving wisdom Gu was simple, the cost was not anything small.

Various rank eight immortal materials had to be merged to create this temporary multicolored whirlpool. And this whirlpool would gradually dissipate not long after, it had no use besides deceiving wisdom Gu to change location.

This cost was naturally borne by Fang Yuan.

After discussing with Lang Ya land spirit, both sides came to an agreement to let Fang Yuan owe the cost for the time being and not immediately pay. After all, Fang Yuan had just been through an intense battle, he urgently needed to fill his immortal essence reserves.

This was also because of the rise in Fang Yuan's status. Before this, he would not have been able to enjoy such great benefits.

But now, after he had pummeled Thunder Ghost True Monarch, he had the dominant status when communicating and negotiating with Lang Ya land spirit.

"Time is tight, I will immediately go into closed cultivation and use all my strength to deduce a way as fast as possible to get out of this predicament." Fang Yuan said.

"Good, good, then I won't disturb you." Joy flashed by Lang Ya land spirit's eyes, his exhausted look easing by a lot.

Fang Yuan returned to his cloud city.

Feng Jiu Ge's group had invaded Lang Ya blessed land and taken several cloud cities. But by some luck, Fang Yuan's cloud city had evaded this calamity and was still safe.

This might also be related to Fang Yuan's powerful luck.

Fang Yuan entered closed cultivation, the other variant human Gu Immortals wanted to get close to him, but Fang Yuan did not meet any of them including those of the snowman race.

Inside sovereign immortal aperture.

Immortal killer move — Strength Reversing Life and Death!

"This move is a strength path killer move, it is not too suitable for my time path clone, I need to modify it into time path in the future."

Fang Yuan's time path clone immediately turned back into an immortal zombie and arrived in front of wisdom Gu.

After a while, wisdom Gu erupted with the light of wisdom, Fang Yuan's time path clone sat cross-legged and began to think rapidly in the light of wisdom.

The issue of the dao marks left by Feng Jiu Ge's group in Lang Ya blessed land was shelved aside by Fang Yuan.

Comparing Lang Ya blessed land's safety and his own, his was of course more important.

"Right now, the most crucial thing is to elevate yama. Otherwise, once I come out of the blessed land, the immortal essence to maintain yama is really too high."

If yama was not elevated, Fang Yuan would be in an extremely passive situation.

If his location was exposed and Heavenly Court continued to make deductions, they would learn of even more secrets which Fang Yuan absolutely did not want to see.

Previously, Fang Yuan had thought it was much better to use ghost official garment along with ghostly concealment's power to block Heavenly Court's deductions.

The killer move yama was a successful result of his attempts.

But now, Heavenly Court had a lot of clues on Fang Yuan, the current yama was not enough to protect him.

This deduction continued for over a month.

Of course, the light of wisdom was not used the whole time.

The whole process went smoothly for the most part, because Fang Yuan had great grandmaster attainment in theft path, quasi-supreme in refinement path, and also had good grasp over ghostly concealment, ghost official garment and other killer moves. The process slowed slightly because of his slightly lacking soul path attainment.

The biggest difficulty was during the mid-late stage. But it was also resolved after Fang Yuan added rank eight Immortal Gu Soul Beast Token.

The killer move yama had a huge transformation, Fang Yuan renamed it to emperor yama!

Emperor yama had four main components. Ghostly concealment, ghost official garment, Soul Beast Token and myriad self.

"Although I have deduced emperor yama, it can only be considered an initial version, I will need to activate it and constantly adjust it."

"My main body will be in charge of this. As for the clone, it will continue to deduce the way to deal with the dao marks left by Feng Jiu Ge."

Just like this, Fang Yuan stayed in Lang Ya blessed land for about half a month.

Fang Yuan finally came out of his closed cultivation.

His clone had already completed its deduction task, Fang Yuan found the method to resolve the problem of the dao marks left by Feng Jiu Ge.

He gave this method to Lang Ya land spirit. The latter's expression immediately changed at this, cursing Heavenly Court's sinister craftiness.

It turned out that if refinement path methods were used to get rid of these dao marks, it would instead help these dao marks. The killer move self cleansing was also ineffective. Heavenly Court was not a match for Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in soul path, but their refinement path foundation was not any weaker than Lang Ya Sect. After all, among the three supreme grandmasters of refinement path, only Long Hair Ancestor was a hairy man, while the other two were humans, and most of their inheritances were gathered by Heavenly Court.

Fang Yuan was a quasi-supreme grandmaster, he saw through this scheme and even provided the simplest way to deal with it.

Fang Yuan could quickly deal with these dao marks when Lang Ya blessed land was relocated. Other methods would require more than ten years.

So the question returned back to the starting point - Lang Ya blessed land's relocation.

"What do we do? Maybe Heavenly Court intentionally made this arrangement to force us to relocate the blessed land." Lang Ya land spirit was very worried.

Fang Yuan also had the same worry.

Heavenly Court had not made any movement in this period of time, but it did not mean they had given up. It was more likely that they had already made preparations and were waiting for Lang Ya blessed land to expose its location.

But if they didn't relocate, Heavenly Court would find this location sooner or later.

"Looks like we can only prepare to relocate. This is the recipe for myriad self Immortal Gu, if it is refined, it will be a huge boost to my battle strength." Fang Yuan said as he gave a Gu recipe to Lang Ya land spirit.

This was the result of his recent deduction.

Using his refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment, Fang Yuan was confident this was already the most outstanding recipe possible.

"Myriad self Immortal Gu?" Lang Ya land spirit's attention was immediately attracted. Although his obsession was different from the previous land spirit, he had originated from Long Hair Ancestor after all.

"If your Immortal Gu recipe is refined, it will be at least a rank seven. But, several of the immortal materials are in scarce amounts in the sect's storage. It will be difficult to purchase them in a short time period even from treasure yellow heaven." Lang Ya land spirit gave a bitter smile.

"No worries, I will gather these immortal materials myself." Fang Yuan waved his hand, giving a slight smile, his gaze deep and eerie.

With the new emperor yama killer move in his hands, he intended to use this chance to test out this move's power in a real battle!

Chapter 1563: Meng Tu

Southeast of the northern icy plain, north of Inkman City, northwest of poison grassland, and at the extreme south of Meng tribe, there was a place called autumn blade plain.

This was a special land created naturally, it was flat with no grass growing on it.

Meng Tu walked step by step in autumn blade plain.

He was tall and well-built, and had a bronze luster to his skin. He was wearing an armored vest that revealed his shoulders. His pants were rolled up, revealing his calves.

He was walking barefoot.

The plain and natural ground was as sharp as knives, as Meng Tu walked on this silver soil, it was like walking on a mountain of blades, as his every step left behind a trail of blood.

But his expression was without a change. He was silent, his eyes closed, and his brows slightly knitted as he pondered over a doubt in his mind.

"Autumn blade plain is full of blade path dao marks, forming countless edge Gu naturally. I have been walking back and forth barefooted for several years now, but what is it that I am lacking for which I am still unable to make a breakthrough in my blade path attainment level?"

Blade path was an extremely small path, it could not be compared to paths like metal path, fire path, earth path and so on.

Sword path could not be left out when mentioning blade path.

These two paths were deeply interconnected and yet conflicting with each other. Because the origin of these two paths was the same, that was edge Gu.

Regarding edge Gu, it was recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>. Ren Zu was walking in Ordinary Abyss where some places were swampy, it was easy to get stuck in the mud, and the stench was foul. Some places were full of thorns, sharp pointy tips were everywhere, Ren Zu suffered a lot of injuries. In some parts of the ground, there were also edge Gu. When Ren Zu stepped on the ground, his soles were injured by the sharp edges, his injuries became larger as blood flowed, when he walked, the pain could be felt striking deep within himself.

Edge Gu was the origin of both blade path and sword path.

Many wild edge Gu were produced in nature, autumn blade plain was one of the few edge Gu production areas in five regions, and was controlled by the super force Meng tribe.

Meng Tu was a rank seven Gu Immortal who cultivated blade path and had peak rank seven battle strength. He was a genius when he was young, and grew rapidly, becoming a famous expert of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, and was one of the pillars of Meng tribe.

Several years ago, he gave a request to the tribe's Gu Immortals, wanting to stay in this autumn blade plain. On one hand, he could look after this important resource point of the tribe, while on the other hand, he was doing this in consideration of his own cultivation.

His blade path had been stuck at quasi-great grandmaster level, he wanted to use this autumn blade plain, by imitating Ren Zu's actions, to truly step into great grandmaster level!

But over these years, although he made some gains, he was always obstructed by a thin veil from stepping into great grandmaster.

Meng Tu had a determined personality, he refused to give up even after not seeing results for several years.

"Sigh, breaking through to great grandmaster realm is truly difficult! The tribe's supreme elders all praised me as a blade path genius rarely seen once in a thousand years, but I am still only at quasi-great grandmaster level even after hundreds of years."

"Although I have already sensed the thin veil obstructing me which seems to be so near to me, it feels like it is far away in the horizon and is as difficult as stepping into heaven!"

"But I need to continue walking, this method still has some effect. Some day, I will definitely be able to become a blade path great grandmaster!"

"Huh? Who is it?"

Right at this time, the Gu formation that covered the whole of autumn blade plain was destroyed abruptly, revealing the clear blue sky.

A figure descended with overwhelming aura, directly charging at Meng Tu without even saying a word!

"Such guts!" Meng Tu shouted in fury, he did not dodge, instead counterattacking with a knife-hand stance.

A loud sound resulted from the collision, the attacker was stable like a mountain, while Meng Tu was sent flying from the force

"My immortal killer move might look like it has no momentum, but all its power is contained within, I can easily break the ordinary defenses of rank seven Gu Immortals. But this person is uninjured after taking my attack head-on! This is a powerful enemy!"

Meng Tu was surprised, he quickly stabilized his footing and shouted at the attacker: "State your name. You dare to intrude on my Meng tribe's territory!"

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan laughed madly, saying in a completely altered voice: "Meng Tu, of course you don't recognize me, but that is not an issue, because the dead do not need to know too much."

Myriad self Immortal Gu's recipe required an enormous amount of edge Gu, more importantly, it required a kind of special rank seven immortal material that was deep under autumn blade plain - drinking blade wine.

This wine was not produced naturally; it was an unusual product formed from the bloodstains left by Meng Tu, which had seeped deep into the ground and merged with this place's blade path dao marks.

Fang Yuan knew from his first life's memories that Meng Tu bitterly cultivated here to breakthrough to blade path great grandmaster, but was never able to meet with that opportunity.

Meng Tu failed to breakthrough, he imitated Ren Zu by inserting edge Gu in his heart to deepen his understanding of blade path. The killer move he created was incomplete and had serious hidden side-effects, Meng Tu's mind gradually started to be affected and he would often fall into a mad demonic state.

Meng Tu also knew that this was not the ideal method, but he kept on insisting on cultivating relentlessly, hiding it from others.

When the five regions chaotic war started, Meng Tu took part in battles, however, the side-effect started up during a battle, he fell into a crazed demonic state, killing his own tribe's Gu Immortals.

After Meng Tu regained his senses, he concealed all traces while also fabricating false reasons, concealing this from the tribe.

However, as this happened suddenly, Meng Tu was not able to deal with the traces completely, Northern Plains' Gu Immortals slowly noticed some clues and found the truth.

Meng Tu faced huge pressure, Heavenly Court came and secretly instigated him.

Meng Tu had initially felt fortunate and wanted to use Heavenly Court to make contributions and make up for his mistakes, but how could Heavenly Court be schemed against by him, a blade path Gu Immortal?

Meng Tu was instead schemed against by Heavenly Court, he made mistakes again and again until he had no way out other than to side with Heavenly Court.

To support this chess piece, Heavenly Court deduced the opportunity to advance to great grandmaster, which was the drinking blade wine deep underground in this place.

Meng Tu followed Heavenly Court's guidance and came to autumn blade plain, he dug the ground and extracted a large amount of drinking blade wine.

When he took a small sip, his organs felt like they were being cut by blades, when he took a large sip, he felt so much pain that he wished for death, by the time he took the third sip, he had advanced to blade path great grandmaster.

From then onwards, he completely devoted himself to Heavenly Court and became the spy with second highest status in Northern Plains after Prince Feng Xian.

Later on, due to a lucky coincidence, his identity was exposed by Ma Hong Yun, but that was another story altogether.

Fang Yuan had deduced and confirmed that this place contained drinking blade wine, although the quantity was not much, he only needed a small amount. As for this Meng Tu, Fang Yuan had carefully picked him to test his emperor yama killer move.

Fang Yuan could not find a rank eight Gu Immortal to test the might of his emperor yama, that would be looking for trouble. As for ordinary rank seven Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan had no use for them. However, Meng Tu, who had peak rank seven battle strength, and was already renowned as a blade path quasi-great grandmaster, was an extremely good choice.

So Fang Yuan made a long trip to autumn blade plain, directly looking for trouble with Meng Tu.

"The attack just now was Meng Tu's hidden killer move, its power is beyond ordinary, but I could block it with just emperor yama. This defensive method is pretty good."

Fang Yuan assessed in his mind.

He had already activated emperor yama.

He was covered in a yellowish-brown robe of an emperor, turning into a ten feet giant.

The giant had a crown on its head which had strings of pearls in front and back. Its face was deep and dark, as if it was shrouded by a layer of fog, or was a dark whirlpool. Its sleeves were long and wide, it had a jade belt on his waist, and a bronze armor was covering his chest and back. The surface of the robe was adorned with golden threads that had weaved into thousands of ghostly monsters who stood orderly and without moving, giving a dignified aura.

Meng Tu's attack was not without any effect, the thin bronze armor on emperor yama's chest had a dent.

But with a little consumption of Fang Yuan's soul foundation, this dent immediately bulged up, restoring itself.

This was the specialty of emperor yama!

Rank nine ghostly concealment did not expend anything and also functioned on its own, while ghost official garment relied on soul foundation.

Emperor yama, which was a combination of the these two moves, did not require immortal essence, but spent Fang Yuan's soul foundation!

"Meng Tu, you are nothing much. You have cultivated here for several years, what new killer moves have you created? It will be a real pity if you don't use them before your death." Fang Yuan provoked.

Meng Tu laughed from anger, then looked at Fang Yuan with pity: "No matter who you are, you are seeking your own death by challenging me here! There used to be a defensive immortal formation here, but do you know why I persuaded the tribe to take it back?"

"Because as long as I am here, there is no need for an immortal formation to guard this place!"

Meng Tu fiercely stomped on the ground with his right foot.

At the next moment, the ground shook as endless blade lights surged up, countless blade path phantoms gathered into a huge army, surrounding Fang Yuan tightly.

Chapter 1564: Decent, I Suppose

In a blink of an eye, Fang Yuan was already surrounded tightly by countless blade path phantoms. Not only this, the endless blade lights filled the whole sky, isolating inside from outside.

"Whoever you may be, your defensive killer move is indeed amazing!" Meng Tu was protected by many layers of blade path phantoms, he gazed at Fang Yuan deeply before smiling and rubbing his hands to ease the numbness from the previous force.

"But!" Meng Tu raised his head slightly at the tall emperor yama, his gaze filled with pity: "You should never have come to find trouble for me here in autumn blade plain."

"Hehe, actually, it was not wrong to find trouble for me here, but your timing is really bad, if it were when I had just come here, you might still have some chance at survival. But now, hehehe…"

Meng Tu laughed, holding his hands behind his back as he shook his head.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan continued after Meng Tu's words: "But now, this place is already filled with your traces. Since years back, you have been comprehending blade path here, trying to breakthrough to blade path great grandmaster realm. Thus, you can greatly influence the dao marks of this place to form an environment that is close to an immortal battlefield killer move[1], like this scene in front of me."

"You…" Meng Tu's expression immediately changed. He had believed no one knew of his trump card, and thus had never expected Fang Yuan to not only be unsurprised, but also speak of his trump card in such a familiar way.

Fang Yuan's low and deep voice continued: "Do you know why I am looking for trouble with you? It is precisely because you have this method which can form such a battlefield environment. This is close to an immortal battlefield, but it is still not a true immortal battlefield, with an essential difference that your influence is already at its maximum, you are unable to control it at will, so it might have trapped me, but aren't you also trapped?"

Meng Tu's pupils shrunk rapidly, his pleased mood had completely disappeared.

"Who exactly are you?" He asked Fang Yuan nervously.

Fang Yuan chuckled, looking at his surroundings: "Although your blade path phantoms are in high numbers, their quality is not up to par. It happens that I also have a similar method, why don't we spar a little."

Fang Yuan's yellowish-brown emperor robe suddenly emitted countless howls and shrieks. Next, those ghostly monsters weaved on the surface of the robe came alive, and started to move, then jumped out of Fang Yuan's emperor yama robe one by one, turning from small to large!

These ghostly monsters had human shapes, but they all had malevolent and terrifying faces, knife-like claws, and bloodshot eyes, looking quite horrifying.

"Kill!" Meng Tu narrowed his eyes, as he mobilized his blade path phantoms to charge towards these ghostly monsters.

These blade path phantoms all had his appearance, but their faces were vague, and compared to the size of the ghostly monsters, they were like rats against carriage wheels.

The ghostly monsters howled and spread their huge arms like a tall tree waving its branches.

Bang bang bang, all the blade path phantoms on their way were destroyed.

The monsters ran amok while letting out crazed screams and howls, easily crushing all the blade path phantoms on their way.

"These ghostly monsters are really powerful, each having rank seven battle strength!" Meng Tu had rich battle experience, as he noticed this with just a short observation. His heart immediately felt as heavy as a mountain, his eyelids twitched violently.

"But it doesn't matter, my blade path phantoms are created from the natural dao marks in autumn blade plain which are almost endless. Although the quality is not good, it can be made up with the quantity!"

Meng Tu quickly calmed down.

"Hmm, these yama children have quite the battle strength." Fang Yuan assessed inwardly and was pleased.

These ghostly monsters originated from the ancient soul beasts that Fang Yuan had gathered in green ghost desert.

After Fang Yuan deduced the killer move emperor yama, he modified these ancient soul beasts, changing them into human shapes and turning them into yama children.

This inspiration came from blood deity Immortal Gu's recipe.

Fang Yuan was a grandmaster in blood path, with the light of wisdom's help, he had already completed the blood deity Immortal Gu recipe.

The current Fang Yuan, with his refinement path quasi-supreme attainment, could change any Immortal Gu recipe into an immortal killer move.

So Fang Yuan was able to grasp the immortal killer move blood deity.

The killer move Yama child was deduced from consulting not only blood deity, but also some main contents of Spectral Soul's true inheritance.

For example, soul beast modification.

Spectral Soul modified the soul beasts in the Door of Life and Death, causing them to become loyal to him, they even faced Duke Long without fearing death.

There was also another soul path immortal killer move — Life and Death Retrieval.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had created this immortal killer move by comprehending the secluded domain of heaven and earth, the Door of Life and Death.

What kind of place was the Door of Life and Death?

When any living being die, their soul would return to the Door of Life and Death. It was only when Red Lotus Demon Venerable damaged fate Gu that the Door of Life and Death's power weakened greatly, allowing countless souls to linger behind in the living world to gradually turn into soul beasts.

Life and death retrieval had the power to let the Gu Immortal retrieve souls from the Door of Life and Death.

Fang Yuan completely merged this move into emperor yama, giving his yama children the ability to instantly return.

Soon, a yama child gave a miserable shriek, its thigh was broken and it was knocked down onto the ground, countless blade path phantoms immediately flocked towards it.

But Fang Yuan willed: "Return."

At the next moment, this yama child immediately turned into fog which flew back into Fang Yuan's emperor robe, turning back into a monster image that was motionless, but was filled with injuries and a broken thigh.

"It can do this?" Meng Tu was astonished once again, his hands, which had been held behind his back, were loosened as his gaze towards Fang Yuan turned somewhat stunned.

This was too outrageous!

Meng Tu had been intending to rely on quantity to kill every yama child, but had not expected them to be able to return like this.

Theoretically, any killer moves could be deciphered, but Meng Tu was a blade path Gu Immortal and not a wisdom path Gu Immortal. Even if he was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, against a rank eight killer move like emperor yama, unless he was a wisdom path great expert, how could he decipher it on the spot?

Even Fairy Zi Wei could not decipher it on the spot.

When deducing reverse flow protection seal, she had to repeatedly gather clues from battles, continuously accumulating them before she was able to gain some results.

Fang Yuan's emperor yama used ghostly concealment as its base. This rank nine killer move was an artificial secluded domain of heaven and earth at the same level as Reverse Flow River, how could Meng Tu break it?

Meng Tu simply could not deduce it, he could only summon his courage to continue fighting with Fang Yuan.

However, the yama children's quantity was limited, although they killed a large amount of blade path phantoms, the injuries accumulated to a serious degree and they were recalled by Fang Yuan.

On the battlefield, there were fewer and fewer yama children, while blade path phantoms seemed to be unlimited. After all, Fang Yuan had limited time, he was not able to modify enough soul beasts.

"This battle has likely weakened autumn blade plain's foundation by more than half." Meng Tu's expression was gloomy.

The price he had to pay was high as he was using the whole of autumn blade plain, the future benefits of Meng tribe, to engage in a battle of attrition with Fang Yuan.

But regardless of how much he had to sacrifice, Meng Tu still persisted with this tactic.

Fang Yuan's previous words had truly scared him, he had already regarded Fang Yuan as the strongest enemy in his life, so he was cautiously using any available methods to deal with Fang Yuan.

But, this was also what Fang Yuan intended to attain with his words.

Only this Meng Tu could be the best whetstone to test his emperor yama killer move.

There were less than ten yama children left and they stood on guard beside Fang Yuan, while the unlimited number of blade path phantoms surged towards them like a tidal wave.

"The speed of recovery is passable." Fang Yuan's expression did not change, he had been standing on the same spot from the start, unmoving like a millennium old tree.

By now, the first yama child he had recalled to his emperor robe had already recovered completely.

When these yama children modified from soul beasts returned to the robe, they would start recovering from their injuries. Naturally, it expended Fang Yuan's soul foundation.

This involved a profundity of Gu refinement.

The yama child was still a soul beast and the healing, from another angle, was like a Gu refinement process.

"If I bring out these recovered yama children, I wonder what expression Meng Tu will have." Fang Yuan smiled inwardly, but did not do this, instead using another method.

"Let me see emperor yama's offensive prowess." At the next moment, Fang Yuan inwardly called out: "Soul explosion!"

The emperor yama suddenly spread its arms, its whole body shook as vast waves of darkness erupted out from it.

The yama children were completely safe in the dark waves, only shaking like they were being blown at by a fierce wind.

But those blade path phantoms were like weak candle-flames under a storm, instantly extinguishing!

In an instant, the whole battlefield was cleared, the unlimited blade lights were instantly destroyed.

Meng Tu was sent back hundreds of steps from the soul explosion and was half-kneeling on the ground, a glaring radiance was being emitted by his whole body as he pushed his defensive killer moves to their limits.

"Such power!" Meng Tu quickly stood up and looked up at Fang Yuan with a shaken expression: "This killer move is truly amazing, it should be a combination move containing both offense and defense! Its defense is so strong, and there is also the powerful method of sending out troops, but its strongest point is its offensive power! I have never seen or heard of this killer move, was it created by this person? If so, then who in the world is this person who can create such a killer move?"

"This soul explosion effect is decent, I suppose." Fang Yuan gave a nod of approval.

One yama child was completely used to create the power of a peak rank seven killer move, but it still did not reach rank eight.

"Defense, yama child, recovery, soul explosion… these aspects are all at the peak of rank seven. But emperor yama's true power lies in two other aspects. Let's try this."

Just as Fang Yuan was thinking, Meng Tu had already charged over, shouting: "Come, try my killer move, heaven and earth blade!"

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

In an instant, a ghost hand, as if from the netherworld, that was as large as a handheld fan appeared behind Meng Tu and directly entered his body. It then came out, disappearing from sight once again.

Puff!

Meng Tu suddenly coughed out a mouthful of blood, the core Immortal Gu of heaven and earth blade was robbed, the killer move failed and the backlash immediately inflicted serious injuries on him.

"What's going on? Where is my Immortal Gu?!" Meng Tu's heart shook in unprecedented fright!

[1] So as I pray... Back

Chapter 1565: Forced To Die

Previously, in green ghost desert, Fang Yuan had used great thief ghost hand to steal rank eight Immortal Gu Soul Beast Token.

Great thief ghost hand was only a rank seven move, and its core was rank seven great thief Immortal Gu. But with the help of the killer move yama, its power rose to the point where it could steal a rank eight Immortal Gu from the legendary immemorial soul beast Qing Chou's body.

Back then, great thief ghost hand's effective range was extremely short, which required Fang Yuan to get near the target.

After returning, Fang Yuan modified yama, adding in great thief ghost hand to form the completely new emperor yama killer move. Right now, great thief ghost hand not only had a long range of effectiveness, it also had the ability to conceal itself.

It was not strange for Meng Tu to be struck by it, instead it would be unusual if he was not struck.

"This is your blade path Immortal Gu? Oh, a white butterfly's appearance and the size of a fist, is it bladewing Immortal Gu?" Fang Yuan recalled the great thief ghost hand, he was holding a rank seven Immortal Gu in his hand, which looked like a butterfly with layers of exquisite cloud patterns on its wings.

Cold sweat dripped from Meng Tu's forehead, he was lying weakly on the ground, he looked at Fang Yuan with narrowed eyes and spoke in a hoarse voice: "You… you actually seized an Immortal Gu from my immortal aperture? Did you obtain a true inheritance of Thieving Heaven?"

"True inheritance of Thieving Heaven… hehe, your guess is correct, I obtained one indeed." Fang Yuan sneered as he stored bladewing Immortal Gu into his immortal aperture right in front of Meng Tu, sealing it in Heaven Sealing Mountain.

Meng Tu's eyelids twitched violently.

Bladewing Immortal Gu was not his vital Gu, but he had raised it from its rank five mortal Gu stage. He had failed dozens of times and expended a huge amount of resources, as well as time and energy to raise it. He had never expected there would be a day where it would be forcibly seized.

Anger surged in Meng Tu's heart. But even more than anger was fear.

Why did Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable become a calamity of the world in the past? Wasn't it because of his Immortal Gu stealing methods? Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could even steal things that were hidden in immortal apertures. And now, Fang Yuan had reproduced Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's method, the nightmare that he had casted upon an entire era was like a thick layer of dark clouds that shrouded Meng Tu's heart.

Meng Tu healed his injuries to the best of his abilities while speaking with a tensed expression: "Since you are a theft path Gu Immortal and have also inherited Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's true inheritance, then you should be aware of the rule set by your ancestor Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable back then. Thieves have their own honor, always leave room for appeasement and never act too overbearingly! Since you have taken my bladewing Immortal Gu, what else do you want? If you want anything else, I can lend them to you."

Back then, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had rampaged throughout the world, with no one able to stop him.

But Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was not evil by nature, he was good natured at his core, he advocated honor and glory. All he wanted was to return home, his cultivation journey and resources stolen were meant for this purpose.

After the five regions' Gu Immortals knew of his goal, as well as being aware that they could not defend against Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's methods, whenever they ran into Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, they would lend anything Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable wanted as long as it did not endanger their lives.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable did not have insatiable greed, after he obtained the things he wanted, he spared the lives of the Gu Immortals and let them off. In most cases, he only took what he wanted, he did not care about other Immortal Gu or immortal materials no matter how high their value was.

Since Fang Yuan inherited Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's true inheritance and was Thieving Heaven's inheritor, Meng Tu knew he could not win, and since the situation was extremely bad, he directly asked for mercy.

Fang Yuan frowned, mumbling: "If you truly want to do this, it is also not impossible…"

Just as he was speaking, Fang Yuan's eyes suddenly glinted, pushing his hands forward as he activated immortal killer move soul explosion!

A vast wave of darkness immediately surged towards Meng Tu.

Meng Tu did not dodge, instead laughing: "You really thought that I, Meng Tu, am a person who begs for mercy?!"

Just as he ended his words, he was submerged by the soul explosion's dark waves. But shortly afterwards, his body let out bright blade lights as he boldly self-detonated!

Boom!!

A loud explosion with terrifying might threw chaos into the whole of autumn blade plain!

After the explosion, not even the corpse of Meng Tu remained, while Fang Yuan's emperor yama was mostly destroyed.

The quasi-immortal battlefield that covered the entirety of autumn blade plain also completely disintegrated, and autumn blade plain's surface sank by five to six feet.

Fang Yuan quickly used his investigative methods to scan the battlefield, and after several scans, he finally confirmed Meng Tu was truly dead.

"Meng Tu actually self-detonated!" Fang Yuan was surprised and had a strange expression, he had not expected Meng Tu would be so bold and direct.

This was clearly somewhat different from the memories in Fang Yuan's first life.

If Meng Tu was someone who disregarded life and death, why would he have sided with Heavenly Court?

It was because of this, Fang Yuan had felt Meng Tu was not strong-willed, so when Meng Tu asked for mercy, Fang Yuan subconsciously chose to believe him.

Naturally, Fang Yuan never intended to let go of Meng Tu, but when he was about to make a move, Meng Tu had self-detonated one step ahead of him!

Such determination and will was truly too straightforward.

"Maybe Meng Tu's nature was gradually changed by all kinds of events. After all, humans do change. Also, in my first life, it was Heavenly Court who made a move, they definitely used some exquisite methods and plans to instigate Meng Tu."

Fang Yuan shook his head as he gave one final glance at autumn blade plain before flying away quickly.

Almost all the edge Gu in autumn blade plain were destroyed after this battle. But their growth potential had become bigger, because with Meng Tu's self-detonation, all his blade path dao marks were engraved in this land.

Fang Yuan had obtained little benefit in this battle.

Besides testing out emperor yama and obtaining the rank seven bladewing Immortal Gu, he did not achieve his original intention, which was Meng Tu's soul and immortal aperture.

Meng Tu's firm resolution had decreased Fang Yuan's benefits, his goal was achieved — even in death, he did not let the enemy obtain the maximum benefits.

After Fang Yuan displayed great thief ghost hand, Meng Tu knew that his Immortal Gu could be stolen one after the other by Fang Yuan, with his serious injuries and the fact he was trapped at this place, he had no hope of escaping so he resolutely chose to self-detonate. From his point of view, it was a rather sensible action.

"It has always been difficult to prepare oneself for death, this Meng Tu has true courage! In my first life, he sided with Heavenly Court, he was cast aside by his tribe and Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world, sullying his reputation as a shameless person. This life, although he died, he will definitely have the glory of a fallen hero." Fang Yuan sighed inwardly.

Regardless, his goal was still achieved after the battle.

Before stealing bladewing Immortal Gu, he had secretly taken out the drinking blade wine from deep underground. In the process, he had casually stolen hundreds of edge Gu which was better than nothing.

Fang Yuan retreated extremely quickly.

Autumn blade plain was in the territory of Meng tribe, when Meng Tu saw Fang Yuan intruding, he would have definitely sent a message to the tribe.

So not long later, Meng tribe will sense Meng Tu's death and many Gu Immortals would come to inspect autumn blade plain.

The items were already obtained, Fang Yuan was looking towards the future when Northern Plains obstructed Heavenly Court's expansion, so it was not worthwhile to kill these Northern Plains Gu Immortals, as it would weaken Northern Plains and be basically helping Heavenly Court.

As he was not in a fight, emperor yama's robe gradually shrunk to a silk-like clothing, while the thin bronze armor on Fang Yuan's chest and back stuck to his muscles.

"Oh? Someone is deducing me." After a while of flying, Fang Yuan's expression suddenly changed.

Meng tribe was a super force and had specially nurtured a wisdom path Gu Immortal. They were definitely shaken by Meng Tu's death and were sure to look for the culprit.

Fang Yuan held his breath, carefully looking at his emperor yama killer move.

Emperor yama's robe gradually expanded and continued to expand along with the increase in intensity of the deduction of Meng tribe's wisdom path Gu Immortal.

Fang Yuan was defending against the other side's deduction while also calculating his soul foundation expenditure.

Meng tribe's wisdom path Gu Immortal deduced for a while before stopping, gaining no results.

Fang Yuan nodded, greatly pleased: "Emperor yama's defense against wisdom path deductions has become stronger and is at rank eight level. Even if Fairy Zi Wei deduces about me, I can block her!"

The conclusion was, emperor yama's defense and offense were at peak rank seven level. The yama children were extremely difficult to deal with, not only could they act flexibly, they could also rapidly recover, and even if there were losses, they could easily be replenished with soul beast modification.

Even more amazing was great thief ghost hand, this method could steal rank eight Immortal Gu. In this battle, with just one attack, it had determined his victory, forcing Meng Tu, a peak rank seven expert, to self-detonate.

At a similar level to great thief ghost hand was emperor yama's defense against wisdom path deductions. This was also what Fang Yuan needed the most.

"However, emperor yama still has room for improvement."

"I should design an immortal battlefield killer move with emperor yama as the core."

"This time, Meng Tu sealed the area, isolating himself from the outside world. If he had not shot himself in the foot, he could have freely escaped, and it would have been much more difficult for me to kill him."

"Also, if I had an immortal battlefield killer move, when Meng Tu wanted to self-detonate, I would have sensed it one step earlier."

Fang Yuan was always striving for improvements, he believed emperor yama could still be elevated further.

Chapter 1566: Meng Tribe's Pursuit

Two Gu Immortals were flying rapidly in the sky, they had rough appearances and were tall and well-built. They were Meng tribe Gu Immortals Meng Zi Zai and Meng Zhao.

Like Fang Yuan had expected, the moment he showed himself, Meng Tu sent the message of an attack to the tribe.

But later, Meng Tu had used the blade path dao marks to cover autumn blade plain with an environment similar to an immortal battlefield, he was no longer able to send messages.

With such an important message like an invading enemy, Meng tribe naturally would not ignore it. They immediately sent a rank seven Gu Immortal, Meng Zi Zai, and a young rank six Gu Immortal, Meng Zhao, to deal with the enemy.

"Uncle, who do you think this ignorant guy who dared to intrude on our Meng tribe is? Hehe, I think it is probably a demonic Gu Immortal who cultivates alone without any contact with the outside world." Meng Zhao said with a smile towards Meng Zi Zai.

Meng Zi Zai was stone-faced, but his eyes revealed a relaxed gaze as he agreed: "Your guess is logical, but you need to plan for the worst in everything. Currently, Longevity Heaven has appeared in front of everyone to unite every Huang Jin tribe, Old Ancestor Xue Hu has disappeared somewhere, Heavenly Lord Bai Zu has turned to the righteous path, the righteous path is at its peak. But there is actually someone who dared to go against the general trend and came to find trouble with my Huang Jin tribe, this fellow is either a lunatic or has some background. This is why the tribe sent us as reinforcements to prevent against any accident."

"Uncle, you are right. But…" Meng Zhao paused before laughing: "That person is truly unlucky, they went into autumn blade plain which is guarded by Lord Meng Tu. Lord Meng Tu cultivates blade path and has quasi-great grandmaster blade path attainment, he is ranked among the top three rank seven experts in the tribe!"

"He might not just be a quasi-great grandmaster anymore." Meng Zi Zai sighed.

Meng Zhao's eyes brightened: "Uncle, you mean that…?"

Meng Zi Zai smiled: "He is the senior brother whom I admire the most in my life, no one in the tribe can match his talent in blade path. He has been cultivating in autumn blade plain for the past years, with his talent, he should have reached great grandmaster realm."

"Blade path great grandmaster! He is indeed worthy of being Lord Meng Tu!" Meng Zhao said excitedly.

"Hahaha, that's right." Meng Zi Zai laughed, he had received a lot of care from Meng Tu in his cultivation, he held Meng Tu in the highest regard. So when Meng Tu messaged the tribe about the enemy, Meng Zi Zai requested to be sent to aid Meng Tu. In fact, he had utmost confidence in Meng Tu, and he only came to catch up on old times with Meng Tu and introduce Meng Zhao to him.

Meng Zhao had been carefully picked by Meng Zi Zai as a Gu Immortal junior to be nurtured by the tribe. Meng tribe also had various factions representing their respective political benefits.

Meng Tu and Meng Zi Zai were of the same faction, Meng Zhao was selected by Meng Zi Zai to draw in new blood to this faction.

Meng Zhao also knew the significance of this trip, so he was very excited.

"Autumn blade plain is not far away from here, we can see senior brother after a short while. Sigh, I have not seen him for a few years, if he could become a blade path great grandmaster, it will be a huge help to our faction." Meng Zi Zai inwardly thought.

But right at this time, his body suddenly shook violently, then his expression paled, and his eyes widened in extreme shock.

"Uncle? What's wrong?" Meng Zhao noticed the change in Meng Zi Zai's expression and was doubtful. Since meeting Meng Zi Zai, he had never seen this calm uncle show such an appearance.

But Meng Zhao saw Meng Zi Zai becoming even more abnormal.

Meng Zi Zai had unknowingly lowered his speed, before finally floating in the air without moving like a statue.

His expression was deathly pale, his eyes were red and tears actually dripped down.

Meng Zhao's heart shook even more, something huge had definitely happened, but he did not dare to continue asking. He could only accompany Meng Zi Zai as they faced the chilling wind.

Meng Zi Zai was dazed for a good while before his expression changed once again. He looked terrifying, his eyes filled with raging fury.

Meng Zi Zai gave a loud shout, the shout was like thunder, resonating over all the surroundings. He then shot forward at an extremely fast speed.

Meng Zhao was caught off-guard, but quickly followed after coming back to his senses.

But how could his speed compare to the rank seven Gu Immortal Meng Zi Zai?

Soon, he was thrown far behind.

Meng Zhao was very puzzled: "What's going on?"

He had a bad feeling in his heart: "Wait a moment! Uncle's direction is towards autumn blade plain. Has Lord Meng Tu met with danger?"

Meng Zhao's whole body shivered at this thought.

If it were really like this, then this was no doubt like a nightmare to him, and was very bad news for Meng tribe as well.

If Meng Tu, who had peak rank seven battle strength, died, then it was an extremely great loss for Meng tribe!

Meng Zhao hurried to autumn blade plain with all his strength.

"This… what happened here?!" Meng Zhao was shocked, before even reaching autumn blade plain, he could sense the surging blade path dao marks in the air.

Autumn blade plain's original layout was already completely destroyed, replaced by countless blade marks which crazily cut across the land, forming pits and trenches all over the area.

Meng Zhao soon saw Meng Zi Zai kneeling on the ground, still like a statue.

He carefully descended to the ground, the dense blade path dao marks here stabbed into his skin, causing him to feel bursts of pain.

He walked to Meng Zi Zai's side and shockingly discovered streams of tears on the latter's cheeks!

Meng Zhao only saw Meng Zi Zai in autumn blade plain, he did not see Meng Tu. That guess in his mind immediately became more distinct by countless times, causing his expression to involuntarily turn into that of fright.

Meng Zi Zai slowly opened his eyes and looked at Meng Zhao, saying in a deep and hoarse voice that let anyone that heard it know the intense pain and anger he was restraining in his heart.

"Brother Meng Tu… has died in battle!"

Meng Zhao's whole body shivered, despite already guessing it, when he heard Meng Zi Zai verifying it, he still could not endure the extreme shock.

Meng Tu had actually died in battle?!

With his battle strength, who could kill him?

Meng Zhao opened his mouth, and after a long while, said: "Uncle, Lord Meng Tu is so powerful, how could he be so easily killed? Maybe he is still alive and has only shifted the battle elsewhere."

But Meng Zi Zai slowly shook his head: "When we were on the way just before, the tribe sent me a message saying Meng Tu's soul lantern was extinguished. But I still held hope… until I arrived here…"

His voice choked as tears flowed out of his eyes once again.

A man does not easily shed tears, unless it is truly a heart wrenching matter!

Meng Zi Zai continued in a weak voice: "I know he has a killer move called blade sacrifice which is a self-destruction method, it destroys his immortal aperture, Immortal Gu and other resources to let out an unprecedentedly terrifying might. Using this move means he is definitely dead."

"If so…" Meng Zhao quickly looked at the whole battlefield, feeling even more shocked.

Meng Tu was dead!

Such a powerful Gu Immortal had actually died, forced to self-detonate within such a short period of time.

Who in the world was the enemy?!

All kinds of past events and memories surfaced in Meng Zi Zai's mind.

He had never expected a situation where Meng Tu died.

Meng Zi Zai cried for a while before slowly standing up.

His face turned expressionless as he said to Meng Zhao: "You should return, our Meng tribe definitely won't let the matter of Meng Tu's death go. But this enemy is unimaginably powerful! Meng Tu had immediately sent a message when the enemy appeared, we also moved out at once, moving here without resting the whole journey. But in such a short period of time, Meng Tu was unable to protect himself and was forced to self-detonate by the enemy."

"I know his temperament, he probably wanted to use this move to drag the enemy with him. But from the looks of it, there is no traces of the enemy's death. This is a powerful enemy which even blade sacrifice could not kill!"

"I must give chase, I will catch the culprit even if I have to spend my whole life! This is beyond your ability, you should return to the tribe and cultivate, don't let this news be exposed."

Meng Zhao nodded with a heavy heart: "I understand, you must be careful, uncle."

With Meng Tu's death, Meng tribe had lost a capable expert and this was not a light loss to them. At the same time, they had got in trouble with a powerful enemy with a mysterious origin and unknown goal, Meng tribe would seal this news for the moment to maintain stability.

As for Meng Zhao, his cultivation was too low and his status was not high, which could be seen from how the tribe had still not informed him of Meng Tu's death.

"Don't worry. Second supreme elder is personally coming with the Immortal Gu House Investigation Courtyard." Meng Zi Zai patted Meng Zhao's shoulder.

Meng Zhao nodded his head, putting his heart at rest as he left.

With Immortal Gu House Investigation Courtyard, they did not have to fear even if they encountered a rank eight existence.

Meng Zhao did not have to wait for long as he saw Investigation Courtyard appear in the horizon.

Not long later, Investigation Courtyard came to a stop, Meng tribe's second supreme elder walked out of the courtyard, nodding at Meng Zi Zai solemnly before immediately starting to inspect the battlefield.

But why would Fang Yuan leave behind any clues?

After Meng tribe's second supreme elder finished inspecting, his expression turned even heavier.

Meng Zi Zai said: "This mysterious enemy is very clean with their methods, I have already inspected the battlefield earlier, they have dealt with the traces with extreme proficiency."

Meng tribe's second supreme elder nodded his head: "No worries, we have Investigation Courtyard here!"

Investigation Courtyard was an information path Immortal Gu House, its specialty was to gather information. Meng tribe's second supreme elder immediately activated one of its killer moves.

They actually managed to find some clues.

"He went in that direction, chase!" Meng tribe's two Gu Immortals entered the Immortal Gu House and chased after Fang Yuan with fury and hatred.

Chapter 1567: Front-back Divine Obstruction Needles

"The clues end here!" Meng tribe's Immortal Gu House Investigation Courtyard slowly stopped in the air.

Meng tribe's two Gu Immortals looked at each other.

Meng Zi Zai looked ahead at a lush valley that was starkly different from the surrounding grassland.

Such a valley would not form naturally, but the two Meng tribe immortals were not surprised. Meng tribe's second supreme elder said in a heavy voice: "This is Sleeping Lady's Divine Needle Valley."

Meng Zi Zai frowned: "Is it her?"

Meng tribe's second supreme elder was silent.

Sleeping Lady was a rank seven lone immortal who cultivated sound path, she did not have outstanding battle strength but she controlled an immemorial desolate beast divine hedgehog. This divine hedgehog was a sword path immemorial desolate beast, and had an ability to shoot out all the spines on its body, which was extremely fast and had terrifying power.

Sleeping Lady created Divine Needle Valley, being in control of the area between Meng tribe and Murong tribe.

She not only had the powerful method to control an immemorial desolate beast, her political wisdom was also excellent. She lived right between the two super forces, so no side dared to truly go against her. Because if one side did that, Sleeping Lady could easily side with the other super force.

The two Meng tribe Gu Immortals were silent.

The situation could become messy.

They followed the clues here, but they had not actually obtained any specific information regarding Fang Yuan.

Sleeping Lady's own strength was not Meng Tu's match, but if she sent the divine hedgehog, she might be able to kill Meng Tu.

This indeed made her a suspect. But…

This matter was troublesome to handle.

Meng tribe and Murong tribe had quite a good relationship with Sleeping Lady, they had expressed goodwill to her since long ago, trying to win her over and preventing her from siding with the other party.

The relationship between Meng tribe and Murong tribe was obviously not good.

Every super force had an instinct to expand their territories. Meng tribe and Murong tribe were so close to each other, how could their relationship be good?

If Sleeping Lady was the culprit, how could she have such guts by herself? So it was very likely she had already sided with Murong tribe. As a super force and a righteous Huang Jin tribe, Murong tribe could not attack another righteous path super force for no reason, so it was entirely possible for them to have used Sleeping Lady as the front.

If Sleeping Lady was not the culprit, then how should the two Meng tribe Gu Immortals investigate? Slight carelessness might make Sleeping Lady develop thoughts of siding with Murong tribe, then Meng tribe's losses would undoubtedly be even bigger.

The two Gu Immortals pondered for a long while before second supreme elder finally said: "Let's go, we will make a visit to Sleeping Lady and inform her of Meng Tu's death. Only by being open and direct will Sleeping Lady realize our Meng tribe's intention. After all, the clues stop at her Divine Needle Valley."

Meng Tu nodded his head.

Investigation Courtyard had not concealed its traces, so the two Meng tribe Gu Immortals' arrival had already startled Sleeping Lady.

However, Sleeping Lady maintained her composure, she had the qualifications and the confidence to cope with all situations, patiently waiting for the two Meng tribe Gu Immortals to come to her.

When Meng tribe's two immortals reached her residence, they immediately narrated the situation to her. She then understood the situation and also realized how serious this matter was!

First, she declared her innocence which was immediately verified by the Meng tribe Gu Immortals. Secondly, she herself was worried when she heard that the clues disappeared in Divine Needle Valley.

"This mysterious culprit could kill Meng Tu, he definitely has powerful methods and terrifying battle strength. Friends, please do me a favor by coming with me to inspect the whole Divine Needle Valley."

Sleeping Lady took the initiative to ask for help.

Meng tribe's two immortals were joyous, this was what they wanted so they immediately agreed.

The three immortals moved in a group, carefully searching Divine Needle Valley.

Sleeping Lady was afraid too.

She had some knowledge of Investigation Courtyard's power, since the clues disappeared in Divine Needle Valley, it was very likely the culprit was still hiding in her valley. Since this mysterious culprit could so viciously kill Meng Tu, why would he not be able to deal with her?

The three immortals searched for a long while but gained no results.

Meng tribe's two immortals glanced at each other, the second supreme elder intentionally saying: "We have searched almost the whole Divine Needle Valley, is the killer really not here?"

Meng Zi Zai pretended to unintentionally reply: "Isn't there still an area which we have not searched?"

Sleeping Lady knew these two were putting on a show, but she was not the culprit and sincerely wanted to search this place, so she nodded: "I specially designed this Divine Needle Valley for the divine hedgehog, only the deepest area of the valley is left now, please follow me."

Meng tribe's Gu Immortals followed Sleeping Lady to the depths of the valley.

An enormous pure-white hedgehog was resting at the dark valley floor. It was sleeping in a curled up position, its breaths were long and slow. It was covered with extremely sharp spines which were full of sword path dao marks.

The divine hedgehog was as large as a hill, Meng tribe's two Gu Immortals slowly flew to its side, they were like ants in front of a carriage wheel.

"Such an amazing immemorial desolate beast!" Meng tribe's second supreme elder softly praised.

Sleeping Lady's expression somewhat softened, this was her most important capital that allowed her to survive in between two super forces.

Meng tribe's second supreme elder carefully inspected before saying: "This batch of front-back divine obstruction needles seems to have very high quality. Sleeping Lady, when are you picking them?"

The sharp spines on the divine hedgehog's body were rank eight immortal materials that could be plucked. Every sharp spine was a front-back divine obstruction needle.

Every time the divine hedgehog encounters a dangerous situation, it would shoot out all its sharp spines to kill the enemy. These released spines naturally could not be put back. When the divine hedgehog goes to sleep, new spines would once again grow on its body.

Sleeping Lady had unique methods which could make the divine hedgehog fall into deep sleep constantly. Doing that after feeding it till its full, Sleeping Lady gained an economic pillar which was the business of front-back divine obstruction needles.

These front-back divine obstruction needles were mostly sold to Meng tribe and Murong tribe, while the remaining small portion was put on sale in treasure yellow heaven.

Sleeping Lady thus was quite well off. Northern Plains was poor in resources, but Sleeping Lady relied on this divine hedgehog to live a far better life than most of the Northern Plains' Gu Immortals.

"I will pick them up soon, there will be four hundred and thirty-six needles this time." Sleeping Lady replied seriously.

There were over a thousand spines on the divine hedgehog, but Sleeping Lady needed to leave behind those short spines to continue growing. What she plucked were the longest spines. Also, she could not sell all the spines, because without these spines, the divine hedgehog's battle strength would fall severely.

"Let's start." Meng Zi Zai suggested.

"Please examine carefully, I will make the divine hedgehog remain asleep." Sleeping Lady said.

Meng tribe's two Gu Immortals began to search for clues with Investigation Courtyard, the commotion was huge but Sleeping Lady's sound path killer move made the divine hedgehog remain deep asleep.

If the divine hedgehog was startled awake, it would definitely become furious and vent its anger on them, attacking randomly. Sleeping Lady had not completely subdued this beast, after all, she was not an enslavement path Gu Immortal.

"We have a new clue!" After a long while of searching, Meng Zi Zai suddenly said with a spirited expression.

Sleeping Lady was terrified: "This person actually infiltrated this deep into the valley and I did not sense it?"

The three immortals followed the trails found that it continued deeper down.

The three immortals followed the trail all the way, unknowingly reaching deep underground where the clues increased further.

Not long later, the trail changed direction, winding up towards the surface.

The three immortals followed the trail cautiously, arriving at the surface after a while.

"This is the territory of Murong tribe, it is hundreds of li away from Divine Needle Valley." Meng tribe's second supreme elder frowned.

The clues completely disappeared here.

Meng Zi Zai's gaze flickered, Sleeping Lady fell silent, she would not make any statements in such a delicate juncture.

The three immortals inspected the surroundings for a long while, but did not find any other clues.

Sleeping Lady proposed to return to her valley to rest, Meng tribe's two immortals had not found any clues, so after thinking for a moment, they agreed.

But how could they have known when they returned to the valley, there was a shocking discovery waiting for them.

The extraordinary divine hedgehog was still in a deep sleep, but its whole body was bare, all the front-back divine obstruction needles were gone!

"What's going on? My divine obstruction needles! I had stayed guard in Divine Needle Valley without going out for a hundred years, spending a large amount of food to feed the divine hedgehog and not stinting on repeatedly using my killer move to make it sleep before I was able to get it to this scale!" Sleeping Lady was pale with shock as she shouted in an anguished voice.

Meng tribe's two immortals looked at each other, cold sweat dripping from their forehead, because they suddenly realized they were used by someone!

Chapter 1568: Sleeping Lady Spits Blood

"I want Meng tribe to give me an explanation, now! Otherwise, although I might be a lone cultivator, I won't let this matter drop!" Sleeping Lady fiercely stared at the two Meng tribe immortals.

Her losses were truly disastrous. This caused her to be so anxious and furious that she directly demanded for an explanation even though the other side was Meng tribe.

She was not like Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan lost his guts Gu business but still had many income sources like dragonfish business, spirit snake transactions, regretful spiders, eerie fire dragon python and so on.

To Sleeping Lady, losing these front-back divine obstruction needles was the same as losing her main financial pillar. Although she still had the divine hedgehog, to regrow the front-back divine obstruction needles would require time as well as an enormous investment!

Sleeping Lady had a long-term plan, every time she harvested some front-back divine obstruction needles, she did not pick all of them, instead leaving behind most of them to continue growing.

But the person who stole the front-back divine obstruction needles was too vicious, they did not leave behind even one tiny spine for Sleeping Lady.

Sleeping Lady's losses were not only those spines which had grown to the limit, her future prospects were also affected.

"A pity that I don't have methods to move this immemorial desolate beast into my immortal aperture! Putting it outside is truly not safe!" Sleeping Lady's fists trembled, she even had a passing thought of suiciding.

But actually, even if she could move it, it would be troublesome.

First of all, she did not have full control over the divine hedgehog, if this immemorial desolate beast acted up inside her immortal aperture, she would suffer severe losses.

Secondly, if Sleeping Lady was about to undergo tribulation, heaven's will would send much more powerful calamities and tribulations that would specifically target the divine hedgehog.

Finally, the divine hedgehog was Sleeping Lady's trump card to survive between Meng tribe and Murong tribe. If she placed it in her immortal aperture, and there was a fight in the future, she might not be able to release it in time to face the enemies.

"Sleeping Lady, calm down, please calm down for a second." Meng tribe's second supreme elder repeatedly persuaded.

"Calm down? How can I calm down? You said a murder happened, Meng Tu died in battle, alright, I believed your Meng tribe and without verifying the truth, I let you guys in and even warmly welcomed you. You said you found evidence, but I did not find anything and only relied on your Investigation Courtyard. Later, there were indeed obvious clues, but were they truly left behind by the culprit? Does Investigation Courtyard not have an ability to tamper with clues?"

As she said this, cold sweat dripped down Sleeping Lady's forehead.

She calmed down and looked vigilantly at the two Meng tribe immortals, a large amount of Gu worm auras started spreading from her body.

Sleeping Lady fixed her gaze at the two Meng tribe immortals while slowly retreating.

Meng tribe's two immortals could only smile bitterly, but also understood Sleeping Lady's mentality.

Right now, the divine hedgehog had lost all its spines, its battle strength had fallen to an all-time low, which was like Sleeping Lady's own battle strength falling down sharply. The trump card which she had used to have dealings with the two super forces was now mostly gone, how could Sleeping Lady not be vigilant?

Meng tribe's second supreme elder sighed bitterly: "Sleeping Lady, if this was really planned out by my tribe to plot against you to secretly steal this divine hedgehog's spines, why would we bother returning with you? If we were plotting against you, we should have already deceived you into a trap like an immortal battlefield using the excuse of finding the trails of the culprit, don't you think so?"

Sleeping Lady was silent for a moment before moving her eyes upward: "That is probably because your Meng tribe belongs to the righteous path and has to abide by rules, so you can't directly make a move against me. On the other hand, I have already set an agreement with your Meng tribe, so you made this plan of lowering my battle strength first and then using eloquent speech to deceive me!"

Meng tribe's two immortals could not help but glance at each other.

Sleeping Lady's words were not unreasonable, her quick thinking made Meng tribe's two immortals not know of what to say.

"Hmph!" Sleeping Lady continued, "You thought I am not aware of your righteous path's tricks? You started this, if your Meng tribe won't give me an explanation… then alright, I will let the world be the judge of it!"

"Stop!" Meng tribe's second supreme elder quickly shouted, his and Meng Zi Zai's expressions were ashen.

But it was too late!

Sleeping Lady directly revealed this matter in treasure yellow heaven, she quickly informed Murong tribe through her contacts.

In an instant, the matter Meng tribe had tried hard to hide about Meng Tu being killed, them being unable to find the culprit, and even implicating Sleeping Lady in losing her front-back divine obstruction needles, were completely revealed.

"You, you, you!" Meng Zi Zai pointed towards Sleeping Lady, his eyes were almost spouting fire of anger.

Meng tribe's second supreme elder was also ashen-faced as he gazed at Sleeping Lady with narrowed eyes and killing intent.

Sleeping Lady's expression was impassive, but was inwardly smiling bitterly.

She of course knew her action had greatly harmed her and Meng tribe's relationship. But she had no other options!

She had to do this.

Any alliance agreement had the chance of being broken by one side. Today's matter was also too severe, Sleeping Lady had to protect herself.

How could she, whose battle strength had fallen to rock bottom, protect herself?

Even if Meng Tu died, the super force Meng tribe was still not something a rank seven lone immortal like Sleeping Lady could go against.

Sleeping Lady believed the best method was to borrow the strength of others, to attract the attention of other Gu Immortals and Meng tribe's competitor, Murong tribe, to this matter and support her to some extent. Even if Meng tribe had some harmful intentions, they would have to restrain themselves, after all, they were a righteous path force!

"Sleeping Lady, at this point, any more words have no meaning. But I will tell you not to be so suspecting, we were likely used by that person!" Meng tribe's second supreme elder said in a deep voice.

The situation was obvious now.

Even if the two Meng tribe immortals did not cultivate wisdom path, they could deduce that the culprit was extremely vicious, not to mention how they had inexplicably forced Meng Tu to self-detonate, they intentionally left behind clues to lead Meng tribe's pursuers to Divine Needle Valley. They then used them to lead Sleeping Lady away, which allowed them to conveniently take away all the spines of the divine hedgehog!

"Our Meng tribe will give you an explanation!" Before leaving, Meng tribe's second supreme elder left behind this sentence.

Meng tribe's two immortals left, Sleeping Lady immediately began to arrange a Gu formation around the immemorial desolate beast divine hedgehog.

Meng tribe had lost their clues so they could only head back.

Even if they obtained any clues now, they would be doubtful if this was another trap by the enemy.

Inside Investigation Courtyard, Meng Zi Zai suddenly said with a fierce glint in his eyes: "This culprit is really crafty, the matter has been exposed now and the whole world knows of it, how about we just sentence Sleeping Lady as the culprit?"

Whether Sleeping Lady was the culprit or not, if Meng tribe attacked and killed her, they could regain their prestige, resolving this crisis to their reputation. And who is to say they won't be able to get the immemorial desolate beast divine hedgehog.

Meng tribe's second supreme elder sighed: "I also thought of this. But, firstly, Investigation Courtyard is not able to deal with Sleeping Lady and the divine hedgehog in a short period of time. This place is also close to Murong tribe, there is no guarantee of them not interfering. Secondly, we have an alliance agreement with her, and will suffer a heavy backlash if we rashly attack her. Finally, the current Northern Plains' situation is not the same as before."

At present, Longevity Heaven had appeared in front of the world, Yao Huang had taken the position of South Desolation Immortal, and Longevity Heaven was uniting all the Huang Jin tribes. In this period of time, they were dedicating themselves to integrate the strength of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

Righteous path forces were basically all Huang Jin tribes, there was almost no need to integrate them. Longevity Heaven's first plan was thus to merge lone cultivators with the righteous path.

This plan was, however, slightly obstructed when Heavenly Court sent someone disguised as Fang Yuan.

But Longevity Heaven still had not given up, they continued to make effort in this plan.

Thus, as a Huang Jin tribe, if Meng tribe rashly attacked the lone immortal Sleeping Lady and did not handle it properly, they would be investigated and blamed by Longevity Heaven.

This was what Meng tribe's second supreme elder had the most worries about.

As the two Meng tribe immortals were heading back, Fang Yuan was also rushing back.

A pile of front-back divine obstruction needles was quietly lying inside his sovereign immortal aperture. Indeed, he was the culprit behind the entire matter.

Fang Yuan knew a lot about Meng tribe, and with his wisdom path attainment, he arranged a simple but effective trap.

And with his powerful luck, Sleeping Lady was indeed drawn away, letting him immediately succeed in this plan.

Ordinary Gu Immortals might not be able to get near the divine hedgehog, after all, their auras were distinct.

But Fang Yuan had familiar face and could completely disguise as Sleeping Lady. Even when the divine hedgehog slowly opened its eyes, he did not panic.

The divine hedgehog went to sleep once again, Fang Yuan was able to pluck all its spines. After obtaining them, Fang Yuan did not do anything to the sleeping divine hedgehog, he directly left.

In his first life's memories, Sleeping Lady was also one of the experts who resisted Heavenly Court. As for the divine hedgehog, why would he take it?

It was of little value to Fang Yuan, instead it was better to let it continue to remain in Sleeping Lady's hands. When Sleeping Lady nurtures a new batch of spines again, Fang Yuan could then come again to steal it!

Fang Yuan had no guilt even when killing others, let alone just stealing things.

"Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was indeed amazing to be able to create a path like theft path." Fang Yuan had tasted its sweet benefits and now had a whole new view of theft path.

In the battle with Meng Tu, it was great thief ghost hand which determined the victory at once. If it had gone normally, Fang Yuan could not have so easily taken Meng Tu's life.

"Before theft path's appearance, Gu Immortals could fight each other to death but still might not be able to obtain much battle spoils. But with theft path's appearance, they could obtain resources without the need to fight a life or death battle. The costs are reduced while the efficiency is raised, this is simply too amazing!"

"Unfortunately, right now is not a good time for me to go around stealing. On one hand, I lack theft path Immortal Gu, and only have the rank seven Immortal Gu Great Thief to support my theft path moves. On the other hand, I have already exposed great thief ghost hand back in Western Desert, if I go around robbing all over the place, someone will probably connect the clues and deduce my true identity."

"There is still a crucial immortal material lacking from the myriad self Immortal Gu recipe. After this, I will hurry back to Lang Ya blessed land and refine myriad self Immortal Gu."

Although Fang Yuan had some theft path methods, he could not overdo it.

Because his soul cultivation was the more urgent matter.

Increasing his soul foundation meant he could make more use of emperor yama, his battle strength as well as plans would be guaranteed. But cultivating soul required guts Gu, required soul cores, and also required the goods from green ghost desert, Suan Bu Jin's identity needed to be kept a secret. This was a chain of requirements.

"Oh right, I also cannot let this matter be easily revealed." Fang Yuan snickered, immediately spreading rumors in treasure yellow heaven, saying Sleeping Lady was lying and scheming against Meng tribe, the front-back divine obstruction needles were kept by herself in preparation to undergo tribulation and advance to a higher level!

The truth was even more obscured now, which was even more helpful in concealing Fang Yuan.

As for Sleeping Lady, when she learned of these rumors, she immediately spat out blood from anxiety and anger!

Naturally, this was of no concern to Fang Yuan.

Chapter 1569: Fifty Percent!

Treasure yellow heaven.

A large lump of transparent fire was silently burning while letting out vast treasure light.

The fire immediately attracted the attention of many Gu Immortals the moment it appeared.

Many wills and a few divine senses were attracted towards the scene.

Black Heaven Temple's Gu Immortal Zhang Ji smiled, he was the owner of this transparent fire.

"I never expected this expedition to give me a batch of a rare rank seven immortal material. Its profits should be enough to replenish my immortal essence reserves."

While thinking, he responded to everyone's questions about the price.

His price was only a slight bit higher than the norm, so many had the thoughts of purchasing.

"I want all of this." One divine sense directly contacted Zhang Ji, offering a high price.

Zhang Ji's heart thumped in excitement, somewhat disbelieving: "You want all of this? The price…"

"Make the deal." The other side was extremely straightforward, directly giving a large amount of immortal essence stones.

"Okay!" Seeing such a huge amount of immortal essence stones, Zhang Ji's eyes immediately brightened, agreeing immediately.

The transaction was completed quickly, the Gu Immortals who were observing the fire were somewhat caught off-guard.

"No need to worry, I still have stock left!" Zhang Ji's divine sense was constantly fluctuating, he quickly proclaimed and took out another lump of transparent fire.

It was just that this transparent fire's amount was much smaller than the previously sold lump.

The first transaction had stimulated other Gu Immortals' desire to purchase, after all, this transparent fire was indeed rare in the market. Usually, they could only accumulate it over continuous purchase, and every purchase was normally only a fist sized or a basin sized lump of fire. They were different from now where the transparent fire was the size of a carriage! They could not lose this rare opportunity.

"But this time, I am going to raise the price." Zhang Ji's smile became brighter. He did not have much knowledge of the transparent fire. This was also his first time selling it and he did not have a proper understanding of the market situation, so the enthusiasm of other Gu Immortals was beyond his expectations.

He continued to raise the price, but few buyers gave up, so the starting price continued to become higher.

"Darn it, looks like I made a mistake in selling earlier!" Zhang Ji looked at this scene with some regret, while also admiring that buyer's decisiveness.

Zhang Ji was not foolish, he had divided his stock of transparent fire into three portions. The first portion was to test the waters, while the one he was selling now was the second portion.

As the transactions continued to increase, he got a clearer grasp over the market situation.

"Floating life fire!" Fang Yuan looked at this lump of transparent fire in his sovereign immortal aperture with a delighted expression.

It was him who took the lead and purchased Zhang Ji's goods.

This floating life fire was transparent and burned silently without any heat. But when it burns a living being, all kinds of past scenes of this living being would turn into images that would constantly replay in the floating life fire. At that time, the floating life fire would emit a multi-colored radiance, and would no longer be transparent.

Floating life fire needed to be preserved with special methods.

Zhang Ji had coincidentally obtained a large amount of floating life fire, he did not have such methods.

After Fang Yuan obtained it, he immediately used a method to preserve the floating life fire. This method was not from Spectral Soul's true inheritance, but was obtained from Lang Ya true inheritance which he had exchanged Spectral Soul's true inheritance for.

"I had thought I needed to travel far and find trouble with other people to seize this floating life fire. Who would have thought that someone was selling it in treasure yellow heaven in such a large quantity now. This luck is truly amazing!"

Fang Yuan smiled.

There were bound to be many Gu Immortals who wanted to purchase floating life fire.

But Gu Immortal wills were usually unable to make the decision, they could only follow the commands left by the Gu Immortal.

And to be able to take out so many immortal essence stones at once was also not something ordinary Gu Immortals could do.

Even if they had the capital, those observing Gu Immortals would want to bargain as the amount they required was usually not that big.

Because of many reasons, Fang Yuan was able to make the first move and gain it for a cheap price!

As for the risk?

This Zhang Ji was a Gu Immortal of Black Heaven Temple, a person of Heavenly Court, but he did not know the buyer was Fang Yuan, neither did Fang Yuan know of his identity.

Transactions in treasure yellow heaven were very secure. If Heavenly Court was able to use this to scheme against Fang Yuan, to have a such a deep influence even in treasure yellow heaven, then it was better for Fang Yuan to just surrender.

All in all, the chance of this was rather low.

Drinking blade wine, edge Gu, front-back divine obstruction needles, and floating life fire, these four main immortal materials were all gathered. Fang Yuan still had to purchase some more edge Gu, which could be completely satisfied by treasure yellow heaven, if not, he still had a channel left in Western Desert's Xiao clan.

Since there was no meaning in staying outside, Fang Yuan hurried back to Lang Ya blessed land.

Passing through the immortal formation, Fang Yuan returned to Lang Ya blessed land. The process was smooth with no danger.

Fang Yuan's return was much earlier than expected, this made Lang Ya land spirit extremely happy.

"Since you have returned, I will prepare for the refinement." Lang Ya land spirit was extremely active, the pressure from Heavenly Court was really too huge.

"I still need to thank first supreme elder and the Gu Immortals of the other three races for lending me so many immortal essence stones." Fang Yuan thanked.

Without their assistance, how could Fang Yuan take out such a huge sum?

"Don't stand on ceremony. We are all on the same side, you getting stronger means Lang Ya blessed land will be even more safe. If Lang Ya blessed land is in danger, they also won't be able to escape due to the alliance agreement!" Lang Ya land spirit's reply was direct and frank.

Indeed, the present situation made it such that Lang Ya Sect as well as the snowmen, rockmen, and inkmen were in the same boat. If anyone encountered danger, the rest would not be able to escape.

Fang Yuan handed the four immortal materials to Lang Ya Sect to process.

These immortal materials required at least fifteen days of processing, the steps were extremely tedious, repetitive and complicated. This was the case when all the hairy man Gu Immortals of Lang Ya Sect put in their full effort.

The superiority of myriad self Immortal Gu's recipe could be seen from this!

With his refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment, Fang Yuan's myriad self Immortal Gu recipe was so outstanding that it could be said to have reached the limits of the world with no room left for improvements.

The crucial procedures of the Gu refinement were shortened to the limit, there were three in total. While the other procedures had over ten thousand steps, most of them were the processing of the immortal materials.

Fang Yuan processed the immortal materials to their best state, spending most of his effort in this. Even if the expenditure of the immortal materials increased because of this, he did not hesitate.

Because these procedures were the ones which Gu Immortals could control. While those crucial steps of the Gu refinement could only rely on the collision and interweaving of the dao marks, Gu Immortals could not control these changes.

Through this method and with the help of Lang Ya Sect's Gu refinement abilities, the success rate of Fang Yuan's myriad self Immortal Gu recipe was at an incredibly high fifty percent!

That meant Fang Yuan had an equal chance to succeed or fail in refining it.

Fifty percent success rate was truly too terrifying.

The absolute majority of Gu Immortals would be happy if they had even one percent success rate when refining Gu.

However, this was also mainly because Fang Yuan was a refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster!

How many refinement path quasi-supreme grandmasters were there in the world? Since ancient times until now, an expert at Fang Yuan's level could be counted with one's fingers. Those who surpassed his level only amounted to three people in the whole of history.

Moreover, there were extremely few Gu Immortals who cultivated multiple paths, and how many of them would cultivate refinement path?

From another angle, most Gu Immortals were actually amateurs in refining Immortal Gu. It would be preposterous if they could raise the success rate of the Gu refinement!

In fact, even Fang Yuan, who had deduced it, was in slight disbelief over the fifty percent success rate.

But then he thought of Long Hair Ancestor.

Long Hair Ancestor had refined many Immortal Gu in his life, including rank seven and rank eight Immortal Gu. He was a refinement path supreme grandmaster, if he did not have such a success rate, would Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable find him for help?

"Furthermore, I am making use of the whole of Lang Ya Sect's strength to refine this Gu. In the present age, when comparing refinement path attainment, Lang Ya Sect should no doubt be the number one force."

"Besides these, the third main reason is my powerful luck."

First was his refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment level, second was the number one refinement force's all-out help, and third was the powerful luck obtained from Giant Sun's true inheritance.

Three big reasons combined to form this fifty percent success rate of myriad self Immortal Gu's refinement!

"I am finally free from the curse of refining Immortal Gu." Fang Yuan was extremely moved to the point of having the urge to tear up.

He knew the most important reason was him becoming a refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster!

The other two reasons were helpful, but they were more or less present in all the previous Gu refinements. His fifty percent success rate was mainly still brought by the refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment.

"And this is when I am only deducing and modifying the Immortal Gu recipe. In the future, when I make up for my lack of foundational skills in Gu refinement, I can personally take charge of the refinement process, the success rate will increase even more!"

"It is a pity that I don't have enough time…"

Chapter 1570: Myriad Self Immortal Gu!

Lang Ya blessed land, Cloud Cover Continent.

Lang Ya land spirit breathed in deeply, shouting: "Formation, activate—!"

Like millions of bees dancing and buzzing, the refinement path super formation activated. Soon, a huge stream of white-gold light burst out and filled the surroundings.

"Enter the formation!" Lang Ya land spirit ordered as he entered the immortal formation at the same time.

Next, Sixth Hair, Third Hair, Fourth Hair, Seventh Hair, and the other hairy man Gu Immortals entered the formation.

Fang Yuan stood at the periphery of the immortal formation as an observer.

He was not personally involved in this Gu refinement, he had handed it to Lang Ya land spirit and the other hairy man Gu Immortals.

Even though Fang Yuan had quasi-supreme refinement path attainment level, he could not compare to Lang Ya Sect's Gu Immortals in terms of practice of refinement fundamentals.

"During normal times, I can still participate in the Gu refinement. But this time, Lang Ya land spirit is using the refinement path immortal formation that Long Hair Ancestor had created personally back then, this immortal formation can only be used by hairy man Gu Immortals. As a human Gu Immortal, if I enter, I will be killed by the immortal Gu formation."

Lang Ya blessed land had deep foundations, this time, they took out one of Long Hair's refinement path formations.

Of course, with Fang Yuan's methods, he could use his transformation path attainment to turn into a hairy man Gu Immortal. But most likely, Lang Ya Sect wanted to keep this formation a secret and did not want to expose it to Fang Yuan.

"I used Spectral Soul's true inheritance to exchange for Lang Ya true inheritance back then. Evidently, this Long Hair refinement path formation is something Lang Ya land spirit is keeping as a trump card, he will not trade it away. Like the lead soul into dream killer move within Spectral Soul's true inheritance, I am also keeping it for myself."

Fang Yuan watched from the side as bright light shone in his eyes.

Even though Lang Ya Sect pushed Fang Yuan to the side, he was quite satisfied with it.

Facing the huge pressure from Heavenly Court, Lang Ya Sect was very anxious, they even activated this Long Hair refinement path formation to quickly refine myriad self Immortal Gu for Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan was one of them after joining Lang Ya Sect, increasing his battle strength was very beneficial for relocating Lang Ya blessed land!

The Long Hair refinement path formation activated slowly, the light continued to change colors, it was originally white-gold, before turning orange-gold, and dark-gold.

The dark-gold light started to flicker with starlight specks, it was very bright.

The immortal formation's buzzing got softer, after a few breaths of time, it became completely silent without any sound.

The hairy man Gu Immortals and Lang Ya land spirit were all standing in a big circle.

Lang Ya land spirit first acted as he activated an immortal formation, opening it and taking out a bunch of already prepared immortal materials.

This immortal material resembled chilled and dried sunflowers, the moment it appeared in the immortal formation, it turned into smoke and fused into the dark-gold light.

Fang Yuan watched solemnly, this was the first crucial step, after the smoke completely fuses into the dark-gold light, they would be able to continue.

Fang Yuan did not feel much pressure.

If this step failed, his losses would not be big, he could restart again.

But an hour later, the immortal material completely turned into smoke and fused into the dark-gold light perfectly.

Within the immortal formation, the dark-gold light continued to condense and shrink, it was everywhere earlier, but now it was the size of a house, trapped within the Long Hair refinement path formation.

When the starlight specks within the dark-gold light turned into ice stars, Lang Ya land spirit activated the immortal formation and started the second step.

As time passed, immortal materials were sent into the immortal formation by the hairy man Gu Immortals one by one, they were all fusing together.

Three days and nights later, Third Hair started tossing Gu worms into the immortal formation.

He first threw in self reliance Gu.

This Gu worm was only rank three, it was shaped like a cockroach, a dark brown colored flat body. There were feelers on its head, and wings on its back.

Self reliance Gu was a strength path Gu worm that had healing effects. The greater the Gu Master's strength, the greater the healing effect.

This was a rare Gu worm, mortals could not find one even if they tried, but Sixth Hair tossed in several hundreds of them.

The quantity of self reliance Gu was strictly calculated.

Because this involved the quantity of dao marks, when refining Immortal Gu, the numbers had to be precise!

When all of the self reliance Gu were tossed in, Lang Ya land spirit shouted as he activated Long Hair refinement path formation fully.

At once, within the formation, fire pillars rose, hundreds or thousands of them that were meters tall blazed within the dark-gold light.

Strong air currents were blowing outwards, but the refinement path immortal formation perfectly trapped them. The hairy man Gu Immortals who were standing around the immortal Gu formation could not feel the temperature rising at all.

The Long Hair refinement formation was very exceptional!

The orange-red fire pillar continued burning for forty-eight hours before weakening. The dark-gold light was completely burned up, even the self reliance Gu were burned into an odd rock that was the size of a horse carriage.

After waiting for a while, the rock solidified completely, Fang Yuan let out a sigh of relief. The second step of refining myriad self Immortal Gu was finally over.

Next, Lang Ya land spirit and the rest started to rest and recuperate while Fourth Hair and Sixth Hair worked to sustain the immortal formation, carving this rock.

After some time, the rock was completely ground up and turned into a pile of rock fragments scattered on the ground.

Third Hair stopped resting and took out the drinking blade wine, pouring it over these rock fragments.

This drinking blade wine was obtained by Fang Yuan not long ago when he killed Meng Tu. It had great use now, turning the rock fragments into traces of grey smoke.

The grey smoke floated up and condensed into balls of smoke, resembling miniature lanterns that floated in the air.

Fourth Hair and Sixth Hair started to rest, while Third Hair took out a number of all-out effort Gu.

This Gu worm was shaped like a rhinoceros beetle, it was a mortal Gu. It had the size of an adult's palm, and was very heavy. It was oval in shape, and had a strong armor exoskeleton. There was a strong horn on its head, looking heavy and powerful. It had several pairs of legs, all strong and thick. Its body was dark brown, and glistened with a metallic surface. People only needed one glance to know it was not ordinary.

Fang Yuan had not refined all-out effort Immortal Gu yet for now, these were all mortal Gu, from rank one to five.

The Gu worm entered the smoke and did not mix with it.

At this time, Lang Ya land spirit started to act, opening the inventory and taking out the floating life fire that had already been prepared.

Within the transparent fire, large numbers of all-out effort Gu and grey smoke started to fuse.

This was a long step.

Half a month later, the fusing was completed, be it the floating life fire, all-out effort Gu, or grey smoke, they all vanished, a drizzle was left.

This drizzle was restricted by the refinement path immortal formation, it was trapped at the center of the formation, raining down endlessly.

By now, the third crucial step was completed too.

Time was pressing now, the drizzle was not stable, it was becoming smaller rapidly.

All the hairy man Gu Immortals and Lang Ya land spirit started to act, they all had different methods, they were in charge of different segments of the Gu refinement.

Front-back divine obstruction needles and other immortal materials were all tossed in, as well as large numbers of mortal Gu.

The myriad self Immortal Gu recipe that Fang Yuan deduced did not expend any Immortal Gu, instead, a large number of immortal materials and mortal Gu were used.

This way, he would not lose Immortal Gu, but his immortal materials and mortal Gu expenditure would increase by tens of times, the amount of work needed for the refinement also increased drastically. This was also why Lang Ya Sect was using the Long Hair refinement path formation.

As time passed, all the crucial steps were passed without much danger or accidents.

After two months in Lang Ya blessed land's time, the refinement of myriad self Immortal Gu reached the final crucial step.

Fang Yuan had time path methods of course, but he could not reduce the time needed. The shrinking of time by time path was essentially carving time path dao marks to influence it. During the refinement process, the addition of time path dao marks would disrupt the refinement itself.

Two months was Fang Yuan's current limit already. He had used all of his time path methods that could be used to perfectly refine the Immortal Gu without additional disruption, by turning the dao marks into materials for the refinement.

The immortal formation resonated and shook, bright light burst into the sky.

Lang Ya land spirit let out a deep sigh, the rest of the hairy man Gu Immortals had tired expressions, but joy was on their faces.

The final step succeeded.

The light faded as a rank seven Immortal Gu appeared.

This Gu worm was more than ten meters long, it was like a centipede that shined in a metallic luster, the mouthpiece on its head looked dangerous while there was a pair of long antennas on its forehead, it had five thousand legs on either side of its body, having a total of ten thousand legs.

Rank seven Immortal Gu Myriad Self!

"To think that the first refinement succeeded!"

"Haha, we finally refined it."

The hairy man Gu Immortals cheered, they were extremely happy.

Myriad self Immortal Gu was trapped at the center of the refinement path immortal formation, because Fang Yuan was not the person who refined it, it was currently still ownerless.

But soon, Fang Yuan refined it rapidly using the help of the refinement path immortal formation.

"Using one attempt to refine this rank seven Immortal Gu, haha." Fang Yuan was also very happy, he had never even dared to dream of such a thing happening in the past!

Fifty percent success rate was too high.

Fang Yuan tried to inject immortal essence into myriad self Immortal Gu, it started to shine as countless Fang Yuan strength path phantoms appeared from within the light, it was like using the killer move myriad self.

"The effect is only slightly weaker, after all, the killer move myriad self uses too many Gu worms." Fang Yuan could feel the difference: "The immortal essence expenditure has fallen greatly, the activation is also much easier now, it only needs one thought. The killer move back then needed time to prepare no matter how familiar I was with it, it also used a lot of mental energy!"

Fang Yuan tested it and was extremely satisfied with myriad self Immortal Gu!

Chapter 1571: Luo Po Seal?

Lang Ya blessed land, Cloud Cover Continent.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Self Giant Hand!

Fang Yuan floated in the air, his aura exploded with a loud sound as a giant hand appeared out of nowhere, slamming towards the ground.

Instantly, air currents pushed out as the huge palm descended like a toppling mountain, slamming fiercely on the cloud soil ground.

Cloud Cover Continent was designed by Lang Ya land spirit personally, it was made of cloud soil, able to float in the air without ever landing.

The cloud soil was not tough, Fang Yuan's myriad self giant hand had rank seven attacking power, this hand shattered the cloud soil of all the surroundings, falling down towards the vast sea below.

Fang Yuan was testing his killer move, he was not trying to destroy Cloud Cover Continent, thus when his hand landed on Cloud Cover Continent, Lang Ya blessed land's super immortal formation activated, a silver light resembling flowing water appeared on Cloud Cover Continent.

After myriad self giant hand landed on the cloud soil, the silver light was destroyed as cloud soil scattered around, the surrounding terrain was completely altered, there was a huge handprint on the ground that was several meters deep.

Fang Yuan willed as the giant hand quickly vanished.

Seeing the effect, he nodded in satisfaction.

"With myriad self Immortal Gu, giant hand is much easier to use now!"

In the past, in order to use myriad self giant hand, Fang Yuan had to first activate the killer move myriad self and store countless strength path phantoms in his immortal aperture. Next, using these strength path phantoms, he had to use group strength Gu to unleash strength path giant hand.

The process was very tedious, if he did not store strength path phantoms in his immortal aperture, he could not use giant hand in a life-and-death battle. But strength path phantoms could not be stored for a long time, they would disappear after some time and disintegrate on their own.

It was usable for battles he was prepared for, but in unexpected situations, or when he was ambushed, myriad self giant hand could not be used.

Thankfully, Fang Yuan had deep wisdom and a cautious mind, he had always been keeping an eye out for such situations, he did not end up in an awkward spot.

"In the past, using myriad self killer move already needed self strength Immortal Gu, bitter strength Gu, borrow strength Gu, self reliance Gu, refine essence spirit Gu, amplify effect Gu, earth strength Gu, fire, water, wind, lightning strength Gu and countless other mortal Gu, but now I just need to use myriad self Immortal Gu."

"But now, my myriad self giant hand only needs myriad self Immortal Gu as the core with some group strength Gu as the supplementary mortal Gu, it requires less than thirty Gu worms in total, and is very simple compared to the past."

The former myriad self giant hand was evidently unusable now.

After refining myriad self Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan modified myriad self giant hand into a new version using myriad self Immortal Gu as the core, the core self strength Immortal Gu was no longer used.

This meant that self strength Immortal Gu could be used in other aspects.

Of course, he could also add it into the myriad self giant hand killer move to increase its strength.

That would depend on Fang Yuan's further modification.

"Actually, myriad self giant hand has room for improvement. For example, if the speed is insufficient, I can add mortal Gu to fix that flaw. I can also add soul path Immortal Gu to allow giant hand to capture souls as well. Furthermore, the power of giant hand is merely limited by my strength path dao marks, I can continue to strengthen it. The current giant hand has rank seven power, but is not at the peak, it is because my sovereign immortal body's strength path dao marks cannot sustain greater power."

Fang Yuan had only started modifying myriad self giant hand, after changing the core Immortal Gu, there was still huge room for improvement.

In the past, the killer move was too complicated and expended too much thinking and time, adding more Gu worms would lower its usability.

But now, myriad self killer move was condensed into one Gu worm, the process was very simple, he could add more mortal Gu and Immortal Gu to make an even stronger giant hand.

Fang Yuan's practice this time was not just on the strength path giant hand, he was also testing Lang Ya Sect's defensive super immortal formation.

When Feng Jiu Ge invaded earlier, this immortal formation had been very useful, it preserved the lives of many variant human Gu Immortals and also helped Lang Ya Sect get through that tough situation.

Feng Jiu Ge used separation song on the immortal formation multiple times, but Fang Yuan had expected it and split the immortal formation into many layers, Feng Jiu Ge separated many layers but did not get to the core after all.

This time, Fang Yuan did not just modify myriad self giant hand, he also modified the immortal formation and allowed its range to extend throughout Lang Ya Sect.

Earlier, when the strength path giant hand landed on Cloud Cover Continent, this immortal formation was the reason why the destructive effect was reduced.

After testing strength path giant hand, he moved on to the more important matter.

Immortal killer move — Reverse Flow Protection Seal!

This killer move determined Fang Yuan's upper limit, it was only through this he could contest rank eights.

Right now, the core of the killer move was the secluded domain of heaven and earth Reverse Flow River, myriad self Immortal Gu, perseverance Immortal Gu, pulling water Immortal Gu, and over a hundred mortal Gu. Even though it was more complex than myriad self giant hand, this was way simpler than the previous reverse flow protection seal!

After simplifying the killer move, the success rate of activation rose sharply, it was more usable in battle now.

"During the battle in green ghost desert, I was sneak attacked and could not use reverse flow protection seal in time. Now, the activation time has shrunk greatly, I should be able to deal with most assaults."

"However… I can no longer conceal reverse flow protection seal's modifications and set a trap. The trick I used on Thunder Ghost True Monarch only works once."

Fang Yuan felt it was a pity.

Reverse flow protection seal killer move had become much easier to use now due to myriad self Immortal Gu, but this was Fang Yuan's current limit. Adding more Immortal Gu would be difficult.

He could no longer set a trap like earlier and reveal a brand new reverse flow protection seal within a short period of time.

After some deductions, Fang Yuan went into seclusion again, deducing other killer moves.

Even though Fang Yuan was calm, he was filled with pressure.

Against a huge force like Heavenly Court, who would have no pressure?

The refinement of myriad self Immortal Gu, was not only to elevate several killer moves. Fang Yuan's true motive was to create a third variation move — Luo Po Seal!

"I was affected by Lu Wei Yin's immortal killer move and lived through three lifetimes. These dreams were very mystical, especially the third life, it was a huge inspiration for my Luo Po seal."

"But I had a lot of obstructions earlier when deducing Luo Po seal, there was a huge hurdle to cross. This myriad self Immortal Gu is like a bridge that might allow me to cross this hurdle and attain success!"

Fang Yuan felt excitement and anticipation.

Even though he raised his reputation using the battle against Thunder Ghost True Monarch and suppressed Feng Jiu Ge, Fang Yuan knew that he was inferior to Feng Jiu Ge in many aspects.

Feng Jiu Ge could fight rank eight because he had a deep accumulation of sound path dao marks, evenly matching rank eight. Even without rank eight sound path Immortal Gu on him, his killer moves could reach quasi-rank eight because of the amplification of his dao marks.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan could fight rank eight because he was using the vast number of dao marks inside Reverse Flow River. His own dao marks in several paths reached rank seven, but he was still far from rank eight.

Even if he annexed the blessed lands inside City Well, he would still be far from rank eight.

Fang Yuan was not inferior to Feng Jiu Ge in talent.

Feng Jiu Ge was unprecedented in creating assimilation wind song, he was the first Gu Immortal able to summon the winds of assimilation. Meanwhile, Fang Yuan created myriad self and combined strength and enslavement path, it was also a revolutionary creation. The two of them were equally matched.

Now that Fang Yuan condensed the killer move into myriad self Immortal Gu, his status had risen again. Because he could create an entirely new path along this route of development! Compared to just a killer move, there was much more room for development.

Gu cultivation paths were created like this, some were the fusion of two paths, while others were sub-classification of existing paths.

Fang Yuan and Feng Jiu Ge were only different in terms of age.

How many years had Fang Yuan cultivated since rebirth? Feng Jiu Ge had already lived for hundreds of years.

Fang Yuan made such achievements before the age of fifty, it was very rare that he could match Feng Jiu Ge. Compared to normal people, he was simply a monster, his cultivation level rose at an unbelievable rate, it could not be assessed normally. After all, Fang Yuan's rebirth had huge advantages.

And the truth was, Fang Yuan's own dao mark accumulation was quite high.

But now, heaven's will was against him and made his tribulations weak so he could not get dao marks. Annexing immortal apertures was a way, but the upper extreme heavenly eagle had not returned to him yet, while other methods needed specific Immortal Gu and were troublesome to refine. Food path methods like snack Immortal Gu could be used for the killer move eat strength, but the efficiency of this increase in dao marks was too low.

While the grass grows the horse starves, Fang Yuan naturally placed his attention on the secluded domains of heaven and earth.

Fang Yuan had quite a few secluded domains of heaven and earth!

Luo Po Valley, Dang Hun Mountain, Reverse Flow River, City Well, a total of four secluded domains of heaven and earth.

Among them, Reverse Flow River had already been used for reverse flow protection seal, it allowed Fang Yuan to fight rank eight existences. Dang Hun Mountain had already been destroyed and was still in the middle of reparation. City Well was needed to raise variant humans, and in terms of rule path, Fang Yuan was lacking.

The most suitable target was Luo Po Valley.

Fang Yuan's soul path attainment level was ordinary, but he had Spectral Soul's true inheritance, the number one soul path inheritance in this world, nobody could deny that.

On that foundation, along with the inspiration that Fang Yuan obtained from the trials of the three lifetimes, and also with myriad self Immortal Gu…

"If I add in the light of wisdom, I should succeed in deducing Luo Po seal, right?" Fang Yuan pondered.

Chapter 1572: Too Late

Time passed quickly, half a month went by.

On this day, Fang Yuan flew out of cloud city, the immortal formation around Lang Ya blessed land activated and burst out with golden light, enveloping Fang Yuan.

The golden light flashed as Fang Yuan vanished on the spot, when he reappeared, he was in a desolate place a thousand li away.

These days, Fang Yuan modified the super immortal formation again, it had the power to teleport other people.

Because earlier, when Feng Jiu Ge attacked the hairy men and killed them, Lang Ya land spirit was aggrieved but helpless.

Lang Ya land spirit remembered this painful lesson, after refining myriad self Immortal Gu, he suggested this modification to Fang Yuan.

Lang Ya Sect helped Fang Yuan to refine myriad self Immortal Gu, using the Long Hair Gu refinement immortal formation in the process, Fang Yuan naturally had to return the favor and modify the immortal formation as they wished.

Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level was extraordinary, with the help of the light of wisdom, he had already finished the modification of the immortal formation long ago.

Arriving at an empty place, Fang Yuan breathed in deeply as he started to practice his killer move.

Immortal killer move — Emperor Yama!

Instantly, his appearance changed, he was tall and majestic, he wore a crown and his face was blurred, he became inscrutable. His imperial robe had ghost and monster embroideries, the numbers were no longer like before, there were over a thousand of them.

This was the result of Fang Yuan's recent cultivation.

Immortal killer move — Soul Explosion!

Fang Yuan moved his finger as black smoke shot out, destroying everything in its path. But due to the immortal formation's protection, Cloud Cover Continent shone in silver light, it defended against the power of the soul explosion to a great extent.

But even so, a killer move at the peak of rank seven could not be defended against by the silver light.

After a chain of explosions, the area around Fang Yuan was decimated, cloud soil scattered as a large number of crevices appeared in the area of several li.

Black smoke dissipated, the soul explosion ended as one yama child monster vanished on Fang Yuan's imperial robe, after a few breaths of time, it faded as if it had never existed before.

This was the price of using soul explosion.

Fang Yuan did not mind the expenditure, after pondering through this, his eyes shone with brilliance.

Immortal killer move — Yama Battlefield!

Whoosh.

Intense wind blew as the world changed colors.

In three blinks of time, a huge surrounding area was enveloped by Fang Yuan's immortal battlefield, the place was completely isolated from the outside!

Within this battlefield killer move, the surroundings were pale green and yellow, vision was blur like there was fog. Dark winds blew, creating wailing sounds, it was scary and chilly.

Fang Yuan let out the yama children, these monsters cackled and flew freely in yama battlefield, their power was amplified, they were like fish in water.

After some testing, Fang Yuan stored all of the yama children and stopped using yama battlefield, the sky turned clear again as he returned to Lang Ya blessed land.

Yama battlefield was the greatest achievement that Fang Yuan had made in this secluded cultivation!

Earlier, Fang Yuan had deduced the immortal battlefield killer move purple star broken life, it was set up using the wisdom path Immortal Gu that Purple Mountain True Monarch left behind, Fang Yuan used it to kill You Chan and Qin Bai He.

But the advantage of purple star broken life immortal battlefield was the effect of concealing itself and isolating from the outside world. The weakness was that it needed time to set up, prior preparation was often required. And Gu Immortals were not stupid, if one tried to use it in battle, they would run away before it was set up.

Yama battlefield was created by Fang Yuan after considering his own situation, using the many battlefield killer moves that were recorded within Spectral Soul's true inheritance.

Yama battlefield was inferior to purple star broken life in terms of concealment and isolating from the outside world. Its advantage was that it only needed three blinks of time to activate.

Even though during that period of time, Fang Yuan could not move as well, it could quickly be used in battle.

In this three blinks of time, as long as Fang Yuan could grab the opportunity and catch his enemies off guard, they would not be able to run away.

After being enveloped by yama battlefield, Fang Yuan's advantage would be huge.

"Currently, I can force the enemies to stay and lose their lives if they are rank six or seven!" Fang Yuan sighed.

Gu Immortals were easy to defeat, but capturing or killing would be hard.

Firstly, there were countless ways to escape, Gu Immortals could not deal with all possibilities, some escaping methods were bound to be effective. Secondly, Fang Yuan was fighting alone and was wanted by Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven, he had to defeat his enemies in a short amount of time.

Thus earlier, Fang Yuan was very vigilant when choosing opponents. If Meng Tu did not have an immortal battlefield that could trap both him and his enemies inside autumn blade plain, Fang Yuan would not want to fight such a person.

Once yama battlefield was completed, Fang Yuan thought of his other method — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

His theft path attainment level was at great grandmaster, using great thief Immortal Gu and ghostly concealment as the cores of the killer move, he could deduce great thief ghost hand which could steal rank eight Immortal Gu.

This move was modified by Fang Yuan and became even more effective. It was used twice but managed to steal rank eight Immortal Gu Soul Beast Token, as well as rank seven Immortal Gu Bladewing, the situation quickly turned around when Meng Tu lost this Gu, resulting in his loss.

"In the past, I could not use great thief ghost hand too often to prevent my identity from leaking. If information gets out, others would be more alert and they would try to deduce my great thief ghost hand, my arrangements inside green ghost desert would also be found out."

"With yama battlefield now, I can trap my enemies and continue to use great thief ghost hand to steal Immortal Gu. There is little chance of the enemies running away, I can kill and plunder them, to accumulate my cultivation resources!"

Fang Yuan's eyes shined with a ruthless light, deep killing intent was accumulating in him.

With yama battlefield, he could start walking on the bloody road of 'killing enemies and stealing Gu while annexing their apertures to gain dao marks'.

Fang Yuan had no misgivings when it came to slaughtering innocent people, he did not feel any guilt or self-blame.

Fang Yuan licked his lips as he shook his head: "It is a pity… now is not the time yet."

If Lang Ya blessed land did not get exposed, if there was no pressure from Heavenly Court, Fang Yuan would leave and go around killing people! But the crucial thing now was to protect Lang Ya blessed land.

At the current moment, the preservation of Lang Ya Sect was more important to Fang Yuan than stealing Immortal Gu!

There was no doubt about it.

As time passed, Fang Yuan's mental pressure got larger.

Heavenly Court would not let this go, once they attacked Lang Ya blessed land again, even if Lang Ya blessed land prepared fully, it might not be able to resist.

This was because Lang Ya Sect's trump cards and secrets were exposed in the previous battle. Meanwhile, Heavenly Court still had unfathomable foundations, it could use some trump cards that targeted Lang Ya Sect or come up with some brilliant schemes to endanger the whole of Lang Ya blessed land!

The best situation was to relocate Lang Ya blessed land before the second invasion of Heavenly Court.

But the relocation would definitely be ambushed by Heavenly Court, it might even be Prince Feng Xian most likely! Fang Yuan had already deduced this clearly.

Against a rank eight, Fang Yuan could defend himself but he lacked offense, that was quite awkward.

He had two ways now.

One was to use a secluded domain of heaven and earth to form a rank eight offensive killer move. The other was to use a rank eight Immortal Gu to create an attacking method as well.

Among the secluded domains of heaven and earth, Luo Po Valley was the best choice, and also his only choice.

Fang Yuan had the inspiration to deduce Luo Po seal, but unfortunately, his progress was quite slow, even after the light of wisdom, Fang Yuan was quite vexed.

In terms of rank eight Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan had four, Attitude, Wisdom Sword, Years Flow Like Water, and Soul Beast Token.

Attitude Gu was the core Immortal Gu of familiar face, Years Flow Like Water produced year Gu, it was not for fighting. Soul Beast Token was needed in emperor yama killer move, it could not be taken out.

Looking at it, he only had wisdom sword Immortal Gu left.

Speaking of which, Fang Yuan had obtained this rank eight Immortal Gu long ago, in order to feed it, he had spent a lot of resources. But he had never been able to use it.

Activating wisdom sword Immortal Gu needed rank eight immortal essence of the user. This was what Purple Mountain True Monarch had designed for Bo Qing back then, but Fang Yuan only had rank seven red date immortal essence now.

This was a fixed rule that could not be changed.

And in fact, most rank eight Immortal Gu used rank eight immortal essence, Fang Yuan's three other Gu were exceptions.

Attitude Gu used mental energy, Years Flow Like Water could use any rank of immortal essence, but its strength depended on the essence used, Soul Beast Token expended the soul foundation of the user, and just looking at their activation requirements, all three Immortal Gu were top tier among rank eight Immortal Gu!

Thinking about it, even though Fang Yuan had many Immortal Gu and inheritances, his rank eight offensive killer move still required Luo Po Valley.

"I managed to deduce reverse flow protection seal earlier because of my water path grandmaster attainment level."

"This time, to deduce Luo Po seal, my soul path is only master level, there is a huge obstruction!"

Fang Yuan had grandmaster attainment level in many paths, his theft path and refinement path were great grandmaster and quasi-supreme grandmaster respectively, but he could not transfer them to his soul path.

His soul path was only at master attainment level.

"But I have the light of wisdom, even though progress is slow, I can still slowly force my way through!"

"The biggest problem is time now, I hope I can make it… hmm?!"

At this time, the world started shaking, a huge dark spiral appeared out of nowhere.

"Oh no!" Fang Yuan's expression changed.

He recognized that the source of this dark spiral were the dao marks that Feng Jiu Ge had left behind.

Fang Yuan had already investigated these dao marks long ago, Lang Ya land spirit did the same. Both felt that this was a tracking method that was hard to get rid of. But now, Lang Ya blessed land was isolated from the outside world, these dao marks possessed no threat.

But to think that without anyone controlling and instilling immortal essence, these dao marks actually gathered into a dark spiral.

"Smash it!" Fang Yuan screamed, Lang Ya land spirit also gave the same orders at the same time.

The defensive formation that Fang Yuan modified immediately activated.

But at the same time, four starlight beams shot out of the dark spiral.

With a loud sound, the dark spiral vanished.

The starlight faded as four Gu Immortals appeared.

Feng Jiu Ge, Chen Yi, and Thunder Ghost True Monarch were present. They were led by a female immortal, she looked around before fixing her gaze on Fang Yuan, she smiled: "Fang Yuan, I finally caught you."

It was Heavenly Court's current leader, the number one wisdom path Gu Immortal — Fairy Zi Wei!

Chapter 1573: Star Cast

Heavenly Court invaded, four Gu Immortals appeared out of nowhere, Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk to pin-size.

Even with his knowledge and countless experiences, he felt that this was unbelievable!

"There is such a method? Sending four rank eight Gu Immortals in at the same time! If we did not destroy that dark spiral instantly, I'm afraid even more Gu Immortals would have entered."

Even though Feng Jiu Ge was not rank eight, his dao marks were at rank eight level, Fang Yuan placed him at the same level as rank eights.

Rank eight Gu Immortals had incredibly dense dao marks, there were few methods that could transport them and they were very hard to use. Even the immortal killer move seven immortal doors that Feng Jiu Ge used earlier could not teleport rank eight Gu Immortals.

If rank eight Gu Immortals wanted to move, they had to either fly themselves through immemorial white heaven or black heaven, unless they were space path great expert who could teleport themselves.

But even so, such space path great experts could only teleport themselves, they could not move other rank eight existences.

And Heavenly Court seemed to have used a method to directly teleport four rank eight Gu Immortals over from Central Continent! Such a method was truly unthinkable.

"Even in the five hundred years of my previous life, during the five regions chaotic war, I did not hear that Heavenly Court had such a move!"

Transporting four rank eight Gu Immortals at once, which was not the limit, and it could even create a tracking effect. Such a method was truly scary, any defense could be ripped apart, the advantage of having such a move could even extend to large scale fights.

Think about it: During the five regions chaotic war, every rank eight Gu Immortal ruled over an area. At this time, if Heavenly Court mobilizes several rank eights to teleport to an enemy rank eight and attack that person as a group, they would have a huge advantage in numbers, they would likely win. Who could endure such attacks if they did it multiple times? Any force would be extremely concerned and feel helpless against this.

"In the five hundred years of my previous life, why did Heavenly Court not do this? Was it because the conditions were not right, or was it not time for this move yet? I think I understand now!"

Fang Yuan's thoughts moved like lightning, he understood why.

If Heavenly Court revealed that they had such methods, once a few rank eight Gu Immortals died in the other regions, they would become alert, they would work together and form a large alliance against Heavenly Court!

It was common sense.

If they did not ally, as the situation progresses, any rank eight Gu Immortal would be in great danger at all times. Heavenly Court could attack any individual rank eight Gu Immortal at any time, they were not stupid, only by working together could they be safe against Heavenly Court.

Of course, Heavenly Court was not stupid, they had kept this move hidden and did not use it. They were afraid that this move's great power would make the other regions work together and form a four region alliance that would target Heavenly Court solely!

But now, in order to attack Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court had to use this move in advance, it showed how determined Heavenly Court was in attacking Lang Ya blessed land!

"No, not just me, they are tempted by rank nine wisdom Gu. At the same time, annexing Lang Ya blessed land would greatly help towards repairing fate Gu!"

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly to himself.

Heavenly Court's attack was too sudden, even though Fang Yuan was already mentally prepared for it.

But there was no helping it, Heavenly Court's method was truthfully out of Fang Yuan's wildest imagination.

"This is why such enemies are the scariest. Because they have too many trump cards from their immense foundation!" Fang Yuan sighed bitterly internally.

"Thief!" At the same time, while the other Heavenly Court Gu Immortals stayed motionless, Thunder Ghost True Monarch directly pounced at Fang Yuan.

She hated Fang Yuan to the limit, he had sold three of her rib bones in treasure yellow heaven, that video had been playing nonstop, it was the greatest humiliation of her life!

Thus, Thunder Ghost True Monarch directly charged at Fang Yuan and attacked, she was filled with intense killing intent.

But at the next moment, Fang Yuan vanished as golden light flashed.

Thunder Ghost True Monarch missed her target, she looked up and stared fiercely at the base of the super formation.

"Huff!"

Fang Yuan was inside the super formation now, controlling it personally. The first thing he did was to activate the formation and bring in all of the variant human Gu Immortals that were scattered over Lang Ya blessed land.

When he had just acted, Heavenly Court also did the same.

Immortal killer move — Separation Song!

Feng Jiu Ge used his signature killer move as separation song started, countering all Immortal Gu Houses and immortal formations in this world.

Bright light shone in Fang Yuan's eyes, he multitasked as the immortal formation flew up and burst out with orange-red light.

Within the red light, separation song was weakening as his voice faded into nothingness.

To deal with separation song, Fang Yuan had made some modifications to the immortal formation! It was extremely effective when used now.

Feng Jiu Ge had once dismantled multiple layers of this immortal formation using separation song, but now, before separation song even got close to the core, it was exterminated, Feng Jiu Ge frowned deeply.

"Let me do it." Fairy Zi Wei flickered her finger as a starry rainbow flew out.

The starry rainbow flew like an arrow, flying past the clouds and wind, shooting into the super immortal formation and turning into a cloud of star sand, it was very dazzling.

The immortal formation activated faster and faster, this star sand fused into the immortal formation's activation and revealed several special forms, like clouds or dust, or even water vats…

Fairy Zi Wei smiled lightly, countless thoughts appeared in her mind, moving like waves of the ocean.

"Oh no! This wisdom path killer move can help her to deduce the workings of the immortal formation, it can also obstruct the cooperation of Gu worms and make the immortal formation slower and non-fluid." Some of the variant human Gu Immortals who came could tell.

"What do we do?"

"What do we do?!"

Almost all of the variant human Gu Immortals were covered in sweat, they had nervous expressions, they were filled with fear and immense pressure of an apocalypse.

Heavenly Court's group was too powerful, they were equivalent to four rank eights, even disregarding Feng Jiu Ge, the other three were rank eight elites and experts, one could be of immense threat to Lang Ya blessed land, not to mention three of them!

"Strange, why is Fairy Zi Wei not using Star Constellation Chessboard?" Fang Yuan had completely calmed down, suspicion flashed in his eyes.

His fight against Fairy Zi Wei was during Southern Border's dream realm battle.

"It is a pity that Star Constellation Chessboard was left in Heavenly Court to sustain the killer move star cast, otherwise, I would be able to easily unravel this super immortal formation with dozens of times the efficiency!" Fairy Zi Wei sighed internally, she did not stop her actions.

Another wisdom path killer move was unleashed without any warning, Fang Yuan did not even know how to deal with it, but the formation was hit and the star sand that invaded expanded to twice of its size!

"Troublesome!" Fang Yuan frowned deeply.

"Heavenly Court, do you think our Lang Ya Sect are easily bullied? Kill them!"

At this moment, Lang Ya land spirit growled, the silver giant formed from ancient battle formation Heavenly Giant Solor descended into the battlefield.

Chapter 1574: Chen Yi

The silver giant was tall and mighty, stretching its arms and sweeping at the four Central Continent Gu Immortals, strong air currents were generated.

Chen Yi's eyes flashed with brilliance, snorting: "Let me!"

Compared to the silver giant, his body was very small, but his aura burst out and contested the silver giant evenly.

Immortal killer move — Immortal Binding Vine!

Chen Yi pointed as countless jade green light threads extended towards the silver giant and coiled around it.

The silver giant punched ferociously, but due to the obstruction of the jade light threads, it was too slow and changed directions, crashing into the cloud soil and creating a huge crater as soil scattered.

Chen Yi watched at the side without moving, he floated in the air as he pointed at the silver giant with his fingers.

The jade threads on the silver giant were increasing in number, surrounding it tightly, the threads got thicker until they reached their limits, becoming vines that were thick and long, binding the silver giant.

Within the battle formation Heavenly Giant Solor, Lang Ya land spirit was shouting in anger, this immortal binding vine seemed to have countered him entirely, even with great strength, he could not use any of it properly, this was quite a frustrating situation.

"Sixth Hair!" Lang Ya land spirit called out.

Sixth Hair immediately used an immortal killer move as golden light appeared on the Heavenly Giant Solor, the immortal binding vines were cut apart inch by inch, but they recovered quickly.

Chen Yi sneered as he used another killer move.

Countless vines were cut down, landing on the cloud soil, but with Chen Yi's help, they grew rapidly, turning into huge trees.

The huge trees were scattered around the silver giant, turning into a huge circle that trapped the silver giant at the center.

Lang Ya land spirit sensed something amiss, but the silver giant was bound by the immortal binding vines, it could not move away.

At this time, between the giant trees, leaves and branches started to intertwine, the roots of the trees under the cloud soil also gathered into a ball and emerged from the soil. With the tree trunks as the main pillars, the branches and roots coiled together and formed a huge cage.

Immortal killer move — Ancient Tree Prison Cage!

The silver giant finally broke free from the immortal binding vines when it immediately got trapped in the ancient tree prison cage. Lang Ya land spirit shouted in anger and ordered the hairy man Gu Immortals to unleash their offensive killer moves.

But the ancient tree prison cage sustained those attacks and even used them as nutrients to strengthen itself.

Lang Ya land spirit saw this and quickly stopped, he tested for a while and found that the most effective way to destroy the cage was with the giant's bare hands.

The hairy man Gu Immortals were helpless, they could only manipulate Heavenly Giant Solor to unleash punches and kicks, slamming at the ancient tree prison cage.

"Damn it!" Lang Ya land spirit cursed, his forehead was covered in sweat. He was trapped here and could not help Fang Yuan, he could only watch as Feng Jiu Ge and Fairy Zi Wei targeted the super immortal formation.

Without any choice, Lang Ya land spirit had to approach the rockman Gu Immortals: "Quick, let that old dragon out!"

Roar—!

There was the cry of a dragon as a huge figure appeared in front of everyone.

The immemorial rock dragon!

Its body was made of rocks, it was filled with dense earth path dao marks, its dragon body was heavy and thick, its dragon fangs were sharp like stalactites, it was majestic and large, having an impressive entrance.

The rock dragon seemed to move slowly, but it was actually fast as it flew into the sky, casting a huge shadow down onto the ground.

Heavenly Court's four immortals were also under the shadow as they raised their heads, expressing shock on their faces.

"To think that Lang Ya blessed land has a hidden immemorial rock dragon!" Feng Jiu Ge sighed.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled: "It does not belong to Lang Ya blessed land, it is likely from those variant human Gu Immortals."

As a wisdom path great expert, she had deduced the truth in an instant.

"Let me destroy this rock dragon!" Thunder Ghost True Monarch licked her lips as battle intent surged.

"No need!" Chen Yi grunted as he stretched his finger, using the same move again.

Immortal killer move — Immortal Binding Vine.

The immortal binding vines extended around the immemorial rock dragon as it became restricted, although it still charged at the four Central Continent immortals.

The four immortals dodged while the immemorial rock dragon hit the ground, next, Chen Yi used the ancient tree prison cage killer move again and trapped it!

"How can this be?!" The variant human Gu Immortals saw this and felt deeply surprised and disappointed.

Even Lang Ya land spirit took in a deep breath, he felt a chill down his spine.

The immemorial rock dragon that they were relying on was restricted so easily. Meanwhile, on Heavenly Court's side, Chen Yi had a great display of prowess, while Fairy Zi Wei and Feng Jiu Ge suppressed the super immortal formation, and Thunder Ghost True Monarch has yet to fight!

Fang Yuan's expression was ugly too, but he did not feel much surprise.

"The immemorial rock dragon is strong in defense and has no fear. Once injured, the rockmen can sacrifice themselves to heal it rapidly, this healing method is very absurd!"

When Gu Immortals get injured, it is very difficult and troublesome to heal them. The higher the cultivation level, the harder they are to heal.

For rank eight Gu Immortals, if they sustained injuries, they would need to pay full attention in healing themselves without distraction. But the immemorial rock dragon's healing method could be done amidst battle, this often gave many Gu Immortals huge headaches when fighting them.

The immemorial rock dragon was also famous because of this.

But today was different, it was up against Heavenly Court's rank eight Gu Immortal Chen Yi!

Firstly, Heavenly Court had been suppressing and killing variant human Gu Immortals, having been established on that foundation, they were very familiar with the rockman tribe's rock dragons.

Secondly, the immemorial rock dragon did not have any wild rank eight Immortal Gu to use, while Chen Yi had rank eight killer moves and the best tactic against it, this led to the immemorial rock dragon's greatest advantage becoming virtually useless.

And finally, Chen Yi's killer move was truly profound, especially the ancient tree prison cage, it did not fear immortal killer moves, it was hard to get rid of.

It was no surprise that the immemorial rock dragon lost to Chen Yi.

Even though it struggled intensely, the restriction on it grew thicker and tighter, without external help, it could not break out of the immortal binding vines, and definitely not the ancient tree prison cage outside of that.

"Hairy men, we need to rely on ourselves!" Lang Ya land spirit shouted as the silver giant finally found an opening in the ancient tree prison cage and destroyed it.

"As expected of the second ancient battle formation, Heavenly Giant Solor." Chen Yi evaluated as he smiled, muttering: "But do you think my ancient tree prison cage is so easy to break out of?"

The silver giant's movements stopped.

Lang Ya land spirit was slightly dazed, he turned around to look and found a wooden hand grabbing the silver giant's leg.

"What is that?" The silver giant turned around and chopped down on the hand with both arms resembling an ax that struck harshly.

The wooden hand was split by the ax but it was only half split, it was not entirely chopped apart.

The silver giant wanted to attack again, but an wooden giant appeared from under the soil.

The wooden giant let go out its hand and lowered its body, charging at the silver giant's chest with its shoulder, slamming it to the ground.

Lang Ya Sect's Gu Immortals were caught unguarded, they were about to make the silver giant stand up but the wooden giant attacked relentlessly, eventually, it jumped into the sky and crashed down on the silver giant with a loud thud.

Under the immense pressure, a hairy man Gu Immortal made a mistake and used an immortal killer move on the wooden giant.

The wooden giant was revitalized as the injuries on its body healed, at the same time, it grew to the same size as the silver giant.

Chen Yi snorted in self-satisfaction, this was his immortal killer move — Giant Tree Divine Statue, it inherited the property of the ancient tree prison cage, immortal killer moves were not of concern, only physical attacks were effective on it.

"So this is the power of Genesis Lotus' true inheritance." Thunder Ghost True Monarch's eyes were flickering with bright light.

At this moment, Chen Yi displayed great power, suppressing both the silver giant and immemorial rock dragon!

This was his true power, as the first supreme elder of Heavenly Lotus Sect, and the inheritor of Genesis Lotus' true inheritance, he had incredible battle strength that was extraordinary.

Earlier in green ghost desert, he had fought with much frustration. Most of the time, he was fighting inside Divine Bean Palace, afraid of damaging it, he could not fight freely, while his opponent, Fang clan's first supreme elder, had a huge advantage with strength path, he could fight in close combat freely, making Chen Yi extremely furious but without options.

Now, Chen Yi could display his true advantage, he erupted with great battle strength, even without using his trump card, karma divine tree, he managed to suppress both the silver giant and the immemorial rock dragon.

Chapter 1575: Fang Yuan's Actions

Chen Yi displayed his true strength as Heavenly Court obtained the advantage. What worried Fang Yuan more was that they had not gone all out yet.

Even Chen Yi, who was doing most of the work had not used karma divine tree.

"Even though Chen Yi is inferior to Purple Mountain True Monarch and Duke Long, he is still a first rate expert among rank eights! Fairy Zi Wei and Thunder Ghost True Monarch are similar, while Feng Jiu Ge cannot be underestimated. I need to act myself!"

Chen Yi suppressed the immemorial rock dragon and silver giant, Feng Jiu Ge and Fairy Zi Wei were resisting the super immortal formation, Lang Ya Sect only had Fang Yuan left who had rank eight battle strength, if he did not act now, who could save them?

And the truth was, Lang Ya land spirit had already urged Fang Yuan multiple times.

Golden light flickered as Fang Yuan appeared in front Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei had expected this, she waved her hand as a gust of divine purple wind started to blow.

As the wind blew, it caused ripples on reverse flow protection seal.

"Oh? This killer move!" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

This divine purple wind matched the strength of its enemy, it was similar to reverse flow protection seal, it was a defensive retaliation type. Reverse flow protection seal did not have any offensive might, as both moves reflected the damage over and over again to each other, neither sides could do anything to the other, Fang Yuan was pushed out by this wind.

"Fang Yuan, you finally came out!" A flash of lightning flickered as Thunder Ghost True Monarch Jing Lan teleported and appeared behind Fang Yuan, smiling sinisterly and full of killing intent.

"Trident lightning dissolution!" Jing Lan shouted as three flashes of lightning appeared from her fingertips.

The lightning crackled and gathered in the air, forming into a trident made of blue lightning.

Trident lightning dissolution landed on Fang Yuan's back but was blocked by reverse flow protection seal and reflected back at her.

Jing Lan laughed loudly as she swallowed this trident lightning dissolution before flying away with eyes crackling with sparks.

Fang Yuan's heart sank: "Oh no, this trident lightning dissolution killer move is meant to probe my reverse flow protection seal. Even though Thunder Ghost True Monarch is not a wisdom path Gu Immortal, with Fairy Zi Wei the wisdom path great expert here, they can try to unravel my reverse flow protection seal here!"

Last time, due to Fang Yuan's trap, Thunder Ghost True Monarch was beaten up and Fairy Zi Wei failed.

However, the trap that Fang Yuan set up was exposed, it could no longer be used.

During this period, Fang Yuan had planned and cultivated intensely, making many preparations, Heavenly Court did the same. Not only did they help Thunder Ghost True Monarch to replenish her Immortal Gu, Fairy Zi Wei even used Star Constellation Chessboard to deduce trident lightning dissolution for Thunder Ghost True Monarch, in order to deal with Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal!

Fang Yuan had a heavy heart but he did not fluster, the truth was, he had expected this.

He actively attacked and tried to fight with Fairy Zi Wei and Thunder Ghost True Monarch, in order to reduce the pressure on the rest.

Both sides fought continuously as Cloud Cover Continent's terrain was completely devastated. The sounds of their battle resounded throughout the skies, the countless hairy man mortals and Gu Masters were extremely fearful and in shock.

After the silver giant destroyed a giant tree divine statue, Chen Yi created another one.

The immemorial rock dragon was trapped in the immortal binding vines, it had little hope of escaping.

Even Fang Yuan could not help it. He had tried but the outer layer of the ancient tree prison cage was too thick and did not fear immortal killer moves, it was a pain to get through.

"This killer move is not immune to all immortal killer moves, we just lack the necessary method. If I had enough time, with my wisdom path methods, I can deduce and unravel this move!"

Fang Yuan sighed to himself.

This was the essence of Genesis Lotus true inheritance's killer moves, it was like reverse flow protection seal which rendered all of Heavenly Court helpless against it.

Now, Fang Yuan was on the receiving side, against this ancient tree prison cage, he had the same feelings as Fairy Zi Wei who had faced reverse flow protection seal earlier.

After some fighting, Heavenly Court still had the upper hand, and their advantage was growing.

Fang Yuan did not deduce Luo Po seal, he did not have an offensive rank eight killer move, he could defend using reverse flow protection seal, but he could not be of any threat to the four immortals.

Ancient battle formation Heavenly Giant Solor was the same, even though the hairy man Gu Immortals had many methods and deep chemistry, they were not fighting against Feng Jiu Ge this time, but Chen Yi instead.

Chen Yi had rich methods that were all at rank eight level, no matter how Lang Ya land spirit resisted, he was suppressed by Chen Yi.

After some more time, Fairy Zi Wei suddenly frowned as she ordered: "Senior Jing Lan, go around and find wisdom Gu."

"Little thief, I will let you off for now!" Even though Thunder Ghost True Monarch hated Fang Yuan, the bigger picture was more important, she snickered at Fang Yuan before flying away from the battlefield like lightning.

Lang Ya's side could only watch helplessly as she left.

The truth was, Heavenly Court's invasion was not just to eliminate Fang Yuan and annex Lang Ya to repair fate Gu, their most important goal was to obtain the wild wisdom Gu.

This legendary rank nine Immortal Gu had been in Star Constellation Immortal Venerable's hands long ago. Ordinary forces could not make use of it, but Heavenly Court had abundant methods. Forget about the rest, with just this wisdom Gu, Star Constellation Chessboard would become a rank nine Immortal Gu House, its power would rise sharply! Just this advantage was enough for Fairy Zi Wei to come personally.

Earlier, when Heavenly Court's four immortals arrived, Fairy Zi Wei had already used her investigative killer moves, even though her search range extended throughout Lang Ya blessed land, she could not find wisdom Gu.

And now, she could only send Thunder Ghost True Monarch.

Seeing that Thunder Ghost True Monarch had left the battlefield, Lang Ya land spirit screamed in anger while fearing that the mortal hairy men would be targeted, but because he was trapped by Chen Yi, the silver giant was still restricted by the immortal binding vine and could not move, even though many layers were pulled off, it was quite frustrating.

"They are looking for wisdom Gu!" Fang Yuan's eyes burst out with bright light.

His wisdom path methods were extraordinary, he had already deduced Heavenly Court's intention.

It was a pity that Heavenly Court did not know wisdom Gu was already in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture. Last time, they had failed to take it from Lang Ya blessed land, that was the best opportunity, the difficulty had risen by thousands of times now!

"In that case…" Bright light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes, he noticed that this was the best opportunity!

Immemorial year beast!

He opened his immortal aperture and let out the monkey immemorial year beast.

At the same time, he charged forward and used countless immortal killer moves to attack Fairy Zi Wei.

Among the four Heavenly Court immortals, the biggest threat was not Chen Yi who had Genesis Lotus true inheritance, rank eight expert Thunder Ghost True Monarch Jing Lan who could resist Spectral Soul, or Feng Jiu Ge who had assimilation wind song, it was Fairy Zi Wei.

The reason was simple, she was a wisdom path great expert!

Just this point alone made her the leader of this expedition. Given enough time, she could deduce and create countless miracles.

He had to eliminate this wisdom path Gu Immortal first!

Chapter 1576: Yama Battlefield

Ancient sword dragon transformation!

Soul explosion!

Strength path giant hand!

Myriad dragon!

Fang Yuan used almost all his methods against Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei laughed: "Fang Yuan, you're at your wits' end."

She also used multiple killer moves of all kinds, they were all profound and actually blocked all of Fang Yuan's attacks! Some even countered his moves.

Fang Yuan's methods had already been exposed long ago. Fairy Zi Wei had been collecting intel and did a lot of deductions, she created many methods that countered him.

This was the incredible power of a wisdom path Gu Immortal.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan's killer moves still had some use, after all, he had also modified his moves to deal with Fairy Zi Wei's deductions.

"But in terms of wisdom path attainment, I cannot compare to Fairy Zi Wei. At this rate, eventually, Fairy Zi Wei will deduce all of my methods and I will no longer be able to fight back."

Thoughts flashed in Fang Yuan's mind, battle intent surged in him but his mind was still cold as ice.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled as she breathed out some purple qi with imposing aura.

The purple qi was delicate like a baby's fist, but it entered the immemorial year beast's mind the moment it hit.

Howl—!

The immemorial year beast growled in pain, it was furiously holding its head, it lost its ability to fight as it rolled around on the ground.

The variant human Gu Immortals controlling the super immortal formation were all stunned!

Fairy Zi Wei's own battle strength was even higher than Chen Yi. Earlier, she had not fought seriously, but now, her strong methods and imposing air were a huge shock to everyone.

Fang Yuan also felt a little discouraged.

He still had two immemorial soul beasts captured from green ghost desert, but he did not want to use them now.

Immemorial desolate beasts alone were often at a disadvantage against rank eight Gu Immortals. That was, unless they had rank eight Immortal Gu in them.

Against these rank eight Gu Immortal experts from Heavenly Court, even immemorial desolate beasts with wild Immortal Gu could not deal with them!

Like how Fang Yuan could capture those two immemorial soul beasts earlier, against Fairy Zi Wei, they held little threat.

"I am clear of this, in order to resist Spectral Soul Demon Venerable in the past, Heavenly Court had obtained many soul path methods. This is why I let the immemorial year beast out, if I summoned the immemorial soul beasts, they would be even weaker against her."

Fang Yuan felt pressure rising in him.

The enemies were just too powerful, they were truly formidable. Fang Yuan did not even have the confidence to kill the weakest person among them, Feng Jiu Ge. Fairy Zi Wei and the rest were all experts among rank eight experts, any single one of them could match Fang Yuan or even defeat him.

To speak the truth, Lang Ya blessed land was already very powerful, it had three rank eight battle strength existences. This was already above the standards of most super forces in the five regions.

Among the five regions, only the top tier super forces had one rank eight Gu Immortal. In Southern Border, why could the number one righteous path super force Wu clan dominate the region for so long? It was because there was a point in time where they had two rank eight Gu Immortals simultaneously, and also at least one rank eight Gu Immortal throughout the generations to hold the fort.

Of course, Immortal Gu Houses could not be neglected, many Immortal Gu Houses had rank eight battle strength too.

The strength of Lang Ya Sect was equivalent to a super force or even above that.

But against Heavenly Court, it was just too weak in comparison!

The immemorial rock dragon was suppressed by Chen Yi, Heavenly Giant Solor was struggling but still at a disadvantage.

Feng Jiu Ge had been dealing with the super immortal formation that Fang Yuan modified, the formation path attainment of the variant human Gu Immortals inside could not match Fang Yuan, while Feng Jiu Ge's separation song was absurdly fierce even though it was countered by the immortal Gu formation, the two sides were at a deadlock.

Fang Yuan's fight against Fairy Zi Wei was locked in a deadlock as well without any breakthroughs.

He could not let this go on!

Once Thunder Ghost True Monarch fails to find wisdom Gu and returns to fight, unless Lang Ya land spirit exposes a new trump card, Fang Yuan would definitely lose.

"Lang Ya blessed land originated from Long Hair Ancestor, it must likely have other trump cards!"

"But now, I cannot depend on this possibility. Immortal killer move — Yama Battlefield!"

Fang Yuan suddenly flew and got closer to Fairy Zi Wei, before using his newly developed immortal battlefield killer move.

Because of the soul explosion earlier, there were large numbers of soul path dao marks in the battlefield, yama battlefield rapidly opened as it formed in a breath of time.

But even at this speed, Fang Yuan could not trap Fairy Zi Wei.

This wisdom path great expert noticed something amiss the moment fy got close to her, she immediately retreated.

Fang Yuan's yama battlefield was created very quickly, one breath of time was faster than most of the immortal battlefield killer moves in this world.

But this amount of time was enough for Fairy Zi Wei to escape.

"I failed!" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

Not being able to trap Fairy Zi Wei, he had wasted his immortal essence.

"However, my efforts were not in vain!" Fang Yuan looked at Feng Jiu Ge who was inside yama battlefield as he surged with killing intent: "I'll kill him first!"

Fang Yuan grabbed the opportunity, the position earlier was perfect, if Fairy Zi Wei had not retreated in advance, he would have trapped the both of them.

Yama battlefield was a new method, even if Fairy Zi Wei wanted to unravel it, she would need some time.

If Fang Yuan could trap both Feng Jiu Ge and Fairy Zi Wei, in the battlefield, there would only be the silver giant, immemorial rock dragon, Chen Yi, and the super immortal formation.

Now that Feng Jiu Ge was trapped, the super immortal formation was safe, if they could grab the opportunity to destroy the ancient tree prison cage, the immemorial rock dragon would also be free.

Chen Yi would have to deal with both the silver giant and rock dragon, as well as a super immortal formation, he would not be able to handle it.

If they could severely injure Chen Yi during that period, even if Thunder Ghost True Monarch returns, Lang Ya's side would be able to regain their footing.

But now, Fang Yuan only managed to trap Feng Jiu Ge, that meant the super immortal formation and Fairy Zi Wei were competing with each other.

But even if Thunder Ghost True Monarch returns, for the time being, they would still be in a deadlock. After all, rank eight battle strength and sufficient foundation meant that they could not fall easily.

Thus, Fang Yuan's target now was to kill Feng Jiu Ge!

And he had to do it quickly, the faster the better!

After killing Feng Jiu Ge, Fang Yuan would dispel yama battlefield and deal with the three Heavenly Court rank eights alongside the rock dragon and silver giant, Lang Ya's side would be in less danger after that.

Thus, Feng Jiu Ge was a crucial point to break through!

"A soul path battlefield killer move? It seems to have theft path mixed in!" Fairy Zi Wei looked at the air in front of her, for the first time in this battle, she frowned.

The immortal battlefield isolated the inside from outside, thankfully, Fang Yuan had used it right in front of her, otherwise, she could not find the point of entry for yama battlefield that was just a tiny spot.

But even if she did, Fairy Zi Wei's deductions were having huge problems.

Because yama battlefield not only contained the profundity of soul path, it also contained ghostly concealment! It was one with the killer move emperor yama.

Chapter 1577: Fang Yuan Versus Feng Jiu Ge

Rumble!

The super immortal formation activated as countless lightning bolts attacked Fairy Zi Wei and Chen Yi.

Since the battle started, this super formation had either been suppressed by Feng Jiu Ge and Fairy Zi Wei or was in a deadlock with Feng Jiu Ge, it could finally displayed its might now.

Chen Yi quickly defended himself, he was quite troubled.

Lang Ya land spirit saw the chance and moved the silver giant, resisting the attack of the giant tree divine statue as it crashed into the ancient tree prison cage trapping the rock dragon.

Fairy Zi Wei quickly thought about it, choosing to attack the super immortal formation while deducing yama battlefield, ignoring Chen Yi's situation.

Fairy Zi Wei chose the safe method.

If Feng Jiu Ge fought with Fang Yuan now, she might not assist him. If he really ended up in a dangerous spot, she might reinforce him, she would still make it in time.

But now, yama battlefield was isolated from the outside, Feng Jiu Ge and Fang Yuan were fighting alone, this was dangerous and accidents might occur.

Feng Jiu Ge was equally important to Heavenly Court, even more than Chen Yi and Thunder Ghost True Monarch, because he was the Dao Guardian of Great Dream Immortal Venerable Feng Jin Huang!

Fairy Zi Wei did not want any mishaps to occur to him.

Fang Yuan wanted Feng Jiu Ge to die right now!

Immortal killer move — Emperor Yama!

Immortal killer move — Yama Child!

Immortal killer move — Soul Explosion!

At once, Fang Yuan attacked in a frenzy, turning into emperor yama form as the yama child army attacked Feng Jiu Ge from all directions, soul explosions were mixed in and caused great damage to Feng Jiu Ge, in just a short period of time, blood was already flowing out of his mouth.

"Great method!" Feng Jiu Ge felt an intense threat to his life, he used his killer move.

Immortal killer move — Yang Pass Tune!

At the moment of crisis, he had to use yang pass tune killer move despite there being a time limit.

Using yang pass tune, he dodged and dodged, but within yama battlefield, his method was greatly restricted, it was quite ineffective.

The yama children were amplified and moved even quicker and with greater force, they attacked without fearing death.

Feng Jiu Ge dodged with all his effort, but he could not shrug off the yama children.

Immortal killer move — Song Warrior!

Immortal killer move — Green Jade Song!

Immortal killer move — Heaven and Earth Song!

Immortal killer move — Submission Song!

Immortal killer move — Separation Song!

Four song warriors protected Feng Jiu Ge as he moved around the yama child army, trying to get close to Fang Yuan.

Capturing the king is essential, this was the most straightforward and wise tactic.

Fang Yuan in his emperor yama form flew around in yama battlefield with utmost ease and agility.

Even though his enslavement path attainment was not high, he could still order the yama children to attack Feng Jiu Ge fluidly.

After a while, Feng Jiu Ge had a grim expression.

Green jade song warrior often shattered the yama children which were turned into jade statues. But these yama children were all unfearing and were tougher to deal with than ancient desolate beasts.

Heaven and earth song had little effect within yama battlefield, separation song could break apart immortal formations, but the Immortal Gu used to sustain this battlefield were inside Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, this was unlike immortal formations and Immortal Gu Houses which had their Immortal Gu House outside. Separation song could not affect the interior of Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture, it was useless.

Submission song that Feng Jiu Ge had entrusted his hopes to was the best method against enslavement path, it had been a great help against Fang Yuan in the past, but right now, this song was an example of 'the bigger the hope, the greater the disappointment'. The yama children were merely affected in movement, they were completely unaffected by the enslavement effect of submission song.

"My yama child uses soul beast modification, soul beast summoning and other methods within Spectral Soul true inheritance, it also relies on ghostly concealment at the core, how can your submission song work against it?" Fang Yuan snickered in his mind.

"Do I need to use assimilation wind song?" Feng Jiu Ge gritted his teeth.

Fang Yuan's battle strength was very shocking!

Even though he was mentally prepared, now that he was suppressed by Fang Yuan, Feng Jiu Ge felt a sensation of disbelief.

How long had it been?

Not long ago, he, Feng Jiu Ge, had chased Fang Yuan from Southern Border to Western Desert and put him in a difficult position .

"Fang Yuan's growth speed is too fast! This time, even if we do not get wisdom Gu, we need to kill him!" Feng Jiu Ge sighed internally, he stopped the notion of using assimilation wind song.

Assimilation wind song was too dangerous.

Once he used it and made a mistake, the first person to die would be Feng Jiu Ge.

Unless he had no choice, Feng Jiu Ge would not use assimilation wind song. Especially in an intense battle like this, the interferences were too great.

"And my assimilation wind song has already been exposed, how can such a crafty person like Fang Yuan be unprepared against it?"

Feng Jiu Ge was very wary of Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment.

"This time, we attacked with a powerful force, because Fairy Zi Wei isn't trapped inside this battlefield killer move, we have the absolute advantage in battle now."

"I need to wait for Lady Zi Wei to deduce and break this immortal battlefield from the outside, that is the best method."

"After all, this immortal battlefield contains soul path and theft path aura, but no time path aura, there should not be any problems with the rate of time."

Feng Jiu Ge dodged as he fought, refusing to let the yama children surround him, he decided to wait for reinforcements after putting his trust in Fairy Zi Wei.

Fang Yuan had been thinking of ending the battle quickly, if Feng Jiu Ge fought against him directly, he would be extremely happy about it.

But was Feng Jiu Ge stupid?

He had a clear understanding of the situation, he chose the best tactic for now, Fang Yuan sighed deeply in disappointment.

"Unfortunately, even though I have time path methods and rank eight time path Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water, it cannot be fused into yama battlefield."

Yama battlefield was not a killer move used on sovereign immortal body, it had the problem of conflicting dao marks.

Fang Yuan had always kept a balance between theft path and soul path, but the conflict had reached the limit, adding time path on top of it was too difficult!

Time path battlefield killer moves could alter the rate of time compared to the outside world, but yama battlefield could not.

In fact, even if Fang Yuan tried to use time path killer moves, any moves that were not theft path or soul path would be resisted by the dao marks of the immortal battlefield.

Immortal killer move — Triple Extreme Sound!

Feng Jiu Ge's methods were unending, the yama children could not get close. Once his song warriors were destroyed, he would create new ones immediately.

But the biggest problem for Fang Yuan was yang pass tune, it allowed Feng Jiu Ge to teleport instantly. Even though this move was restricted in this battlefield, having a limited range and would not break out of yama battlefield, Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand was too slow, at least, when compared to Feng Jiu Ge.

Even though yang pass tune had a time limit, Fang Yuan could not wait, he needed to end this fast, he had to kill Feng Jiu Ge as soon as possible, in order to help in the battle outside.

Immortal killer move — Familiar Face!

Fang Yuan turned from emperor yama into a yama child as he sneaked into the army.

Feng Jiu Ge's heart jumped, his teleportation became more frequent.

But Fang Yuan was still in the dark while he was exposed in the open, after a while, Fang Yuan found his opportunity.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

The ghost hand was completely concealed, going past the four song warriors and aiming for Feng Jiu Ge directly.

Feng Jiu Ge was still using triple extreme sound, he did not sense its movement. Great thief ghost hand entered Feng Jiu Ge's immortal aperture and grabbed an Immortal Gu tightly before leaving rapidly.

"Oh no, Fixed Immortal Travel!!" Feng Jiu Ge stared with his eyes wide opened, he was deeply shocked by the assault.

He quickly turned around and burst out with sound waves, forcing great thief ghost hand to reveal its appearance before him.

He was about to attack the great thief ghost hand but Fang Yuan was well prepared, a large number of yama children rushed up and sacrificed themselves, protecting the great thief ghost hand as it entered Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

Chapter 1578: Fang Yuan's Rank Eight Offensive Method!

"To think that I would regain Fixed Immortal Travel one day!" Fang Yuan sighed deeply as he looked at the Immortal Gu that was captured by great thief ghost hand.

"Oh? It's been raised to rank seven. It is indeed what I had deduced from the information earlier." Fang Yuan was secretly joyful.

Even though he had ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel which could replace the use of Fixed Immortal Travel to some extent, it had many flaws, needing four Gu Immortals to execute. Furthermore, it had a smaller range than Fixed Immortal Travel, which was able to go anywhere in the world.

Rank seven Fixed Immortal Travel still had the same appearance as its rank six version.

Right now, this Gu was struggling in great thief ghost hand, but it did not move, holding onto Fixed Immortal Travel as it flew rapidly.

After flying into Heaven Sealing Mountain inside Mini Southern Border, great thief ghost hand opened and tossed Fixed Immortal Travel into the immortal formation.

This immortal formation used two Immortal Gu as the core, Self Love and Affection, along with countless mortal Gu, the main effect was to help great thief ghost hand refine the stolen Immortal Gu quickly.

Even though Reverse Flow River could be used here, it was already the core of reverse flow protection seal that Fang Yuan needed in battle.

Fang Yuan had already succeeded once in using Immortal Gu Self Love and Affection to refine other people's Immortal Gu long ago.

His plan was originally to incorporate Affection and Self Love into great thief ghost hand so that after it steals Immortal Gu, the Gu can be refined instantly on the spot.

This seemed unnecessary but that was not true.

If he could refine it on the spot, great thief ghost hand would not need to suppress the Immortal Gu and bring it back to Fang Yuan, it could continue to steal more Immortal Gu consecutively.

After being put inside Heaven Sealing Mountain, Fixed Immortal Travel was suppressed and the refinement was automatically done, Fang Yuan could see results soon.

Fang Yuan placed his sights on Feng Jiu Ge again.

Feng Jiu Ge's expression was one of alertness and solemness, a look of disbelief was hidden deep within his eyes.

"Fang Yuan actually has such a method to steal others' Immortal Gu? Even those inside the immortal aperture are not spared?! Did he obtain another Thieving Heaven true inheritance?"

This method made Feng Jiu Ge feel an intense threat!

The sound wave attack that he used to force out great thief ghost hand was activated again, he did not want to cancel it.

"This move is too terrifying! If the stolen Immortal Gu earlier was the core Immortal Gu of my triple extreme sound killer move, wouldn't my killer move activation fail, causing me to suffer backlash and receive severe injures?"

Feng Jiu Ge felt a bit of relief and also lingering fear.

Fang Yuan felt that it was a pity, but great thief ghost hand could not choose its target, if he really stole the crucial Immortal Gu again like when he fought Meng Tu, Feng Jiu Ge's killer move would fail and the battle would turn around, he could even be killed quickly.

Even though Fang Yuan succeeded, Feng Jiu Ge was completely alert now, he used yang pass tune to teleport non-stop, refusing to stay at one spot. At the same time, he used his sound wave killer move without regard for immortal essence consumption. As for triple extreme sound, Feng Jiu Ge stopped using it, he did not dare to, his focus was all on escaping the pursuit of the yama children.

After Fang Yuan was exposed, he used familiar face again to disguise as a yama child to approach Feng Jiu Ge subtly.

This was an immense mental pressure to Feng Jiu Ge.

But Fang Yuan was not feeling great either.

Feng Jiu Ge was too slippery, he kept moving around the place, using his sound wave move and preventing Fang Yuan from getting any opportunities to attack.

"It seems that I will need to put some effort into the concealment of great thief ghost hand." Feng Jiu Ge actually had a way to force out the great thief ghost hand to show itself, this was out of Fang Yuan's expectations, he immediately thought of formless hand.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's signature method could interchange between phantom and solid, if it was used instead of great thief ghost hand, it would fear no sound waves. Formless hand was also extremely fast, once used, the enemies of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable could only watch as their Immortal Gu were all stolen one by one, they would spit out blood from anger and helplessness!

But Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand only had a small trace of formless hand's glory.

Even so, it made the great Feng Jiu Ge fluster and escape in anxiety while feeling fearful.

Fang Yuan forced Feng Jiu Ge to move around the place but he felt no arrogance that he succeeded, he was clear that he only had hopes of victory if he killed Feng Jiu Ge quickly now and went back to help out Lang Ya blessed land!

But in the following battle, Feng Jiu Ge did not leave any flaws for Fang Yuan, he was also a demonic path cultivator that shocked the whole of Central Continent, challenging all ten sects at once, he had rich battle experience.

As time passed, yang pass tune's time limit finally arrived!

"A chance!" Fang Yuan was anxious and joyful. He was anxious because so much time had been wasted and Feng Jiu Ge was still alive, but he was joyful because the flaw had finally appeared.

Feng Jiu Ge's heart sank!

In the past, his fierce attacks would render his enemies helpless. After becoming a famous person, he had never been faced with a situation where a rank seven Gu Immortal chased after his life.

Now, he had experienced this from Fang Yuan, he finally recognized his own weakness, that was the movement aspect.

With yang pass tune unusable, Feng Jiu Ge's speed fell drastically, he was soon surrounded by yama children and could no longer dodge as easily.

Feng Jiu Ge was forced to defend himself at one location. His killer moves had great power as he attacked the yama children who surrounded him from all directions.

Fang Yuan hid among them perfectly, great thief ghost hand was prepared to strike the moment Feng Jiu Ge's defenses revealed a flaw!

But at this moment, the entire yama battlefield started to shake as it emitted a sharp noise.

"Oh no!" Fang Yuan's expression changed.

"Lady Zi Wei must have done it." Feng Jiu Ge was very happy.

The entire yama battlefield started to shake with greater intensity, Fairy Zi Wei's actions were extremely effective after this amount of time.

"So little time had passed, Fairy Zi Wei actually managed to deduce the workings of my yama battlefield, she is so fast! No, at this rate, yama battlefield cannot last for thirty breaths of time, I need to obtain victory now!"

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with a ruthless light.

"I was saving this for Fairy Zi Wei and the rest, but I will use it on you first!" There was no time, if yama battlefield was broken, Fang Yuan would lose the chance to kill even Feng Jiu Ge, he made up his mind to use this trump card.

Immortal killer move — Soul Explosion!

It was still the soul explosion method, but Fang Yuan was not detonating any ordinary yama child, it was an immemorial yama child!

Fang Yuan had two immemorial soul beasts originally, during this period of cultivation, he turned the two immemorial soul beasts into yama children as well.

These two yama children were extraordinary, Fang Yuan had finally used them after hiding them for so long!

Ancient yama child soul explosion was a peak rank seven killer move, while immemorial yama child soul explosion was rank eight.

Even though Fang Yuan did not deduce Luo Po seal successfully, he still had another hidden rank eight offensive method!

Boom!

Immemorial yama soul explosion!

Feng Jiu Ge was directly hit!

Splat.

At a certain area in Central Continent, Feng Jin Huang went into a daze, the cup in her hand fell to the ground and shattered.

"Hmm?" Duke Long sent her an inquiring gaze.

Feng Jin Huang held her chest with an uncertain expression, just a moment ago, she felt an intense sensation in her heart.

Chapter 1579: Fate Armor

"He didn't die? What Immortal Gu is this!" Fang Yuan stared with slightly widened eyes as Feng Jiu Ge floated in the air.

Feng Jiu Ge's seven orifices were bleeding intensely, but a thin light armor surrounded his body, this armor saved his life, allowing him to survive the immemorial yama soul explosion.

"Rank eight Immortal Gu — Fate Armor." Feng Jiu Ge coughed out blood as he said.

Fang Yuan's expression was very dark.

This was the first time he was seeing fate armor Immortal Gu, even though Feng Jiu Ge used it in the River of Time earlier, Fang Yuan had sent Feng Jiu Ge into the River of Time back then, he did not witness this personally.

Thus, Fang Yuan did not know the existence of fate armor Immortal Gu.

And precisely so, he miscalculated.

"Heavenly Court's foundation…" Fang Yuan smiled helplessly, but at the next moment, his determination surged as he looked at Feng Jiu Ge with a menacing gaze: "This fate armor Immortal Gu can protect you once, but can it save you again?"

Fang Yuan still had another immemorial yama child.

Feng Jiu Ge was pale as paper, he had sustained severe injuries but he spit out some blood: "Cough, you can try. I'm not afraid to let you know, fate armor Immortal Gu's effect is defense, its power varies but it only follows the results dictated by fate. If I am not meant to die now, fate armor Immortal Gu can protect me from any killer move in this world. If I am fated to die already, then Fate Armor's protection will be as weak as paper."

"Fate!" Fang Yuan frowned tightly, saying the name of one Immortal Gu.

"You are right, this has to do with fate Immortal Gu." Feng Jiu Ge nodded as he sighed.

If fate Immortal Gu was destroyed, Fate would no longer restrict all living beings, Fate Armor's power would be reduced greatly, restricted by its rank, rank eight Immortal Gu would only be able to unleash rank eight defensive power. But now, Fate was injured and not fully destroyed, fate still bound the people of this world, this allowed fate armor Immortal Gu to unleash defenses beyond rank eight.

"My reverse flow protection seal is a tortoise shell already, but this fate armor Immortal Gu is even more sturdy." Fang Yuan was shook, but his attacks became even fiercer.

Feng Jiu Ge used Fate Armor with all his strength, his immortal essence expenditure was huge but he could last for some time. This time when attacking Lang Ya blessed land, Fairy Zi Wei had already provided him assistance in the form of immortal essence storage.

Rumble!

At this time, there was an intense explosion as a purple galaxy appeared in yama battlefield, it expanded and revealed the appearance of the outside Lang Ya blessed land.

"Why is she so fast?!" Fairy Zi Wei's speed of deducing yama battlefield was way faster than Fang Yuan's expectations.

Fang Yuan grunted as he bled from his nose and mouth, yama battlefield collapsed, he had to face the backlash of this killer move.

Fairy Zi Wei did not give Feng Jiu Ge fate armor Immortal Gu simply to protect him. Once it was activated, Heavenly Court would sense it. Back then in the River of Time, Lord Huang Shi had used Fate Armor to locate Feng Jiu Ge and save his life.

Now, Fairy Zi Wei was already close to breaking into yama battlefield and unraveling it. Fate Armor acted as receptor for Fairy Zi Wei to increase her deduction of yama battlefield, she could open up a pathway with a shorter amount of time.

In history, wisdom path deductions have been the hardest at the starting step. All the wisdom path Gu Immortals in the world were trying to deduce matters on Fang Yuan, but he used wisdom path protection methods, as long as they were intact, they could not find him. Among the three wisdom path Gu Immortal experts of Eastern Sea, Hua An was also helpless and even reverse deduced by Fang Yuan.

When she had just started to deduce it, yama battlefield was complete and had no loopholes, but now that she tore an opening in it, the hardest part was over, the difficulty had fallen greatly.

Tear, tear…

The sound was endless as streams of purple galaxies tore through the sky, creating countless tears in yama battlefield.

Boom!

With an intense explosion, yama battlefield broke apart entirely, Fang Yuan spit out a mouthful of blood as a large number of mortal Gu died in his immortal aperture, the Immortal Gu used were also injured to some extent.

Fang Yuan returned to Lang Ya blessed land while in emperor yama form.

"Be careful, he has a way to steal Immortal Gu from the immortal aperture!" Feng Jiu Ge escaped and managed to fly back to Fairy Zi Wei, the moment he came out, he gave this intel to all his teammates.

"It's you!" Chen Yi was the first to speak, he shouted angrily with wide opened eyes.

He recognized that Fang Yuan was the one who fought him in green ghost desert, the one who stole Qing Chou's Soul Beast Token right in front of him!

Fang Yuan's heart sank to rock bottom.

He did not manage to kill Feng Jiu Ge, fate armor Immortal Gu ruined his hopes. And even worse, emperor yama and great thief ghost hand's intel were exposed, the enemies found out about them.

This was something Fang Yuan had been trying to avoid. Since the start of the battle, he had been keeping this trump card hidden, hoping to use it in this battle to kill a strong enemy, using yama battlefield to conceal the traces and keep his secrets hidden, but his wishes were not answered, Fang Yuan did not manage to kill anyone while his trump cards were exposed.

"Fang Yuan, you are truly a source of chaos, Liu Guan Yi is you, Suan Bu Jin is also you." Fairy Zi Wei's eyes flickered with purple light, she instantly understood Fang Yuan's plan: "So that's it, you want to control green ghost desert to collect soul cores and use Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley to cultivate. It is a pity Dang Hun Mountain has been destroyed! Hmm? No, there is orderly well… you have a way to restore Dang Hun Mountain!"

Fang Yuan did not speak, this Fairy Zi Wei was a wisdom path great expert indeed, she exposed so many of Fang Yuan's secrets in an instant.

Fairy Zi Wei was also feeling deep lingering fear.

"To think that Fang Yuan has such a method to steal other people's Immortal Gu directly!"

"Thankfully, great thief ghost hand is much weaker than formless hand, it cannot choose what Immortal Gu to steal. Otherwise, if it stole a crucial Immortal Gu, Feng Jiu Ge's killer move activation would fail, he would face a backlash and would need to use Fate Armor in advance. It would be a problem of whether he could last until I deduce and broke this immortal battlefield killer move."

"Great thief ghost hand can steal rank eight Immortal Gu, thankfully it did not manage to take Fate Armor, otherwise, how could Feng Jiu Ge survive? Feng Jiu Ge is indeed a Dao Guardian, he has strong luck and was not suppressed by Fang Yuan's luck."

"However…" Fairy Zi Wei looked at Fang Yuan with an eerie gaze: "This demon managed to steal Fixed Immortal Travel, it means that his luck is very strong, even though he failed to kill Feng Jiu Ge."

Fate Immortal Gu was damaged by Red Lotus Demon Venerable, even though it was not destroyed, it was greatly weakened. Thereafter, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable rose up and created luck path.

As long as Fate did not recover, luck path would continue to be this strong. Fang Yuan's luck path attainment level was not high, he did not have any strong offensive killer moves in luck path, but luck path had always been helping him subtly, like burning soul bursting luck.

Boom boom boom!

Explosions resounded as both sides fought again, ending up in a chaotic battle.

Feng Jiu Ge had lost a lot of his battle strength as he went under Fairy Zi Wei's protection. Fang Yuan was also without options against Chen Yi's ancient tree prison cage, he could only join up with the super immortal formation and Heavenly Giant Solor to deal with Chen Yi and Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei displayed the might of a rank eight expert now, her killer moves were used with great execution, far above Chen Yi.

Chen Yi had Genesis Lotus' true inheritance, while Fairy Zi Wei cultivated Star Constellation's true inheritance, it was not that Genesis Lotus' true inheritance was inferior to Star Constellation's true inheritance, but because wisdom path killer moves were fundamentally more complex and expended much more mental energy.

Fang Yuan still had one immemorial yama child, emperor yama and great thief ghost hand were already exposed, Fairy Zi Wei and the rest could counter it.

They did not put down their guard, they were covered by immortal killer moves that exploded continuously. If great thief ghost hand got close to them, the explosions would force them out, there was no opportunity to steal.

The truth was, Chen Yi and Fairy Zi Wei's investigative methods were very exemplary, but Fang Yuan stopped using great thief ghost hand frequently after fearing that it would be found out.

The more he used it, the more flaws he would expose. Especially against Fairy Zi Wei, the more intel he leaked, the more she could deduce.

Bam!

With a thunderous sound, Thunder Ghost True Monarch appeared in a flash, she had returned!

Chapter 1580: Heavenly Court's Call to Surrender

The moment Thunder Ghost True Monarch returned to the battlefield, the expressions of both sides changed.

Heavenly Court's immortals were extremely happy while Fang Yuan's side turned grim.

The two sides were evenly matched, at this time, Heavenly Court gained a new rank eight battle strength who was a first rate expert, this would cause a huge change in the battle result!

But Thunder Ghost True Monarch's report made Fairy Zi Wei's gaze turn dark: "What, you did not find wisdom Gu?"

Wisdom Gu was refined by Star Constellation Immortal Venerable and the refinement process was recorded in Star Constellation's true inheritance, allowing Fairy Zi Wei to know a lot about it. But Fairy Zi Wei did not know that wisdom Gu had the trait of following after information path environments.

"Wisdom Gu is wild, did they refine it? Or did they destroy it? Or do they have any method to resist the light of wisdom and relocate wisdom Gu?"

Thoughts rumbled in Fairy Zi Wei's mind, she was thinking at lightning speed.

She stood up and looked at Heavenly Giant Solor, gazing at Fang Yuan as she shouted: "Hand over wisdom Gu, I will allow you to surrender!"

Heavenly Court's current invasion was mainly for rank nine wisdom Gu, Fang Yuan was only secondary.

Immortal Gu were unique and hard to refine, rank nine Immortal Gu were at the pinnacle of the pyramid, in the current five regions, in this entire world, there were likely less than ten rank nine Gu.

Rank nine wisdom Gu was too important for the growth of Heavenly Court's strength, it was second to fate Gu! Ignoring anything else, just Fairy Zi Wei alone, with just her wisdom path attainment and Star Constellation Chessboard, she was already one of the three strongest wisdom path great experts in the world.

If she could obtain rank nine wisdom Gu, and use Star Constellation Chessboard to refine it, she would be the number one wisdom path great expert in the world, she would comprehend all of the profundities of wisdom path in this universe, she would stand at the very top, the second strongest person would be miles away from her, she would have an unthinkable deduction ability.

Even if Fang Yuan had emperor yama, or even a rank eight wisdom path method, he would not be able to block Fairy Zi Wei's deductions. Only rank nine methods could work.

But how many rank nine wisdom path methods were there? At least in Fang Yuan's true inheritances of Lang Ya and Spectral Soul, there were no such records!

"Surrender?" The hairy man Gu Immortals shook.

Lang Ya land spirit shouted in anger: "Surrender my ass! Lang Ya blessed land will only have hairy men dying in battle, we will not be kneeling slaves!"

Fang Yuan was quite curious: "I am a complete otherworldly demon, in order to get wisdom Gu, will your Heavenly Court spare me?"

Fairy Zi Wei smiled arrogantly: "So what if you are a complete otherworldly demon? Our Heavenly Court predecessors have known about otherworldly demons long ago, we have recruited them before, it was merely not written in history. Look at now, Zhao Lian Yun is the best example."

"Fang Yuan, Heavenly Court is far more magnanimous and accepting than you think. Even if you are an otherworldly demon who possessed Spring Autumn Cicada and Spectral Soul's true inheritance, as long as you turn over a new leaf and contribute your sovereign immortal aperture into Heavenly Court, you will be one of us. And according to Heavenly Court's rules, we will treat you equally as everyone else!"

After hearing these words, Fang Yuan's expression did not change, he still smiled coldly, but Chen Yi had a complex expression, there was suspicion and jealousy in his eyes.

Chen Yi believed what Fairy Zi Wei said, because Heavenly Court's rules were as such, regardless of who you were in the past, after joining Heavenly Court as a righteous path member, after giving up your immortal aperture, you would be a member of Heavenly Court, there would be no differential treatment.

"But it is so difficult to join Heavenly Court! I, Chen Yi, have worked hard my whole life, I only managed to join Heavenly Court because of my battle strength and the fact that I have Genesis Lotus true inheritance, how many years has this Fang Yuan cultivated? He killed people and caused havoc everywhere, but if he turned around now and become a righteous person, he would get to join Heavenly Court!"

At once, Chen Yi felt a strong sense of injustice, he even felt a little grievance in his heart.

But Thunder Ghost True Monarch's expression was unchanged, because Heavenly Court had once tried to recruit someone else, this person slaughtered the people in the world, he was a much greater problem than the current Fang Yuan.

He was Spectral Soul Demon Venerable!

Before Spectral Soul Demon Venerable reached rank nine, Heavenly Court had tried to recruit him multiple times. After becoming rank nine, they also tried to recruit him once.

"Heavenly Court is the Heavenly Court of humanity! Fang Yuan, you are extremely talented, you managed to roam freely as a rank seven and evade Heavenly Court's pursuit for so long, it shows your qualification to join us. I can swear on my life, after joining Heavenly Court, not only would you preserve your life, you would be able to cultivate and continue being a free Gu Immortal." Thunder Ghost True Monarch said.

"Fang Yuan…" At once, the hairy man Gu Immortals looked at Fang Yuan with worry.

Even Sixth Hair did the same.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "To obtain wisdom Gu, you guys are willing to let me go and recruit me, it shows how important rank nine wisdom Gu is to all of you! Then how about this, if you do not let us off today, I will destroy wisdom Gu in your face, your attempt will end in failure."

"Hmph, incorrigible! How can the grand righteous path be threatened by the likes of you? Since you want to die, I will grant you your wish!" Thunder Ghost True Monarch charged at Fang Yuan with deep anger.

Boom boom boom!

Fang Yuan fought against Thunder Ghost True Monarch on barely even grounds, thunder was rumbling, air currents were turbulent.

"Oh? That means wisdom Gu is on you now?" Fairy Zi Wei's eyes flickered with brilliance, she started to act as well.

Fairy Zi Wei was suppressed by Thunder Ghost True Monarch and Fairy Zi Wei's cooperation, he could only use reverse flow protection seal to defend himself, he could not fight back at all.

He transmitted to Lang Ya land spirit: "First supreme elder, this is an emergency! If you have any methods left, use it now, otherwise, there will be no time to regret!!"

Lang Ya land spirit shouted: "Forget it, I'll show you the true power of Lang Ya blessed land!"

As he said that, the entire sea surface of Lang Ya blessed land started to bubble, it was as if the ocean was boiling.

Countless refinement path dao marks shone with the light of dao marks, be it Gu Immortals or mortals, they could see it with their naked eyes.

The aura of an immortal killer move burst out like a grand tornado, it rampaged in the entire Lang Ya blessed land, none of Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were spared, they were all hit by the move.

"What is this?!" Chen Yi and the rest had changes in expressions, all of their defensive methods radiated with a brilliant light, forced to resist the move.

The mysterious killer move was incredibly powerful, even Fang Yuan was hit by it, there were countless ripples on his reverse flow protection seal.

"Quick, come inside." Lang Ya land spirit transmitted, moving the silver giant towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan successfully fused into Heavenly Giant Solor formation, this was not the first time he was entering this ancient battle formation.

"What move is this?" A flash of joy sparked on Fang Yuan's face.

Lang Ya land spirit's move was very powerful, all four Heavenly Court immortals were all forced to defend themselves, they could not attack.

Lang Ya land spirit smiled bitterly: "These were the gains in battle that my main body had obtained when he killed a water path great expert in his life, using it, he comprehended the strongest refinement path killer move — Omnipresent Four Seas! This move expends an immense amount of seawater, unless we are refining rank eight Immortal Gu, we would not use it. Against the enemy now, it can only last for dozens of breaths."

Fang Yuan observed carefully, Lang Ya blessed land's sea level was truly falling, a vast amount of water was expended to maintain this omnipresent four seas killer move.

Fang Yuan had a realization: "So this Lang Ya blessed land's terrain was carefully designed. The three continents float on the vast sea, but the seawater is not simple at all, it is actually the refinement path foundation of the blessed land, it is truly precious."

Fang Yuan looked at Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals as he sighed: "It is a pity that this move cannot differentiate friend and foe, otherwise, if we can attack now, we can gain the upper hand!"

Actually, omnipresent four seas could be contained in an area, but that place needed to have a corresponding immortal formation to draw out the power of the killer move and refine Gu.

And this refinement path immortal formation is none other than the Long Hair refinement path formation used to refine Myriad Self for Fang Yuan.

Heavenly Court would naturally not be lured into such an obvious trap, and in this situation, Lang Ya land spirit had no choice but to use this move fully across the whole of Lang Ya blessed land, in the sky, land, and sea.

But this way, Fang Yuan's super immortal formation would also be attacked by omnipresent four seas. Thankfully, Lang Ya land spirit was prepared for it and went towards the silver giant, disassembling as the Immortal Gu were collected back, the variant human Gu Immortals of the three races also entered the silver giant.

"What do we do now?" Fang Yuan looked at Lang Ya land spirit as he asked.

He felt that Lang Ya blessed land still had some trump cards left.

And this battle would be decided by those trump cards!

Chapter 1581: Thunder Ghost's Death!

Lang Ya land spirit had a look of pain.

As he looked at the falling sea level, he frowned tightly, feeling deep loss.

This seawater seemed ordinary but it was not, Long Hair Ancestor had painstakingly created this refinement water during his late years. Right now, there was only the quantity of one sea, if there were four seas, he would be able to use a secret method to cause a qualitative change and create a man-made secluded domain of heaven and earth!

For this goal, Lang Ya blessed land had been kept at crescent moon lake for a long time, using the water path environment and immortal tribulation tempering aperture killer move to trigger water path tribulations and increase water path dao marks for Lang Ya blessed land.

But now, in order to resist Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, Lang Ya blessed land's accumulations were rapidly expended, after this battle, it would definitely be depleted.

"Ahhhh!" Lang Ya land spirit growled, leading the band of hairy man Gu Immortals to mobilize Heavenly Giant Solor.

The silver giant attacked with immortal killer moves as Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were faced with explosions.

The attacks were extremely powerful, they were at rank eight level, at once, Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals had no way to fight back, Thunder Ghost True Monarch's armor was broken, while Chen Yi and Fairy Zi Wei spat out blood, Feng Jiu Ge's state was even worse, his face was pale as paper as he gritted his teeth, he was holding on with fate armor Immortal Gu!

Omnipresent four seas was in essence a refinement path killer move, it used the refinement path dao marks of Lang Ya blessed land, it was the accumulation of Long Hair Ancestor's entire life.

This move did not care about ally or foe, Fang Yuan would be hit if he was within range, but hairy men could move freely. The reason was that hairy men had refinement path dao marks naturally!

And when Lang Ya land spirit's side uses killer moves, the refinement path killer moves would be amplified by omnipresent four seas, each hit would be extremely powerful, having first rate rank eight power.

As for the silver giant, it could also move freely as it was an ancient battle formation instead of an Immortal Gu House, Heavenly Giant Solor depended on the user, right now, with the hairy man Gu Immortals controlling it, it was a refinement path giant.

This was also why Fang Yuan and the variant human Gu Immortals of the other three races did not participate.

If he attacked, he would be restricted by omnipresent four seas, there would not be any point.

"Kill, kill them all!"

"Lang Ya's foundation is truly unfathomable."

The variant human Gu Immortals of the three races gasped, but Fang Yuan frowned deeply, telling Lang Ya land spirit: "First supreme elder, even though your all-out attacks are powerful, they cannot determine victory. Omnipresent four seas cannot last long, we have limited time, if you do not use any of your remaining methods…"

"I know, shut up!" Lang Ya land spirit growled, his eyes were bloodshot, he gritted his teeth, having a fierce expression, he was very uneasy in his heart.

On the surface, he had a great advantage, but Heavenly Court's four immortals could not be killed, they were like rocks by the seashore, no matter how hard the waves crashed into them, they remained motionless.

After more than ten breaths of time, even though the silver giant burst out with immense might, Heavenly Court's four immortals were still alive, while Lang Ya blessed land's seawater had dried up, not a drop of water remained, even the seabed was exposed.

"It is time to retaliate." Thunder Ghost True Monarch breathed in deeply, her expression was sinister, she started to condense her black armor again.

"As expected of Long Hair Ancestor's legacy." Chen Yi sighed deeply, healing his own injuries rapidly.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals had deep foundations, they resisted the silver giant's attacks with only mild injuries.

"You forced me, you all forced me!" Seeing the approaching Heavenly Court Gu Immortals, Lang Ya land spirit muttered as he screamed afterwards: "Come, come if you want to lose your life!"

Omnipresent four seas could not defeat the enemies, but Lang Ya land spirit took out another trump card.

Rumble!

Intense thunder rumbled and red lightning flashed, in an instant, the whole of Lang Ya blessed land was enveloped.

"This is?!" Heavenly Court's four immortals' expressions rapidly changed to great shock. Be it the plotting Fairy Zi Wei, or the Thunder Ghost True Monarch bursting with battle strength, or Chen Yi who was once the authoritative figure of a sect, or Feng Jiu Ge with immense talent, they all lost their cool.

Fang Yuan was also dazed, memories flashed in his mind as he spoke: "Steal Life?"

The other hairy man Gu Immortals were stunned, they did not know what this trump card was, even Lang Ya land spirit looked at Fang Yuan in surprise: "That's right, this is Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's rank eight steal life Immortal Gu! You know about it?"

Fang Yuan was deeply shocked, Lang Ya land spirit actually had steal life Immortal Gu in his hands.

Fang Yuan knew about steal life Immortal Gu from Thieving Heaven's dream realm, to think that Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had left this Immortal Gu to Long Hair Ancestor.

Defend!

Heavenly Court's four immortals tried to defend themselves.

They were extremely nervous now, hundreds or thousands of times as before!

Because they could tell that this was the red light emitted by steal life Immortal Gu.

At the next moment, the overwhelming red light suddenly retracted, as if thousands of arrows were shot out before flying back to the bows like time was reversed.

The red light brought away the lifespan of all lifeforms!

In an instant, Feng Jiu Ge turned from a handsome young man to an old and wrinkled man with white hair.

Fairy Zi Wei spit out a mouthful of blood, wrinkles appearing on her face.

Chen Yi was extremely pathetic, his long hair broke as strands flew in the wind.

As for Thunder Ghost True Monarch, she held her chest, originally, she looked like a young girl, but after the red light retracted, she completely turned into an old lady, her hair was white and her eyes were blurry, she gasped in weakness as she tried to breathe, there were barely any teeth left in her mouth.

"Good!" Seeing this, Fang Yuan smiled.

Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals were very powerful, but most of them were slumbering in the immortal graveyard, unless they had no choice, they would not wake up. Because they had already expended most of their lifespan, with their already limited lifespan, they would not be able to live long.

And now, Lang Ya land spirit used steal life Immortal Gu, this weakness was targeted, greatly influencing the Heavenly Court's four immortals.

"However, Lang Ya land spirit is only using steal life Immortal Gu, it is not a killer move and has a singular effect. Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals activated their methods urgently, they were all defensive but could not block everything."

"And this steal life Immortal Gu did not differentiate ally from enemy, even the silver giant was useless against it, our Gu Immortals were also affected." Fang Yuan looked at himself, he was also covered in white hair and wrinkles.

But it was not a problem, he had four thousand years of lifespan Gu, he quickly used a few to become a young man again.

As for the other variant human Gu Immortals, they originally had longer lifespans than humans, even without lifespan extension methods, they could also continue to live. Even those mortal hairy men could survive.

This was also why Lang Ya land spirit had kept this steal life Immortal Gu until now without using it.

"Even if Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals are stronger, so what? We will compete with them using lifespan! First supreme elder, use Steal Life again!" Fang Yuan's eyes burst with ruthlessness, he urged Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit smiled bitterly: "Back then, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was afraid that this steal life Immortal Gu would cause chaos in this world, even though he gave it to my main body, he set up methods to only allow it to activate thrice before self-detonating."

"What? Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable is such a merciful person?" The variant human Gu Immortals were very surprised.

As for Fang Yuan, thinking about Thieving Heaven's dream realm, he understood why.

"Who cares if it can be used thrice or twice, when else do you want to use it!" Fang Yuan urged again.

Lang Ya land spirit nodded deeply, using steal life Immortal Gu again.

In the blink of an eye, the red light retracted again.

"Urgh…" Thunder Ghost True Monarch sighed with a weak tone: "To think that I… Jing Lan… would die here."

She tried to open her eyes, but she was too weak, her eyes closed again.

She — had died of old age.

Chapter 1582: Time To Retreat

"Senior Jing Lan!" Fairy Zi Wei cried out in sorrow.

Chen Yi and Feng Jiu Ge also had expressions of sorrow, hatred, anger, and other emotions.

Jing Lan's death was unexpected, because they did not expect that Lang Ya blessed land actually had steal life Immortal Gu!

"Wasn't it said that before Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable vanished mysteriously, he had been worried that steal life Gu was too powerful and would cause great chaos in the world if it ended in others' hands, so he destroyed it along with the Gu recipe?" Fairy Zi Wei frowned.

Evidently, this was false information, but Heavenly Court thought it was real.

If Fairy Zi Wei wanted to know the details, she could only interrogate Lang Ya land spirit after capturing him.

After all, in the past, Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had asked Long Hair Ancestor to refine Gu for him, whatever internal transaction they had or whatever information they leaked to deceive Heavenly Court was known to only these two parties.

"Hahaha!" Lang Ya land spirit laughed heartily: "You think that Lang Ya Sect is so easy to bully? This time, you will all die!"

"Be careful!" Fang Yuan suddenly shouted in warning.

"What?" At the next moment, Lang Ya land spirit gasped.

Because even though Jing Lan died, her heart was still shining with lightning sparks. Soon, her aged body melted entirely from the lightning heart's heat and current.

The electric current filled the black armor, this unmanned armor actually raised its head, bursting out with a grand aura that could trample heaven and earth!

"This?!"

"Isn't she dead?"

"Not good, this is not good!"

The variant human Gu Immortals gasped in fear and shock.

Fang Yuan had a grim expression, saying his deduction: "Thunder Ghost True Monarch indeed died, but her black armor is soul path in essence. Even though she died, the armor remained, it is akin to a special soul. And most importantly, her heart seems to be the final trump card, it has great power, we need to be wary of it!"

But at this moment, Thunder Ghost True Monarch's armor burst out like a shooting star, towards the silver giant.

A vast amount of blue electric currents leaked out of the black armor, forming a trail of electricity behind it.

Fast!

The armor was extremely fast, after hearing Fang Yuan's words, the hairy men were forewarned, but they had no time to dodge or use killer moves.

Because it was too fast!

Thunder Ghost True Monarch was most skilled at movement, her strength overall was at high standard within rank eight, but her speed was at the peak of rank right.

Right now, the lightning armor flew with speed that surpassed the peak of rank eight, it was at quasi-rank nine!

The silver giant could not dodge, it was hit by the lightning armor.

"We will retreat!" Fairy Zi Wei's eyelids were twitching, she wanted to escape but it was too late!

Boom—!

An intense explosion occurred.

Countless flashes of lightning weaved and danced, the central area turned into a pool of lightning plasma due to the dense electricity!

At once, the world turned white, the light was simply too blinding. Countless mortal hairy men looked at the sky, they were crying, holding their eyes as they rolled on the ground, they had all gone blind after taking one glance.

As the light faded, an unparalleled air current blew in all directions.

Even Fairy Zi Wei and the rest were pushed away, they could not help themselves, they were like rafts in the middle of a tsunami.

The entire Cloud Cover Continent's central area was blown to bits, a huge hole of gigantic size was created.

The whole of Lang Ya blessed land shook intensely, originally, the refinement path dao marks emitted dense light of dao marks, but now within the range of the explosion, they were all destroyed. The refinement path dao marks that were near the explosion had decreased greatly in numbers, while the ones left faded and dimmed.

At the center of the explosion, there was an empty space, only several Gu Immortals remained in the vast area like tiny ants.

"Cough, cough!" The remaining variant human Gu Immortals all had rank seven cultivation level and were people with great battle strength. They continued to cough as they spat out blood, they were in a pathetic state.

Lang Ya land spirit was translucent now, fading like an illusory shadow, he was on the brink of collapsing.

Only Fang Yuan was unharmed, but his expression was very dark, the reverse flow protection seal on him had been almost depleted! The Reverse Flow River within sovereign immortal aperture had expended ten percent of its water from this one attack!

"Worthy of the rank eight expert that once resisted Spectral Soul Demon Venerable! Even in death, she could retaliate to this extent!"

"This move condensed all of her lightning path dao marks into her heart, detonating it at once and erupting with overwhelming might."

"After that, the battlefield had no lightning path dao marks remaining, it shows how she had made use of every single dao mark, she definitely had lightning path great grandmaster attainment level."

Fang Yuan's mind flashed with thoughts.

Even though he was not injured, his losses were severe.

Thunder Ghost True Monarch's final attack had quasi-rank nine power. When the explosion occurred, the silver giant first resisted it, but after the silver giant broke apart, Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal resisted it. Even then, Reverse Flow River lost water amounting to ten percent of its total capacity.

Reverse Flow River sustained the reverse flow protection seal killer move, it was not unlimited, Fang Yuan had used it multiple times already, only sixty percent was left.

Fang Yuan was in a better shape, but the rest were in pitiful conditions.

The silver giant broke apart, the backlash coupled with Thunder Ghost True Monarch's final explosion caused half of the variant human Gu Immortals to die, their corpses were decimated, their souls had disintegrated, only their immortal apertures were left.

The remaining immortals who were alive had severe injuries, some showed shock on their faces, while others were emotionless, they were completely stupefied from the explosion.

Thunder Ghost True Monarch's explosion caused great damage to the entire variant human alliance!

"Protect Lang Ya land spirit, we still have steal life Gu, we can fight!" Fang Yuan shouted, at the same time, he flew in front of Lang Ya land spirit, protecting him. At the crucial moment, Fang Yuan had to control the situation.

"That's right, we have… steal life Immortal Gu!" The battle was at the most crucial moment, Lang Ya land spirit knew that he could not be angry or upset now, he immediately moved to use steal life Immortal Gu a second time.

"Quickly act!!" Fairy Zi Wei and Chen Yi charged.

Seeing that steal life Immortal Gu was about to be used again, how could they not be anxious?

Immortal killer move — Karma Divine Tree!

Chen Yi's body shook as green smoke emerged to form a huge divine tree.

Meanwhile, Fairy Zi Wei attacked fiercely.

Immortal killer move — Dead Inside From Sorrow!

She directly used her strongest method, the emotion of sorrow quickly spread, there were no bright lights from her method, but many of the variant human Gu Immortals defending Lang Ya land spirit twitched as they grasped their hearts, their eyes rolled over as they died mysteriously!

"Sixth Hair!" Fang Yuan called out, Fairy Zi Wei's attack could not be guarded against, Sixth Hair had barely survived the explosion earlier, he was almost dead, with this attack from Fairy Zi Wei, he could not take it anymore, he died.

Fang Yuan's expression changed, even though he was unharmed, Reverse Flow River lost another ten percent of its water, this meant that Fairy Zi Wei's offensive killer move was on par with Thunder Ghost True Monarch's final self-detonated explosion!

"No—! Save me!" Lang Ya land spirit shouted, grabbing Fang Yuan's arm as he used a defensive killer move against Fairy Zi Wei's attack.

Fang Yuan looked at him helplessly.

Because reverse flow protection seal could only protect him, it could not defend Lang Ya land spirit as well.

"First supreme elder, you cannot use steal life Immortal Gu anymore in this state. The only way now is to move the entire Lang Ya blessed land into my immortal aperture, that is the only way left!" Fang Yuan urged with an earnest expression.

But Lang Ya land spirit rejected him, he stared at Fang Yuan angrily: "No, this won't do, I can still fight!"

Bump.

At the next moment, he reached his limit, his defensive methods were all broken, his entire body shattered into countless shards, dying on the spot, disintegrating and breaking down!

"Killed him!" Fairy Zi Wei saw this and relaxed, she almost fell down and fainted on the spot.

Dead inside from sorrow had great backlash, Fairy Zi Wei laughed bitterly in her heart, after using it this time, she would have to rest for a very long time.

"Lang Ya land spirit, damn it…" Fang Yuan frowned, cursing: "But I have not lost my chance! Maybe…"

At the next moment, at the place where Lang Ya land spirit died, a figure appeared.

He had a white beard and eyebrows, it was the previous white haired Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya blessed land had two obsessions, causing there to be two land spirits, the black haired land spirit was killed, but the white haired land spirit appeared once again.

"What? A second Lang Ya land spirit appeared!" Fairy Zi Wei frowned deeply, she knew of this secret, but she was very confident in dead inside from sorrow, she felt that both land spirits could be killed together.

But the truth was, Lang Ya blessed land was more profound than her estimations.

Even though Fairy Zi Wei could use dead inside from sorrow killer move again, there was no time. And could ordinary methods kill Lang Ya land spirit defended by Fang Yuan?

Fairy Zi Wei was not flustered, instead, her lips curled up, she started to focus on defense, protecting her teammate.

That teammate was Chen Yi.

Chen Yi's karma divine tree was already bearing a huge fruit.

"Every cause has an effect, the effect can eliminate the cause[1]!" Chen Yi shouted as he extended his right hand, grabbing this fruit and squeezing it.

Guh.

The fruit was instantly squashed as the purple fruit juice splattered on Chen Yi's face and body like poisonous venom.

Chii Chiii Chiii…

Intense pain assaulted him as Chen Yi cried out, his face and body was corroded by the fruit juice, pieces of flesh and skin rotted as his bones were exposed in a few breaths of time.

Chen Yi paid such a huge price, injuring himself gravely to use karma divine tree forcefully, he had his motive!

Lang Ya land spirit's expression changed as he said grimly: "They destroyed steal life Immortal Gu!"

"Sigh!" Fang Yuan sighed deeply, urging again: "Now, you can only fuse Lang Ya blessed land into my…"

Before he finished, white haired Lang Ya land spirit interrupted: "No need, my Lang Ya blessed land has its trump card! My former main body had made an agreement with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in the past. If we face any danger of extermination, we can request help from Longevity Heaven to seek help from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's descendants. Afterwards, we will join Longevity Heaven and fuse into it while being on equal status!"

Saying so, a door opened deep within the blessed land.

A few breaths of time later, legendary immemorial desolate beast Mao Li Qiu charged out from deep underground.

Behind it, there were several Gu Immortals with rank eight aura approaching with battle intent.

"Lang Ya blessed land is now the territory of Longevity Heaven!"

"Heavenly Court! Your claws are even longer than mine, I, Mao Li Qiu, will chop them all off today, hahaha[2]."

"Fang Yuan is here too, kill him, we will take revenge for the collapse of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and reclaim the luck path true inheritance!"

At once, with strong reinforcements, the situation of the battle was turned around immediately.

"Sigh…" Fang Yuan let out a deep sigh, he told himself internally: "It is time to retreat."

[1] Like I said before, effect uses the same character as fruit. Back

[2] The non-literal meaning is that they are interfering in matters beyond their jurisdiction. Back

Chapter 1583: Bull Demon, Flower Lady

"First supreme elder, how can you say this!" Longevity Heaven's members were filled with animosity towards Fang Yuan, he retreated as he chided Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit snorted, not showing Fang Yuan any kindness: "I have not settled the score with you! You had ulterior motives and pushed Black Hair to the brink of destruction, haven't you obtained enough benefits during this period?!"

Lang Ya land spirit turned on him.

Fang Yuan's expression turned grim: "Aren't you afraid of the alliance agreement…"

"Black Hair was the one who set the agreement with you, not me!" Lang Ya land spirit responded.

"As expected." Fang Yuan sighed internally, the white haired land spirit's decision showed some problems. Fang Yuan had guessed it already, he merely confirmed it with Lang Ya land spirit personally.

"Fang Yuan, where can you run to!" Saying so, Mao Li Qiu pounced and slammed its claw on Fang Yuan.

Boom!

The huge force impacted Fang Yuan as he was pushed away, he crashed like a meteor onto the dried seabed.

Even though Fang Yuan looked pathetic, he was unharmed, while Mao Li Qiu shrugged its claws and said with anger: "This Reverse Flow River is truly annoying!"

"Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, fight us!" A muscular brute with a thick beard said with a thunderous voice, he was extremely tall and strong, having a powerful aura.

There was another Gu Immortal, she was a little girl with a flower on her head, she sat on the muscular man's shoulder, giggling as her crystal-like eyes on her innocent cute face stared at Fairy Zi Wei.

The two Gu Immortals had rank eight cultivation level but they did not attack Fang Yuan, they charged at Fairy Zi Wei.

Fairy Zi Wei was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, there was great risk for Longevity Heaven to keep her in the battlefield, she had to be eliminated first!

"Bull Demon, Flower Lady, you are both here…" Fairy Zi Wei's pupils shrunk, she recognized who these people were as solemness flashed on her eyes.

"Hahaha, since you, Zi Wei, can move around, so can the two of us!" The brutish Bull Demon laughed maniacally.

Boom boom boom!

A chain of explosions occurred as Bull Demon and Flower Lady forced Fairy Zi Wei to retreat time and again.

Fairy Zi Wei had little lifespan to begin with, she was lucky to have Star Constellation true inheritance helping her, but after facing the effect of Steal Life twice, she was in a poor state now. In contrast, Longevity Heaven expended its foundation and summoned Bull Demon and Flower Lady in perfect condition, they had the advantage.

Fairy Zi Wei blocked their attacks while observing the battlefield.

When she saw that Mao Li Qiu slashed at Fang Yuan, she suddenly reminded: "Be careful, Fang Yuan had rank seven Fixed Immortal Travel, don't let him escape!"

Even though Longevity Heaven wanted her dead, she was still calm as ice, she was not overwhelmed by them, her intention to kill Fang Yuan had never wavered.

Mao Li Qiu frowned immediately.

They had brought three rank eights, one legendary immemorial desolate beast, and one Immortal Gu House here, but they were not space path related.

Fixed Immortal Travel was a space path Immortal Gu, only space path Gu Immortals were the most skilled at countering it.

Mao Li Qiu had a change of mind as it charged at Fang Yuan, shouting at Lang Ya land spirit: "Old man, quickly act, deal with Fang Yuan, we will give you a lot of credit for it!"

Lang Ya land spirit was hesitant, but he quickly shouted: "Shut up Mao Li Qiu! Since Fang Yuan wants to leave, let him. What rights do you have to order me around? Even though I sought help from Longevity Heaven, according to our agreement back then, we are on equal status!"

Lang Ya land spirit had thought of killing Fang Yuan, but he soon thought of how Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven failed to kill Fang Yuan after hunting him down for so long, how could he succeed?

Fang Yuan knew everything about Lang Ya blessed land, he also had great thief ghost hand, reverse flow protection seal, Fixed Immortal Travel, and countless unscrupulous methods, Lang Ya land spirit did not want to aggravate such a demon.

"You!" Mao Li Qiu shouted in anger, but it could not do anything to Lang Ya land spirit.

Lang Ya land spirit said to the remaining variant human Gu Immortals: "You are all clear of the situation now, even though Black Hair died, I am not restricted by the agreement. But don't worry, as long as you all join my Lang Ya blessed land, I can ensure your safety!"

The variant human Gu Immortals had ugly expressions, they looked at each other and nodded.

There was no choice, they were exposed now and were under the alliance agreement, Lang Ya land spirit also knew a lot about them. There was no options left, if they did not want to die, they would need to surrender.

Ancient sword dragon transformation!

Myriad dragon!

Familiar face!

Fang Yuan used three moves at once, with myriad self Immortal Gu, he could be very efficient in using consecutive killer moves, before Mao Li Qiu got close to him, it had to face the myriad dragon army.

Mao Li Qiu growled, using immortal killer moves to summon wind, frost, and lightning, killing countless sword dragon clones.

But at this time, Fang Yuan had already gotten close to Lang Ya land spirit.

"Be careful, he is there!" Five Elements Grandmaster shouted, he found out Fang Yuan's location in advance.

He had sneaked into Longevity Heaven but got trapped in Immortal Gu House Calamity Luck Altar after he was discovered. After a long time of resisting the Longevity Heaven Gu Immortals, Five Elements Grandmaster realized that he had no chance of escaping, he could only lower his head and join Longevity Heaven.

This time, Longevity Heaven came to reinforce Lang Ya blessed land, he was one of the ones who came.

"He actually found me! But… it is too late!!" Fang Yuan turned into the ancient sword dragon and roared, his dragon fangs were sharp and sinister.

"Fang Yuan, what are you trying to do?!" Lang Ya land spirit shouted in shock, he quickly used his defensive immortal killer move.

"Naturally to kill you! Immemorial yama child — Soul Explosion!" Fang Yuan shouted angrily.

Boom—!

The rank eight killer move erupted, pitch black smoke spread out as it engulfed everything, the entire Lang Ya land spirit was covered in the black smoke.

"Don't!" The variant human Gu Immortals shouted.

"Quickly stop, we are allies by marriage…" Snowman Gu Immortal Bing Yuan screamed.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan could not care about their lives anymore, Lang Ya land spirit knew too much, since it did not want to join Fang Yuan, it had to die!

"Quickly save the land spirit! Don't let him die!" Mao Li Qiu was so shocked its hair was standing, it resisted the soul explosion as it charged at Fang Yuan.

"Calamity Luck Altar!" Five Elements Grandmaster directly let out this Immortal Gu House and went inside, crashing towards Fang Yuan while moving it.

Calamity Luck Altar was one of the foundations of Longevity Heaven, they had actually brought it over to help Lang Ya blessed land!

"Hmph, he escaped quickly." Fang Yuan's eyes shone with a cold light.

He did not take Lang Ya land spirit's life, at the crucial moment, Lang Ya land spirit teleported away.

If Five Elements Grandmaster had not reminded him, Lang Ya land spirit might not have reacted in time. But now, this was his domain, without using other methods to restrict him, he could teleport away from Fang Yuan.

"It is not so easy to take my life. Everyone, we will meet again." Fang Yuan looked around as he left his final words, using Fixed Immortal Travel afterwards.

He was in the center of the soul explosion, it was like the eye of the tornado, he was safe and sound. To approach Fang Yuan, the rest had to resist the soul explosion which had dense soul path dao marks, their immortal killer moves were restricted.

Rank seven Immortal Gu — Fixed Immortal Travel!

Jade light flashed as Fang Yuan vanished on the spot before anyone could interfere, he retreated successfully.

"We did not manage to kill this demon!" Fairy Zi Wei felt regretful.

Mao Li Qiu roared in anger, its bloodshot eyes stared at Fairy Zi Wei.

Without Fang Yuan, only Longevity Heaven and Heavenly Court were left.

Bam bam bam…

Continuous explosions resounded, the battle went into the climax right from the start.

"Stop, stop, don't destroy my blessed land. Damn it!" Lang Ya land spirit stomped his feet in anger, moving away as he tried to gather the lucky survivors on the three continents.

Fang Yuan's vision changed, when he regained his senses, he was in an underground cave.

"Fixed Immortal Travel is just so convenient." Fang Yuan sighed.

After stealing this rank seven Fixed Immortal Travel, he placed it in Heaven Sealing Mountain's immortal formation for refinement, it quickly became Fang Yuan's.

After confirming that there were no traps, Fang Yuan used it and left Lang Ya blessed land.

Lang Ya blessed land had rank eight Gu Immortals fighting, while outside there was Prince Feng Xian lying in ambush, Fang Yuan was an eyesore for both forces, he could not stay. If others were given enough time, or if he was hit by any special move and could not leave, it would be too stupid of him.

"Who is it?"

"Ah, it's elder Fang Yuan!"

Several rank six Gu Immortals sensed the immortal aura as they ran over, after seeing Fang Yuan, they bowed and asked: "Elder Fang Yuan, how is the situation in Lang Ya blessed land?"

Fang Yuan smiled viciously, he did not speak, he spread his arms instead.

Immortal killer move — Yama Battlefield!

Chapter 1584: Slaughter

"What happened?"

"Immortal battlefield… this, this is not funny."

"Lord Fang Yuan, we are on the same side!"

Panic and shouting ensued, the rockman and snowman Gu Immortals screamed while revealing deep wariness in their eyes.

In the current world, humans were the dominant race, these snowmen and rockmen were living desperately in the icy plain, they had a huge pressure of survival. In this environment, those variant humans who could become Gu Immortals were not useless.

If not for Fang Yuan's rank seven aura and publicly recognized rank eight battle strength, these rank six variant human Gu Immortals might have attacked already.

Fang Yuan's expression did not change, he looked at the sole rank seven Gu Immortal among the variant humans as he sighed: "Don't panic, I am your ally, how can I harm you? Lang Ya blessed land lost the battle, only I managed to escape, we lost because there was a traitor among you."

"What? We lost!"

"Lang Ya blessed land has been taken over by Heavenly Court?"

"We have a traitor?"

Fang Yuan's words were shocking, all the variant human Gu Immortals were deeply shook.

The sole rank seven snowman Gu Immortal frowned deeply: "Lord Fang Yuan, please open the immortal battlefield, let us communicate with our tribe!"

But before he finished his words, his body shook, he screamed: "My Immortal Gu!"

It was Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand, it had succeeded in stealing the Gu.

The other variant human Gu Immortals were confused, they asked in concern: "Lord Bing Zhuo, what happened?"

That's right, the snowman Gu Immortal guarding their base was Bing Zhuo. He had a rather good relationship with Fang Yuan, he had once invited Fang Yuan to drink his ice wolf wine.

Bing Zhuo stared at Fang Yuan angrily, he was about to scream with Fang Yuan took the initiative and pointed at him, saying with great certainty: "You are the traitor!"

The variant human Gu Immortals felt deep shock again.

"I am not a traitor! Fang Yuan, you stole my Immortal Gu and accused me, what is your intention?!" Bing Zhuo was furious, he grabbed the air as a pair of ice spears formed in his hands, emanating with deep frost energy.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly and said with deep anger and sadness: "I am right! You guys heard correctly, look, my alliance agreement did not trigger, this Bing Zhuo is a Heavenly Court Gu Immortal in disguise! The real Bing Zhuo died long ago."

The other variant human Gu Immortals looked at each other, female immortal Xue Er was Fang Yuan's fiancée, she asked: "Is there any misunderstanding? Lord Bing Zhuo has been with us all along."

"I am not a traitor! There has to be some misunderstanding, Lord Fang Yuan, you might have fallen for the enemy's ploy. Quickly return my Immortal Gu." Bing Zhuo said with a cold expression.

But at the next moment, Xue Er's body shook as she revealed great fear: "My, my Immortal Gu!"

Bing Zhuo was covered in frost energy, great thief ghost hand could not approach him, but Xue Er was an easy target.

"Fang Yuan!" Xue Er looked at Fang Yuan in disbelief.

Bing Zhuo charged at Fang Yuan as he shouted in anger: "I knew you humans were all incorrigible!"

Fang Yuan snickered: "Clown."

Saying so, yama children emerged from his emperor's robe, dozens of them flew out towards Bing Zhuo and the other variant human Gu Immortals.

At this moment, Fang Yuan exposed his ill intent, the variant human Gu Immortals no longer had any illusions, they charged at Fang Yuan after a temporary shock.

But how could their strength match these yama children with rank seven battle strength?

After the first clash, the variant human Gu Immortals' formation was broken by the yama children, they were separated and forced into their respective desperate fights.

Fang Yuan turned into emperor yama form and controlled the situation while he watched these variant human Gu Immortals fight the yama children.

Yama children were useless against Feng Jiu Ge and the rest, but against the variant human Gu Immortals, they were sufficient.

If not for Fang Yuan intentionally holding back, these rank six variant human Gu Immortals would have been killed by the yama children already.

The only rank seven Gu Immortal Bing Zhuo was also in a tough fight, he could not escape.

Great thief ghost hand!

Great thief ghost hand!

Great thief ghost hand!

Fang Yuan used great thief ghost hand consecutively, stealing the Immortal Gu of these variant human Gu Immortals one by one.

This was the reason why Fang Yuan held back, if he forced them too much, they would despair and destroy their Immortal Gu and resources, Fang Yuan would lose all his gains.

But now that they had hope, these variant human Gu Immortals would resist till the end, only few were as resolute as Meng Tu in suiciding.

Furthermore, the variant humans had been living in seclusion, they only sparred regularly, they had little experience with battles that involved life and death.

As a wisdom path Gu Immortal, Fang Yuan had already deciphered the thoughts of these variant humans, right now, even though his tactic was simple, it was incredibly effective.

The variant human Gu Immortals had their Immortal Gu stolen, their battle strength fell drastically, they were becoming weaker.

"Fang Yuan, I was wrong about you! How can you be so unscrupulous, you harmed your allies!" A rockman Gu Immortal shouted in anger and agony.

Bing Zhuo smiled coldly: "Haven't you realized? This guy has gotten rid of the alliance agreement already, he is not an ally, he is an enemy!"

"Sigh, you speak too much crap." Fang Yuan sighed lightly, making a yama child self-detonate.

Immortal killer move — Soul Explosion!

Bing Zhuo was a close combat specialist, the yama child was too close to him, he could not dodge, after getting hit, the explosion destroyed his corpse entirely.

"Lord Bing Zhuo!" A sorrowful cry resounded.

Xue Er almost fainted.

Fang Yuan had a cold expression, he had almost stolen all of these Gu Immortals' Immortal Gu, the rest were well guarded and great thief ghost hand could not get close to them. Fang Yuan had limited time, he did not want to drag this on, he started to kill them.

Variant human Gu Immortals died one after another, only Xue Er was left eventually.

"You demon, I will not let you off even as a ghost!" Xue Er had a distorted expression, saying her final words with deep hatred.

At once, several yama children went up and tore her into pieces of shredded meat.

As for her soul, it was preserved in yama battlefield, imprisoned by Fang Yuan along with the other variant human Gu Immortals' souls.

Soul search!

Using his extremely proficient soul search method, Fang Yuan quickly grasped the details of the snowman and rockman tribes.

Fang Yuan dispelled yama battlefield as he returned to the icy plain again.

This slaughter took some time, but the process was not hindered by any external forces, there were no deductions or attacks on yama battlefield. This showed that the variant human Gu Immortals were the final batch of Gu Immortals left here.

According to the soul search results, Fang Yuan went deep underground and found large numbers of rockman and snowman Gu Masters, and even more normal mortals.

Fang Yuan forcefully moved them all into his sovereign immortal aperture.

After a while, he excavated the treasury of these two tribes and moved them into his immortal aperture.

The snowman tribe's ice tear and the rockman tribe's bumpy rice were specialty immortal materials of the two tribes. Other than that, there were normal immortal materials left behind from the Olden Antiquity Era and Remote Antiquity Era, they were all nearly nonexistent by now, unable to be found in treasure yellow heaven. Among them, there was face changing silver, this metal could mimic any beautiful woman and turn into their face.

As for the immortal apertures of the dead variant human Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan sealed them temporarily, he did not want to land the apertures here.

Rank seven Fixed Immortal Travel!

Using this Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan left freely, leaving the empty crime scene behind. This paradise of the rockmen and snowmen had been destroyed completely.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan appeared in Southern Border.

"Who?!" The two Gu Immortals in Southern Border shouted as Fang Yuan activated emperor yama.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly as he pointed.

Soul explosion!

Soul explosion!

Soul explosion!

Soul explosion!

…

After five to six soul explosions, the two Southern Border Gu Immortals ran away in great fear. Who was this person, he was simply crazy! Attacking with a series of killer moves at once that were all at rank seven peak power!

The two immortals left using the immortal Gu formation, Fang Yuan could do nothing about it.

But soon, he destroyed this immortal Gu formation with brute force and destroyed the two Immortal Gu and countless mortal Gu inside.

Once the immortal formation was destroyed, the inside was exposed.

Fang Yuan smiled, this flowing light was bright and dazzling, it was a dream realm!

Chapter 1585: Fang Yuan's Attainment Levels

This dream realm was not very big.

The reason why Fang Yuan could find it was because he had thrown this dream realm out personally.

Back then, he disguised as Wu Yi Hai and entered the righteous path, secretly entering dream realms to raise his attainment level. When the battle started, Heavenly Court interfered and Purple Mountain True Monarch died, Fang Yuan inherited Shadow Sect and brought the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and escaped for his life.

Along the way, he used the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies to resist the strong enemies and managed to escape safely.

But he used up all the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies in the process.

This place was where Fang Yuan fought against Yi clan's Gu Immortals, he detonated two Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and forced back Yi clan's Immortal Gu House Bay Pavilion.

After the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies detonated, they formed into this dream realm. The Southern Border Gu Immortals were not going to let it go, after some contest, two clans won and created an immortal formation to develop using this dream realm.

Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel to arrive here and sent the guarding Gu Immortals running before he destroyed the immortal formation.

Even though using great thief ghost hand now could steal Gu worms, it could not target Immortal Gu specifically, with so many mortal Gu here, there was a big chance of great thief ghost hand stealing mortal Gu consecutively.

To prevent the immortal formation from sending reinforcements or self-detonating, Fang Yuan decided to strike first and destroyed it.

Even though Immortal Gu were unique, Fang Yuan did not really mind it now.

Fang Yuan had a lot of Immortal Gu, after slaughtering the rockman and snowman Gu Immortals, he gained a lot of rank six and seven Immortal Gu, there was going to be a headache later on how to feed them.

What Fang Yuan lacked were Immortal Gu that suited him, firstly, they had to be rank seven for him, rank six Immortal Gu were too low ranked now. And the path also had to be among the ones he was specialized in.

With Fang Yuan's refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment level, any Immortal Gu recipe could be turned into an immortal killer move, if he needed any specific Immortal Gu, he could use Immortal Gu to deduce recipes and use them instead. (Of course, the deduction's difficulty would vary according to the specific situations. Even with the light of wisdom, some Immortal Gu recipes that needed decades or even centuries would be ignored by Fang Yuan in this case.)

"Hmm, the dream realm has shrunk a little." Fang Yuan noticed when he took a second look.

The original dream realm was made of two Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, it was slightly smaller now.

"Because others explored it and consumed it…"

Other Gu Immortals did not have Fang Yuan's advanced methods, but they could still explore it for dream path Gu materials.

But these materials could be harvested in their own dreams too. The true value of dream realms was the true meaning left behind by others, the Southern Border Gu Immortals were simply giving up the treasure for scraps. But they were happy to do this, the forces were busy gathering dream path Gu materials and buying them for high prices in treasure yellow heaven."

"If I remember correctly, these two dream realms are ice and snow path along with space path."

These dream realms originate from Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, he was a great grandmaster in every path, his dream realms comprise all the different paths currently known.

Fang Yuan had specially chosen these Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies. But because he was trying to escape, he gave up on them as they were not very useful to him.

But that was in the past, right now, they were very useful.

Fang Yuan needed space path attainment level, because he could design an immortal killer move for Fixed Immortal Travel so that the teleportation time was reduced.

Fang Yuan needed ice and snow path attainment level even more. He had just killed many variant human Gu Immortals, the immortal apertures that the snowman Gu Immortals left behind were mostly ice and snow path, he needed attainment level to annex them.

"Right now, among my paths, refinement path is the highest at quasi-supreme grandmaster."

"Followed by theft path at great grandmaster."

"The third group of strength path, wisdom path, star path, transformation path, blood path, dark path, formation path, and water path are all at grandmaster attainment level."

"The fourth group are luck path, soul path, enslavement path, and earth path at master attainment level."

"Below that are sword path, space path, time path, dream path, poison path, fire path, metal path, and others, they are all ordinary."

"And finally, information path, ice and snow path, qi path, light path, sound path, phantom path, rule path, and others, I have not been involved in them in both lives."

Among all his paths, Fang Yuan needed to raise time path the most!

His time path attainment level was only ordinary, Fang Yuan had to become a grandmaster at the very least.

"Heavenly Court is too big and strong, it had countless hibernating experts. Even now, with the wisdom path great expert Fairy Zi Wei leading them, with Chen Yi and the rest supporting her, they managed to invade Lang Ya blessed land without even Duke Long's presence."

"If not for Long Hair Ancestor's and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's agreement, so that Lang Ya blessed land could gain Longevity Heaven's assistance, it would have fallen already."

Fang Yuan was not someone who did not know his limit, he knew clearly: even if he had reverse flow protection seal and emperor yama, or even if he deduced Luo Po seal, he was only counted as a rank eight Gu Immortal, against Heavenly Court, his strength as a single individual was useless.

In his previous life, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable led Shadow Sect and successfully defied heaven, mixing into Heavenly Court and concealing himself, becoming the mastermind that wreaked havoc in the five regions, secretly supporting Ma Hong Yun and Western Desert's Tang clan, even causing the death of Feng Jiu Ge in Lang Ya blessed land and Feng Jin Huang's death by Fang Yuan and the others, Shadow Sect was behind all these events, they had unfathomably deep influence.

But now, heaven's will used Fang Yuan as a pawn to rebirth and change the past, Shadow Sect lost the fight and Heavenly Court had the absolute advantage.

Fang Yuan was using Shadow Sect's inheritance to maintain his footing, but it was too difficult to deal with Heavenly Court. The loss of Lang Ya blessed land was a clear example.

"My only hope of defeating Heavenly Court is to obtain Red Lotus' true inheritance. Using the power of Red Lotus' true inheritance, I will resist Heavenly Court and destroy fate Gu!"

"But to inherit Red Lotus' true inheritance, I will need to enter the River of Time. Heavenly Court must already have a huge force in there waiting for me!"

Even now that Fairy Zi Wei and the rest were trapped in Lang Ya blessed land fighting against Longevity Heaven's experts, Fang Yuan did not think of exploring the River of Time.

How could Fairy Zi Wei leave out such a big flaw?

The River of Time contained countless time path dao marks, even though the sovereign immortal body was not restricted, when Fang Yuan uses killer moves of any other path, it would be greatly weakened. Rank six immortal killer moves would become as weak as mortal killer moves.

Earlier, Fang Yuan entered the River of Time to catch Heavenly Court off guard, because he had the immemorial year monkey, and because Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had already taken over one of the stone lotus islands. Eventually, he used the stone lotus island to kill Lord Huang Shi, but in the process, he did not truly fight.

And now, Fang Yuan wanted to find another true inheritance of Red Lotus, he wanted to find a new stone lotus island. The immemorial year monkey died in Lang Ya blessed land, while Fang Yuan's reverse flow protection seal, emperor yama and other killer moves were all weakened in there.

"In the River of Time, the most suitable methods are time path killer moves!"

"Even though I have Hei Fan's true inheritance and Spectral Soul's true inheritance has lots of time path details, the former lacks an offensive rank eight time path method, even though Years Flow Like Water is rank eight, its effect is to produce year Gu and create defensive killer moves. As for the latter, Spectral Soul's true inheritance has many time path offensive methods, including rank eight, but I do not have the necessary time path Immortal Gu."

Thus, Fang Yuan wanted to obtain time path grandmaster attainment level and use the light of wisdom to deduce killer moves that he could use personally. With these methods, he would be able to resist Heavenly Court in the River of Time!

Immortal killer move — Heaven's Will Dissipation!

While thinking, Fang Yuan multi-tasked and completed his killer move.

A grey-white light appeared on his body.

The grey-white light spread into the dream realm in front him as it spread their radiance everywhere, like ink entering clear water.

Soon, the entire dream realm was covered by grey-white light specks.

The multicolored eyes appeared from these specks.

These eyes were very special, they changed colors with each blink.

The number of multicolored eyes increased rapidly, after a few breaths of time, they went from tens to hundreds, and to thousands in a flash.

The colored eyeballs blinked continuously, each time they blinked, it was an attack against heaven's will.

Eventually, the multicolored eyes fell in numbers until they vanished entirely.

Immortal killer move — Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation!

Fang Yuan used a second move as this dream realm condensed into two human figures, one was intact while the other was handicapped.

Fang Yuan opened his immortal aperture's entrance and sent these two Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies inside.

Using Fixed Immortal Travel, he vanished in a few breaths of time, leaving behind an empty space.

Chapter 1586: Snow Crystal Formation

The two Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies entered the sovereign immortal aperture and settled down in Mini Green Heaven.

The sovereign immortal aperture had five regions and nine heavens, among all the nine heavens, Mini Green Heaven was the least developed. Thus, Fang Yuan used it as the storage area of dream realms.

Shadow Sect's members, Ying Wu Xie, Lady White Rabbit, Hei Lou Lan, Fairy Miao Yin, and Bai Ning Bing were all cultivating in Mini Yellow Heaven.

Lang Ya's battle was too high end, everyone who participated had rank eight battle strength. Even the variant human Gu Immortals relied on the super immortal formation to fight, once it was destroyed, they could not fight anymore.

In a crucial moment, Fang Yuan would possibly need the Shadow Sect members to use ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel, so they did not join that fight after all.

As for Fang Yuan's time path clone, he was at the most northern part of Mini Northern Plains.

"Tch!"

With a soft click, as the time path clone placed the final mortal Gu in, the Gu formation activated.

This Gu formation had a huge range of a few dozen square kilometers of land, there were tens of thousands of mortal Gu used to create it from rank one to five, they were of all paths but most of the Gu worms were ice and snow path. The core was made of two ice path Immortal Gu, they were obtained from the snowman Gu Immortals, refined into Fang Yuan's property.

The cores of the Gu formation were three of the rank eight immortal material, ice path crystal essence!

Each ice path crystal essence was large like a mountain peak.

The entire crystal was ice-blue in color, it had crystallized texture, the surface had countless holes of varying sizes, a large amount of cold and icy air was spewing out of these holes unceasingly.

If the frosty air was allowed to spread, the ice and snow path dao marks would also be carved in the surroundings, modifying the environment and creating a habitat suitable for snowmen and snow monsters to live in.

Thus, Fang Yuan's plan earlier was to use an ice path crystal essence to create a snow monster production line and establish new sources of revenue.

His original ice path crystal essence was obtained from his marriage with Xue Er. But earlier, he slaughtered the snowman tribe and obtained two more ice path crystal essences.

"With these three ice path crystal essences, I can easily produce snow monsters."

"I will name this formation, snow crystal formation."

Fang Yuan's time path clone observed for a while before nodding in satisfaction.

Attainment level was shared between his clone and main body, Fang Yuan had formation path grandmaster attainment level, so did his clone.

This was different from Shadow Sect, back then in order to deceive heaven, Spectral Soul made use of the fact that his split soul clones did not carry his full attainment level, so that almost all of them only focused on one path.

Even if Shadow Sect's members fought against Heavenly Court, they would not be found out as the Demon Venerable's split soul. This was also why Shadow Sect was able to plant spies into Heavenly Court.

As for Fang Yuan's time path clone, it was easy to expose, but Fang Yuan did not need it to go outside and fight anyway. Fang Yuan's motive was different from Spectral Soul, his time path clone was meant to make use of the light of wisdom.

And to deduce matters in the light of wisdom, attainment level was needed. Fang Yuan made a wise choice between the two options.

The snow crystal formation was created by time path clone, its main purpose was to emit the frost energy that would constantly alter the environment inch by inch.

Of course, the formation also had the ability to monitor and control the area.

"It is a pity I am a formation path grandmaster and not a great grandmaster. Grandmasters can mimic other paths while great grandmasters can use natural dao marks directly. If I am a great grandmaster, I will not need ice path Immortal Gu for this snow crystal formation, I can use these three ice path crystal essences directly."

This way, Fang Yuan would be able to free up these two ice path Immortal Gu for other uses.

Of course, Fang Yuan did not lack Immortal Gu so that was not an issue. But normally speaking, Gu Immortals had very few Immortal Gu, if they used the Immortal Gu for formations, they would not be able to use them in other aspects. Thus, attainment level had an incredible effect — Gu Immortals could save use of Immortal Gu!

After setting up the snow crystal formation, Fang Yuan's time path clone flew away.

Even though he was not a land spirit and could not teleport, he had Immortal Gu and could fly very quickly.

After a while, the time path clone went past several hundred li as he looked down on the ground while concealing his figure.

There was a group of moving snowmen on the ground.

They were either mortals or Gu Masters, they were all captured by Fang Yuan from the northern icy plain, there were several thousand of them.

Snowman slaves on the order of thousands in numbers were not rare in treasure yellow heaven, but the quality of this batch far exceeded the norm, because among these snowman slaves, Gu Masters were a high proportion. This was not normal, in treasure yellow heaven, this batch of snowmen could be exchanged for ten times the usual number of snowman slaves!

These snowmen had left the place where they lived for a long time and entered the sovereign immortal aperture, they were very fearful and timid.

At this moment, the group moved forward while conversing intensely.

When Fang Yuan slaughtered the snowman and rockman Gu Immortals, it was inside the immortal battlefield, he kept it hidden. When he captured these snowmen, he disguised as a snowman Gu Immortal, so these slaves did not know the truth.

Immortal killer move — Familiar Face!

Fang Yuan's time path clone turned into Bing Zhuo and descended from the sky.

Using Gu worms, he created a blizzard in the sky as snow descended slowly.

"Ah! The immortal of our tribe!"

"Quickly kneel down, kneel down and greet lord immortal!"

"Welcome, great immortal Bing Zhuo."

The snowmen quickly knelt as they paid respects to Fang Yuan's time path clone.

Fang Yuan's time path clone was expressionless, saying: "The world is in chaos, but we are in paradise. The three mountains have immortal fog, the snow race has nothing to fear."

His voice was not loud but it was heard by everyone clearly.

Whoosh.

A gust of wind blew as the blizzard stopped, the snowmen raised their heads but only saw the empty sky, Bing Zhuo's figure had faded with the wind.

The snowmen were stunned, after realizing that Bing Zhuo had vanished, they got up with joy on their faces, they thought about his words.

The snowman tribe leader thought and said to the elders: "Earlier, we came here due to the vague guidance of great immortal Bing Zhuo, he wanted us to come here. And now, he has shown up to tell us that there are three mountains ahead where we can live in peace?"

After talking for a while, everyone agreed and set off, they were no longer hesitant, even though they brought the young and old with them, the speed was much faster than earlier.

To create snow monsters, the snow crystal formation was not needed. Just the three ice path crystal essences were enough to show effect just by existing, it was a simple matter.

But time path clone spent so much effort to create the snow crystal formation, he wanted to give these snowmen a place to live and grow.

"With the snow crystal formation, the snow monsters and snowmen can live here without obstructing one another. But I cannot isolate them completely, I need them to interact and conflict with each other, so as to develop."

"The snow crystal formation's maintenance is not a problem with food path methods, but the three ice path crystal essences are expendable, they will be used up eventually." Time path clone flew as he thought.

The frost energy that the ice path crystal essence emits contains the ice and snow path dao marks of the crystal itself, these dao marks would be carved in the surroundings for a while before dissipating, they would not increase sovereign immortal aperture's total number of ice and snow path dao marks. But the environment it creates would suit the snow monsters and snowmen a lot.

But it was too early for this problem, the three ice path crystal essences would only be depleted after a long time.

After managing the snowmen, the time path clone went to Mini Southern Border and had the rockmen settle down.

In the five mini regions, Mini Southern Border had the densest earth path dao marks, it was most suited for rockmen to live in.

The process of settling down the rockmen was very simple, the time path clone used almost the same method as before.

While the time path clone was managing the immortal aperture, Fang Yuan's main body was at another end of Southern Border.

This was a huge Earth Trench, it was deep and dark, even in broad daylight, it was covered in darkness.

These dark shadows were dark path dao beasts — shadow monsters, this was Plunder Shadow Earth Trench.

"Back then, I succeeded in learning ancient battle formation Omni-directional Travel here, I used many Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies to stop the righteous path pursuers. Hmm…"

Fang Yuan observed and had a moved expression: "Southern Border's righteous path built an immortal formation here too, and it is not weak at all."

"Who is it? This is an important place of Southern Border's righteous path, any unauthorised lone immortal should leave before regretting it." At this time, a Southern Border Gu Immortal's voice resounded from the clouds, he was hidden within the immortal formation, not showing his true figure.

"Oh?" Fang Yuan's lips curled up, killing intent surging in his eyes: "I want to see how you'll make me regret it."

Boom!

With a loud sound, he started to attack the immortal formation forcefully.

Chapter 1587: Death by Ghost Hand

Boom boom boom!

With a chain of explosions, multicolored lights shone like fireworks. Metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wisdom, strength, soul, poison, star, refinement… killer moves of many paths were used easily by Fang Yuan.

Under such attacks, the figure of an immortal formation appeared. It was like a reinforced castle, white lights shielded it like a mountain, blocking all of Fang Yuan's attacks.

"Hahaha, colorful attacks with little power, your methods are too flashy, they cannot take down our formation!" Within the immortal Gu formation, Yang clan's Gu Immortal Yang San Mu mocked loudly.

Fang Yuan was currently in emperor yama form, Southern Border's Gu Immortals could not tell who he truly was.

"No, this person's formation path attainment is not low, he is using all sorts of methods to probe our formation!" Chi Qiu's expression changed as he said in a low tone.

This immortal Gu formation was set up by Chi clan, Chi Qiu was tasked here to guard it, as a formation path cultivator, his words were seriously noted by the rest.

Yang San Mu frowned immediately, asking Chi Qiu: "We are defending passively, do we let him continue testing his moves?"

Chi Qiu shook his head: "Our formation has offensive methods too, when the Gu formation is destroyed to some extent, the attacks will be unleashed. Don't look at me, I cannot command the Gu formation to retaliate, all of you know that this setup has its reason, I am sure there is no need for me to explain it?"

The immortals looked at each other helplessly.

The fundamental cause was Fang Yuan after all, he had once disguised as Wu Yi Hai and mixed into Southern Border's righteous path, at the crucial moment, he controlled the immortal formation and left after gaining great benefits. Southern Border's Gu Immortals lost a lot of face, they made changes after that battle. Chi clan's immortal formations were no longer controlled by outsiders, they operated on their own, it was to prevent traitors like Fang Yuan from succeeding.

Yang San Mu saw that Chi Qiu was without options, he turned to look at Xia clan's Gu Immortal Xia Fan.

Xia Fan was a wisdom path cultivator, seeing that Yang San Mu had turned to him, he shook his head and answered: "The other party has very powerful wisdom path defensive methods, I cannot deduce his origins, unless we can gain crucial information later."

Yang San Mu heard this and his expression sank.

Next, he shouted at Fang Yuan: "Hahaha, scoundrel, why are you using so little strength, are you here to scratch my back?"

Yang San Mu, Chi Qiu, and Xia Fan had rank seven cultivation level, they were also defended by the immortal formation, they did not fear the rank seven Gu Immortal Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan snickered and ignored him, he continued to probe this formation from different angles.

"This immortal formation is more complex and strong than I had expected!"

Yang San Mu continued to provoke him, but Fang Yuan was completely immune to his words.

Yang San Mu frowned: "He is just one rank seven Gu Immortal, while we have many people and the immortal formation. If we hide here and let him attack freely, wouldn't we lose face in the righteous path? Will any Gu Immortal be willing to face this daring scoundrel, if you can kill him, it will be quite a good story."

Once he said that, nobody moved.

Almost all Gu Immortals were not rash people, it might seem easy to deal with Fang Yuan who was alone, but that was the problem. Why would any ordinary rank seven Gu Immortal have the guts to attack this fortified immortal formation alone?

The Southern Border immortals were thinking that an ambush was likely here, they were not going to take the risk.

Yang San Mu could not get anyone to move, he was quite gloomy.

He was the temporary leader among these people, if they avoided battle this time, news would spread and others would put the blame on him. Yang San Mu would lose the most reputation among them.

"Right now, Southern Border's earth veins are moving as immortal materials and Immortal Gu are being exposed constantly from the Earth Trenches, and yet I am here guarding a bunch of dream realms."

"I wanted to go around and leave this post. After paying a huge cost, I was about to succeed, but if I avoid battle this time, and allow this person to leave, the clan would have an excuse and evidence against me, I will never be able to relocate myself."

Thinking of this, Yang San Mu gritted his teeth: "The enemy is quite peculiar, as a righteous path member, I cannot let him off. Everyone, guard the formation, I will go fight him."

The Gu Immortals heard this and had varying expressions.

Some urged him to be careful, some clapped and praised him for the bravery, some assured Yang San Mu that they would guard the formation and he could go in peace.

Yang San Mu sneered in his heart, but showed an attitude of acting for a righteous cause, after saying some words that boosted his reputation, he left the formation to fight Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan saw him and was slightly surprised, before understanding Yang San Mu's mentality immediately.

Soul explosion!

Fang Yuan pointed as an immortal killer move was used against Yang San Mu.

Yang San Mu fought against Fang Yuan for some rounds, he could not take it much more, he panicked as he thought: "This person must cultivate soul path! Even though his attacks are simple, they were very powerful, and his defensive method is very profound, I am not his match and will lose sooner or later. I should retreat now while it has not turned ugly yet. I have found out about his background anyway, I can explain myself later."

But Fang Yuan's battle experience was incredibly deep, after seeing that Yang San Mu had the intention to retreat, he quickly activated yama battlefield.

Instantly, Yang San Mu's vision changed, he was trapped inside yama battlefield with no way of escaping.

Yang San Mu was shocked: "Immortal battlefield? How can this be! How can there be such a rapidly activated immortal battlefield in this world!!"

He was shocked and panicked but he tried to stay calm: "Don't fluster, this immortal battlefield was created so quickly, it must be deeply flawed. Maybe it is easy to deduce and break? I have other immortals on my side, they will have seen this immortal battlefield appear and surely help me get out of this."

Fang Yuan pointed as three yama children attacked Yang San Mu.

Yang San Mu's heart jumped, he fought as he retreated, trying to stall for time.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

Suddenly, Yang San Mu's body shook intensely, a look of shock was frozen on his face as his eyes almost popped out, he shouted: "My Immortal Gu!"

Fang Yuan successfully stole an Immortal Gu, he threw it into his immortal aperture without looking.

Yang San Mu spat out a mouthful of blood, he was immediately in bad shape after suffering heavy injuries.

It turned out that Fang Yuan stole the core of his movement killer move. With the loss of the Immortal Gu, the killer move failed and he suffered a backlash, the battle quickly went sour for him.

"It seems my luck is much better than yours, I could not steal Feng Jiu Ge's core Immortal Gu, but you?" Fang Yuan snickered.

"Feng Jiu Ge? Who exactly are you?!"

Great thief ghost hand!

Fang Yuan succeeded again.

Guh.

Yang San Mu spat out blood again, his killer move's activation failed, with this second backlash, he lost his life.

Great thief ghost hand could actually kill people!

Chapter 1588: Scheming Against Each Other

"He actually died?" Fang Yuan saw this result and was slightly stunned.

"It seems this Yang San Mu is really unlucky. He got the core Immortal Gu of his killer moves stolen by me twice in a row." Fang Yuan had a plain expression as he shook his head.

This effect was from their difference in luck.

Earlier, he could not subdue Feng Jiu Ge because he was a Dao Guardian with similar luck as Fang Yuan. But Yang San Mu was a normal person, thus he died from great thief ghost hand.

Fang Yuan suddenly realized that luck path and theft path were very powerful when combined together. Even though his luck path true inheritance was not complete and his theft path true inheritance was also incomplete, these inheritances originated from two venerables. It was a rare case in history to have inherited true inheritances of two venerables at once.

Inside the immortal Gu formation, the Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals saw that Yang San Mu was trapped in the immortal battlefield, they became quite nervous.

Chi Qiu urged Xia Fan: "Quick, quick, quick, haven't you deduced this immortal battlefield yet?"

Xia Fan was deep in thought, seemingly not listening to anything.

The other Gu Immortals were discussing with uncertainty.

"What immortal battlefield did he use, it was set up so quickly, this is simply unprecedented."

"No wonder he has the guts to provoke us alone, he has quite the incredible move."

"It will all depend on Lord Xia Fan now."

Xia Fan heard their chatter, he rolled his eyes and thought to himself: "These people know nothing about wisdom path! Do they really think immortal battlefields are so easy to unravel and break?"

Xia Fan could feel the difficulty, he thought to himself: "Oh Yang San Mu, I hope that you can last some time."

But as time passed, his pressure intensified.

There was only one wisdom path Gu Immortal here, if he could not deduce it, no matter how many Southern Border Gu Immortals there were, they could not enter the immortal battlefield and help. If he failed, his personal reputation in terms of capability would suffer a hit, but that was nothing compared to the rumors that might spread, saying that he had the ability to do it but refused and watched Yang San Mu die, his reputation would go down the drain if that happened.

But how could Fang Yuan's yama battlefield be so easily deduced and broken?

Fairy Zi Wei could do it because she was among the top three wisdom path great experts in the current world. But Xia Fan was not!

"I cannot deduce it! This killer move's foundation is too deep, it seems to have a terrifying origin!" After deducing for a while, Xia Fan was already full of sweat.

The Southern Border Gu Immortals were still talking among themselves, Xia Fan felt increasing annoyed, he opened his eyes and anger showed in them: "Can you people shut up?"

The immortals stopped talking.

Chi Qiu coughed: "That's right, be quiet, let's not disturb Lord Xia Fan, I believe he will not disappoint us with his abilities!"

Saying this, Xia Fan was forced into a corner!

Xia Fan looked at Chi Qiu with a dark gaze while the latter had a supportive look, Xia Fan gritted his teeth in anger.

But he was a wisdom path Gu Immortal after all, with a shift of his thoughts, he smiled: "Everyone, calm down, you must have forgotten that Yang San Mu is most skilled in investigative methods. He went out to fight because he is very confident, he must have detected some information or truths that we do not know."

Xia Fan and Yang San Mu were not on good terms, they hated each other.

But now, Xia Fan praised Yang San Mu and placed him on a high pedestal.

Everyone was stunned before realizing.

If it was like what Xia Fan said, Yang San Mu's actions were simply too much! He had left them aside and went out to take all the credit for himself.

Right now, Southern Border's earth veins were moving and immortal materials as well as Immortal Gu were appearing everywhere, who would want to guard this place? Who would not want to go out and seek fortune?

If Yang San Mu gained credit here, he would be redeployed and leave this place.

Not only Yang San Mu, everyone else here desired to leave.

Soon, the immortals started to change their words.

They started to agree with Xia Fan.

"Lord Xia Fan is right, Lord Yang San Mu's investigative methods are renowned in Southern Border, who does not know that?"

"That's right, that's right, I remember the time when he investigated the turbulence in black heaven clearly. After reporting to Yang clan, they moved out in advance and actually arrived at the accurate spot for the meteor rain. It is said that Yang clan obtained three hills worth of star path immortal materials from that."

"Lord Yang San Mu had even chased after the demonic path Gu Immortal Nian Wang Huai before, that guy was so vile and devious, staying hidden for a long time and evading Tie clan's capture multiple times, but he eventually ended up in Lord Yang San Mu's hands."

"In my opinion, Lord Yang San Mu must be very confident this time. We must trust his judgment, we cannot fluster. I also need to remind everyone, after Lord Yang San Mu wins this time, we need to place him in the sub formation and inspect him carefully. Remember the matter about Fang Yuan not too long ago."

Fang Yuan had used familiar face to disguise as Wu Yi Hai and was in the righteous path for a long time, he toyed around with the Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals during the dream realm battle.

The moment Southern Border's Gu Immortals heard this name, they became extremely angry.

"Hmph, Fang Yuan is a demonic path scoundrel who infiltrated the righteous path, one day, he will be punished!"

"Demonic will never defeat righteousness, this is the rule of this world. The demon might be arrogant for now, but he will face retribution one day. Even Spectral Soul Demon Venerable got his soul captured after death by Heavenly Court, didn't he?"

"I want to kill this demon personally, sigh, it is a pity I could not join that fight."

Chi Qiu did not speak, he looked at Xia Fan with a deep gaze.

Xia Fan shut his eyes as he started deducing again.

Chi Qiu sighed internally: "As expected of a wisdom path Gu Immortal."

He had said that earlier to trap Xia Fan, but Xia Fan actually reversed the situation easily with a few words.

Xia Fan hinted that Yang San Mu was greedy for credit and did not want to share it with the rest. All of the Gu Immortals here were savvy people, they soon understood what Xia Fan was trying to say.

He meant: if that was not the case, and Yang San Mu was instead stupid and entered the enemy's trap, what would they do? If he died inside the formation, everyone would be implicated, they would be labeled as being 'vicious people who watched their comrade die in battle while they cowardly hid inside the formation', right?

Thus, these immortals had to praise Yang San Mu to the sky. Xia Fan used their mentality to easily get past Chi Qiu's attack.

But Xia Fan's mood was bad now: "This immortal battlefield cannot be unraveled by me alone. Damn it! We need to seek help, but before that, I need to make some credit, I cannot be so useless. Hmm?!"

At this time, yama battlefield disappeared as Fang Yuan reappeared, Yang San Mu had vanished from sight.

"This, this, this!"

"What happened?"

The Southern Border immortals drew in a sharp breath, the rank seven Xia Fan and Chi Qiu had changes in expressions.

The situation was clear, only the enemy was left now, Yang San Mu was likely to be gone.

But why was it so quick?

Yang San Mu was a skillful person at the very least, he had ample battle strength, how could he die so easily?

The enemy's immortal battlefield had a dense soul path aura, without any time path aura. There was no time difference inside it.

Thus, the biggest possibility was that this mysterious demonic path rank seven Gu Immortal's battle strength dominated Yang San Mu! But was that possible? Or rather, he must have used some peculiar and uncommon method. right?

The Southern Border immortals were shocked and found this unbelievable.

Fang Yuan looked at the formation as his gaze flickered in cold light.

Originally, he wanted to disguise as Yang San Mu and dispel yama battlefield, getting into the formation by disguise. But after soul searching him, he found out Southern Border's arrangements and gave up on that plan.

Southern Border's righteous path had deep foundations, looking down on them would be stupid. Familiar face was already exposed, it was impossible to replicate 'Wu Yi Hai's' success again.

Even though this killer move came from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, in the world of Gu cultivation, there had never been invincible killer moves. After such a long time, the era had advanced greatly.

Of course, Southern Border's righteous path might not be able to easily produce Immortal Gu or killer moves that could see through familiar face, but they had other methods to decipher the identity of Gu Immortals.

Especially with Heavenly Court's guidance, Southern Border's righteous path had many ways of ascertaining identities, the process was strict and had many procedures. Especially when they had soul lantern Gu and other identity type Gu, it was hard for Fang Yuan to disguise himself even with familiar face.

"Demonic scoundrel, what did you do to Lord Yang San Mu?"

"Quickly release Lord Yang San Mu!"

"Lord Yang San Mu might have already escaped that immortal battlefield using some method that he had."

The Southern Border Gu Immortals spoke, some were still carrying illusions in their minds.

Fang Yuan's expression turned increasingly cold.

"This immortal formation was set by Chi Qu You personally, if I try to deduce it step by step, there will not be enough time. I can only force my way through now, let's see how tough this formation is!"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan dispelled emperor yama, used ancient sword dragon transformation and activated reverse flow protection seal.

Next, he used immortal killer move myriad dragon, causing a sea of ferocious dragons to charge at the formation.

This killer move was currently Fang Yuan's trademark, upon seeing this, if any Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortal could not tell it was Fang Yuan, they were just purposely acting unaware!

"Ah! This person is Fang Yuan!"

"Oh heavens, that demon is here!"

"He is here again, he is simply too daring, he is acting so freely, he is truly looking down on the righteous path of Southern Border!"

The Gu Immortals screamed one after another, unable to conceal the shock on their faces.

Other than shock, there was also fear that they tried hard to hide.

Chapter 1589: Attacking Forcefully

Fang Yuan had to conceal and hide himself in the past, but now against the immortals of Southern Border's righteous path, he did not need to anymore.

Fang Yuan's appearance was very shocking to the Southern Border righteous path Gu Immortals now!

In the past, Fang Yuan disguised as Wu Yi Hai and obtained great benefits in the battle of the dream realm, becoming the leader of Shadow Sect, eventually he was chased down by Southern Border's righteous path, but he was able to escape.

Heavenly Court's pursuit could not do anything to Fang Yuan.

Months ago, Fang Yuan suddenly appeared in Southern Border and killed two Gu Immortals from Hou clan and Shang clan, if not for Paradise Earth's inheritor, even Tie Mian Shen would have died.

Afterwards, Heavenly Court sent out the rank eight Gu Immortal expert Thunder Ghost True Monarch, the process of the battle was unknown but Fang Yuan managed to take away three of her rib bones, the scene of her getting beaten up was displayed in treasure yellow heaven. Instantly, the world was shaken, Fang Yuan's reputation completely suppressed Feng Jiu Ge as the number one rank seven expert! Most Gu Immortals realized that even though Fang Yuan only had rank seven cultivation level, he was a unique individual on par with and should be treated as a rank eight Gu Immortal.

Furthermore, Fang Yuan was an otherworldly demon who was reborn using Spring Autumn Cicada, he was vicious and devious, many people despised his nonexistent bottom line, even as a Gu Immortal, he attacked mortals.

And now, Fang Yuan was the most dazzling and rapidly rising demonic path overlord!

Such a person had shown up, Southern Border's righteous path immortals were naturally surprised, shocked, and panicking.

"Lord Yang San Mu had sacrificed himself heroically, our Southern Border's righteous path and this vicious Fang Yuan have yet another debt of hatred! One day, we will make him pay the price!" Xia Fan patted his chest as he said in sadness.

The immortals were silent, nobody held any illusions anymore. Fang Yuan's appearance made them feel intense lingering fear and also a sense of pity for Yang San Mu — why was he so unlucky as to face the great demon Fang Yuan? He could have stayed in the formation but he chose to go out, wasn't he courting death?

But silence did not last long, someone shouted immediately: "This Fang Yuan is as vicious as ever, he lured Lord Yang San Mu out, thankfully, we were led by lords Xia Fan and Chi Qiu, under their leadership, we managed to hold our ground and did not give this scoundrel a chance to sneak in."

The immortals all had varying expressions, someone wanted to speak when suddenly, the world shook, the entire immortal formation started trembling intensely.

Outside the immortal formation, countless silver scales filled the sky. Myriad dragons flew and charged at the white formation.

The Southern Border immortals' expressions also turned pale from the reflection of the silver scales' light.

Fang Yuan's immortal killer move myriad dragon was like a tsunami, even though they were protected by the immortal formation, they felt extremely small and weak.

Fang Yuan's myriad dragon did not get much more powerful than before, but with myriad self Immortal Gu, it was far easier to use myriad dragon now. When activating it, the steps were fewer and the success rate was higher, the time it took Fang Yuan to use myriad dragon once or twice before was enough to unleash it five to six times now!

Fang Yuan continued to use myriad dragon, countless ancient sword dragons charged at the formation, causing the formation to explode with greater force.

Pure white light ripples spread like waves or the contours of mountains, blocking the attack of the myriad dragons.

"Interesting." Fang Yuan observed carefully, even though the immortal formation was shaking, its roots were not shaken, as he increased the power of his attacks, so did the defensive power of the immortal formation.

"We have the Gu formation, we should last for some time." A Southern Border Gu Immortal said in uncertainty as he looked at Chi Qiu.

Chi Qiu's gaze was flickering intensely, currently, the immortal formation was keeping them safe, but!

The other party was not ordinary, he was Fang Yuan!

The demonic path overlord that Heavenly Court could not deal with even after pursuing him for so long!

"Everyone, seek help from your clans, tell them Fang Yuan is here, quick! Do you think this formation can block such a person?" Chi Qiu sighed.

The immortals saw that Chi Qiu was very anxious, they did not wait but started to seek reinforcements.

Earlier, Fang Yuan did not state his identity, he was just a rank seven Gu Immortal, how could the Southern Border Gu Immortals ask for help? They only reported this battle normally.

But now that Fang Yuan exposed his identity, these Gu Immortals started to ask for help openly and loudly.

Roar…

The dragons roared as Fang Yuan attacked, the immortal formation blocked him with all its strength, it was also increasing in power.

"Block him, even if we die, we must block him!"

"The western part of the formation is broken, quickly repair it."

"I don't have enough immortal essence, who will replace me?"

The Southern Border immortals blocked him desperately, due to the strong pressure from Fang Yuan, these immortals stopped scheming against each other, they were truly united.

Chi Qiu tried to fix the Gu formation while Xia Fan spat out blood multiple times, in order to try and deduce the flaws of myriad dragon, he had given it his all.

They were rank seven Gu Immortals but they were like this, the rank six Gu Immortals were in far worse conditions.

Outside the immortal formation, Fang Yuan crossed his arms as he watched quietly, he was calm as a breeze.

After having myriad self Immortal Gu, the killer move myriad dragon was much more usable, it was no longer his strongest method, it was a killer move that could be used conventionally and regularly.

Fang Yuan's strongest method was now an immemorial yama child's soul explosion. But he did not have any immemorial soul beasts to modify now. He had already used both immemorial yama children, one to kill Feng Jiu Ge and the other to kill Lang Ya land spirit, but neither succeeded.

As for an ancient yama child's soul explosion, it was similar in power to myriad dragon, but it was amplified by yama battlefield and would be slightly stronger.

Thus, Fang Yuan used this method to attack the immortal formation.

Intense winds blew, Fang Yuan floated in the air, looking at the dragons attacking this formation.

His demonic might was already developed, right now, he singlehandedly suppressed Southern Border's Gu Immortals, they were busy defending against his barrage of attacks.

However, Fang Yuan frowned lightly.

It was taking quite a while. Fang Yuan needed some more time to break this immortal formation.

Fang Yuan still had three methods left, but reverse flow protection seal could not be used against the immortal formation. This formation got stronger as the attacks targeted at it got stronger, reverse flow protection seal could not reflect anything.

Lead soul into dream had failed against Heavenly Court once before, measures had been taken against it when they fought Lord Huang Shi. Lead soul into dream needed to sense the target's soul, but these Southern Border Gu Immortals were hidden in the formation, Fang Yuan could not sense them.

As for great thief ghost hand, it could not be used, the immortal formation was hidden behind the white light in multiple layers, great thief ghost hand was unable to get close.

"Lord Chi Qu You!" At this time, inside the immortal formation, Southern Border's immortals received a surge of morale.

The reason was simple, Chi clan's first supreme elder, rank eight formation path Gu Immortal Chi Qu You, had arrived in secret.

"To think that this immortal formation had this hidden pathway in it, allowing a rank eight existence tens of thousands of li away to teleport here! The clan truly put in a lot of effort into this." Chi Qiu praised in his mind.

This hidden pathway was left by Chi Qu You just in case a situation like the dream realm battle occurred again. In that situation, Chi clan, which had access to the hidden pathway, would have a huge advantage.

And now, Fang Yuan suddenly attacked, Chi Qu You thought about it and decided to expose this hidden trump card.

"Continue controlling the immortal formation, act like you cannot last long, I will make an arrangement to lure this demon into my trap." Chi Qu You smiled.

Fang Yuan had lots of treasures on him and was a demonic path overlord, Heavenly Court had a huge headache against him. If Chi Qu You could use formation path to capture Fang Yuan or kill him, not only could he gain a lot of loot, he could also raise his reputation to the limit, he could also use this matter to raise Chi clan's ranking in the Southern Border righteous path by several levels.

Even though Fang Yuan had great achievements, Chi Qu You was a formation path great grandmaster and had rank eight cultivation level, he was extremely confident in his formation path attainment,after learning about this, he came here to take Fang Yuan's life. Any other rank eight Gu Immortal who did not cultivate formation path would not have Chi Qu You's advantage and ease.

With Chi Qu You as the mastermind, Southern Border's immortals had a huge surge of confidence, they started to contest with Fang Yuan patiently.

Chi Qu You had formation path Immortal Gu, his methods were very quickly set up, he soon created a formation inside the immortal formation. This was Chi Qu You's expertise to begin with.

But when he was about to succeed, Fang Yuan suddenly stopped and left the battlefield using Fixed Immortal Travel.

"Did he sense me?" Chi Qu You frowned, but he thought about how he vigilantly created the Gu formation, he did not expose anything. The chance of that was low, so why did Fang Yuan retreat?

"This is contact heart river bank?" Jade light flickered as Fang Yuan appeared in the sky.

He looked down, the surrounding hundreds of li were covered in mountains, only the land below him was flat with fog in it, it could not be seen clearly.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, using myriad dragon killer move again.

Myriad dragons attacked as the fog rose, clashing with each other.

But soon, the fog could not stand up to Fang Yuan's attacks and faded, exposing the true terrain.

A shallow deep blue lake surrounded by silent verdant mountains. Around the lake were pure white round rocks, they stacked at the river bank.

On the river bank, there were a large number of wisdom path contact heart Gu, there was also the obvious aura left behind by some Chi clan rank six Gu Immortal.

Fang Yuan did not chase them, he looked at contact heart river bank and grabbed, starting his plunder!

Information that contact heart river bank had been robbed soon got to Chi Qu You, this was Chi clan's resource point, even though there was a Gu formation, the defense was not as strong, Fang Yuan easily took it over.

Chapter 1590: Cloud Bamboo Mountain Range

"Come." Fang Yuan floated in the air as he opened his immortal aperture's entrance.

A large number of wild contact heart Gu were drawn by a gentle force, gathering in the air like a beautiful colored cloud, entering Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

The process lasted for several minutes.

Fang Yuan estimated: "More than three thousand are rank five contact heart Gu, fifty thousand are rank four, and over a million are rank three and below."

Contact heart Gu resembled colored yuhua stones, they had different colors and shapes according to their rank. It was a wisdom path Gu worm that could steal the opponent's concentration and make them enter a daze, losing the ability to perceive and think. If combined with other relevant Gu worms, it could form killer moves. Contact heart Gu had a lot of value in combat, the most usual method was to supplement it with enslavement path methods to enhance the enslavement ability. Of course, wisdom path Gu Masters used it too, but wisdom path was a rare and mysterious path.

Gu Masters face difficulty in raising Gu, most of them had less than ten Gu at once. But for Gu Immortals, they could get tens of thousands of mortal Gu easily, only Immortal Gu were hard to get.

Fang Yuan's situation was simply a rare exception.

"Contact heart river bank is a mid-sized resource point, I attacked and destroyed the Gu formation here, while the defending Gu Immortal escaped for their life without destroying the contact heart Gu, this was why I could obtain this wealth."

If the defending Gu Immortal took away or destroyed the contact heart Gu before leaving, Fang Yuan's gains would be greatly reduced.

That Gu Immortal must have exerted all their effort to block Fang Yuan, they could not distract themselves by storing the contact heart Gu. When they left, they either had no method or lacked the resolve to destroy this place.

After storing the contact heart Gu, Fang Yuan's gaze returned to the river bank.

Rank six strength path Immortal Gu — Pulling Water.

He activated this Immortal Gu, the river water was pulled up like silk by a formless force, before being moved into Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

This contact heart river bank was a special area filled with wisdom path dao marks, there were earth path, water path, wood path, and other dao marks as foundation, but they paled in quantity compared to wisdom path.

Fang Yuan took away the water, but the dense wisdom path dao marks still remained here.

"It is a pity that most of the wisdom path dao marks are on this land." Fang Yuan sighed to himself.

There was no helping it.

Even though he had pulling mountain Immortal Gu, it was targeted at mountains, not land.

"I'll bring the rocks with me." Contact heart river bank's rocks were filled with wisdom path dao marks too, they were excellent materials. Fang Yuan brought them along.

He took everything that he could take.

A moment later, he used rank seven Fixed Immortal Travel to leave this place, leaving behind a ransacked resource point.

Fang Yuan was currently being pursued, he could not stay at a place for long. Otherwise, his enemies would be able to encircle and plot against him.

Thus, when he attacked Plunder Shadow Earth Trench earlier and was blocked by the formation, he retreated wisely, it was not because he found out about Chi Qu You's scheme.

Fang Yuan focused his mind as he used Fixed Immortal Travel, crossing an enormous distance, arriving above a mountain.

This mountain range was majestic and huge with curved contours. There were no trees on it, only bamboos. These bamboos were very thick and each were the size of giant trees. The leaves of the bamboo were triangular with a long base and sharp tip, the tips were thin and sharp but tough, many mortals would pluck these leaves and tie them to wooden rods to create wooden spears. This was also why this bamboo was called spear tip bamboo.

The spear tip bamboo forest was huge and covered the entire mountain range. There were many lifeforms living in the bamboo forest, it was filled with vitality. Most had cloud path dao marks, the highest quantity group was the cloud fox. This fox had snow white skin and could float in the air temporarily. Right now, Fang Yuan could see a group of cloud foxes floating around in the bamboo forest, playing with each other happily, it was a serene sight.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone: "This is cloud bamboo mountain range, a large resource point under Chi clan's control."

The super forces of the five regions controlled resource points, classified into five groups, mini, small, middle, large, and giant.

Fang Yuan's dragonfish sea area in sovereign immortal aperture was a giant resource point, it could produce copper, iron, silver, and gold dragonfish. It was Fang Yuan's most important source of revenue now.

"Oh, oh no, the demon Fang Yuan is here!"

"Plunder Shadow Earth Trench was attacked, contact heart river bank was taken by him, to think that he would come to cloud bamboo mountain range at this crucial moment. Sigh."

The two Chi clan rank six Gu Immortals defending the place saw Fang Yuan and were flustered.

Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel to arrive here, there was a huge disturbance as Fang Yuan did not conceal himself, Chi clan's two Gu Immortals immediately noticed it.

The two Gu Immortals were currently deep within the mountain range, there was a huge spear tip bamboo in front of them, it was over twenty meters tall, the bamboo was so large that even ten grown men could not surround it with their arms.

And inside this giant bamboo, an Immortal Gu was being nurtured.

Indeed, a wild Immortal Gu was about to form here!

Chi clan's two Gu Immortals were putting their focus here while defending cloud bamboo mountain range, Immortal Gu were unique, this wood path Immortal Gu that was about to form was the most important thing in cloud bamboo mountain range.

Boom boom boom!

Fang Yuan waved his sleeves, sending out sparks and smoke. The two Chi clan Gu Immortals sighed together, activating the Gu formation to block Fang Yuan's attacks.

Chi clan was most skilled at formation path, while Chi Qu You was a formation path great grandmaster who could use natural dao marks and mortal Gu to create immortal formations.

Thus, Chi clan's resource points all had immortal formations, and these resource points had something in similar, they were all dense with dao marks!

As Fang Yuan attacked, jade green light appeared on cloud bamboo mountain range that blocked Fang Yuan's attacks. Countless spear tip bamboos started shaking as leaves shot out with intense winds, it was like a tornado of countless spears that shot at Fang Yuan with great intensity.

"This immortal formation is not only larger than the one at contact heart river bank, it can even retaliate." Fang Yuan smiled, using reverse flow protection seal.

The bamboo leaves landed on his body and were all sent back to attack the immortal formation without question.

"This is reverse flow protection seal! Quick, quick, stop the retaliation method." The two rank six Gu Immortals panicked before encouraging each other: "The Immortal Gu is about to form, it is a few minutes away from completion, we need to wait for the clan's reinforcements."

The immortal formation was manipulated by them and stopped attacking, it focused on defense.

Fang Yuan could not reverse its attacks anymore but he smiled nonchalantly, dispelling reverse flow protection seal.

He activated myriad dragon killer move again, sending a barrage of attacks at the immortal formation.

The immortal formation shook intensely, the two rank six Gu Immortals were sweating profusely, gritting their teeth as they spat out blood, defending themselves desperately.

After a while, Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance as he found a flaw of this formation.

Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level was at grandmaster after all!

He noticed this flaw and started attacking it.

After a while, cloud bamboo mountain range's immortal formation exploded intensely as a portion of the green light covering the mountain range dissipated suddenly.

"Oh no, he destroyed a portion of the immortal formation!"

"Hang on, reinforcements are coming."

The two Chi clan rank sixes were greatly shocked.

Fang Yuan sent out attacks again, creating explosions on the defenseless cloud bamboo mountains.

Yama child soul explosion!

He found that soul explosion was more suited for destroying the immortal formation, he used it without hesitation.

The start was the most difficult, after creating a hole in the cloud bamboo immortal formation, the difficulty reduced drastically, Fang Yuan made good use of the weakness.

The two Chi clan Gu Immortals' dreams did not come true.

Fang Yuan's dismantling speed became faster and faster, he destroyed more and more of the formation until he reached the Chi clan Gu Immortals.

"It's too late, let's retreat!"

"What about the Immortal Gu? We are only a few minutes away from its creation."

"Leave, we will lose our lives if we stay."

The other Gu Immortal jolted into realization as he wiped his sweat: "You're right, we'll leave! What about the Immortal Gu?"

The Gu Immortal companion struggled for a moment before gritting his teeth: "Destroy it!"

Chapter 1591: Plunder and Development

Boom!

Fang Yuan waved his sleeves, black smoke spread out to the surroundings, he had used soul explosion.

This was a rank seven peak method, it immediately destroyed the core of the immortal formation on cloud bamboo mountain range that Chi clan had created with ease.

Rumble!

There was another explosion as the formation's core broke apart, the other areas of the immortal formation also collapsed.

At this point, the entire mountain range's formation was destroyed.

"They left after all." Looking at the empty place, Fang Yuan's gaze was dark and unsurprised at all.

His attack on the formation earlier was met with great resistance that was quite skillful. But later on, Fang Yuan noticed that the immortal formation was getting more slow in reacting to his actions.

Immortal formations and Immortal Gu Houses needed people to manipulate them. Even wills or formation spirits left behind could not replace the use of a Gu Immortal.

"Oh? An Immortal Gu was destroyed here?" Fang Yuan soon noticed a special aura. He confirmed quickly that there was an incomplete Immortal Gu here, Chi clan's Gu Immortals had destroyed it before leaving.

Fang Yuan sighed in pity, but he admired their resolution. He would have done the same thing.

There was nothing valuable at the core area, Fang Yuan flew into the sky and started to ransack cloud bamboo mountain range.

Cloud bamboo mountain range had a large number of cloud path lifeforms.

Like the cloud fox.

Fang Yuan used an enslavement path method as orange-yellow light burst out of his bodys, shrouding all the surroundings.

Within the light, cloud foxes and other lifeforms struggled intensely, they had a painful expression as they growled. But soon, their resistance weakened as they stopped moving, they stayed on the spot as they became Fang Yuan's enslaved beasts.

Fang Yuan opened his immortal aperture door as these lifeforms gathered and went into sovereign immortal aperture like a flowing river.

Fang Yuan continued his actions as a large number of lifeforms entered his immortal aperture.

Suddenly, there was a sudden sound as two desolate beast cloud foxes emerged, running towards the outside of the mountain in a panic.

"Come back!" Fang Yuan laughed, flying as he chased them, using his enslavement path killer move to make these two desolate beast cloud foxes sprawl and admit him as their master.

Cloud bamboo mountain range was a huge large sized resource point, it was filled with dense dao marks, it was normal for desolate beasts and plants to grow here, even ancient desolate beasts could grow. Immortal Gu were rarer, there was one but it was destroyed before it could form.

After Fang Yuan finished his exploration, he obtained seven desolate beast cloud foxes, a total of eleven desolate plants of three species, cloud qi root, white hair root, and spear tip bamboo. The thing that made Fang Yuan the happiest was the quantity of a rank seven immortal material, cloud soil, it was huge.

However, he did not see any ancient desolate beasts or ancient desolate plants.

"The Gu Immortals guarding this place must have brought them away, or maybe they never existed."

According to the laws of nature, there was a possibility of ancient desolate beasts or plants appearing here. But this place was governed by Chi clan for countless years, they were skilled at formation path but lacked enslavement path expertise. They would not allow an uncontrollable ancient desolate beast that could rival rank seven Gu Immortals to stay in their territory..

Fang Yuan did not mind it, he continued to search the entire mountain for spear tip bamboos.

These spear tip bamboos were ordinary Gu materials, the desolate plant spear tip bamboos had already been completely taken by Fang Yuan.

But it was quite troublesome now.

Fang Yuan had rich enslavement path methods but he could not use many wood path methods due to his lack of wood path Immortal Gu.

"I need an appropriate wood path method to relocate these spear tip bamboos." Fang Yuan sighed.

If he wanted to move these spear tip bamboos, he would need delicate wood path methods. Methods of other paths would carve different dao marks on these bamboos, even temporary ones would damage the spear tip bamboos and reduce their quality.

Actually, Spectral Soul's true inheritance had lots of wood path methods, but Fang Yuan did not have the necessary wood path Immortal Gu.

Thus, he could only use mortal methods to take these spear tip bamboos.

But this lowered his efficiency greatly, far worse than immortal killer moves. And this cloud bamboo mountain range was huge, the amount of spear tip bamboos that Fang Yuan had taken were still very insignificant.

"A pity that pulling mountain Immortal Gu is only rank six, even though it can pull mountains, it cannot move the entire mountain range."

In the past, Fang Yuan had pulled up Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley, but it was because these two secluded domains of heaven and earth was modified by Spectral Soul Demon Venerable using the killer move orderly well.

Cloud bamboo mountain range did not have such a treatment.

Of course, Fang Yuan could smash the mountain range but the results from that would not be under his control.

Trees had tree roots, mountains had mountain roots, unless he had an appropriate earth path method, he could not preserve these mountain roots.

"What? Fang Yuan is attacking cloud bamboo mountain range!" Chi Qu You's frowned deeply, he had a grim expression.

He was the first supreme elder of Chi clan, information had gotten to him at the very first moment.

The contact heart river bank earlier was a middle sized resource point, the losses were not too big. But cloud bamboo mountain range was a large resource point!

"In the past, our clan paid a hefty price to invite an earth path great expert to move the mountain veins and develop cloud bamboo mountain range, only forming scale similar to today after a hundred years. To think that it would be targeted now."

Chi clan was a super force, it had many large resource points, but cloud bamboo mountain range was quite a unique one.

Back when Chi clan was still in its infancy period, Chi clan's ancestors had scrimped and saved when they were weak to slowly develop it.

In Chi clan's history, this cloud bamboo mountain range provided Chi clan a steady source of income over time and did not disappoint its initial creators.

After generations of hard work, the clan got stronger and its territory expanded continuously. Even though they had many large resource points now, and cloud bamboo mountain range became less important, it was never neglected, it was always guarded by two Gu Immortals.

Cloud bamboo mountain range was not just a resource point, it was a form of mental encouragement to Chi clan's members.

"Forget about other large resource points, but cloud bamboo mountain range cannot be destroyed. Mobilize the Immortal Gu House, find Fang Yuan and take back cloud bamboo mountain range!" Chi Qu You thought about it for a moment before ordering with a firm tone.

"What about you, first supreme elder?" Chi clan's Gu Immortal asked.

Chi Qu You snorted: "Fang Yuan seems to know that I am here, his true motive is to take the dream realms here! I will stay guard here, he will definitely come again. Of course, you all must put up a facade that I am going to find him personally."

Thus, Chi clan moved its Immortal Gu House and went to cloud bamboo mountain range.

Fang Yuan had not left yet, he was still collecting spear tip bamboos. This bamboo had very deep roots of fifty to sixty feet, specific methods were needed to relocate them into his immortal aperture without any damage.

Chi clan's Gu Immortals saw Fang Yuan and hesitated, this was cloud bamboo mountain range, if they fought against Fang Yuan here without any immortal formation's protection, cloud bamboo mountain range might get destroyed.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

Fang Yuan was already prepared, his great thief ghost hand had been lurking for a while, it directly targeted Chi clan's Immortal Gu House.

Inside sovereign immortal aperture.

At the north-most end of Mini Northern Plains, snow was falling as frost energy permeated.

The snowmen had traveled for a long time, they finally arrived at their destination.

The cold weather made the snowmen reveal smiles of joy.

"This is a good place for us to live."

"This place is so huge, we will not have to crowd around like before."

"Thanks to great immortal Bing Zhuo's guidance. Sob sob sob…"

Some elderly snowmen were already kneeling on the ground, sobbing profusely.

"Quickly look!" Someone shouted.

The snowmen raised their heads and saw a scene they would never forget. The huge blizzard suddenly stopped as three huge crystal mountains appeared from within the fog. Gu Immortal 'Bing Zhuo' floated in the air as he nodded at them, before the fog gathered and concealed the three mountains again.

"It's great immortal Bing Zhuo!"

"This is the home that great immortal has guided us to — Triple Sacred Mountain."

"It seems that the immortals of our tribe live on Triple Sacred Mountain!"

The snowmen were very excited, they knelt down and prayed towards the direction of Triple Sacred Mountain.

They did not know that 'great immortal Bing Zhuo' concealed by the fog turned back into a stranger, he was Fang Yuan's time path clone.

"Food, environment, and plants, they are all set up already, even though the environment is plain, it is enough for them to live."

"At this point, the snowman relocation is finally completed."

The time path clone nodded lightly as he controlled the snow crystal formation, looking at another area.

Over there, a group of snow monsters emerged from the snow, looking around curiously as they moved around.

"Not bad, under the effect of the snow crystal formation, snow monsters are forming too. This snow monster production line is starting to work. In time, it will bring me huge profits."

After leaving Mini Northern Plains, the time path clone arrived at Mini Central Continent.

Not long ago, he had set up a river bank here, he directly copied the name of contact heart river bank.

On the river bank, there were countless white round rocks of varying sizes.

There was a river with flowing water, contact heart Gu lived inside it.

Fang Yuan obtained a large number of contact heart Gu, he sold most of them in treasure yellow heaven. The remaining river water, rocks, and a small number of contact heart Gu were left as seeds. In time, he could develop this into a source of revenue too.

The time path clone flew again, towards the southeast of contact heart river bank, he only stopped after a while.

It was a barren land without any lifeforms.

Time path clone started to plant spear tip bamboos here while releasing the cloud foxes and other beasts.

There was no mountain range here, but Fang Yuan planned to start building a cloud bamboo forest here.

Chapter 1592: Number Nine in the World, Great Space Temple

Southern Border.

Fang Yuan broke into cloud bamboo mountain range and scavenged it, but he knew about the significance of this resource point, he was ready for Chi clan's counterattack.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

His great thief ghost hand that had been lurking for a while directly targeted Chi clan's Immortal Gu House.

The Chi clan Gu Immortals in the Immortal Gu House were shocked.

But immediately, the Immortal Gu House's surface shined with a dazzling golden light, the surface of the Immortal Gu House had ripples that formed into a spiral, absorbing great thief ghost hand into it.

At the next moment, the spiral vanished without a trace, Fang Yuan grunted as he lost his connection to great thief ghost hand.

Bright light shined in his eyes for a moment: "As expected of one of the top ten Immortal Gu Houses, Great Space Temple!"

Chi clan had two Immortal Gu Houses, they were both extraordinary, Great Space Temple was the stronger one, able to resist rank eight Gu Immortals!

From the outside, it looked like it was made of marble, it was pure white and round, there were golden accents on it, it radiated with sunlight and was extremely grand, giving people a feeling of warmth and hope.

In the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, during the five regions chaotic war, all the different forces competed with each other as the world went into chaos, Immortal Gu Houses were mobilized often and fought against each other. With ample battles, people started to learn of the strength of different Immortal Gu Houses, they were able to create a ranking list for the Immortal Gu Houses.

Chi clan's Great Space Temple was ranked ninth on this list, it was not simple.

It had one move called moving space domain, it could trap rank eight Gu Immortals. When Heavenly Court attacked Southern Border, this Immortal Gu House trapped four rank sevens and two rank eights, it had an extremely incredible use in that battle.

"I'm afraid that great thief ghost hand is trapped inside moving space domain, that's how I lost contact with it. But the usage of moving space domain has a huge price, it needs time for preparation. How did they respond so quickly? They seem very prepared?" Fang Yuan's thoughts moved rapidly in his mind, he quickly saw a problem.

"There really was such a theft path method!"

"Demon Fang Yuan is getting harder to deal with, thankfully we were amply prepared."

"We only made it in time due to Heavenly Court's intel. If he really succeeded in stealing the Immortal Gu of this Immortal Gu House, what would happen?"

Chi clan's Gu Immortals felt deep after-fear and relief.

"Kill!"

"Prepare moving space domain for demon Fang Yuan's theft path method."

"But we need to be careful, this demon Fang Yuan has a defensive killer move made using Reverse Flow River."

Rumble!

Under the Chi clan Gu Immortals' manipulation, rank eight Immortal Gu House Great Space Temple erupted with fearsome might, quickly suppressing Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan retreated while his mind entered treasure yellow heaven.

At the next moment, his heart shook. Like he had expected, Heavenly Court had placed a clip in treasure yellow heaven, showing the fight scene earlier. His usage of great thief ghost hand against Feng Jiu Ge was also exposed.

Not just that, Heavenly Court also released a lot of deduction results that were free for everyone to view.

These deductions were all about Fang Yuan, they were exposing his secrets.

In treasure yellow heaven, there were lots of commotion. The Gu Immortals in the five regions were very shocked, they were discussing his methods and Gu worms, they felt deep envy and jealousy towards Fang Yuan's resources.

This was a huge blow!

Intel of Gu Immortals was usually very crucial. In most cases, once Immortal Gu and killer moves were exposed, they would be easily countered by others.

Like now, not only did Chi clan defend against great thief ghost hand, they even trapped it inside moving space domain. They were going to research on this great thief ghost hand and trace it back to the source, exposing more weaknesses of this move.

If they were not guarded and Fang Yuan succeeded, he might be able to steal a few Immortal Gu and earn a fortune, and even gain an advantage.

Fang Yuan had used treasure yellow heaven to show himself thrashing Thunder Ghost True Monarch and it deeply affected Heavenly Court's prestige. They were merely giving him a taste of his own medicine now, dealing with Fang Yuan using the same method.

"I have great thief ghost hand, Fairy Zi Wei must be very worried that I would use this move to steal more Immortal Gu and strengthen myself!"

"Since she could distract herself to do this, I'm afraid Lang Ya blessed land's battle has ended."

Fang Yuan's heart shook.

He wanted Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven to fight to the death, it was best if Lang Ya blessed land got destroyed. But both sides were very smart, they would not do something so stupid.

"I'm afraid that Heavenly Court took the initiative to retreat. After all, in order to deal with Lang Ya blessed land, Fairy Zi Wei, Chen Yi and the rest were all injured to some degree. Feng Jiu Ge had lost his battle strength after fighting me, Thunder Ghost True Monarch died from battle… while Longevity Heaven has Lang Ya land spirit's help, they have the absolute advantage."

Another thing Fang Yuan noticed was that Prince Feng Xian's traitor identity was not exposed yet.

"Prince Feng Xian might possibly be hiding near Loose Tail Ridge, waiting for a chance."

"It seems that Heavenly Court is very prepared, even without Prince Feng Xian, they managed to escape."

Fang Yuan was not foolish enough to expose Prince Feng Xian's identity in advance.

Heavenly Court knew that Fang Yuan was an otherworldly demon that had reborn, but they did not know that Prince Feng Xian's identity was already known to Fang Yuan.

"Right now, I have no evidence to testify against Prince Feng Xian. Actually, even if I have solid evidence, Prince Feng Xian is still a rank eight Gu Immortal, Longevity Heaven will have a tough time dealing with him, if they do not prepare amply, he might even escape."

Fang Yuan had to make good use of this, he might be able to reap great benefits in the future. Using it now would just be venting his anger, a successful person would have deep tolerance, how could he be swayed by emotions and act foolishly?

"However, I cannot let all of you off either!" Fang Yuan sneered, he immediately sent a video clip into treasure yellow heaven.

This video recorded Heavenly Court using star cast and sending multiple rank eight Gu Immortals into Lang Ya blessed land.

It was like a huge rock tossed into a lake, it created huge ripples and waves!

Heavenly Court had such a method?!

It was like Fang Yuan's Fixed Immortal Travel, the incredibly useful effect could influence important battles!

Other than Central Continent, the Gu Immortals of the other four regions and leaders of super forces felt greatly shocked, their alertness towards Heavenly Court rose to an incredible degree.

"Goodbye." Fang Yuan smiled as he waved at Great Space Temple. At the next moment, he used the opportunity to activate Fixed Immortal Travel, escaping successfully.

Rank seven Fixed Immortal Travel was too useful!

Great Space Temple was not an immortal battlefield, even if it contained an immortal battlefield killer move, Fang Yuan would not let himself be trapped easily.

Even if he was trapped, many immortal battlefields could not contain Fixed Immortal Travel.

Unless it was an incredible method or countered Fixed Immortal Travel, Fang Yuan then would be in trouble when he gets trapped.

At the next moment, jade light flickered as Fang Yuan arrived at Chi clan's third resource point.

Wind Flame Mountain!

This mountain had countless sunset parasol trees, the leaves were red like fire. There were many birds and barely any land beasts, a small number of fire phoenixes were resting inside the parasol forest. Sensing Fang Yuan's animosity, these phoenixes raised their heads and looked at Fang Yuan fearlessly, they had an aura of indomitability!

This giant resource point was rare even for super forces, it was one of Chi clan's most important sources of revenue.

"Demon Fang Yuan is here!" A rank seven from Chi clan was here, they first activated the defensive immortal formation before reporting to the clan, seeking reinforcements.

"If I can take down this resource point, Chi clan would really feel heartache. Hehe." Fang Yuan laughed coldly as he charged down and crashed like a meteor.

With an intense explosion, the immortal formation remained unmoved. Giant resource points had far greater defenses compared to middle and large resource points.

Fang Yuan stopped his movement as his gaze flickered with uncertainty, he rapidly deduced in his mind while using countless killer moves like they were cheap fireworks.

"Scoundrel Fang Yuan, you are so devious!" After receiving news of this, Chi Qu You was extremely furious, he could no longer stay, he left and went to reinforce the resource point.

Wind Flame Mountain was quite a unique resource point, other than raising phoenixes, at a certain timing each year, many wild phoenixes would come here and lay eggs.

If something happened to Wind Flame Mountain, the wild phoenixes might choose other locations, Chi clan would suffer great losses.

But Wind Flame Mountain was very far from cloud bamboo mountain range, Chi Qu You was the closest to it. Even though this Chi clan first supreme elder had already set up the formation in Plunder Shadow Earth Trench, he had to give up on that plan and save his resource point from Fang Yuan.

When he arrived, Fang Yuan had already broken up more than half of the formation of Wind Flame Mountain, many ancient phoenixes also died, Fang Yuan even captured three.

"Fang Yuan, you scoundrel, don't run if you have the guts!" Chi Qu You screamed in anger.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly as he greeted politely: "Senior Chi Qu You, we finally meet."

Chapter 1593: Transaction

"You want to meet me so urgently, it seems you really want to die." Chi Qu You snickered.

"First supreme elder is here, I'm saved!" The Chi clan Gu Immortal defending Wind Flame Mountain felt great ease as he shouted.

"I waited specially for you, are you interested in the dream path results that I have?" Fang Yuan suddenly transmitted in secret.

Chi Qu You was slightly dazed.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan pointed with his finger as immortal battlefield killer move yama battlefield formed and trapped Chi Qu You in it.

Chi Qu You was slightly shocked but he soon calmed down, he even looked around the battlefield calmly: "This is the battlefield that trapped Feng Jiu Ge?"

Fang Yuan laughed loudly: "Senior Chi wants to say, is this the immortal battlefield that Fairy Zi Wei broke?"

Heavenly Court not only exposed Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand in treasure yellow heaven, they even released their understanding of yama battlefield and even the way to break it publicly.

Thus, with this information, Chi Qu You was not worried. He was not even anxious at all, as a formation path great grandmaster, he could defend himself inside yama battlefield. Meanwhile, Fang Yuan had limited time, if the righteous path Gu Immortals could encircle him, he would be in trouble.

There were no invincible Gu in this world, only invincible Gu Immortals, Fixed Immortal Travel could be countered in many ways.

Compared to that, Chi Qu You's bigger headache was that after Fang Yuan leaves, he would continue targeting Chi clan's resource points. That was a huge problem.

"Take a look, senior Chi." Fang Yuan tossed an information path mortal Gu over.

Chi Qu You took a look, it was truly an information path mortal Gu, he looked into it and his gaze flickered.

This information path mortal Gu recorded details about the formation that Chi clan had set up on Wind Flame Mountain. As a formation path grandmaster who had the light of wisdom, it was not hard to make such deductions.

Chi Qu You instantly understood Fang Yuan's intention.

According to the info in this information path mortal Gu, Fang Yuan could totally destroy the immortal formation on Wind Flame Mountain, but he purposely chose not to and waited for Chi Qu You's arrival.

Chi Qu You nodded: "You are indeed a genius, your formation path attainment is so high, no wonder Chi Shang acknowledged you."

Formation devotee Chi Shang was a rising star of Chi clan, he was recognized by Chi Qu You as a future formation path great grandmaster. Earlier, Fang Yuan disguised as Wu Yi Hai and interacted with him, they built a good relationship. When Fang Yuan got exposed and was pursued by everyone, Chi Shang publicly announced that he was an enemy of Fang Yuan, putting a clear line between them.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly before looking at Chi Qu You solemnly: "What if I told senior that my formation path attainment level was obtained from the dream realm, what do you think?"

"Oh? Is that true?!" Chi Qu You was moved, he assessed Fang Yuan again as he said with a questioning tone: "You really want to transact with me?"

Fang Yuan retorted: "Why not? I need dream realms, but Southern Border's dream realms have defensive formations made by Chi clan. I want to use dream path gains to exchange for Chi clan's cooperation. To display my sincerity, I want you to see this."

Fang Yuan tossed out another information path mortal Gu, Chi Qu You received it and his gaze flickered, he unconsciously grasped the information path mortal Gu in his hand, as if afraid that it would fly off.

Information regarding dream path had an incredible attraction to Chi Qu You, he quickly looked into it.

When he raised his head, he looked at Fang Yuan with a different expression.

"As expected of the one who used Spring Autumn Cicada to rebirth and had inherited Shadow Sect, the amount of dream path information that he is willing to release already far exceeds the total amount of research our Southern Border's righteous path has done!"

"Furthermore, this is only a small part of the information, a lot of things are missing, there is even some vague content not explained in detail."

Thinking of this, Chi Qu You was deeply moved.

He had to be moved!

Fang Yuan's bait was simply too attractive to him!!

Currently, the Gu Immortal world agreed that dream path would be greatly developed in the future. Not only would dream path be created, it would prosper and create Great Dream Immortal Venerable. Thus, be it super forces or rank eight Gu Immortals, they knew the importance of dream path, they explored dream realms and tried to advance further in this path than anyone else.

Whoever gave up on pursuing dream path would be left behind by this upcoming great era!

It was like how Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created theft path, Reckless Savage Demon Venerable created transformation path, Primordial Origin Immortal Venerable created qi path… in the long history of humanity, countless experiences had proven this point.

However, the start was the most difficult, dream path was only a concept now, no matter who explored it, they would have to pay a huge price with little gains.

Because he knew this, Chi Qu You understood that this information path mortal Gu was extremely valuable. If it was revealed to the outside world, all the super forces would fight for it, even if they had to fight until blood flowed into a river, they would do it without hesitation!

Chi Qu You caressed the information path mortal Gu in his hand as he looked at Fang Yuan with a sharp gaze: "I can see your sincerity, but there are many Southern Border righteous path forces, why did you choose me?"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "I have interacted with Chi Shang before, I also have Shadow Sect's and Wu clan's information, I know a lot about Chi clan. Chi Bang is your son, but he lacks the ability to become the first supreme elder, that was why you needed Chi Shang, the future formation path great grandmaster, to help him. Senior Chi, you have limited lifespan, when you die and chaos starts, can Chi Bang protect Chi clan?"

"You!" Chi Qu You's expression turned dark, killing intent leaked out of him, but Fang Yuan was completely ignoring it.

Chi Qu You had no choice but to admit Fang Yuan was right.

Southern Border's earth veins were shaking, such situations occurred in the other four regions too, a person at Chi Qu You's level could also sense the chaos of the future.

Chi Qu You had already used many lifespan extension methods, lifespan Gu were not effective on him anymore. He had already started preparing long ago, for the sake of his son's succession.

Even though he knew that Chi Bang lacked talent, as a father, he had his selfish side. But he could not be selfish entirely. If Chi clan was destroyed in Chi Bang's hands, even if Chi Qu You died, he would not rest in peace. And if Chi clan was destroyed, would Chi Bang be safe?

Therefore, Chi clan needed Fang Yuan's dream path gains, with this, Chi clan would be able to protect itself in the future, it would also ride the tide of the great era and become an even stronger super force!

"Hahaha." Chi Qu You suddenly laughed loudly as if his killing intent never existed. He looked at Fang Yuan and shook his head: "Fang Yuan, you are truly the number one demonic figure of the five regions. I have finally seen your true abilities today, no wonder Heavenly Court and Wu clan were helpless against you. I will accept this transaction!"

Fang Yuan nodded, Chi Qu You's response was within his expectations, there was nothing peculiar.

Chi Qu You was the leader of a righteous path force, while Fang Yuan was a demon that everyone was after, how could they make a deal? This seemed quite unthinkable.

But actually, for the terms righteous path and demonic path, everyone had their own understanding of it. The central thing that mattered were benefits, be it righteous path or not.

Look at Chi clan, it had so many resource points, it had to promote the advantage of the righteous path, that evil cannot defeat righteousness, so that they had the moral high ground to defend their territory and attain stability.

As for demonic path Gu Immortals, they had to deal with calamities and tribulations, they needed to become stronger and that needed resources. But what to do when they had no resources? The only way was to rob and steal, to kill and loot.

It was all for gains and benefits.

Precisely because of this central reasoning, why would Chi Qu You not agree to Fang Yuan's deal? They were just getting what they needed, for their respective benefits.

The talk was done, Fang Yuan dispelled the immortal battlefield and acted like he was forced to retreat in a panic.

Chi Qu You won but Fang Yuan managed to escape, his expression was quite ugly. For the following days, he defended cautiously, preventing Fang Yuan's retaliation from coming.

Seven days later, Fang Yuan suddenly appeared in Plunder Shadow Earth Trench, breaking the formation and successfully taking the dream realm.

Chapter 1594: Righteous Path Schemes Against Fang Yuan

"We need to get rid of Fang Yuan, he dared to attack our righteous path's formation openly, he is too daring!" Luo clan's first supreme elder screamed.

"This time, our clan's Gu Immortal was sacrificed heroically, this demon Fang Yuan already has the blood of two Gu Immortals on his hands, he needs to pay the price!" Hou clan's first supreme elder said in an aged tone, filled with rage.

Yao clan's first supreme elder sighed: "Fang Yuan needs to be dealt with, but he is not an ordinary demonic path Gu Immortal. His identity is very complex, he not only is an otherworldly demon, he also has Spring Autumn Cicada and has returned from the future, he destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and has Giant Sun's true inheritance, he also inherited Spectral Soul true inheritance and became the leader of Shadow Sect, as well as the funding of Lang Ya blessed land. Even with Central Continent Heavenly Court's pursuit, he still remains scot-free, he continued to harm the world while getting stronger at a rapid rate, far beyond logic. To speak the truth, he has the demeanor of a Demon Venerable in his youth."

"Hmph! There will only be Great Dream Immortal Venerable in the future, there will not be a Great Dream Demon Venerable. Yao clan, are you afraid?" Xia clan's first supreme elder immediately said sarcastically.

Yao clan's first supreme elder snickered: "I'm just stating the truth. If we want to kill Fang Yuan, we need to recognize this truth. Like how your Xia clan lost to my Yao clan earlier."

"You!" Xia clan's first supreme elder was incredibly furious.

Recently, due to the turbulence of the earth veins, large amounts of cultivation resources were unearthed from underground, Southern Border's righteous path, demonic path, and lone cultivators competed for them. During this period, lots of conflict was natural, Xia clan had fallen into an ambush by Yao clan and lost, but Yao clan paid a huge price too. Therefore, their conversation was very hostile.

"Alright, our discussion is not for bickering, we need to plan on how to deal with Fang Yuan. If he continues his plunder, what will we do?" At this time, Shang clan's first supreme elder spoke in a moderate tone.

There was silence.

Shang clan had always been neutral and was specialized in trading with all the different forces. When Shang clan's first supreme elder spoke, everyone had to listen.

A while later, Ba clan's first supreme elder broke the silence: "Fang Yuan must have ways to explore dream realms and obtain great benefits. Otherwise, why would he impersonate Wu Yi Hai back then to get into our righteous path? This time, he attacked Plunder Shadow Earth Trench and took all the dream realms away, this proves my point. I wonder what Wu clan's first supreme elder has to say about this?"

Wu clan's first supreme elder was naturally none other than Wu Yi Hai's elder brother — Wu Yong.

Wu clan has already dominated the number one spot in the righteous path, Ba clan had been after their position, but Wu Yong showed up with Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, destroying Ba clan's hope of replacing them as they solidified their status. Ba clan would not let this chance go now.

Wu Yong was silent for a while before speaking: "Fang Yuan is an enemy of everyone. Yesterday, he plundered Chi clan's resources, tomorrow, he might show up anywhere else, our resources and even clansmen might be targeted by him."

Wu Yong said plainly that dealing with Fang Yuan was the responsibility of all the Southern Border righteous path members. Ba clan and others could not make Wu clan take on this role and exert great effort alone.

Hearing Wu Yong's words, many people frowned.

Wu Du Xiu and Wu Yong were vastly different. If this was Wu Du Xiu, she would charge ahead as the vanguard, that was the style of Wu clan.

But Wu Yong stepped back this time, it was as if the humiliation that Fang Yuan gave to Wu clan earlier did not exist.

Ba clan's first supreme elder was not going to let Wu Yong off, he added: "The reason why Fang Yuan is a problem to deal with is because he has Fixed Immortal Travel. I wonder if Wu clan's first supreme elder has any good method to restrict Fixed Immortal Travel?"

Wu Yong smiled bitterly: "I am ashamed, Wu clan does not have such methods. I cannot compare to my mother, we can defend ourselves but that is our limit. In my opinion, Chi clan's first supreme elder set up effective immortal formations earlier, even though Fang Yuan broke through, he still spent quite some time. Why doesn't Chi clan's first supreme elder help us to set up immortal formations around our resource points, so that we can stall for some time when Fang Yuan attacks?"

Chi clan's first supreme elder Chi Qu You quickly waved his hand: "I am ashamed! My immortal formations were all destroyed by Fang Yuan, I will disappoint all of you."

Wu Yong smiled: "No need to be so humble, Fang Yuan did not manage to destroy the formation on Wind Flame Mountain. The immortal formation set up in Plunder Shadow Earth Trench also blocked Fang Yuan's assault once. But his formation path attainment level is too high, he was friends with your clan's formation devotee Chi Shang, we all know that."

Wu Yong's words had deep meaning, Chi Qu You snorted coldly, he remained silent.

Southern Border's super forces had all sorts of resource points. If Chi Qu You had to set up immortal formations one by one, when would he finish?

And most importantly, this matter was very sensitive.

Resource points were the most important areas of the different clans, they would not feel easy if outsiders were the ones setting up their defenses.

Among the clans here, only Chi clan had been plundered, without experiencing it for themselves, the other clans did not feel an urge to ask for Chi Qu You's help.

Chi Qu You understood this, which was why he stopped talking.

Wu Yong saw that Chi Qu You was silent, he could not say anything else.

At this moment, Tie clan's first supreme elder said excitedly: "Actually, Wu clan first supreme elder's method is the best way to deal with Fang Yuan, but that is only half of it. Chi clan's first supreme elder's immortal formations can block Fang Yuan for some time. At this time, if there is our Tie clan's Beacon Tower, we would be able to teleport there and block Fang Yuan, to kill him together! With the combination of both methods, Fang Yuan is not a problem at all!"

Once he said that, the Gu Immortals became even quieter.

Beacon Tower was an Immortal Gu House of Tie clan, its greatest use was similar to Western Desert Xiao clan's Ten Thousand Li Silk Corridor. This Gu House was made of multiple Beacon Towers, they could transport Gu Immortals to each other, if many Beacon Towers were put together, they could even transport rank eight Gu Immortals!

Tie clan first supreme elder's idea was not wrong. In fact, Tie clan had been trying to set up more Beacon Towers around Southern Border.

But this arrangement was too much of a threat to the other super forces. Thus, the forces had been trying to stop Tie clan from creating more Beacon Towers.

And now, Tie clan's first supreme elder used this chance to promote the Beacon Towers again, the leaders of the different clans did not agree, they only kept silent, showing their resistance to it.

"I have another plan." A long while later, Shang clan's first supreme elder spoke.

After fifteen minutes, the discussion between these Southern Border righteous path leaders concluded.

Under the moonlight, Chi Qu You stopped using his killer move, he flew in the sky while riding a thick cloud, having an eerie gaze.

Southern Border's Gu Immortal world was full of conflicts between major forces to begin with. During this period, the earth veins shook, while it gave great benefits, it also intensified the conflict between forces. This made the super forces more hostile to each other.

Other than scheming against each other, just look at this time when Fang Yuan attacked Chi clan's resource points, not a single force helped them out.

After flying for some time, Chi Qu You's vision changed, he ended up in an immortal battlefield.

He was not nervous, because this was yama battlefield.

He had already set up a meeting time with Fang Yuan.

"These are yours." Fang Yuan tossed out multiple Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and an information path mortal Gu: "Where are my things?"

"I brought them." Chi Qu You took out a large number of immortal essence stones and immortal materials of all kinds, there was also one information path mortal Gu, an information path inheritance was recorded in it.

Both sides inspected the goods and traded successfully before parting. Chi Qu You frowned lightly while Fang Yuan smiled.

"Chi clan's first supreme elder, in the future, I will transact with you again!" Before leaving, Fang Yuan transmitted.

"How will you contact me?"

"You will know by then."

Both sides quickly left the place, they were extremely alert, nobody found out about this transaction.

"The information in this Gu worm is not complete, I can see that Fang Yuan still has a lot of dream path research results. But what I obtained this time has already far exceeded the other super forces of Southern Border!" Chi Qu You looked at the dream realms in his immortal aperture as he sighed deeply.

Thinking of Fang Yuan, his gaze turned dark: "Fang Yuan is a scoundrel, he obviously wants to cooperate with me again. After all, he wants to know about Yi Tian Mountain's formation, I should work with him now and obtain more dream path research results, I will use Southern Border's righteous path in the future to eliminate him afterwards!"

The transaction between Chi Qu You and Fang Yuan was merely for benefits. His intention to take down Fang Yuan now was also for benefits.

After all, if Fang Yuan sold these dream path research results to other super forces, Chi clan's advantage would be lost, their benefits would be greatly affected.

"Even though I gave Chi clan a few dream realms this time, I have already obtained a lot of time path dream realms, I am going to cultivate now and raise my time path attainment level!" Fang Yuan was thinking and planning.

Chi clan had obtained dream path methods, they naturally needed more dream realms to explore. Even though Yi Tian Mountain had a huge dream realm, they could not explore it under everyone's watchful gaze, that was too risky.

Fang Yuan wanted to encourage these transactions but he did not want Chi clan to be exposed either.

"This time, I succeeded in invading Plunder Shadow Earth Trench, Southern Border's righteous path must be plotting against me. Even though Fixed Immortal Travel is good, it can be countered. Let alone the foundation of Southern Border's righteous path, close connections between Wu Yong and Heavenly Court will make sure they help out as well. I should lay low now."

The truth was, Fang Yuan could use the dream path research results to find any super force and become allies with them to undergo transactions.

But Fang Yuan chose Chi clan, there were reasons behind it.

The most important reason was that during the chaotic period of his previous life, Chi clan was a firm force in resisting Heavenly Court!

In his previous life, Wu clan was the same, but because Wu Yong managed to take back many Immortal Gu from Southern Border's righteous path this time, Fang Yuan thought about it and could not trust them.

Chapter 1595: Water Text Gu

The moon was bright outside the window, while a faint candle lighted the room.

Wu Yong paced around in his room.

He felt worry and frustration in his heart, he could not let it go.

Right now, Wu Yong had rank eight cultivation level, he had supreme authority in Wu clan, he used Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building to help Wu clan get through tough times. He even got back the Southern Border righteous path's Immortal Gu from Heavenly Court, his reputation was at its peak. During this period, he had worked hard to nurture some Gu Immortal seeds, Wu clan was doing very well, why was he so worried now?

Fang Yuan!

Disguising as Wu Yi Hai, he even deceived Wu Yong, managing to take away lots of resources and even Immortal Gu. Not only did he toy around with Wu clan, even Wu Yong's pursuit saw no results.

Fang Yuan was like a thorn in his heart, whenever Wu Yong thought about it, he would feel heartache, humiliation, anger, and hatred.

This time, Fang Yuan suddenly appeared in Southern Border, destroying Plunder Shadow Earth Trench's formation and taking the dream realms, Wu Yong seemed very calm and composed now, but his heart was bleeding from this thorn that stabbed deeply into his wound!

"Shang clan first supreme elder's method can target Fang Yuan's Fixed Immortal Travel, but…"

Wu Yong frowned as he walked around, shaking his head.

He felt that it was not reliable, could this method really kill Fang Yuan?

Thinking about how he failed to kill Fang Yuan even with all the Southern Border righteous path forces. Thinking about how Heavenly Court failed to capture him after multiple attempts. Could the Southern Border righteous path really succeed this time?

Wu Yong shook his head.

He admitted that he was quite wary of Fang Yuan now. This demon's strength improved by leaps and bounds whenever he appeared, he could not be looked at with logic.

And also, Wu Yong was not confident in Southern Border's righteous path.

Wu clan was the leader of Southern Border's righteous path, Wu Yong had been nurtured under Wu Du Xiu's wings, how could he not see the weakness of Southern Border's righteous path!

They all had their individual desires, they were filled with conflict and wariness, unless they had no choice, there would not be a leader that could unify them.

Even for Wu clan, even if Wu Du Xiu was around and worked with Wu Yong, they could not be an absolute leader.

Wu Yong could imagine that on the day of the operation, Southern Border's righteous path would be very wary of each other, they would make excuses and refuse to be the first ones to act, they would want to fight for benefits. How could such a group deal with the crafty Fang Yuan?

Especially now, only Chi clan was plundered by Fang Yuan, the other clans were untouched, with the turbulence of the earth veins, they had to fight for the resources underground, how could the clans spend their effort on Fang Yuan?

"Or rather, Fang Yuan noticed this, so he only plundered Chi clan's resources!"

Wu Yong's heart sank.

From this angle, he really wanted Fang Yuan to go all-out and aggravate all the clans. But he was simply too crafty, he only targeted one clan.

If Wu Yong knew that Fang Yuan not only plundered Chi clan, he even made a deal with them secretly to plot against Heavenly Court during the five regions chaotic war, who knew what he would think.

After walking around for a while, Wu Yong made up his mind: "I should communicate with Heavenly Court, I should use them to get rid of Fang Yuan!"

This was quite a tough decision.

Even though this was a wise choice, since the enemy of an enemy was a friend, it was taboo. The five regions excluding Eastern Sea had a mentality against foreigners, Southern Border did too.

If Southern Border's forces and Gu Immortals knew that Wu Yong was working with another region's super force to meddle in Southern Border's affairs, he would receive huge criticism, even if he was Wu clan's first supreme elder, even if he had rank eight cultivation level, he would not be exempt from it.

It could be said that Wu Yong was taking a huge risk. If he was exposed, Wu clan's current advantageous position would be destroyed.

"Oh? Wu Yong contacted me? It must be due to the demon Fang Yuan…" Fairy Zi Wei was resting, seeing that Wu Yong had contacted her, she smiled as she replied.

Wu Yong had a special status, he was the first supreme elder of Wu clan, even without trying to influence him, the cooperation between them was already his weakness.

Both sides talked for a while, Wu Yong got to the topic of Fang Yuan.

Fairy Zi Wei thought: "Like I expected, Fang Yuan has Fixed Immortal Travel and because I exposed his methods in treasure yellow heaven, Wu Yong is even more wary of him now, he wants to eliminate Fang Yuan despite the risks."

Heavenly Court was not in good shape recently.

Not long ago, they failed to achieve any of their goals in their second attack on Lang Ya blessed land. Wisdom Gu was taken by Fang Yuan who escaped successfully, Lang Ya blessed land was guarded by Longevity Heaven, while Heavenly Court's Thunder Ghost True Monarch died. Chen Yi, Fairy Zi Wei, and Feng Jiu Ge also suffered injuries to certain degrees, they were all recuperating now.

But even so, after hearing Wu Yong's words, Fairy Zi Wei agreed without hesitation.

Fang Yuan needed to die!

Even if he had rank seven Fixed Immortal Travel, there were ways to restrict this Gu.

Or rather, even if they failed to kill Fang Yuan, as long as they pressured him and did not give him time to grow further, it would be a success for Heavenly Court!

"Fang Yuan's growth is simply too fast and too scary! And this is already with heaven's will giving him hurdles constantly through its influence. Once in a while, he shows up with shocking improvements. Even if we fail to kill him, we must make sure he has no time to cultivate. If he gained new methods, we must expose all his trump cards."

Fairy Zi Wei felt deeper wariness against Fang Yuan.

To pursue him, she had put in so much effort, and right now, even Lang Ya blessed land was nearly taken down by her, but Fang Yuan?

He was still free and roaming around!

Heavenly Court had the absolute advantage, be it fate Gu's repair, the nurturing of Great Dream Immortal Venerable, or even the imprisonment of Spectral Soul, Fang Yuan could not match their achievements.

But in the deepest part of Fairy Zi Wei's heart, she started to feel fear and unease.

This emotion was absurd, but she truly felt fear and unease.

Fear and unease due to Fang Yuan!

"Southern Border's righteous path is dealing with Fang Yuan now, this is a chance. Forget my injuries, I need to go all-out to kill Fang Yuan and eliminate this problem." Determination flashed in Fairy Zi Wei's eyes.

Southern Border's righteous path was plotting against Fang Yuan, because of Wu Yong's contact, before Heavenly Court even made a move, they were already the mastermind. Once Heavenly Court moves, they would unleash a terrifying attack.

It was a pity that Fang Yuan had expected this.

After the transaction with Chi Qu You, he went into seclusion, exploring the dream realms that he had.

This was a time path dream realm.

Inside this dream realm, Fang Yuan was an old man, he was the main character of this dream, having rank four cultivation level.

Right now, he was surrounded by five or six Gu Masters with hostile expressions.

"Lord Bai Lian, this is the treatment fee in advance, please follow us." The leader Gu Master also had rank four cultivation level, looking at Fang Yuan, he spoke threateningly.

Fang Yuan first looked at the Gu worms in his aperture, they were all time path Gu worms used for support, they could not heal. Thinking about it, Fang Yuan probed: "I am just an ordinary time path Gu Master, I am not a doctor, aren't you making things difficult for me?"

The other party replied: "Hmph, you will go whether you want to or not. Do you dare to defy the request of our Central Continent's Meng clan? We already know everything about you, don't worry, we are asking you to go because of your abilities, we know you can heal Lord Meng Bi's illness. Come, do you need us to invite you by force?"

"Let's go, lead the way." Fang Yuan smiled bitterly.

Following these Gu Masters, Fang Yuan soon arrived at Meng clan, he saw the patient Meng Bi.

Only to see that this person was frail and yellow, his bones were protruding from his skinny body, he rested in bed as he grunted weakly.

"How did this happen? What illness is it?" Fang Yuan probed.

A servant started crying as he said: "My master has always been healthy and strong, he sprints as fast as a wolf, to think that this would happen. He was harmed by that unscrupulous merchant, he bought a water text Gu. The merchant said that this Gu would allow him to write beautiful words that resembled flowing water. Master has always been brutish, the others have always said that he had brawns but no literary flair. Because of this, master bought this water text Gu at a high price, wanting to write a beautiful verse that night."

"Is the problem regarding that water text Gu?" Fang Yuan asked.

The servant nodded: "Initially, master used that water text Gu with no issue. He wrote verses after verses, master was extremely happy, he wrote fifty to sixty texts. But in the morning, before he ate, he started to have diarrhea. It poured like flowing water, he had the runs for over twenty times. Even with master's tough body, he ended up like this after a day."

Fang Yuan realized at last, he gained confidence in solving this.

Water text Gu was not the problem, but overly using it caused the diarrhea, nobody could deal with that side effect.

Rushing leads to worse results, this was quite common. Using Gu carried risks, Meng Bi truly brought it upon himself.

"Meng clan was right to invite me, my time path Gu worms might not be able to heal, but in this situation,they are appropriate in healing Meng Bi." Fang Yuan thought.

Chapter 1596: Time Cutting Edge

Fang Yuan was not a novice at exploring dream realms, he had a lot of experiences.

Fang Yuan had already understood Meng Bi's dream realm at this point.

"I need to use the time path Gu worms in the aperture to create a time path killer move and heal Meng Bi's injuries."

Meng Bi was injured from overly using water text Gu, this time path killer move must target the root cause.

Even though Fang Yuan had ordinary attainment level in time path, he had Spectral Soul's true inheritance, Lang Ya's true inheritance, and Hei Fan's true inheritance. Especially the final one, it was a huge help for this problem.

This dream realm was testing the explorer's knowledge and ability to formulate killer moves.

Of course, it was not so simple.

Fang Yuan analyzed them, he found that the time path mortal Gu in this aperture were unique to this dream realm, they did not exist in real life.

Fang Yuan was not surprised, this was a dream realm after all, it was different from the real world.

Others, including time path great experts, would have to test their luck now. But Fang Yuan's luck was very good.

However, he had a better option.

Immortal killer move — Unravel Dream.

This move was useless when he explored Thieving Heaven's dream realm, but now, because this dream realm was much smaller, it had an extraordinary effect.

The necessary Gu worms started to float in the aperture, giving Fang Yuan the answer directly.

Fang Yuan already had a blueprint in his mind, using these Gu worms, he started to test them.

After failing twice, he succeeded in the killer move, Meng Bi was saved. And with this, the dream realm was over.

His soul returned to sovereign immortal body as Fang Yuan opened his eyes.

He joyfully discovered that his time path attainment level had risen from ordinary to master level.

But his joy did not last long, his expression suddenly changed.

At the same time, immortal killer move emperor yama that was shielding his soul started to expand rapidly from its original state.

"Someone is deducing my location, they are quite proficient!" Fang Yuan smiled coldly.

If this was before the defensive battle of Lang Ya blessed land, he would be worried. But he had emperor yama now, his defense against deductions made even Heavenly Court's Fairy Zi Wei without options for now.

As expected, after deducing for a while, the other party was unable to break emperor yama, they paid a huge price for nothing.

Fang Yuan's emperor yama killer move shrunk back into a simple garment on his soul again.

Fang Yuan's gaze flickered with cold light, he looked around as emperor yama's aura burst out in the surroundings, to play safe, he decided to leave this place immediately.

Using Fixed Immortal Travel again, it was simply too convenient to move around with this Gu.

In a flash, Fang Yuan went from one side of Southern Border to the other side, who knew how far the distance was.

Fang Yuan flew for a while before lurking in a grey valley that was filled with mist.

"My soul foundation is only at thirty million man soul now." Fang Yuan calculated as he sighed.

Using emperor yama would place a burden on Fang Yuan's soul, his soul foundation would be depleted. Earlier, against that mysterious expert, emperor yama expended a million of Fang Yuan's soul foundation, the deducer was truly powerful.

Long ago, Fang Yuan's soul foundation far exceeded thirty million, but in the battle of Lang Ya, he expended it greatly.

And also, exploring dream realms consumed soul foundation and also caused great harm to the soul.

If this was before, Fang Yuan could use his resources to raise his soul foundation again. But now, Dang Hun Mountain was still being repaired, it could not be used.

Without Dang Hun Mountain to produce guts Gu, with just Fang Yuan's guts Gu in stock, they could not last long.

"To repair Dang Hun Mountain, I have been using landscape as before Immortal Gu. Event hough Dang Hun Mountain has the effect of Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's orderly well killer move, it is just a rank six Immortal Gu, this task has been draining my immortal essence."

Fang Yuan's immortal essence storage was drying up.

His abundant storage had already been depleted by the intense battles earlier.

Heavenly Court's attacks on Fang Yuan did not kill him but they were not in vain, his foundation was deeply hit by this!

The lack of immortal essence was also why Fang Yuan wanted to work with Chi Qu You instead of fighting.

Actually, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had an incredible amount of time path resources[1], the rate of time was rapid, his immortal essence was produced at the fastest rate in the world compared to all other rank seven Gu Immortals.

But his expenditure was even greater, just him alone could not make up for the deficit. The dragonfish business was sustaining him for now.

The dragonfish business was raking in huge profits, Fang Yuan used these immortal essence stones and constantly converted them into immortal essence, alleviating his problem.

"With the dragonfish business and my guts Gu storage, I can still sustain myself. When Dang Hun Mountain is repaired, everything will get better."

With Fixed Immortal Travel and Omni-directional Travel, Fang Yuan was not afraid of people approaching him.

The truth was, with emperor yama's protection, there was little possibility of them deducing his location quickly.

Fang Yuan decided to continue exploring time path dream realms.

He had left many time path dream realms in Plunder Shadow Earth Trench, after setting up a Gu formation to alert himself, he entered the dream.

On a snowy mountain peak, an old man looked at Fang Yuan with his hands behind his back.

"Kneel down." The old man said plainly.

Fang Yuan was dazed but quickly followed the old man's words.

The old man's expression turned solemn and grand, he said slowly: "From now on, I will impart upon you the strongest killer move of our clan — Time Cutting Edge! Once this is shot out, it will not miss, anyone hit by it will die. There is only hope in taking revenge on our clan's mortal enemy after you learn this move."

"Yes." Fang Yuan heard his words and had a feeling he was going to have huge gains in this dream realm exploration!

As expected, the old man taught him the entire killer move, time cutting edge.

This move was very complex, much more than Fang Yuan's own creation, myriad self. And the harder thing was, this move had a very short completion time, hundreds of steps needed to be completed in three breaths of time. Otherwise, Fang Yuan would face the backlash of this killer move.

"Three breaths? How can that be possible?" Even Fang Yuan felt that it was impossible.

However, the old man's explanation had not ended. Fang Yuan listened closely, the solution was for Fang Yuan to use another time path killer move to shorten time cutting edge's activation time to three breaths, that would allow him to use it.

If other paths uses time path methods to accelerate their killer moves, they would be adding fuel to the fire, the effect would backfire and the move would fail, resulting in a backlash.

But time cutting edge was a time path killer move to begin with, when using other time path killer moves, there would be no conflict, instead they complemented each other.

Thus, rather than time cutting edge itself, Fang Yuan started to learn the supplementary killer move — Shrink Time.

[1] Maybe I should mention this, author writes space path resources = size of aperture, time path resources = speed. Back

Chapter 1597: Time Path Grandmaster

Time path dream realm.

Fang Yuan turned into a young looking rank six Gu Immortal, his eyes were shut as his body was covered in specks of white light.

As the number of white lights increased, Fang Yuan's aura became denser and more stable.

Suddenly, his body shook, his aura became chaotic, it was like a tall building collapsing into the abyss.

Guh.

Fang Yuan opened his mouth, spitting out a mouthful of blood.

"I failed again." He opened his eyes, bright light shining within.

He had already failed to activate shrink time three times, this was a rank six killer move used to supplement time cutting edge.

With three consecutive failures, Fang Yuan's soul foundation fell with each injury, his thirty million man soul had fallen to twenty-nine million six hundred thousand.

This was not Thieving Heaven's dream realm after all, the soul foundation loss in Thieving Heaven's dream realm was too absurd.

Fang Yuan did not feel discouraged, his gaze flickered as fighting spirit rose in him.

Ignoring the rest, just shrink time itself was very valuable. It was not only useful for time cutting edge, he could supplement it for other time path killer moves.

The exploration failed, Fang Yuan's soul left the dream realm, returning to heal in the sovereign immortal body.

Guts Gu.

Fang Yuan took out a guts Gu and used it.

Earlier, he had an abundant supply, but now, he had to use them wisely.

He did not have many guts Gu, Fang Yuan planned to use them for the healing of his soul. Therefore, he could only stop his soul path cultivation.

The truth was, not only would Fang Yuan's soul foundation remain stagnant, as he explored more dream realms later, it would continue to fall. This was something to be expected, there was no helping it.

Soul path cultivation was no longer his priority, he needed to head into the River of Time and obtain Red Lotus' true inheritance, that was the most logical plan!

Fang Yuan needed to go soon.

Firstly, the longer he waited, the more problems that would arise. His enemy was Heavenly Court which had a deep foundation, they might have another great expert awakening at any time. Heavenly Court also had traps set in the River of Time, the more time passed, the more traps there would be.

Secondly, Fang Yuan was placing his hope on Red Lotus' true inheritance to resist Heavenly Court and preventing fate Immortal Gu from being repaired. This had the greatest chance of success now. But in the worst case scenario that Red Lotus' true inheritance could not help him, he had to make other plans. Thus, the earlier Fang Yuan obtained Red Lotus' true inheritance, the more time he had to deal with the future.

As for his soul path cultivation becoming stagnant or falling, or even the lack of immortal essence, Fang Yuan did not care. Of course, he was not ignoring them, he already had the way to settle them. Once Dang Hun Mountain was repaired, everything would be in order again!

Other than this method, Fang Yuan had no way of resolving these problems now.

Currently, Dang Hun Mountain was about thirty to forty percent restored, but the soul path dao marks had not reached a qualitative change yet, it could not produce guts Gu.

After resting his soul, Fang Yuan entered the dream realm again.

This time, he finally succeeded in activating shrink time.

The first three failures were not for nothing, each failure led Fang Yuan closer to success.

Fang Yuan finally grasped the killer move shrink time.

Of course, the shrink time obtained in the dream realm might not be usable in the real world. After all, dreams and reality were different.

Fang Yuan was clear in his mind, the content of shrink time was accurate. Even if there were differences, with the light of wisdom, he could spend some time to create a version usable in real life.

At this point, this stage of the dream realm has been cleared, the entire cultivation area faded from Fang Yuan's view.

His time path attainment started to rise rapidly before stopping.

"I am still a time path master. But… compared to before, it has risen a bit, I am approaching grandmaster."

In the second stage of the dream realm, Fang Yuan started to practise time cutting edge.

This move was even more difficult and complex than myriad self back then.

Fang Yuan focused his mind and practised, he soon felt his head spinning, thoughts were expended rapidly in his mind, it was like a dried pond.

Fang Yuan was very patient, he practised the contents continuously over and over again, moving towards the path of success.

While practising, he got injured again.

After leaving the dream realm and going back to his body, Fang Yuan was shocked to find out that not only did his soul foundation fall from this injury, his lifespan was also shaved off to some extent!

"Getting injured in this dream realm will expend lifespan!" Fang Yuan's heart jumped, this was a new discovery. But thankfully, he had a lot of lifespan Gu now, there was no issue. Of course, other Gu Immortals would think differently.

Just like this, after a while, Fang Yuan got injured four times before he finally managed to use time cutting edge in the dream realm.

Just once was enough, this was not reality after all, the dream realm collapsed as Fang Yuan entered the third stage.

The old man appeared again: "After six years, you finally learned time cutting edge, not bad. But we will have to test it in battle first."

Fang Yuan cupped his fists: "Please arrange it."

The old man laughed: "Rank seven Gu Immortal Li Xin is that person's right hand man, there is chaos in the south due to ancient desolate beasts, he is there to suppress them, go kill him!"

Fang Yuan frowned slightly, he only had rank six cultivation level under this identity, without deep foundations, how could he kill a rank seven?

The only advantage was his killer move time cutting edge!

Before Fang Yuan could think anymore, the dream changed, the surroundings were covered in flames. A person stood in the sea of fire, looking at Fang Yuan with his triangular eyes: "So you are a lingering member of Bo clan, hmph, die!"

Saying so, dark red flames surged towards Fang Yuan like a huge wave.

Fang Yuan quickly retreated, at the crucial moment, he activated the time path Immortal Gu in his immortal aperture.

At the next moment, the flames engulfed him.

Fang Yuan died in battle.

The dream realm exploration failed, Fang Yuan moved his injured soul back into his body.

This dream realm was quite ridiculous. The battle started immediately, Fang Yuan had no time to react.

"Furthermore, other than time cutting edge, I can only use the other time path Immortal Gu without formulating any killer moves."

Fang Yuan was quite vexed.

These time path Immortal Gu were all rank six, when used alone, how could they match the rank seven Gu Immortal Li Xin? And his dark red flame killer move was clearly rank seven!

"It seems that I can only counter offense with offense and use time cutting edge against him." Fang Yuan made up his mind after a moment.

If this was real life, Fang Yuan would fight cautiously. But the dream realm was a different case.

After a while, Fang Yuan entered the dream realm.

Dark red flames came at him, but Fang Yuan did not dodge, he used immortal killer move time cutting edge.

A thin blade formed instantly.

The flying blade shot out with the flash of a sharp light.

"Hmm! What is this killer move…" Li Xin had a shocked expression as he fell, the dark red flames surged and burned him to a crisp.

Fang Yuan was deeply shocked.

"This move is amazing! It could easily kill a rank seven, even though this Li Xin was covered in defensive methods. Even in the dream realm it is so powerful… it seems it is not weak in real life either!"

With Li Xin's death, the dream realm dissipated.

The third stage of the dream was passed, Fang Yuan became a time path grandmaster!

Chapter 1598: Forget

The dream realm reached the fourth stage.

"I killed Li Xin." Fang Yuan said.

The old man stood in front of Fang Yuan, nodding: "It seems that you are already proficient in time cutting edge. But you only learned the rank six version of time cutting edge. I will impart you the rank seven version now, listen carefully."

Fang Yuan focused his mind and memorized it.

The rank seven killer move was many times more complex than the rank six version!

Fang Yuan got a headache from just listening to the steps, this was the most complex killer move he had ever heard of, there was no competition.

After imparting him the killer move, the old man said to Fang Yuan before leaving: "After you succeed in learning this rank seven killer move, come find me."

Fang Yuan was left alone in the dream realm.

"It seems that the fourth stage still wants me to practise the killer move." Fang Yuan pondered.

Having understood this, he started to work, practising laboriously in the dream realm.

Even though the killer move was complex and difficult to master, Fang Yuan had lots of patience.

His personality had already been tempered into a piece of black steel by his previous life and the toying of fate, he was extremely firm and determined.

These small setbacks would not make him dejected or feel like giving up.

While Fang Yuan explored the dream realm and practised his killer move, inside the sovereign immortal aperture, Fang Yuan's time path clone was sitting in front of wisdom Gu, using the light of wisdom to make deductions.

Next, he opened his eyes, muttering: "The formation's deduction has reached a certain point. Next, I will move onto time cutting edge."

It was actually quite strange.

This killer move, time cutting edge, had exceptional power, why was it not recorded inside Spectral Soul's true inheritance?

After all, this time path dream realm came from Spectral Soul himself, normally speaking, time cutting edge should be recorded inside Spectral Soul's true inheritance.

But in fact, Fang Yuan's true inheritance of Spectral Soul did not have such content.

"We have not deduced Fang Yuan's location yet?" Xia clan's first supreme elder said with a grim expression.

In front of her, a group of Southern Border Gu Immortals fell into silence, they all had ugly expressions.

Because Fang Yuan destroyed Plunder Shadow Earth Trench and took away all the dream realms earlier, Southern Border's righteous path gathered together and sent out their people, forming a group of specialized individuals to track Fang Yuan.

The leader of this group was Xia clan's first supreme elder, Xia Cha.

Xia Cha had white hair and wrinkles on her face, even though she was old, she had a grand disposition, her gaze swept across the crowd as she dominated everyone with her aura.

The Southern Border immortals lowered their heads.

Who did not want to find Fang Yuan? But he had emperor yama protecting him, even Heavenly Court's wisdom path great expert Fairy Zi Wei was without options against him, not to mention this hastily gathered group of Southern Border Gu Immortals.

Of course, Southern Border's righteous path had deep foundations, they were not to be underestimated. These people were not completely incapable of finding out Fang Yuan's location, they just needed more clues, like when Fang Yuan appears again to attack another resource point.

With sufficient clues, there was a possibility that these people could use their various methods and cooperate to unravel emperor yama.

Emperor yama was strong, but if it remained the same over time, as deductions piled up, it would eventually be broken.

Xia Cha knew this too: "This damned Fang Yuan, after plundering Plunder Shadow Earth Trench, he vanished into thin air!"

Xia Cha felt pressured.

As long as Fang Yuan was still alive, as leader of this expedition, her reputation would continue to plummet. If it got serious, the whole of Xia clan would suffer too.

"This demon Fang Yuan, he is hiding in seclusion, he must be exploring dream realms and gaining benefits! We must eliminate him fast, otherwise, he will get much stronger again." Xia Cha said eerily: "Everyone, if you have any trump cards, use them, I swear on my name that I will compensate you all fairly."

The Southern Border immortals looked around at each other, they did not move.

Xia Cha felt increasingly disappointed, her gaze swept across the people and stopped at one person: "Liu Hao, I wonder what brilliant method you have?"

Liu Hao was slightly stunned.

He had a tall body, he wore a green robe and had a goatee, his face was yellow, he was the representative of Wu clan.

Because of the turmoil earlier, many of Wu clan's Gu Immortals had been sacrificed, thus they recruited a lot of outside Gu Immortals recently as their external supreme elders. Liu Hao was one of them.

But the truth was, he was a Central Continent Gu Immortal, a spy sent by Fairy Zi Wei, arranged by Wu Yong as a Southern Border righteous path member.

Xia Cha was familiar with the other Gu Immortals except Liu Hao, on the surface, he was a secluded cultivator and did not have much reputation.

Liu Hao reacted in time and smiled bitterly: "I am ashamed! I cannot do anything about this, our information is severely lacking, especially clues connected to Fang Yuan. In my opinion, we are not weak, the problem is that we have nothing to work with."

"Indeed, indeed."

"Liu Hao is correct!"

Liu Hao's words resonated with everyone present.

Xia Cha was slightly disappointed, but she did not suspect Liu Hao of lying, after all, Wu clan and Fang Yuan had deep enmity between them.

"What do we do now? Do we continue waiting? If Fang Yuan does not show up, will we do nothing but wait for him to appear?"

Xia Cha thought about this and felt a headache coming.

But at this time, an unknown voice suddenly spoke around them: "I can help in this matter."

"Who is it?!" The immortals were shocked, even Xia Cha stood up as her eyes shined brightly, she stared hard.

An unknown Gu Immortal with a muscular body and conical hat suddenly appeared in the immortal formation. If he did not speak, nobody would have noticed!

"Who are you?!" Southern Border's immortals were all prepared to fight, the atmosphere was extremely tense.

"Wait, you are…" The expression of Tie clan's representative changed as he stopped the immortals.

"That's right, I am Lu Wei Yin." The person said plainly with a smile.

Dream realm.

The old man nodded with satisfaction and a bit of shock: "Rank seven time cutting edge, you mastered it as well!"

Fang Yuan had a plain expression, cupping his fists: "I did not disappoint you."

The old man nodded: "It seems that you are talented in this aspect, very good, our clan's revenge can finally see some hope. But I have some things to tell you."

"Please tell me."

"First." The old man raised his right index finger: "Rank six time cutting edge can kill rank seven, but rank seven time cutting edge cannot kill rank eight Gu Immortals. Rank seven and eight are too different in strength. Thus, even if you mastered time cutting edge, do not seek the enemy for revenge yet. You are only rank six now, you will only be courting death."

"Second." The old man raised his right middle finger: "You only have rank six cultivation level, using rank seven time cutting edge is quite difficult. You need to raise your cultivation level to rank seven or even rank eight! When you raise your cultivation level, you will be able to learn rank eight time cutting edge. With a rank eight killer move, you would be able to take revenge, but before that, you need to endure!"

"And third." The old man raised his fourth finger: "Time cutting edge is an extreme move, it has incredible power but the drawback is huge. The higher the rank, the stronger the drawback. You must have realized it now, right? That's right, time cutting edge will remove your memories related to it. The more you use it, the more you forget. One day, you will forget me, the enemy, and even this killer move itself. Thus, before you lose too many memories, you need to control yourself and not use this move excessively."

Chapter 1599: Tribulation and Divine Technique

Southern Border.

The sovereign immortal aperture had already been placed, the entrance was open and swallowed a vast amount of heaven and earth qi.

Swoosh swoosh!

The turbulent heaven and earth qi approached grandly, if anyone saw this, they would be deeply shocked, no blessed land had ever been able to absorb so much heaven and earth qi at once.

Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal body was near the entrance, watching the heaven and earth qi flow in. Because it was too dense, the qi could be seen like moving fog or clouds.

"Absorb more, absorb more, take in everything you need." Fang Yuan smiled, he could tell that the sovereign immortal aperture was very 'hungry'.

City Well, Reverse Flow River, and Luo Po Valley, even though the three secluded domains of heaven and earth were unique and amazing, they caused a huge burden on the blessed land, the expenditure of heaven and earth qi was intense. From time to time, Fang Yuan had to absorb heaven and earth qi from the outside world to replenish them.

"And this is before Dang Hun Mountain gets repaired, after it is restored, the amount of heaven and earth qi needed will be even higher!"

From this aspect, the destruction of Dang Hun Mountain had a tiny bit of benefit to Fang Yuan.

Of course, the biggest reason was that sovereign blessed land had a lot of resources, it was like a huge foundation that could handle the weight of four secluded domains of heaven and earth. Ordinary blessed lands could not sustain two of them at once.

Placing his immortal aperture and opening the immortal aperture's entrance had several drawbacks to Fang Yuan.

At this moment, because the inside and outside were connected, when he absorbed heaven and earth qi, Fang Yuan's location would be exposed to heaven's will.

And if any Gu Immortal tried to make deductions on him, the difficulty of defending himself would be many times higher.

Thus, Fang Yuan had been buying immortal materials and turning them into heaven and earth qi to replenish his immortal aperture. But recently, his focus was on repairing Dang Hun Mountain, he started lacking funds, he could not buy them anymore so he had to place his immortal aperture to absorb heaven and earth qi.

The sovereign immortal aperture was definitely a big eater, it needed dozens or even hundreds of times of heaven and earth qi as ordinary blessed lands.

The sovereign immortal aperture had its fill, but heaven and earth qi continued to pour in unceasingly.

This phenomenon did not shock Fang Yuan, because he knew that this time was different, his tribulation was coming.

Fang Yuan was a rank seven Gu Immortal, he faced an earthly calamity every ten years, a heavenly tribulation every fifty years, and a grand tribulation every one hundred years.

Ever since Fang Yuan used his time path methods to modify the sovereign immortal aperture's rate of time to its quickest, his calamities and tribulations had been coming at a rapid rate!

This was an earthly calamity.

But be they earthly calamity or heavenly tribulation, they were not a problem for Fang Yuan, especially when he had the killer move exposing heavenly secret. This move used heavenly secret Immortal Gu as the core with supplementary Gu worms to allow Fang Yuan to deduce the contents of upcoming calamities and tribulations.

Thus, before this earthly calamity even formed, Fang Yuan already knew what it was.

As expected, the calamities and tribulations formed like how Fang Yuan had predicted.

Earth qi continued to rumble under Fang Yuan's feet, forming into huge yellow spirals. Heaven qi rumbled in the sky, booming as green lightning in the sky continued to flicker.

Screech screech screech!

With a chain of shrill noises that could burst eardrums, terrifying statues emerged from the center of the yellow spiral.

These giant statues were ten meters tall, they were muscular and had sharp teeth that protruded out of their faces. Suddenly, they opened their red eyes as the purple bat wings on their backs expanded, they flew up and charged at Fang Yuan.

"Yellow spring ghost martial statues." Fang Yuan floated in the sky, his arms were behind his back as he looked at these statues calmly.

He was very relaxed, he could even look at the sky during this critical moment when the enemy approached.

In the sky, the green lightning split apart the cloud layer, countless statues that resembled the yellow spring ghost martial statues appeared.

The yellow spring ghost martial statues bore their fangs and claws, but these statues were very orderly like a group of troops, they had solemn expressions and huge bodies, there were eagle wings on their backs.

"Green lightning divine martial statues." Fang Yuan smiled in his mind, recognizing the second type of statue.

At this moment, the yellow spring ghost martial statues had already reached Fang Yuan, they slashed their claws and opened their mouths, biting at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan did not move, ripples appeared on his body.

It was the famous creation of Fang Yuan, immortal killer move — Reverse Flow Protection Seal!

Be they the yellow spring ghost martial statues or green lightning divine martial statues, their attacks were all reflected back and injured themselves. Fang Yuan was completely unharmed and could not be defeated.

"Begone." Fang Yuan waved his hand, immortal killer move myriad dragon burst out, within the sea of silver scales, myriad dragons flew and attacked endlessly.

Even though there were many yellow spring ghost martial statues and green lightning divine martial statues produced by the heaven and earth qi, how could they match Fang Yuan's myriad dragon?

At the start, they could still resist, but soon, they were engulfed by the myriad dragon army, losing their numbers rapidly. The heaven and earth qi were scattered by the myriad dragons, even though heaven's will was unresigned and sought to try again, the next wave of myriad dragon destroyed the gathering heaven and earth qi again.

A moment later, the calamity was over, the immortal aperture's entrance closed, the sovereign immortal aperture became peaceful again as the turbulence ended.

Fang Yuan nodded to himself and concluded: "This earthly calamity only had the yellow spring ghost martial statues originally, but changed because I did not go through the previous earthly calamity, instead using the immortal killer move endless trouble to delay it."

Immortal killer move endless trouble was among the contents of Hei Fan's true inheritance. It could delay the current tribulation until the next time, and undergo both tribulations together. The weakness was that it would anger heaven's will, the following calamities and tribulations would increase greatly in strength.

Heaven's will was trying to suppress Fang Yuan and prevent his cultivation level from advancing, it intentionally made his calamities and tribulations as weak as possible so he could gain few dao marks.

In this situation, the weakness of endless trouble was actually advantageous to Fang Yuan!

Thus, Fang Yuan used this killer move to undergo two tribulations together, he could gain dao marks and heaven's will could not stop him.

"Yellow spring ghost martial statues were the earthly calamity, while green lightning divine martial statues were on the level of heavenly tribulation. This time, i gained quite a few dao marks!" Fang Yuan inspected it, his soul path and transformation path dao marks had increased.

These were both useful to Fang Yuan.

Of course, he needed time path dao marks the most.

The sovereign immortal aperture had a huge space, Fang Yuan intentionally chose an empty area to undergo tribulation. Even if heaven's will wanted to destroy anything, it had no target.

Even though the calamity was over, Fang Yuan's body remained here. He started to activate heaven's will dissipation, only stopping after he confirmed that the remaining heaven's will was cleansed away.

When Fang Yuan's main body underwent tribulation, his time path clone had been staying with wisdom Gu, deducing immortal killer moves continuously.

Previously, Fang Yuan successfully explored the dream realm, his time path attainment level rose drastically to grandmaster level.

With this attainment level, he was very successful in deducing time path killer moves.

Actually, Fang Yuan's main body had many time path killer moves. Spectral Soul's true inheritance had many, followed by Hei Fan's true inheritance and Lang Ya Sect, in theory, Fang Yuan with refinement path quasi-supreme attainment could deduce and modify these immortal killer moves.

But for Fang Yuan, Hei Fan's true inheritance was his main consideration. Because his time path Immortal Gu were mostly from Hei Fan's true inheritance.

For example, rank eight Years Flow Like Water, rank seven year Gu and after Immortal Gu.

The remaining time path Immortal Gu were all rank six. Most were left behind from Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage, and Fang Yuan also had day Immortal Gu.

The time path clone's main job was to use Hei Fan's true inheritance as the foundation along with other immortal killer moves and time path Immortal Gu recipes to deduce the most appropriate time path methods for Fang Yuan.

Even though not long had passed, the time path clone was extremely efficient!

Currently, Fang Yuan had an entire set of time path methods, covering offense, defense, movement, and healing. He just needed to spend some time practising them and he could easily grasp them.

"But this is not enough!" The time path clone opened his eyes, sighing.

The light of wisdom faded away as wisdom Gu flew away slowly.

The time path clone went to an empty area to experiment on the killer move.

Immortal killer move — Time Cutting Edge!

A flying blade tore through the sky, instantly vanishing with shocking speed.

But the time path clone's blood flowed out of his mouth as he shook his head, greatly disappointed.

"I deduced rank seven time path methods that are suitable for me. But in the River of Time, when searching for Red Lotus' true inheritance and facing the obstruction of Heavenly Court, I will need to have rank eight time path methods."

Hei Fan's true inheritance had rank eight defensive killer moves that used years flow like water Immortal Gu as the core. But it did not have rank eight offensive methods.

In Hei Fan's case, he only obtained Years Flow Like Water in his later years. With limited time, deducing rank eight defensive methods were already not easy. He had rank eight level dao marks, rank seven offenses were enough for him. Of course, most importantly, he solely had Years Flow Like Water, he could either use it to attack or defend himself at one point in time. Defense was naturally more important than offense, especially for a righteous path member.

"And time cutting edge is very extraordinary. Even though rank seven time cutting edge cannot kill rank eight experts, it can harm them. It is a pity that after modifying it, the power is far lower than the original, and the backlash is heavier."

Fang Yuan was not unfamiliar with this situation.

Like how he had created myriad self Immortal Gu's recipe, because of his refinement path quasi-supreme attainment level, he had modified it to its limits. Any minor adjustment would be detrimental and make it worse than before.

Fang Yuan's modification of time cutting edge was similar.

"It seems that the complete time cutting edge killer move is a rank nine killer move!"

Like how Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's immortal killer move orderly well was also rank nine and could not be modified further.

Even though Fang Yuan only obtained the rank six and seven time cutting edge, even the incomplete versions could not be modified. After forcefully changing the content, the disadvantages far outweighed the advantages.

Furthermore, with Fang Yuan's deductions, time cutting edge's memory loss effect was not simple. It was not as plain as the old man had described it, the memories lost were not just about the move, but everything related to the move.

Any information related to this move, be it memories or records in information path Gu worms, even carvings on stones would be erased from the River of Time as this move got used continuously.

"Spectral Soul must have obtained time cutting edge in the past, but because he used it often, all of the information that he had regarding time cutting edge was erased from the River of Time, therefore, it was not inside Spectral Soul's true inheritance."

"Of course, there is a possibility that Spectral Soul's true inheritance is not complete, Shadow Sect still kept a small portion of it including this hidden from me, but that is very unlikely."

"Regardless, I am sure of something, this time cutting edge is truly a divine technique. If I can grasp it, I will have more confidence in the River of Time, my chances will rise by twenty percent!"

A day later.

"This is it." Lu Wei Yin half-knelt on the ground as he placed his palm down, sensing the changes in the earth qi.

Next, several figures descended from the sky and landed behind Lu Wei Yin. They were led by an old woman, the rank eight time path great expert, Xia clan's first supreme elder — Xia Cha!

"Fang Yuan placed his aperture here and absorbed the heaven and earth qi, in fact… he went through a tribulation here." Lu Wei Yin said with deep certainty.

Xia Cha's eyes flashed brightly, Lu Wei Yin was indeed Paradise Earth's inheritor, his earth path methods were profound to this extent!

The Gu Immortals behind them started to converse.

"With Lord Lu Wei Yin here, we will be able to find Fang Yuan!"

"Fang Yuan has many secluded domains of heaven and earth, the burden of heaven and earth qi is huge, with such a clue, we will definitely find him."

"Don't you all find it strange? He has Fixed Immortal Travel, why is he staying in Southern Border? Why not go to Eastern Sea or Western Desert, aren't those places safer?"

"Hmph, he is already wanted by everyone, nobody can tolerate him, nowhere is safe."

"This demon is too vicious, he is likely staying in Southern Border because he wants to rob our resources, especially the dream realms in Yi Tian Mountain, we cannot let them go unguarded!"

"Kill, we need to kill this demon before we can rest at ease!"

Chapter 1600: Ambush, Reverse Scheme

In treasure yellow heaven, the higher the value of items, the taller and brighter the treasure light.

At this stall, the treasure light had been consistently tall and bright, it was like a torch compared to the other stalls.

Southern Border Gu Immortal Tie Qu Zhong's divine sense was moving around this stall.

"I want three thousand copper dragonfish. Hmm…" After hesitating for a moment, Tie Qu Zhong added: "And two hundred silver dragonfish."

The transaction was completed quickly, Tie Qu Zhong paid a hefty amount of immortal essence stones for them.

When he withdrew his divine sense and flew around Southern Border's sky with his main body, his vision was obscured by clouds.

Tie Qu Zhong's worry had dissipated.

"With these dragonfish, my rank seven edge Gu can be fed for now. However, dragonfish is only a temporary replacement item, to solve this problem, I need to be self sufficient and create the white steel extract resource point in my immortal aperture."

White steel was a rank six immortal material, one of the earth vein essences. White steel extract was a rank seven immortal material, often, there would only be a small bowl of white steel extract from a huge piece of white steel.

Tie Qu Zhong wanted to create a resource point to produce white steel extract, but it was a huge project to start with.

If he could not solve the problem, purchasing dragonfish to feed his rank seven edge Gu time and time again would incur huge costs, he would be making a loss.

When Gu Immortals cultivate, they do not just fight, resource management was also of utmost importance, occasionally even more than fighting.

Thinking of the white steel extract, Tie Qu Zhong's gaze turned to his right, there was Gu Immortal moving with him hundreds of steps away.

"Shang Hu Zhang." Tie Qu Zhong transmitted.

The Shang clan Gu Immortal immediately replied with a nervous expression: "Have you found traces of that demon Fang Yuan?"

It turned out that the two rank seven Gu Immortals, Tie Qu Zhong and Shang Hu Zhang, were members deployed by Southern Border's righteous path to hunt down Fang Yuan.

Because of Lu Wei Yin, the group that chased after Fang Yuan had always been consistently following his tracks, finding new clues from time to time.

This time, the immortals went to the southeast of Southern Border, due to Lu Wei Yin's suggestion, rank eight time path Gu Immortal Xia Cha ordered the Gu Immortals to work together and search for new clues.

Shang Hu Zhang and Tie Qu Zhong were one of such pairs.

Tie Qu Zhong smiled lightly: "No need to be worried, I just wanted to ask about the white steel extract."

Shang Hu Zhang heard this and relaxed, he smiled too: "So you want to create a white steel extract resource point to feed your edge Gu. This is not hard, Shang clan can assist with that, but the price…"

Both sides negotiated for a while, Shang clan eventually fought for a price that was not too low, while Tie Qu Zhong made up his mind and gritted his teeth as he agreed.

After succeeding in the transaction, Shang Hu Zhang's smile widened, he praised: "Friend Qu Zhong, you want to create the resource point, it is truly wise. Even though the investment is expensive, in the long term, it will save you a huge amount."

"Indeed, like how I bought dragonfish this time to replace a portion of the white steel extract, if I do this every time, the expenditure is huge." Tie Qu Zhong sighed.

Shang Hu Zhang's gaze suddenly flickered: "Dragonfish? To speak the truth, our Shang clan has a dragonfish stall in treasure yellow heaven too. Not only do we sell ordinary dragonfish, we also have copper dragonfish. Sigh, friend, you should have told me earlier, I would be able to give you discounts."

Tie Qu Zhong chuckled: "Shang clan is also in the dragonfish business?"

"Our Shang clan is interested in any kind of business. Friend Tie Qu Zhong, you also know that the biggest seller of dragonfish now is Fang Yuan! Come, come, I'll introduce you to the stall, it is run by one of us. Trading with outsiders will lead to their growth after all." Shang Hu Zhang said with an earnest tone.

Tie Qu Zhong had to thank him profusely but he felt unmoved on the inside.

Even though Shang clan gave discounts, the price of the dragonfish was still quite high. And this stall only sold copper dragonfish, there were no silver dragonfish here.

Fang Yuan killed Qin Bai He and You Chan, obtaining the number one spot in the dragonfish business. Fairy Zi Wei obviously knew about this, she had exposed Fang Yuan's information in treasure yellow heaven earlier, other than great thief ghost hand and other methods, the dragonfish business was also exposed.

Thus, the Gu Immortals of the entire world knew that Fang Yuan was the current number one seller of the dragonfish business in treasure yellow heaven.

And naturally, he attracted the 'envy and jealousy' of these Gu Immortals.

There was naturally an impact dealt, but the actual loss to his dragonfish business profits were marginal and inconsequential.

Copper dragonfish had already been replicated, but the cost of production was much higher than Fang Yuan. This made his competitors' copper dragonfish much more expensive and unable to compete with Fang Yuan.

Other than that, silver dragonfish was exclusive to Fang Yuan, currently, Gu Immortals interested in the dragonfish business could not create it yet. This was a huge advantage for Fang Yuan.

With these two elements, Fang Yuan's number one spot in the dragonfish business could not be taken away.

Of course, Fang Yuan was not going to sell dragonfish using just one identity. He opened many stalls and created the scene of many Gu Immortals replicating his silver dragonfish, selling these for huge profits every day.

"But even so, my immortal essence stones are dwindling rapidly." Fang Yuan sighed.

Repairing Dang Hun Mountain used a lot of immortal essence, and immortal essence was converted from immortal essence stones, Fang Yuan's huge expenditure was far beyond his immortal aperture's production speed.

However, the good news was that due to his full investment, Dang Hun Mountain was now sixty percent repaired, the soul path dao marks reached a qualitative change and could now produce guts Gu again.

But the production of guts Gu was terribly little, Fang Yuan needed to continue repairing Dang Hun Mountain.

"Dragonfish business has too much profits, not only would many forces and Gu Immortals interfere, Heavenly Court would definitely try to suppress me. But currently, silver dragonfish is too hard to create, while ordinary dragonfish, iron dragonfish, and copper dragonfish have expensive methods of production that cannot match mine."

In time, Fang Yuan's advantage would continue to dwindle, especially after Heavenly Court obtains Spectral Soul's food path inheritance from soul searching, his dragonfish business would definitely face a huge challenge.

Fang Yuan knew this, he needed new sources of income.

The dragonfish business would not last long while guts Gu was exposed already, even though it was a monopoly, because the plans in green ghost desert was halted, Fang Yuan lacked souls to mass produce guts Gu.

Even though Fang Yuan had started his preparation, like the snow monsters and spirit snakes, these were not very profitable businesses.

Especially when Fang Yuan planned to refine time path Immortal Gu.

Time cutting edge needed specific time path Immortal Gu. Fang Yuan thought about it and decided to give it a try. After all, the original time cutting edge had incredible attack power and prospects, Fang Yuan did not want to give up.

"Oh?" At this moment, Fang Yuan's expression changed.

At the next moment, Southern Border's Gu Immortals appeared around him, encircling him.

The leader was an old woman, it was the time path rank eight Gu Immortal Xia Cha, she smiled coldly at Fang Yuan: "Scoundrel Fang Yuan, you have finally fallen into my hands."

"Lord Lu Wei Yin is truly incredible, we found this demon at last!" Shang Hu Zhang laughed loudly.

"Kill, kill this demon and eliminate all future threats!" Tie Qu Zhong said loudly with deep killing intent.

Heavenly Court's spy Liu Hao had a grim expression, fixed space Immortal Gu was ready to activate in his immortal aperture, this Gu could counter Fixed Immortal Travel and prevent it from being used in a certain area.

Lu Wei Yin was silent, he wore his conical hat that covered his expression entirely.

Fang Yuan laughed instead: "You guys are too slow but you came after all, my planning was not in vain."

Southern Border's immortals were originally very excited, but upon hearing this, the atmosphere changed.

Xia Cha squinted as cold light flashed in her eyes: "Hmph, little scoundrel, you still want to deceive us when you are going to die?"

"That's right, he must be putting up a front! Lady Xia Cha has acted personally to conceal our traces." Someone shouted.

Fang Yuan smiled: "Of course I did not sense your presence, however, I could sense your deductions. Why do you think I purposely stayed in Southern Border, leaving behind clues and allowing you to make deductions on me?"

At the next moment, there was a loud sound as a formation activated!

Chapter 1601: Years Flow Execution Formation

The surrounding space became sealed, heaven and earth were fused at once, this was an area of blue space.

The Southern Border immortals' expressions changed.

"This is a trap!" Someone shouted.

Many people were flustered.

Lu Wei Yin was silent, while Xia Cha's gaze became increasingly cold, she stared at Fang Yuan fixedly.

Fang Yuan's smile gradually faded, turning into an expressionless face as he looked at these Southern Border Gu Immortals like he was a mighty deity.

In the past, when Eastern Sea's wisdom path genius Hua An made deductions on him, Fang Yuan did a reverse deduction and found out about Hua An's identity. And now, when these Southern Border Gu Immortals chased after Fang Yuan, they were also exposed to him!

Fang Yuan was a wisdom path grandmaster, how could he fall to their schemes so easily? He made himself bait to lure these Gu Immortals into a trap.

"Stay calm! We have strength in numbers, what can just Fang Yuan do?"

"That's right, we have Lady Xia Cha and Lord Lu Wei Yin, we are not afraid of his immortal battlefield!"

"This immortal battlefield does not seem to be yama battlefield."

"Of course, his yama battlefield has already been broken by Central Continent, the video is still playing in treasure yellow heaven, how can he still use it?"

Southern Border's immortals were brilliant figures, they soon calmed down and regained their morale.

At this time, Lu Wei Yin spoke: "This is not an immortal battlefield, it is a super immortal formation."

"Time path formation." Xia Cha added.

"Both of you are very perceptive." Fang Yuan smiled as he nodded.

Among Fang Yuan's immortal battlefields, the strongest were purple star broken life and yama battlefield. The former was used to kill Qin Bai He and You Chan, while the latter had trapped Feng Jiu Ge and kept him in a desperate situation.

But both were rank seven, they could not trap the rank eight Gu Immortals Xia Cha and Lu Wei Yin. Thus, Fang Yuan chose an immortal formation.

Immortal formations and immortal battlefields were different.

The Gu worms used for immortal battlefields were usually left on the Gu Immortal, and they would create an isolated environment for fighting. Meanwhile, for immortal formations, Gu worms remained in the outside world. Most immortal formations were defensive internally and offensive externally, Fang Yuan's time path formation had the effect of isolating the formation space, so that he could kill his enemies.

Boom boom boom!

Explosions occurred and continued unceasingly.

"Since this is an immortal formation, we can find the formation cores and destroy them to break this formation!" Some Gu Immortals were impatient, they started to attack and probe this formation.

But after a while, they found something amiss. The killer moves that burst out like fireworks were all extinguished without showing much effect.

Tie Qu Zhong's expression changed, he shouted to remind them: "Everyone be careful, this formation is already active."

"It is indeed a time path method to accelerate our killer moves and make them reach the time limit, causing them to fade away themselves." Liu Hao said in a dark tone.

The Southern Border Gu Immortals' attacks halted, they started to change their methods.

Chai clan's Gu Immortal puffed up his cheeks and blew out orange-red flames, they continued to spread out even when there was nothing to burn.

Qiao clan's Gu Immortal placed his palms together as large pieces of ice started to gather and sweep everywhere.

These methods were continuous and did not have much of a time limit.

Fang Yuan's gaze was cold, he watched these Southern Border Gu Immortals attack without stopping them.

At the next moment, the time path formation shook as the flames, ice, and other attacks all became slow.

The Gu Immortals who were attacking felt their hearts sinking.

"This immortal formation is so responsive, there must be people controlling it."

"Who can it be? It must be Shadow Sect's remaining members!"

The immortals conversed.

As they had expected, Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, Lady White Rabbit, Fairy Miao Yin, and Ying Wu Xie were all in charge of one formation core each, they were manipulating this time path formation to kill the Southern Border immortals.

Earlier, during the battle of Lang Ya, they were not strong enough to participate, but against these Southern Border pursuers, they were adequate.

Southern Border's immortals went against Ying Wu Xie and the rest, while Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin, and Xia Cha remained watching. The surrounding Gu Immortals subconsciously left some space for the three of them.

Fang Yuan's attention was on these two rank eight Gu Immortals. He knew clearly that these two would strike with a terrifying power the moment they attacked!

Lu Wei Yin and Xia Cha did not act, but they were starting to investigate Fang Yuan's immortal formation.

Lu Wei Yin was slightly frowning, he cultivated earth path, even though he could relate it to other paths, this time path formation was too intrinsic and brilliant, someone unfamiliar with it like him could not see through it easily.

But Xia Cha was a time path great grandmaster, she could see more things than Lu Wei Yin. However, Fang Yuan's time path formation did not just have time path in it, it was also a formation path product!

Xia Cha's formation path was only at ordinary attainment level.

If Fang Yuan took out a time path killer move, Xia Cha could easily understand it, but the time path formation had this layer of added difficulty, making it an obstacle for Xia Cha.

"Sect leader, we're ready!" At this time, Ying Wu Xie suddenly transmitted to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled as he replied: "Then let them all in."

Saying so, his figure faded in front of Lu Wei Yin's and Xia Cha's very eyes.

Howl—!

Right after he vanished, beast howls could be heard everywhere.

Howl! Howl! Howl! Howl! Gah!

At the next moment, a chain of wild beast cries started to resonate with each other.

A huge spiral formed from nothingness as countless year beasts charged out like a rushing tide.

These year beasts were of various forms, including monkey, snake, dragon, and tiger, they were all at least desolate beasts and even quite a few ancient desolate beasts among them.

In the formation space, other than year beasts, there were only the Southern Border immortals.

Wild year beasts did not have high intelligence, they soon directed their savage gazes towards the Southern Border Gu Immortals, they charged ahead.

"Kill them all." Xia Cha said indifferently.

Lu Wei Yin sighed.

The Southern Border immortals turned around and started to fight these year beasts.

Liu Hao waved his sleeves as countless flying blades shot out, slicing year beasts into pieces wherever they hit.

"It seems that there is a tributary of the River of Time here, Fang Yuan is trying the same method again, he used a similar formation back when he fought Feng Jiu Ge, the resemblance is uncanny!"

Fang Yuan had once used the flood discharge formation to send Feng Jiu Ge into the River of Time, but now, this formation was the combination of three formations, creating years flow execution formation.

Firstly, Shadow Sect had used the dense time path natural dao marks to create the immortal formation. This formation concealed the existence of the tributary of the River of Time, this made the Southern Border immortals unable to sense it.

Secondly was the flood discharge formation, it could connect to the tributary of the River of Time.

And finally, the immemorial year beast fishing formation! Fang Yuan used the rank eight Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water to create this formation, he could summon year beasts from the River of Time to fight against the Southern Border immortals.

Originally, Fang Yuan did not have the ability to do this, but after his time path attainment level reached grandmaster, his final insufficiencies to complete this were eliminated.

Fang Yuan's formation path and time path were grandmaster, he also had Hei Fan's true inheritance and Spectral Soul's true inheritance, with the help of the light of wisdom, he could deduce this super immortal formation and create this huge formation naturally!

"Kill!" Ba clan's Gu Immortal shouted as his body inflated to a giant size, he stomped as bloody water splattered, he had directly stomped an ancient year beast to death.

Puff! A great fire spread out and set dozens of year beasts on fire, Chai clan's Gu Immortal was bathed in flames, resembling a divine general.

Tie Qu Zhong was silent, his hands moved rapidly as golden light shot out with immense sharpness, splitting year beasts into halves easily like tofu.

"Demon Fang Yuan, we have to thank you for such a huge amount of wealth. Hahaha!" Shang Hu Zhang laughed as he used his wood path killer move, trapping the surrounding year beasts and keeping them in his immortal aperture.

These desolate level year beasts and ancient year beasts had wild mortal Gu but no Immortal Gu in them, against the Southern Border Gu Immortals, they were disadvantaged and easily slaughtered.

After all, these Southern Border Gu Immortals chasing after Fang Yuan were all powerful experts in their clan, they had at least rank seven cultivation level and were not ordinary at all. This result was to be expected.

Fang Yuan was still cold and calm, he had a faint smile and cold light in his eyes. This situation was within his deductions, the battle had just begun.

Howl…

Year beasts continued to stream into the formation, Southern Border's Gu Immortals were fighting against them tirelessly, but the year beasts just kept coming!

"Why are there so many?!"

"This demon Fang Yuan is trying to exhaust us!"

"Breaking apart this formation is the way to victory."

The Southern Border Gu Immortals conversed, they could tell what this battle was about. But they had no way of distracting themselves to do that.

Lu Wei Yin and Xia Cha were the most likely people to break the formation.

Caw caw!

At this time, the spiral suddenly expanded drastically as an arrogant year beast stepped into the battlefield.

A rank eight level immemorial year beast had finally been lured over.

The Southern Border immortals were shocked, Lu Wei Yin wanted to act but Tie Qu Zhong stood up: "Let us deal with it, both lords need to break open this formation, that is the wisest move!"

Tie Qu Zhong and several Southern Border rank seven experts faced off against the immemorial year rooster. They were powerful rank seven Gu Immortals after all, by working together, they could resist the immemorial year rooster for now.

"There is a formation core here." Suddenly, Xia Cha's eyes flashed as she pointed her finger, the rank eight killer move activated as profound light shot out, causing a huge sound. The formation shook thrice before it stabilized.

The Southern Border immortals were overjoyed, there was a formation core indeed, Xia Cha destroyed it according to everyone's expectations.

Fang Yuan snickered, muttering: "The formation's true power starts now."

The formation core was destroyed, a second spiral entrance appeared as large numbers of year beasts rushed in.

The immortals' expressions turned to shock.

Roar!

With a loud roar, an immemorial year tiger jumped into the battlefield.

"Let me." Lu Wei Yin moved for the first time, he grabbed with one hand, as a huge yellow hand formed and grasped the immemorial year tiger, preventing it from escaping despite its struggles.

Chapter 1602: Spring Scissors

The Southern Border immortals had a surge of morale, while Shadow Sect's members had twitching eyelids, their expressions were dark.

Lu Wei Yin was indeed Paradise Earth's inheritor, he managed to subdue a fierce immemorial year tiger in one move. Even though he had no attacking methods, this move was unfathomable and made people feel great admiration towards him.

Hiss hiss hiss…

An immemorial year snake dragged its thick and long body while hissing as it slithered out of the spiral entrance into the battlefield.

A third immemorial year beast!

This time, be it Lu Wei Yin or Xia Cha, their expressions changed.

Because this immemorial year snake had the aura of wild Immortal Gu in it. This immemorial year snake was much more dangerous than the previous two immemorial year beasts.

And most importantly, at this rate, a fourth or fifth immemorial year beast might appear without much doubt.

"What formation is this!" Qiao clan's Gu Immortal shouted, feeling deep pressure.

The other rank seven Gu Immortals all had heavy hearts, they were no longer as relaxed as before.

"I'll do it." At the crucial moment, Lu Wei Yin stood out again, facing the immemorial year snake.

But this time, he was very vigilant, before he probed what the Immortal Gu in the immemorial year snake's body were, he was not going to act rashly.

"Kill!" Southern Border's Gu Immortals shouted as they emitted strong killing intent.

The year beasts roared as they bore their fangs and claws.

The Southern Border Gu Immortals whipped up a bloody storm, countless year beasts died, but without destroying the spiral entrances, year beasts continued to pour into the formation unceasingly.

The year beasts kept coming, as the battle continued, Southern Border's Gu Immortals felt their conditions slipping as some started to get injured.

"There are too many year beasts, this formation must have been heavily modified, the year beast numbers far exceed the ones from Feng Jiu Ge's battle." Liu Hao was secretly shocked, he had some deductions from Heavenly Court, but he did not know how to hand them over. After all, he was not a time path or formation path Gu Immortal.

"This damned formation, we must destroy it for a chance of victory!"

"Actually, as long as we destroy a portion of it, we will be able to send out information and get reinforcements from our righteous path allies."

The Southern Border immortals knew how to deal with the situation, but they lacked methods to do so. This years flow execution formation was deduced by Fang Yuan after his time path attainment level rose, how could it be broken so easily?

"This time path formation is truly profound…" Xia Cha frowned, after finding the first formation core, she could not find the second one.

"The formation is complete and flawless. My formation path attainment is too low, maybe I should go all out and make this formation unable to handle the attack, I can create a flaw myself!" Xia Cha's killing intent surged.

She was Xia clan's first supreme elder, a time path great expert, she was an extremely proud expert, she was getting impatient after Fang Yuan's scheme trapped her here.

Lu Wei Yin could sense Xia Cha's intention as he quickly urged: "Don't fall into the demon's trap. Fang Yuan is very devious, even Heavenly Court cannot capture him. Shadow Sect had obtained Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage before, even though it was destroyed, many of the Immortal Gu were left in their hands. If you attack with your full strength, you might fall into Fang Yuan's trap, he would use it against you."

Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage's signature method was to seal the enemy's attack and send it back at them.

Lu Wei Yin spoke earnestly and wisely, even Fang Yuan raised his brows. Even though he was not a wisdom path Gu Immortal, his deductions were accurate, this years flow execution formation used almost all of Fang Yuan's time path Immortal Gu, the Immortal Gu in Hei Fan's true inheritance were used as the cores while Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage's Immortal Gu were used the supplement them.

Xia Cha listened to him and breathed in deeply, she snorted coldly and looked towards the immemorial year rooster in the battlefield.

The immemorial year rooster was being attacked by a group of Southern Border immortals. They were all rank seven and had powerful killer moves, but against the immemorial year rooster, their attacks were simply like light scratches.

The immemorial year rooster had rank eight battle strength, it also had a sturdy body and could not be harmed by the Southern Border immortals even if they tried.

But when Xia Cha's gaze turned to the immemorial year rooster, it felt a strong threat as it raised its head, breaking away from the Southern Border immortals and charging at her.

"A mere beast." Xia Cha laughed from anger, aura of many Gu worms burst out of her body, forming into an immortal killer move.

A pair of scissors that was jade green in color and large as an elephant flew towards the immemorial year rooster's neck as it clipped.

The immemorial year rooster felt no pain, it endured the move that felt like spring, as a warm wind was blowing, the sun was bright, the grass and flowers emitted fragrance that spread to everyone's noses.

After a momentary daze, the immemorial year rooster's neck had a deep cut as blood spewed out of it like a fountain.

THe immemorial year rooster shuddered, its vicious nature was triggered as it raised its speed, moving towards Xia Cha.

Xia Cha did not dodge, right before the immemorial year rooster hit her, she vanished like a bursting bubble.

Next, the jade green scissors flew towards the immemorial year rooster's head again, clipping at its neck.

Xia Cha vanished entirely, the immemorial year rooster's attention was lured to the jade green scissors, both sides fought relentlessly.

"This is Xia Cha's spring scissors, it is truly powerful and extraordinary." Fang Yuan who was hidden watched the battle closely, upon seeing this result, the relevant information appeared in his mind.

Xia Cha had a set of killer moves, four in total, spring scissors was just one of them. Undeniably, this was a rank eight offensive killer move, it was extremely sharp and even the immemorial year rooster's sturdy body could not protect it from the sharp scissors.

Fang Yuan was secretly envious.

This was something he needed the most now.

Spectral Soul's true inheritance had rank eight time path killer moves too, but Fang Yuan lacked the necessary rank eight Immortal Gu. Even if he modified them and used rank six or seven Immortal Gu as replacement, the power could not reach rank eight.

Fang Yuan's sole rank eight time path Immortal Gu, Years Flow Like Water, had several killer moves in Hei Fan true inheritance that used it as the core. For example, year beast summoning, unlucky year and others.

Rank eight year beast summoning could summon immemorial year beasts to fight for Fang Yuan.

And unlucky year that used Years Flow Like Water as the core could mimic luck path's effect using time path. But both were not attacks like spring scissors, it had an immediate impact in battle.

Thus, Fang Yuan could only place his attention on time cutting edge.

Caw caw!

The immemorial year rooster had no wild Immortal Gu, it could not rival Xia Cha's spring scissors, it was injured all over its body as it cried out in pain.

Xia Cha had only used one move, but she managed to heavily injure an immemorial year beast, it showed how powerful she was.

"As expected of the person holding the greatest authority in Xia clan! Such strength is already on the level of Heavenly Court's members." Fang Yuan sighed internally.

Seeing that the immemorial year rooster was about to die in Xia Cha's hands, the formation activated, the immemorial year rooster vanished on the spot.

"Submit to me." Behind the scenes, Fang Yuan targeted this weakened immemorial year rooster as he used his overbearing enslavement path method, the immemorial year rooster had no choice but to lower its head, submitting to Fang Yuan.

Thus, Fang Yuan successfully obtained the immemorial year rooster.

He helped the year beasts to fight the Southern Border pursuers while also using the Southern Border pursuers to weaken the year beasts so he could enslave them.

This old method had already been used back in Western Desert when Heavenly Court pursued him.

But repetitive methods were not a problem as long as they worked.

She was about to kill the immemorial year rooster and obtain all of its rank eight immortal materials that were worth a fortune, but to think that it would vanish on the spot.

Many of Southern Border's Gu Immortals scolded angrily while Xia Cha's expression turned dark, but she smiled at once: "You finally exposed a flaw, so what if you get a few immemorial year beasts?"

It turned out that Fang Yuan's formation would not be exposed if he only transported year beasts. But once he moved the immemorial year rooster, the formation would have to be shifted and that would give Xia Cha an opportunity to learn more about it.

As expected, not long after, she found the second formation core and destroyed it.

But the Southern Border immortals' cheering did not last long, after the formation core was destroyed, it turned into a spiral entrance that transported more year beasts inside.

"How can this be?" The Southern Border immortals were stunned.

Chapter 1603: Summer Fan

More and more year beasts entered the battlefield, fighting against the Southern Border immortals.

As time passed, the conditions of the Southern Border immortals continued to slip unconsciously.

They were about to puke from killing these year beasts, it was simply never going to end. The killer moves prepared for Fang Yuan and the cooperation between Gu Immortals were all used on these year beasts, they were truly helpless and tired beyond belief.

Years flow execution formation was made of three formations, while the tributary of the River of Time here was huge and had the support of Fang Yuan and the rest, the great power made these immortals feel great pressure.

A moment later, even Lu Wei Yin was panting roughly. Not only was he facing two immemorial year beasts alone, he was also secretly helping the rank seven Gu Immortals.

Whenever one immemorial year beast lost, Fang Yuan would take it away and enslave it. But soon, a new immemorial year beast would be lured into the battlefield.

Lu Wei Yin and Xia Cha faced huge pressure consistently, the battle was intense.

But they still made great progress. During this period of time, Xia Cha found two more formation cores and destroyed them. These two formation cores did not turn into new spiral entrances, the current years flow execution formation could only sustain three spiral entrances, this was its limit.

This intense battle lasted for an entire day.

Fang Yuan gained seven immemorial year beasts, while Xia Cha destroyed nine formation cores.

The entire years flow execution formation was already shaking, it was no longer as sturdy as before.

"The time is now." Fang Yuan snickered as he finally acted.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

A sinister hand whipped up eerie winds as it flew out of an ancient year beast's mouth. Tie Qu Zhong was caught off guard, he lost an Immortal Gu to this huge hand.

"My rank seven edge Gu!" He coughed out a mouthful of blood, his killer move failed and the backlash made him heavily injured. However, he felt greater pain from the loss of his rank seven edge Gu, Fang Yuan had stolen it away!

"Hahaha, not bad, not bad at all, it's edge Gu after all." Fang Yuan laughed in happiness, this edge Gu was what he needed now, it was one of the core Immortal Gu of the killer move time cutting edge.

"Friend from Tie clan, hold on, I will save you!" Shang Hu Zhang and the rest saw that Tie Qu Zhong was attacked, they quickly forced their way past the year beasts to reinforce him.

Fang Yuan was hidden behind the scenes, laughing to himself coldly.

He did not kill Tie Qu Zhong, he wanted their reinforcement.

"Oh no!"

"This is an ambush!"

"We were tricked!!"

The Southern Border Gu Immortals who came to help were all attacked, they were robbed by the great thief ghost hands that stole multiple Immortal Gu.

"Everyone be careful, some of these year beasts are enslaved by Fang Yuan, they are very dangerous!!" Shang Hu Zhang had no time to mourn over the loss of his Immortal Gu, he was sweating from shock as he quickly shouted.

If this was the start of the battle and the Southern Border immortals had their full battle strength, great thief ghost hand would not be able to get close. But now, they were exhausted and their battle strength fell drastically, their attentiveness had also fallen, Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand was finally usable.

Great thief ghost hand was concealed to begin with, while Fang Yuan had schemed and placed many ghost hands inside the ancient year beasts' mouths.

The Southern Border immortals were all extremely alarmed by this and wary, they started to attack more frequently and stayed guarded, any year beast that tried to get close would be attacked before they reached.

At once, Southern Border's side gained the advantage again.

Fang Yuan remained calm, no longer taking overt action.

Soon, Southern Border's Gu Immortals experienced a fall in battle strength again, they had fought for too long, they could not sustain that intense offense for long.

Fang Yuan waited for his chance before acting again.

The Southern Border Gu Immortals were hit again, multiple Immortal Gu were stolen by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan could only use one great thief ghost hand at a time, but inside the years flow execution formation, he could use the formation to summon three at once.

It was unlike an immortal battlefield like purple star broken life where great thief ghost hand would be suppressed by the environment, this formation space had no dao marks, great thief ghost hand would not be strengthened but it could display its usual power at least.

The killer move unlucky year had already been used with years flow execution formation, Fang Yuan's luck was too dominant, when these Southern Border Gu Immortals had their Immortal Gu stolen, most were the cores of their killer moves, or those that Fang Yuan needed.

After another round of stealing, several Southern Border Gu Immortals faced the backlash of their killer moves and suffered deep injuries.

But regrettably, Lu Wei Yin and Xia Cha had impeccable defenses, they destroyed the two great thief ghost hands targeted at them. They even had the energy to help the other rank seven Gu Immortals, especially Lu Wei Yin, even without an offensive method, he was extremely skilled at defending the other Gu Immortals. If not for him, there would be Gu Immortals dying already.

Fang Yuan did not use lead soul into dream now.

Lead soul into dream had already been known for a while, the Gu Immortals of the five regions were guarded against it. And most importantly, if the move activation failed, Fang Yuan would be dragged into the dream, thus, he had been very careful about using it.

Unless he did it like Ying Wu Xie, using the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique to use this move. In that case, even if he failed, there would not be any problems.

There were no invincible killer moves, they would gradually get countered. Great thief ghost hand was going to face the same problem eventually, unless Fang Yuan modified it as time passed.

But now, great thief ghost hand had been used far less than lead soul into dream, with the help of the killer move unlucky year, the Southern Border immortals in their poor states were susceptible to great thief ghost hand, turning the situation towards Fang Yuan's favor.

But at this moment, Xia Cha suddenly shouted: "Break!"

The winds around her whipped like a storm, lightning crackled, these illusions condensed into a huge fan that she held in her hands.

Xia Cha waved her fan as Fang Yuan grunted, his seven orifices bled as the formation core that he was at broke apart, exposing his location. He was the one controlling the formation and manipulating three great thief ghost hands, while also enslaving immemorial year beasts and arranging the year beast army, his remaining thoughts were not enough to activate reverse flow protection seal.

Xia Cha waved towards her left, Bai Ning Bing felt a huge threat as she used the killer move Bai Xiang, before shattering from the impact of the killer move.

Xia Cha waved towards her right, Lady White Rabbit could not dodge in time, the formation core shattered as her entire body burst into blood and flesh, she died!

The battle had suddenly changed, the Southern Border immortals did not even have the time to cheer in reaction.

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

After three waves, the years flow execution formation was about to break, Fang Yuan and the rest were injured, Xia Cha breathed roughly as the dimmed fan in her hands lit up again.

If she waved it again, Fang Yuan and the rest would lose for sure.

"To think that Xia Cha had already deduced the years flow execution formation so deeply. She could clearly destroy a few more formation cores earlier, but she controlled herself and attacked with a devastating blow at once. If I did not use great thief ghost hand and threatened them, she might not have used this method!" Fang Yuan's heart shook.

Xia Cha's performance exceeded the contents of Shadow Sect's information, her time path attainment level was perhaps not just great grandmaster! It was possible that she had formation path attainment level too, but nobody knew about it. How could the foundation of a rank eight Gu Immortal be so easily exposed?

This years flow execution formation was a true rank eight immortal formation, Fang Yuan used it to trap the Southern Border pursuers, including two rank eights, Lu Wei Yin and Xia Cha.

This was the specialty of formation path.

As long as the formation was set up, it could fight against many enemies, and allow the Gu Immortal to display above average battle strength.

But formation path's weakness was that once the formation becomes clear to the enemy, they would destroy it and that would cause the Gu Immortal controlling it to face huge backlashes. They might even get heavily injured or die.

Right now, Fang Yuan was facing this crisis. If the formation broke apart, his injuries would be unimaginable. Even if he used reverse flow protection seal now, it would be very awkward. The reflected damage would go to the Gu worms that made the formation, he would basically lose them.

The formation space was already breaking apart, the Southern Border immortals could see the Gu worms surrounding them with their naked eyes.

"Fang Yuan, it is time to die!" Liu Hao shouted in excitement, at this moment, he used fixed space Immortal Gu.

Instantly, Fang Yuan got hit and could not use Fixed Immortal Travel in this area.

"Escape, but even if you run to the River of Time, I can kill you there." Xia Cha waved her fan as she smiled proudly.

"Escape? Why would I escape?" Even in this desperate situation, Fang Yuan's eyes shone with an eerie light.

The Southern Border immortals were stunned, at the next moment, the ancient year beasts around them turned stiff as rocks, dream realms swept out like huge gusts of wind from their bodies, quickly covering the area.

The Southern Border immortals were shocked, they tried to dodge.

Even Xia Cha's eyelids were twitching, she quickly waved her fan.

But this powerful immortal killer move was useless and completely ineffective against the dream realms.

Some tried to escape in a panic, but the formation had not broken apart yet, the immortals were still trapped in this immortal formation.

The dream realms quickly closed up as Xia Cha, Lu Wei Yin, and the rest were trapped, before it extended to the surroundings and started to corrode the years flow execution formation.

Soon, the entire years flow execution formation was submerged by dream realms, it lost its use immediately.

The noisy battlefield turned silent all of a sudden.

Even those year beasts were affected by the dream realms and fell asleep.

"This is the power of dream path!" Fairy Miao Yin gasped in amazement.

"No wonder almost all forces want to explore and research on the dream realm." Bai Ning Bing recovered already, in Bai Xiang form, she could regenerate with even a tiny fragment.

It was a pity that Lady White Rabbit had died in this battle.

One skill to dominate the world.

Dream path was a brand new path, it was like theft path, transformation path, and luck path back then, when they were first created, they were nearly unstoppable. During this period of time, existing paths were unlikely to have measures that could counter or resist it.

Chapter 1604: Captives

The mountains were filled with lush forests, the sky was clear and cloudless.

A strange light suddenly made its appearance, it then dimmed and turned into a strange tall man.

This person had a pair of thin white brows that extended towards the outer sides of his face. The pair of eyes under the snowy brows were closed. He was dressed in white clothes that was not stained by even a single speck of dust, the robe as well his skin and hair all released a faint trace of radiance.

This radiance was not glaring, but made him appear divine.

This person was Jun Shen Guang, a rank eight Gu Immortal who cultivated light path, and was a supreme elder of one of the ten great ancient sects in Central Continent. He had recently been recruited into Heavenly Court by Fairy Zi Wei.

"Liu Hao disappeared here." Jun Shen Guang's eyes were closed, but he seemed to be able to see the outside world clearly.

Shortly, he found many traces of battle.

"This does not look good for Liu Hao. There was definitely a fierce battle here, unfortunately Liu Hao did not even send any request for reinforcements. Was it an immortal formation or an immortal battlefield?"

Jun Shen Guang frowned with a heavy expression.

Liu Hao was a spy of Heavenly Court put in Southern Border's forces with the help of Wu clan. He held fixed space Immortal Gu which specially targeted Fang Yuan's Fixed Immortal Travel.

As for Jun Shen Guang, he was backup arranged by Fairy Zi Wei. If Southern Border's Gu Immortals fought Fang Yuan and made him escape with heavy injuries, Jun Shen Guang, who specialized in tracking methods, would be Fang Yuan's fatal assassin.

"The Southern Border team who is chasing after Fang Yuan consists of experts from their respective clans. Most of them are rank seven experts, they can preserve their lives even when facing an immemorial desolate beast."

Tie clan's Tie Qu Zhong had impressive battle achievements in the current Southern Border Gu Immortal world, and was known as Great Sir Tie! When he made his debut, he had captured and killed over ten demonic path Gu Immortals. Southern Border's demonic immortals trembled at his name.

Shang clan's Shang Hu Zhang cultivated transformation path and wood path, and had methods to make the two paths not conflict with each other, much like Thunder Ghost True Monarch. His methods were complex and comprehensive, he was a peak rank seven expert of Shang clan!

Yang clan's Yang Ku was one of the peak representative experts of soul path in Southern Border's Gu Immortal world. He had once destroyed the nest of a herd of ancient desolate beasts by himself, and had successfully escaped from the pursuit of an immemorial desolate beast.

These rank seven Gu Immortals could be said to be elites of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, any one of them was a trump card expert of their force.

"Not to mention this group also has the current Paradise Earth inheritor Lu Wei Yin, as well as Xia clan's first supreme elder Xia Cha!"

These two did not need to be explained, they were both rank eight Gu Immortals!

Jun Shen Guang heaved a deep sigh.

It was because of this grand team that Jun Shen Guang had been at ease. Even if they fought Fang Yuan, Jun Shen Guang would have enough time to quietly sneak closer.

Jun Shen Guang had been wary of Lu Wei Yin's and Xia Cha's methods, being worried they would discover him and create a misunderstanding. So he had been following from far behind without daring to come closer.

"Two rank eights as well as several rank seven experts, they had all done enough preparation and had all kinds of methods to target Fang Yuan, yet they still lost! And this was not just a loss, it was a complete defeat."

Jun Shen Guang repeatedly shook his head.

"Fang Yuan should have made use of dream realms!" Soon, his gaze landed on the only small dream realm in the battlefield, becoming even more certain of his guess: "Besides using dream realms, Fang Yuan's other methods, no matter how much incisive they are, cannot create such a result. Hmm?"

Just as Jun Shen Guang was carefully inspecting the battlefield, he suddenly looked towards the south.

There was no one in the boundless clear sky.

But in Jun Shen Guang's investigative range, an Immortal Gu House was rushing over.

Jun Shen Guang did not need to identify the aura to know that these were Southern Border natives.

The Immortal Gu House was extremely fast, but it would still take a short while to reach here. Jun Shen Guang knew he had to use this time to quickly leave this place.

Because this Immortal Gu House had a great reputation and Southern Border Gu Immortals had many strange investigative killer moves, if they discovered Jun Shen Guang, there was definitely going to be a misunderstanding.

Not long after Jun Shen Guang disappeared, the Immortal Gu House arrived.

This Immortal Gu House was not glorious or grand, and looked just like a bamboo building from outside.

This bamboo building had two stories, made entirely out of bamboo, there were even bamboo leaves growing on the bamboos, drops of dew were dripping down from the leaves, green as jade.

It was the awe-inspiring rank eight Immortal Gu House — Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building!

Wu Yong had used this Immortal Gu House to retaliate and firmly stabilize Wu clan's position as the number one force.

The bamboo building's entrance opened from which a rank eight Gu Immortal flew out.

This person was a middle aged man with an ordinary appearance, but had a well-built body. His sharp eyebrows were slightly raised, giving him a dark and hazy aura. But his actions were full of a mighty prestige that no one could neglect.

He was Wu Yong, Wu clan's current first supreme elder.

Another person flew out right after Wu Yong.

This person was old but energetic. He had deep, dark eyes and his cheekbones were protruding out. He also emitted rank eight aura. He was Chi clan's first supreme elder Chi Qu You.

With the two rank eight Gu Immortals at the lead, several rank seven Gu Immortals rushed out of Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building. They came from various clans, and every one of them had an anxious expression.

"They disappeared here!" The Ba clan Gu Immortal's expression was dark.

"Quickly investigate what happened here. My clan cannot reach our first supreme elder." Xia clan's Gu Immortals were extremely anxious.

Thereupon, all kinds of investigative killer moves were thrown out in succession, and in just a while, this place had been completely searched over dozens of times.

Every person, including the two rank eight Gu Immortals, had a steely expression.

"It looks like there was a tributary of the River of Time here."

"There was also a time path immortal level formation, the group rushed here then fought a very fierce battle!"

"What is up with this dream realm?" Someone saw that remaining small dream realm left behind by Fang Yuan.

Like Jun Shen Guang before, Southern Border immortals' gaze was quickly attracted to this dream realm.

Besides this dream realm, all other traces were removed by Fang Yuan, the remaining ones had no value. The only clue was this dream realm.

"Be careful." The Southern Border immortals gradually separated and encircled this small dream realm.

"This dream realm is continuously shrinking." Someone suddenly exclaimed.

Shortly, the other immortals also noticed that the dream realm was indeed shrinking and quite rapidly at that.

After a while, several Gu worms fell out of the shrinking dream realm.

Southern Border Gu Immortals quickly caught and carefully inspected them.

They found that these Gu worms were wild information path mortal Gu. Then they discovered that there were actually some messages left within these information path mortal Gu.

The contents of the messages were simple, but it made the expressions of the Southern Border immortals rapidly change to that of extreme shock!

"Friends of Southern Border, I am notifying you that your clansmen are in my, Fang Yuan's, hands. If you want to redeem them, please wait for my message."

"This, this, this…" One person was tongue-tied, his whole body started trembling as he stammered while pointing at the information path mortal Gu in his hand.

"Blatant lies! How can this be possible? Our organized team was actually captured by Fang Yuan? Hmph!" Someone fiercely shook their head, repeatedly denying this: "This must be a huge fraud!!!"

"But none of us can contact any of those clansmen." Someone retorted.

The Southern Border Gu Immortals fell into dead silence.

They were so still that they looked like human shaped statues from afar.

Wind blew, soft air blew the sleeves of the immortals.

Chi Qu You's white beard slightly shook in the wind.

Wu Yong's expression was ashen, he closed his eyes heavily and only after a long time, he opened them slowly.

No matter how unimaginable it was, the truth was right in front of them!

And the truth forced them to accept this cruel fact.

Southern Border's righteous path brought in many people to organize a troop of experts to specially chase and kill Fang Yuan, but not only were they unable to kill Fang Yuan, they were instead taken captive by Fang Yuan!

Slap!

This was like a fierce slap at these Southern Border's righteous path Gu Immortals' faces. The slap stupefied them, while their cheeks started swelling rapidly.

"When we discovered we were unable to contact Xia Cha and the rest, we hurriedly assembled a team and came to reinforce them, altogether it has only been a few hours. Lord Chi, do you think this is because of a time path formation?" Wu Yong suddenly broke the silence, his voice slightly hoarse.

His words were vague, but others understood what Wu Yong's meaning was.

Chi Qu You slowly nodded, saying in a heavy voice: "We have already deduced the strength of Fang Yuan and Shadow Sect members, we even evaluated them carefully. Based on the battle strength of Xia Cha and the rest, it is impossible for them to be taken captive by Fang Yuan in such a short period of time. There is indeed a time path formation here, it is shockingly complex, being at rank eight level, far beyond ordinary."

Chi Qu You was a formation path great grandmaster who was able to set up an immortal formation by using just the dao marks in the natural environment. Fang Yuan had cleaned up the battlefield, but it would not be possible for all the dao marks to be cleaned in such a short period of time, so there were still a large amount of time path dao marks remaining in the battlefield.

Based on the movement and number of these time path dao marks, Chi Qu You was certain a time path formation had been set up in this place.

Wu Yong nodded his head slightly: "That's right. Lu Wei Yin and Xia Cha are both rank eight immortals, it is not easy to restrain these two unless it was a rank nine immortal battlefield, either that or a rank eight level immortal formation. We rushed over, although we appeared quickly, a long period of time might have gone by in this time path formation."

A Shang clan Gu Immortal spoke at this time: "I remember that in treasure yellow heaven, Heavenly Court had exposed a formation of Fang Yuan that can be set up in a tributary of the River of Time to lure a huge amount of year beasts to fight."

Many Gu Immortals' expressions became dark upon hearing these words.

Chapter 1605: Imprisoning the Hostages

An approximate outline of the truth had manifested in the Southern Border immortals' minds.

"Among these year beasts, there are likely to be immemorial year beasts and not in a small number too. Fang Yuan indeed has the ability to battle the pursuing team with these year beasts. Moreover, this demon Fang Yuan has inherited Shadow Sect, he has countless true inheritances, constructing a time path formation that can trap our clansmen is within his capabilities."

Chi Qu You paused here before continuing with a frown: "It is just that I still don't understand some things. If it was an immortal aperture which had been placed and hidden into one spot, it is normal for others to be unable to sense it. But can a time path formation be hidden so well? Both Xia Cha and Lu Wei Yin were unable to sense it?"

Time path formations were not that good at concealment unlike phantom path, space path, or theft path.

Xia Cha and the rest were trapped in the formation, and had to battle with immemorial year beasts before finally being taken captive because of the dream realms. This could be understood.

However!

The most unusual thing was at the very start. They actually did not discover and even directly rushed into Fang Yuan's trap.

Even Chi Qu You, a formation path great grandmaster, was bewildered.

It was not that time path formations could not be concealed, it was just extremely difficult to conceal them to this degree, it would be much more difficult than space path, theft path, phantom path or other paths.

Chi Qu You had never heard of such a time path immortal formation that could be concealed to such a degree that even two rank eight Gu Immortals could not sense it.

"The dream realm has dissipated, wait a second, there is a person inside!" Someone exclaimed.

Right at this time, the dream realm's transformation broke the Southern Border immortals' thoughts. This small dream realm that was left in the battlefield actually contained a person?

Soon, this person's appearance was revealed, he was Lu Wei Yin.

He was holding his arms across his chest, his eyes were shut as if he was in a deep sleep, unmoving like a statue.

But following the dream realm's dissipation, he soon opened his eyes and regained clarity.

"You…" Lu Wei Yin's expression changed slightly when he saw Wu Yong and the rest, he then looked at his surroundings and blurted out: "Oh no!"

"Lord Lu Wei Yin, please explain what in the world happened to all of you."

"Right! Did my clan's Gu Immortals really fall into Fang Yuan's hands?"

"Wait a second, we cannot be sure of his identity yet."

The situation instantly became noisy from the discussions between the Southern Border immortals.

"Let's first verify his identity. Fang Yuan has familiar face and also has methods to quickly escape from dream realms." Wu Yong said.

Chi Qu You was silent, but his body moved slightly, trapping Lu Wei Yin with Wu Yong in the front and him at the back.

Lu Wei Yin was slightly stunned before nodding: "Go ahead."

The Southern Border immortals had unique inspection methods. And for safety purposes, these methods were not limited to just one kind, they were complicated and varied.

After a while, the expressions of Wu Yong and the rest softened a little. Lu Wei Yin verified his identity, he was the real deal and not Fang Yuan's disguise.

Lu Wei Yin then quickly informed them of what he encountered.

After the Southern Border Gu Immortals learned of the information, their expressions became incomparably ashen, once again falling into deathly silence.

Lu Wei Yin shook his head and sighed: "I am ashamed, I don't have any offensive methods and could only watch the situation happen. If I did not possess special methods that can protect me in dream realms, I might also have fallen into Fang Yuan's hands."

"Forget it for now, let's return first." Wu Yong took a deep glance at Lu Wei Yin, then his sleeves waved as he entered Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building.

Not long after the Southern Border Gu Immortals left, a strange light shot towards the area, turning into Heavenly Court's Jun Shen Guang.

Jun Shen Guang inspected the traces in the battlefield and frowned after a while, mumbling: "This time path formation is extremely mysterious, looking at the traces of the dao marks, there are no dao marks of phantom path, space path, or theft path. It is not a combined immortal formation, and is purely a time path immortal formation, but it actually concealed itself to the extent where Xia Cha and Lu Wei Yin could not sense it."

Rank eight Gu Immortals had deep foundation.

Xia Cha had plentiful methods as the first supreme elder of the super force Xia clan. And Lu Wei Yin was an inheritor of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable. Neither of them actually sensed this grand formation, causing the group of Southern Border Gu Immortals to fall into the trap.

Jun Shen Guang checked several times, confirming there were indeed no other clues, he then turned into a strange light that quickly disappeared.

Sovereign blessed land.

A large castle-like formation that was letting out silver radiance suddenly floated in Mini Green Heaven.

Fang Yuan's time path clone as well as Shadow Sect immortals were surrounding this immortal formation, paying close attention to the captives inside.

Most of these captives were the Southern Border immortals whom Fang Yuan had ambushed and captured. Shang Hu Zhang, Tie Qu Zhong, Yang Ku, and so on were experts of rank seven, right now, they were firmly locked up, their eyes were closed as they were trapped in dream realms.

The strongest captive was the rank eight Gu Immortal Xia Cha who was given utmost attention by Fang Yuan. An extremely dense dream realm surrounded and fluctuated around her.

Pure will would be worn down when they fell into dream realms, but they would immediately recover if they escaped the dream realm. But the soul was different, even if they were taken out of the dream realm, they would still be trapped in the dream for a certain period of time, it would be as if they were struck by the killer move lead soul into dream.

It was because of this crucial point that Fang Yuan could capture these Southern Border Gu Immortals and move them into his sovereign immortal aperture.

In this present time, the old immortal killer moves had no effect on dream realms. Even Immortal Gu Houses like Bay Pavilion and Heaven Overseeing Tower started disintegrating when they fell into dream realms.

To be in a dream realm for Gu Immortals was to be in dire straits.

But Fang Yuan had an extraordinary method, that was the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique!

Fang Yuan had the immortal killer move pure dream reality seeker transformation which he used to transform the dream realms in his sovereign immortal aperture into Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies. He then used these temporary dream path clones to enter the dream realms and take out the Southern Border Gu Immortals, locking them up inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

He then turned the dream realms in the battlefield to Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies and successfully retrieved them.

Finally, he hurriedly cleaned the battlefield, not leaving behind any clues before he left.

So when Jun Shen Guang and Southern Border's immortals arrived, they saw such a scene.

The time path clone's brows slightly furrowed: "Although we are using the dream realm to imprison these Gu Immortals, there is a huge risk. If any one of them wakes up and causes havoc in my sovereign immortal aperture, it will really be a great loss."

To Gu Immortals, the immortal aperture was an important resource area as well as the foundation of their cultivation. The hidden risk in imprisoning these Gu Immortals here was really huge.

"One skill to dominate the world, most Gu Immortals are helpless against dream realms currently. Even rank eight Gu Immortals can meet their calamity in dream realm. But just in case, I need to grab this time to take out these Gu Immortals' Gu worms and resources. Then, I will use soul path methods to separate their souls and bodies, only then will the situation be safe."

Fang Yuan thought of Lu Wei Yin.

This person was trapped in a dream realm, but when a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body went to take him out, it actually lost its way and was unable to approach him!

Being able to show effect in a dream realm, this was clearly a dream path method!

Recalling a past event, Fang Yuan had been ambushed by Lu Wei Yin and had gone through three lifetimes, that was also a dream path method.

Lu Wei Yin was not only an inheritor of Paradise Earth, he was also moving forward with the era, and held at least two dream path methods, almost similar to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's dream path methods were only unravel dream, lead soul into dream, and switch soul in dream.

It was because of this that Fang Yuan gave up on capturing Lu Wei Yin. Even if he could take him away, Fang Yuan did not dare to take the risk. Who knew if he had some other dream path methods. In case he woke up in the sovereign immortal aperture, that would truly be an example of luring a wolf into one's house, without any way of expelling it!

"Sigh, I really did not expect there to be a day where these high and mighty Gu Immortals would become our prisoners!" Fairy Miao Yin sighed with emotions.

Although she was one of the famous fairies of Southern Border, she was a lone cultivator and had suffered a lot at the hands of Southern Border's righteous path. She had deep resentment towards these famed experts of Southern Border's righteous path.

"Such a pity that sister White Rabbit died. Sigh…" Fairy Miao Yin's expression was truly mournful.

When she joined Shadow Sect, she had become very close with Lady White Rabbit, because she liked the latter's straightforwardness.

Lady White Rabbit had inherited the Black Tigress true inheritance and would turn into Black Tigress when faced with life-threatening danger, her cultivation would also soar to rank seven. Regretfully, she faced Xia Cha's direct attack using immortal killer move Summer Fan, she simply did not have time to react and died immediately.

Fang Yuan was powerless to help, Man as Before was only a rank six Immortal Gu and had no hope for success against such an injury.

Even Fang Yuan's main body was heavily injured at the moment.

It was Bai Ning Bing instead who had no injuries.

At the crucial moment, she turned into Bai Xiang, although it was shattered into pieces, Bai Xiang could resurrect with just a small fragment.

This move had once shaken Southern Border, renowned as the White Terror that had shrouded the whole of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world. Its profundity was that it could remove all harmful dao marks along with most of the body, then revive with just a tiny fragment.

However, Bai Ning Bing's current expression did not look good.

She looked at the trapped Southern Border immortals, thinking to herself: "Even if I use Bai Xiang, I will still be trapped in the dream realm with no strength to resist. Strange, Fang Yuan actually did not use such a method to deal with me. He already has methods to resolve the alliance agreement on him, if I were him…"

Bai Ning Bing felt a huge pressure.

After all, she was not a Shadow Sect member, and moreover, she was currently in Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture which was the same as being in someone else's headquarters.

The stronger Fang Yuan's strength and methods, the greater the pressure on Bai Ning Bing.

"Alright, Ying Wu Xie, you shall remain here, I have lent you the Gu worms. In the next few days, you will be in charge of guarding this place, if anything abnormal occurs, use a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body to activate lead soul into dream to continue putting these Southern Border Gu Immortals to sleep."

"Formation Spirit, guard this place properly. If the dream realm moves and endangers the formation, inform me immediately."

Fang Yuan's time path clone issued two commands.

"Yes, sect leader."

"Understood, master."

Supervision should be sufficient enough with Ying Wu Xie and the Formation Spirit, Fang Yuan was able to put his heart at ease slightly.

Chapter 1606: Spring, Summer, Autumn, Winter

In the sovereign immortal aperture's time, several days later.

Fang Yuan's time path clone once again went in front of the immortal formation in Mini Green Heaven.

"Be careful, I am going to start." The time path clone said solemnly.

"Okay." The Formation Spirit materialized, nodding its head.

There was a Gu Immortal standing to the side, he was Ying Wu Xie, looking tense at this moment.

A Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body entered the dream realm, not long later, it grabbed Xia Cha's foot and dragged her out.

The whole process was done cautiously.

Xia Cha was still in a deep sleep, she showed no abnormal movements.

Even though Fang Yuan was using a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique clone, he only dared to drag out half of this rank eight Gu Immortal's body.

Xia Cha's upper half was still inside the dream realm, while the lower half was exposed outside the dream realm.

The crucial immortal aperture was near her stomach area, so it was okay to do this.

Next, it was the turn of Fang Yuan's main body. He had already prepared for a while, activating immortal killer move great thief ghost hand immediately.

The eerie great thief ghost hand slowly flew towards Xia Cha's immortal aperture. However, before it could touch her, wisps of dao marks shined on her body.

This was a passive time path method, even if Xia Cha was deep in sleep, it could automatically activate.

This defensive method could show no effect in the dream realm. But Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand also was useless in dream realms.

Only by dragging Xia Cha outside the dream realm could Fang Yuan steal her Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan was not even the slightest bit surprised at seeing the great thief ghost hand being obstructed.

He had been making attempts since a few days back, and this was not the first time.

This time path defensive move was indeed troublesome, but with his time path attainment level and using the light of wisdom, Fang Yuan had already deduced a way to get rid of it.

Thereupon, Fang Yuan activated another killer move.

The killer move showed remarkable effect, the dao marks light on Xia Cha's body dimmed immediately, the great thief ghost hand successfully disappeared into her immortal aperture.

"Fortunately, Xia Cha's defensive method is not as remarkable as the people of Heavenly Court. It is probably a temporary arrangement to deal with my great thief ghost hand, which is why I was able to resolve this move within a short period of time."

This time path defensive move was only a rank seven move. Fang Yuan used his time path Immortal Gu along with many mortal Gu to form a killer move that could get rid of it.

"In the ambush against Southern Border's pursuing forces using the time path formation, the important time path Immortal Gu were not damaged, but almost all the mortal Gu as well as multiple rank six time path Immortal Gu were destroyed. This is rather damaging to my plan in the River of Time. Let's see what I can obtain from Xia Cha's body."

Fang Yuan was full of anticipation.

Soon after, his expression suddenly changed as the great thief ghost hand flew over unsteadily.

It was now clenched into a fist, there seemed to be something inside that was struggling to break free.

Fang Yuan was not surprised, but happy to see this.

Ying Wu Xie, who had a rough understanding of great thief ghost hand, blurted out in joy: "Awesome! Stealing a rank eight Immortal Gu at the very first attempt!"

At this time, however, the Formation Spirit spoke: "Master, there seems to be some disturbance in Xia Cha's soul."

Fang Yuan's time path clone immediately turned heavy, quickly controlling the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body to drag Xia Cha back into the dream realm.

The Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body stopped beside Xia Cha and observed for a good while, it only returned after seeing Xia Cha stabilize and continue to be in deep sleep.

Ordinary Gu Immortals would become unstable if only half their body was in dream realm, they would show indications of waking up from the dream, but it would take a long while.

Seemingly because Xia Cha cultivated time path, this time period seemed to have greatly shortened for her. Fang Yuan had sensed this back when he moved her into the sovereign immortal aperture. Back then, Shadow Sect immortals had broken out in cold sweat.

Only after resolving Xia Cha's situation did Fang Yuan and the rest inspect what Immortal Gu the great thief ghost hand had stolen.

This Immortal Gu was struggling fiercely, but great thief ghost hand borrowed the power of rank nine killer move ghostly concealment. Previously, it had stolen Soul Beast Token, so stealing rank eight Immortal Gu was completely within its capability.

Adding on Fang Yuan's plentiful methods, refining it was a done deal with no surprise.

After taking a while, Fang Yuan successfully refined this Gu.

This Gu worm was a milky-white silkworm, the size of an adult's index finger. It only had the weight of a chicken egg, and was tender to the touch like an infant's cheeks. There was a small green leaf growing on its head, which looked like a mulberry leaf. Interestingly, when the silkworm curled up its body, the mulberry leaf wrapped around its whole body.

The dense aura of the Gu worm reflected its extraordinary identity at all times — rank eight time path Immortal Gu!

But as for what Immortal Gu it was, Fang Yuan was not certain.

He could only guess: "This is probably the rank eight time path Immortal Gu Spring."

If spring Gu was used alone, it could bring the season of spring to an area. Ice and snow would melt, warm wind would blow, and new sprouts would grow.

Gu Masters nurture, use, and refine Gu. Using Gu was a deep and profound topic. When one obtains an unknown Immortal Gu, it needed to be constantly probed and tested to deduce its ability, this aspect often had unmeasurable danger.

After Fang Yuan refined this Immortal Gu, he was not in a hurry to examine it, because he had more reliable ways to obtain the correct answer.

This answer was in Xia Cha's body.

As long as he searched her soul, Fang Yuan would not only obtain this Immortal Gu's status and its usage, he could even understand the spring scissors killer move which she had used.

Fang Yuan was not in a hurry to search her soul as well, Xia Cha's soul was protected by her body, and it would not be easy to search her soul with her rank eight cultivation. Fang Yuan had a strict plan, he planned to first extract Xia Cha's soul, separating it from her body before targeting the soul!

Extracting Xia Cha's soul was also a troublesome matter and would need Fang Yuan to prepare for some time.

Moreover, before this, Fang Yuan needed to first steal all the Gu worms in Xia Cha's immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan continued to deal with Xia Cha the same way.

The second time, great thief ghost hand only stole a rank five mortal Gu, a huge contrast with the first time.

"Looks like unlucky year's effect has already disappeared, the difference between my luck and Xia Cha's luck has been reduced by a lot." Fang Yuan quickly understood the reason.

For rank eight Gu Immortals to have their accomplishments, they themselves represented extraordinary luck, and might also have methods to increase their luck.

Fang Yuan relied on his incomplete luck path true inheritance to possess luck that was higher than ordinary rank eight Gu Immortals. But this could not possess a great threat to a person like Feng Jiu Ge, let alone Feng Jin Huang.

After Fang Yuan was clear of the reason, he continued to use unlucky year on Xia Cha while frequently using great thief ghost hand to steal her Immortal Gu.

Over ten days passed by in the sovereign immortal aperture's time.

Fang Yuan had obtained a large amount of mortal Gu as well as Xia Cha's four Immortal Gu.

These four Immortal Gu formed a complete set, Spring, Summer, Autumn, and Winter.

Spring Gu was like a white silkworm with a mulberry leaf on its head.

Summer Gu was like a black mosquito the size of a palm, but it had three pairs of thin wings, and shined with multi-colored lights when it flew.

Autumn Gu was like a dark red cricket carved from precious and ancient wood. Its cry was extremely loud and resounding.

Winter Gu was a gray pupa that emitted bursts of cold air.

Spring Gu and summer Gu were rank eight, while autumn Gu and winter Gu were rank seven.

After Fang Yuan stole these four Immortal Gu, he repeatedly used great thief ghost hand but could only steal mortal Gu. Thus, he conjectured Xia Cha likely only had these four Immortal Gu!

This was similar to Hei Fan's situation. Hei Fan also had few Immortal Gu, back then, Fang Yuan had only obtained rank eight Years Flow Like Water along with rank seven year Gu and after Gu.

Although Xia Cha had two rank eight Immortal Gu, Hei Fan's years flow like water Gu brought enormous benefits. Possessing it meant becoming the number one giant of year Gu business in the whole world!

All of a sudden, Fang Yuan gained four more Immortal Gu, they were all of time path, two rank eight and two rank seven. This addition greatly filled the huge demand Fang Yuan had in this aspect.

But he still had to soul search Xia Cha to know how to use them.

The moment he obtained these Immortal Gu, the pressure on him greatly dissipated. Without Immortal Gu, even if Xia Cha accidentally woke up, she would be like a tiger without claws, with extremely low strength.

The primary task was to take out the Immortal Gu of all the Gu Immortal captives.

Second was to extract their souls, separating their soul and body. Besides the soul, the body could also be controlled by wills. Several wills left casually in the immortal aperture could temporarily substitute the soul to control the body.

Only then would Fang Yuan make a move on their immortal apertures.

However, Fang Yuan had to slow down the task of stealing Immortal Gu.

His immortal essence was running out!

It was already showing signs of depletion before, and in recent times, he had set up an immortal formation, fought a huge battle, then set up another immortal formation after returning to the sovereign immortal aperture, while also repeatedly using pure dream reality seeker transformation, great thief ghost hand, and other killer moves.

Fang Yuan's immortal essence reserves had already fallen to a dangerous level.

The year Gu business was doing dismally in treasure yellow heaven, even his dragonfish business was unable to support his enormous expenditure. Dang Hun Mountain was still recovering.

However, this did not go beyond Fang Yuan's control.

He sneered: "Hehe, it is time for those Southern Border forces to bleed."

It was definitely going to be a fun time ahead.

Not only was he going to extort immortal essence stones, Fang Yuan was going to extort large amounts of resources to raise and feed his newly obtained Immortal Gu.

Without cultivation resources, how could he get stronger?

Get stronger my ass!

There was a good saying — Kill and rob to earn wealth. Killing, extorting, pillaging and burning were the hallmarks of the demonic path!

Chapter 1607: One Million Immortal Essence Stones

Southern Border.

Yan Shou Mountain.

Xia clan's headquarters, Jian Wen blessed land.

Inside the blessed land, there were many mortal Gu Houses forming into a magnificent scene of an unbroken range of palace halls.

In the central hall, Xia Fei Kuai was moving on the ground in a hurry.

He was a rank seven Gu Immortal who cultivated light path, he had extraordinary battle strength, only slightly weaker than Wu clan's Wu Yu Bo. Because of cultivating a certain immortal killer move, his nature became impatient.

Fang Yuan had once fought him and set an agreement of five years in the disguise of Wu Yi Hai. Now that Fang Yuan's identity was revealed and had rank eight battle strength, Xia Fei Kuai had naturally thrown this five years agreement to the back of his mind.

"Where did this news come from?" Xia Fei Kuai quickly moved while asking.

Beside him was a featherman maid with rank five cultivation.

Xia clan raised a large group of featherman slaves, feathermen were the highest in quantity in Jian Wen blessed land.

This featherman maid was not an ordinary slave, she was one of the stewardesses of this hall and knew a lot of information.

Xia Fei Kuai was aware he would know everything when he entered the central hall, but he could not wait, impatiently asking this featherman maid.

The featherman maid quickly replied: "It came half a day ago from treasure yellow heaven. That demon Fang Yuan took the initiative to contact us. He sent an information path Gu worm to my purple spiritual light stall in treasure yellow heaven. The Gu worm had a ransom note."

Purple spiritual light was a rank seven immortal material, it was not gathered from white heaven, but originated from deep underground ores.

This was Xia clan's number one source of revenue. Xia clan possessed the most amount of purple spiritual stone lodes in the five regions, so they firmly held dominance over this business.

Although any Gu Immortals could casually change their identities for transactions in treasure yellow heaven to prevent others from discovering them, it was more profitable for a force like Xia clan to maintain their identity, establishing their reputation and creating their signature products.

So Xia clan's stall had an explicit identity and Fang Yuan found it easily.

"Hmph! His guts are greater than heaven, to think he would actually dare to extort my grand Xia clan!" Xia Fei Kuai was extremely furious.

The featherman maid did not dare to say anything, obsequiously accompanying him to the hall entrance, before stopping. She did not have the qualifications to enter.

The hall entrance was already open, the main seat was empty; it was usually occupied by Xia Cha or her will.

And in the top seat in the left row was Xia clan's second supreme elder Xia Zhao.

He was slightly fat, he had a steady temperament, he cultivated earth path, and was currently Xia clan's main backbone.

Sitting opposite Xia Zhao, in the top seat in the right row was Xia clan's third supreme elder, Xia Chen Yuan. He was similarly an earth path Gu Immortal.

Besides them, the other seats were already occupied by the main bodies or wills of Xia Liu Pei, Xia Qing Cang, Xia Zhuo Mo, Xia Fan and other Gu Immortals, only Xia Fei Kuai was missing.

"No need to stand on ceremony, take your seat." Xia Zhao said in a deep voice.

Xia Fei Kuai restrained his temperament, nodding his head before quietly taking his seat.

An information path mortal Gu was handed to Xia Fei Kuai from the left seat.

Xia Zhao looked at everyone: "Since everyone is here, let's begin the discussion."

Xia Fei Kuai sent his divine sense into the Gu worm. This information path mortal Gu was the ransom note sent by Fang Yuan.

There were only a few words in the ransom note, but it was concise and comprehensive.

However, there was an image attached at the end that showed the scene of Xia Cha trapped in sovereign immortal aperture.

Xia Fei Kuai's anger flared up when he finished browsing the information, almost crushing this information path mortal Gu in anger.

"This scoundrel Fang Yuan is a heinous criminal, he should be damned to death! We have to kill him!" Xia Fei Kuai shouted with a fierce expression.

Xia clan's other Gu Immortals did not respond, they looked ashen and had unsightly expressions as they maintained their silence.

The hall was filled with a heavy and stifling atmosphere.

Besides anger, these people felt incredulous.

The grand Xia clan, a super force, actually had a day where they were blackmailed by one demonic path Gu Immortal!

What shocked them the most was Xia Cha, the grand first supreme elder, the authoritative figure of Xia clan and a rank eight existence, she not only failed to capture Fang Yuan, but was instead taken captive alive by him!!

Yes, Fang Yuan indeed had outstanding battle strength that could rival rank eight.

The Xia clan Gu Immortals had viewed the video where he had pummeled Thunder Ghost True Monarch. But so what?

Defeating a rank eight Gu Immortal and capturing a rank eight were two different concepts. The difficulty level was as massive as the gap between heaven and earth.

Xia clan immortals had never expected such a result!

Even now, most of them still felt dazed as if they were dreaming, the truth was really unimaginable.

Fang Yuan, a rank seven Gu Immortal, had captured a rank eight along with a dozen rank seven Gu Immortal experts!

Almost all these rank seven Gu Immortals were the trump card battle strengths of their respective clans.

Each of them possessed unique methods, and in the absence of rank eight, they were major factors that could influence the whole of Southern Border's situation and dominate an area.

Southern Border's righteous path had been resolute in capturing Fang Yuan, so they had established such a powerful team.

But now, these people were all taken captive by Fang Yuan.

Compared to other clans, Xia clan's situation was the most pressing. Because what they had lost was not a rank seven Gu Immortal, but their clan's only rank eight!

This was no longer just a matter of a decrease in their prestige, but something that directly shook their foundation.

In this world where the strong were respected, a person's safety could affect the whole situation. Xia Cha played an irreplaceable role in Xia clan.

"I did not convene you all to make you stare anxiously. This is a critical juncture for the clan, we are in an extremely dangerous situation. At this time, we need to unite and get through this difficulty." Xia Zhao spoke while looking at the silent immortals.

When the situation had occurred, every Xia clan Gu Immortal was stupefied, Xia Zhao was not an exception.

Over these days, as the second supreme elder, he had been facing the greatest pressure.

When the ransom note finally came, his heart instead eased slightly.

"You have all seen that mortal Gu, Fang Yuan is demanding one million immortal essence stones. What are your thoughts on this?" Xia Zhao said.

After a while of silence, Xia clan's third supreme elder intentionally coughed before saying: "One million immortal essence stones is not a small amount, but it is not big either, our Xia clan can afford it. But what I am concerned about is this message only mentioned his demand, and did not mention anything about handing over Lady Xia Cha!"

The other immortals nodded at this.

Xia Fei Kuai's brows rose up in agitation, blurting out: "How about we inform the other clans? We are being extorted, they are probably facing the same situation as well."

Xia Liu Pei glanced at Xia Fei Kuai with a sneer, not speaking.

Xia Fei Kuai was furious, glaring at him: "What do you want to say? Just say it."

Xia Liu Pei was a rank seven Gu Immortal who cultivated wisdom path, moreover he had a powerful wisdom path attainment, and was a top expert at deductions in the present Southern Border.

He sneered: "How can we rely on outsiders? Right now, they are eager to see us lose our first supreme elder. Since you realize that demon Fang Yuan is not extorting just us, then have you heard the other clans' responses? Have you seen them trying to contact us?"

Xia Fei Kuai was silent.

Xia clan had suddenly lost its rank eight pillar, which immediately made it seem like it occupied an excessive number of territories and resources.

This situation was much more dangerous than that of Wu clan before.

Back then, Wu clan still had Wu Yong, a rank eight Gu Immortal, but under repeated schemes of Shadow Sect, he had been trapped in a difficult situation, besieged from all sides, almost unable to make a turnaround.

Southern Border was filled with many individual forces, there were always internal conflicts and contradictions between righteous path forces. Wu clan had occupied the throne of the number one force for a long time, but still did not have the ability to lead the whole situation.

So as far as Xia clan was concerned, they absolutely could not lose Xia Cha!

When Fang Yuan's will once again went up to the purple spiritual light stall, he received one million immortal essence stones from Xia clan.

"We need to talk." Xia Zhao personally received Fang Yuan, his divine sense fluctuating constantly.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, not refusing: "Alright. But I am in a hurry right now. Whatever you want to say, use an information path Gu worm to send it to this stall."

"Please wait a second, listen to me…" Xia Zhao wanted to press Fang Yuan to stay, but Fang Yuan's will directly left. Xia Zhao was furious but also helpless.

He could only look as Fang Yuan's will left, his heart feeling extremely heavy.

Chapter 1608: The Trick to Extortion

It was obvious what Fang Yuan was busy with.

Having the Southern Border immortals in his hands, Fang Yuan had firm hold of the initiative and occupied huge dominance.

He had such invaluable hostages in hand, he could extort however he wanted.

But Fang Yuan was cautious and did not overdo it. He only extorted three clans at first.

Xia clan was undeniably the main target. First supreme elder Xia Cha was Xia clan's only rank eight Gu Immortal, she was Xia clan's foundational pillar, an extremely important person. Xia clan simply could not lose her, or else the whole clan's force would shrink by seventy to eighty percent!

Yi clan was the second.

Because the Yi clan Gu Immortal Fang Yuan had taken captive was Yi Yang.

This space path Gu Immortal was the strongest rank seven expert of Yi clan, and everyone was optimistic of him having the qualifications to enter rank eight. More importantly, he was blood related to Yi clan's first supreme elder, and was a successor of the clan being nurtured by the first supreme elder.

In Fang Yuan's first life of five hundred years, during the five regions chaotic war, there were endless internal conflicts in Southern Border. Yi Yang was schemed against and fell into Shang clan's hands, Yi clan's first supreme elder had not hesitated to pay an enormous price to bring back Yi Yang.

So Fang Yuan was rather expectant of Yi clan's ransom.

Finally, the third was Chi clan.

Fang Yuan's Chi clan Gu Immortal captive was Chi clan's second supreme elder, which was a very important position! Adding on that Chi Qu You had transacted with Fang Yuan previously, obtaining dream path research gains, it was natural for Chi clan to compromise.

Fang Yuan was deeply aware of the human mindset, his first extortion targets was not Wu clan, who hated him deeply, nor Tie clan, who deeply detested the demonic path.

As long as these three clans gave in, it would be much easier for Fang Yuan to extort other Southern Border righteous path forces.

After all, with these precedents, the righteous path would not be so tough in their stance anymore.

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Green Heaven, at the immortal formation.

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

The ghost hand entered Yi Yang's immortal aperture and returned with a rank seven Immortal Gu.

Ying Wu Xie and the Formation Spirit looked on quietly from the side with impassive expressions.

They were no longer surprised by this sight.

Because in this period of time, Fang Yuan had already looted a huge amount of Immortal Gu! Moreover, he had even looted Xia Cha's two rank eight Immortal Gu, Spring and Summer. With such sensational gains, the remaining loot looked mild in comparison.

Fang Yuan had constructed another immortal formation to refine these Immortal Gu.

This immortal formation used wisdom refinement formation as the foundation along with many wisdom path Immortal Gu to form a completely new version.

Wisdom refinement formation was constructed by using the light of wisdom along with Woman's Heart and Unravel Mystery to refine other Immortal Gu. If there was the other person's will, the effect would become even more outstanding. Fang Yuan had used Mo Yao's fake will to help him refine the Immortal Gu he had obtained from Bo Qing's immortal zombie body, including change soul Immortal Gu, which had been of the utmost significance in the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain.

At present, Fang Yuan still used the light of wisdom as the core, the brand new wisdom refinement formation was even more powerful.

Wisdom Gu was a rank nine Gu, so it was truly easy to suppress those rank seven Immortal Gu.

Moreover, with the large improvement in Fang Yuan's formation path and wisdom path methods, the wisdom refinement formation's effect became even more remarkable.

After a while, Fang Yuan finished refining the newly stolen Immortal Gu.

This was a space path Immortal Gu that looked like a blue jade sphere with a pair of snow-white wings.

Fang Yuan recognized this Gu, it was called Space Travel and had a remarkable movement ability. Shadow Sect's true inheritances had relevant records, for instance, this Gu was initially captured from the body of an immemorial desolate beast level pegasus.

Fang Yuan stored this space travel Gu.

He did not cultivate space path and had ordinary attainment in it, moreover, he did not have many space path dao marks.

However, he had too many true inheritances, countless immortal killer moves and Immortal Gu recipes, he did not lack methods to make use of Immortal Gu.

By now, he had already stolen most of the Immortal Gu of the Southern Border Gu Immortal captives.

As for the issue of the shortage of immortal essence, it was already solved.

Xia clan's one million immortal essence stones were like a waterfall descending from a heavenly river and pouring on this parched land.

One million immortal essence stones meant one million beads of green grape immortal essence, which was equivalent to ten thousand beads of red date immortal essence. This amount had already far surpassed Fang Yuan's highest record of red date immortal essence.

Fang Yuan continued to use great thief ghost hand but he was not able to take out any more Immortal Gu from Yi Yang's body.

Thereupon, he threw this person back into dream realm, and dragged out another person. It was Chi clan's second supreme elder, an earth path rank seven Gu Immortal.

Fang Yuan made a move on him without hesitation.

He was going to take out Immortal Gu of all these Southern Border Gu Immortals and store them in his pockets.

As for the people, he would have to release some of them.

Extortion or blackmailing could be seen as a form of transaction, where as long as the seller was powerful enough, the buyer could only remain helpless. And in a transaction, buyers and sellers needed to pay attention to reputation, if he did not release some hostages, why would Southern Border's righteous path believe Fang Yuan, how could he continue his extortion plan to gain huge benefits?

Fang Yuan intended to first release Chi clan's second supreme elder and Yi clan's Yi Yang.

He had done transactions with Chi clan previously after all, and he also intended to support Chi clan in the future, to resist Heavenly Court. Naturally, he was definitely going to extort these two clans to the limit.

Despite it being difficult to raise a Gu Immortal, a hostage's price was fixed and limited.

These righteous path forces could stay in power until now, they were not fools.

If Fang Yuan's demands were too much and exceeded the value of these Gu Immortals, or the acceptable price that these clansmen were willing to pay, they would not do this unreasonable transaction.

All in all, extortion was a skill.

Several days later, another batch of immortal essence stones was obtained.

That was Yi clan's first ransom, one million and two hundred thousand immortal essence stones.

Comparing value, Yi Yang could not compare to Xia Cha, but Yi clan had a lot of wealth, at least richer than Xia clan. So they had much more immortal essence stones reserved in their hands.

A super force's immortal essence stones reserve was more or less around one million immortal essence stones.

So Fang Yuan first extorted immortal essence stones, not only because he himself was in shortage of it, the more important reason was that other forces could totally take that sum out. Although it was not without a level of difficulty, the difficulty was small.

First make them give in, then continue to extort them more harshly, making them bleed little by little. Fang Yuan was well versed in the ways of extortion.

"It is just that although I captured Southern Border immortals, I did not receive any response from Heavenly Court. What did Heavenly Court prepare in the River of Time?"

Fang Yuan could not help but think.

He constructed years flow execution formation mainly to deal with the Southern Border immortals, but it was also to lure Heavenly Court into making a move.

If Heavenly Court had laid an ambush and saw the commotion there, they could have followed the tributary of the River of Time to pincer-attack Fang Yuan.

But from the start to finish, Fang Yuan did not see Heavenly Court's ambush.

Fang Yuan's scheme was fruitless in this regard, leaving him with even more wariness and suspicion.

Chapter 1609: Three Plans

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Red Heaven.

Fang Yuan's time path clone immediately attracted the attention of countless year beasts the moment he appeared.

Howl! Roar! Growl!

Countless year beasts roared and snarled as they pounced upon Fang Yuan. Large numbers of ancient desolate beasts shoved the desolate level year beasts to the side as they looked at Fang Yuan with a thirsty expression.

But a moment later, an immemorial year rooster flew over gallantly and spiritedly; the desolate level year beasts and ancient desolate beasts in its path quickly and chaotically moved aside.

The immemorial year rooster arrived before Fang Yuan's time path clone and lowered its head, displaying a tamed look.

Fang Yuan smiled as he stroked the immemorial year rooster's bright red crown, then he waved his sleeve, scattering countless mortal year Gu.

The immemorial year rooster squawked as it opened its beak wide, creating a powerful attractive force that absorbed most of the year Gu into its stomach. Only a few year Gu scattered in the surroundings which was immediately fought over by the surrounding ancient year beasts.

The immemorial year rooster had a great meal but was still not satisfied, it looked at Fang Yuan's time path clone with shining eyes.

Fang Yuan repeatedly waved his sleeve, countless year Gu were scattered like the crushed pebbles on a beach, forming a rain of year Gu.

This time, there was a portion for everyone, the year beasts immediately fell into frenzied joy.

After a good while, every year beast including the immemorial year rooster had their fill. Their impatience because of hunger had disappeared, resuming a lethargic state as they lay down on white clouds to rest.

Fang Yuan's time path clone gazed around, nodded and flew away.

In Mini Red Heaven, there were seven year beast communities like this one, this was already the third community Fang Yuan fed.

There were already a lot of year beasts being raised in sovereign immortal aperture, and not long ago, Fang Yuan had used years flow execution formation to ruthlessly plot against Southern Border righteous path, besides capturing the group of Southern Border immortals, his greatest battle spoils were the year beasts he had subdued in the battle.

These year beasts were of high quality, they were at least of desolate level year, there was a large amount of ancient year beasts, as well as seven immemorial year beasts.

Originally, Fang Yuan's soul foundation was only enough for him to enslave one or two immemorial year beasts. But now, his soul cultivation had made rapid breakthroughs, although it was decreasing recently, the remaining soul foundation was enough to enslave seven immemorial year beasts without a problem.

A noteworthy thing was there were three immemorial year roosters among these seven immemorial year beasts. The other four immemorial year beasts were tiger, dragon, rabbit, and horse.

In the River of Time, at every set interval of time, a certain kind of immemorial year beast would be more common than others. This recent period of time was clearly a prosperous time for immemorial year roosters.

However, even though Fang Yuan had seven immemorial year beasts, when comparing individual strength, they were all weaker than his immemorial year monkey. Unfortunately, that immemorial year monkey had already died in battle.

Of course, if all the seven immemorial year beasts combined their strength, they were much fiercer than one immemorial year monkey.

There was a clear difference between the strength of different immemorial year beasts. This was like the difference between rank eight Gu Immortals.

Fang Yuan fed these year beasts while thinking: "The food expenditure has soared by dozens of times with the addition of these year beasts! If not for the immortal essence stones extorted this time, I might not have been able to feed them."

The higher the rank of the year beasts, the larger their appetite. And the food of year beasts was year Gu.

Fang Yuan used rank eight Immortal Gu Years Flow Like Water to refine countless mortal year Gu, barely filling the bellies of these year beasts.

And activating years flow like water Immortal Gu spent Fang Yuan's red date immortal essence.

Fang Yuan's immortal essence expenditure in feeding year beasts was not small even before. Now, with the addition of so many year beasts and seven immemorial year beasts, feeding them had already taken the largest share of Fang Yuan's expenditures.

"Currently, Dang Hun Mountain has already been restored by eighty percent, guts Gu's production is no longer a terrible sight, it has become just passable."

"When Dang Hun Mountain is completely restored, the year beasts will become the new burden."

Fang Yuan had to feed year beasts every set interval of time. Refining year Gu through Years Flow Like Water was already the most economical method, but it still amounted to a huge expenditure.

Moreover, Fang Yuan needed to raise these year beasts to deal with the future battle in the River of Time, so he had to resolve the issue of feeding them.

Actually this issue was not only regarding the year beasts, but also eagle groups.

Fang Yuan had previously enslaved the upper extreme heavenly eagle, purchasing a large amount of eagle beasts. The feeding of these eagle beasts was also a burden.

If he wanted to make them self-sufficient and truly integrate them into sovereign immortal aperture's world, he would have to spend a huge amount of energy and capital to build a complete food-chain.

Big fish eats small fish, and small fish eats shrimps.

Creating a proper food chain was also a form of deep research and understanding of the Heavenly Dao by the Gu Immortal.

But compared to eagle groups, year beast's scale was much larger so its feeding issue needed to be prioritized.

And because of the year beasts' characteristics, building a complete food chain for them was much easier.

Fang Yuan, who had Spectral Soul's true inheritance, Lang Ya's true inheritance, and so on, had methods to solve it.

Currently, he could select from three plans.

The first plan was to construct a year essence pool.

This was a resource point, and could also be seen as a mini River of Time. Its effect was to imitate the environment of the River of Time, providing a place for year beasts to survive, reside, and procreate.

The year essence pool's size could be large or small, and was classified into rank six, rank seven, rank eight, and rank nine levels.

The advantage of this plan was it saved space, at the same time, as the year beasts lived here, it would produce a certain amount of year Gu. When managed for a long time, it could even produce other wild time path Gu worms, even giving birth to day Gu, month Gu and so on, finally forming a micro River of Time.

Its disadvantage was the cost was absurdly high. Just the creation of a rank six year essence pool was an enormous sum. In terms of immortal essence stones, it was in the millions!

And a rank seven year essence pool was even more exaggerated, requiring many rare immortal materials which had no supply in the market. Rank six level year essence pool could still be constructed if one was wealthy enough, but the rank seven year essence pool was not something that could be solved with just immortal essence stones.

As for Fang Yuan, he needed a rank eight year essence pool to contain the seven immemorial year beasts!

The second plan was Golden Age Platform.

This was a rather special rank seven time path Immortal Gu House, because it was fixed in place and could not move freely like most of the other Immortal Gu Houses. Once it was constructed, Golden Age Platform would transform into a bright moon that would float to the sky of the blessed land, constantly rising and setting.

Golden Age Platform could store a large amount of year beasts and even put them into deep sleep. Like this, their food requirement would fall sharply.

This plan's advantage was that Golden Age Platform could extract year beasts' strength for its use, and did not require Fang Yuan to expend his immortal essence. In peaceful times, this meant Fang Yuan was fully using year beasts and not just freely feeding them.

This plan's disadvantages were very obvious.

First, constructing this rank seven Immortal Gu House required a lot of time path Immortal Gu. But Fang Yuan needed these time path Immortal Gu to protect himself.

Secondly, Golden Age Platform's position had to be fixed so it could automatically operate on its own inside the immortal aperture. So even if it was constructed, it would be of no help to Fang Yuan when fighting in River of Time. It itself was also not proficient in offensive methods.

Thirdly, this Immortal Gu House spent the year beasts' strength, if it wantonly extracted their strength, the year beasts could die and their time path dao marks would also be destroyed, making their corpses be of no value.

Finally, when the year beasts are awakened, they would need far more food than normal to fill their appetite.

The third plan was Twelve Zodiac battle formation.

Twelve Zodiac battle formation was constructed by using twelve different species of immemorial year beasts as cores.

This formation was specialized in offense, completely different from Golden Age Platform. And although it was a large formation, it could be moved.

Because its cores were twelve immemorial year beasts, during inactive times, these immemorial year beasts could be sealed, becoming like statues, unmoving and not requiring food. But during battle, the seal would be released, they would form into the battle formation and attack the enemy.

Evidently, this large formation that used immemorial year beasts as cores was not a present age Gu formation, but an ancient battle formation. Like Green City Rampage or Heavenly Giant Solor, the difference was that these two used Gu Immortals as the cores, while this Twelve Zodiac battle formation used immemorial year beasts as the cores.

This plan's advantage was that it truly saved feeding expenditure.

But the disadvantage was it only used immemorial year beasts. Fang Yuan would be unable to construct Twelve Zodiac battle formation if he used ancient year beasts or desolate level year beasts.

However, to do this, Fang Yuan needed to search for even more immemorial year beasts, moreover these immemorial year beasts had to be of different species.

This gathering task not only looked at strength but also luck, its difficulty was high and also took a very long time.

Fang Yuan considered it deeply before deciding to choose the first plan.

Although the first plan needed the highest investment, it brought the largest benefits as well.

"With my capital, if I want to construct a rank eight level year essence pool, my finance will probably fall into a dangerous state before I can construct even thirty percent of it."

Fang Yuan was actually very affluent, but most of his resources like Reverse Flow River could not be sold. Moreover, he still needed to deal with external pressure from forces like Heavenly Court. He needed to look at all aspects, and could not just spend all his assets on a year essence pool, without regard for anything else.

"But now is the best time for me to construct a year essence pool."

"Xia clan, you want to negotiate with me? First, send three portions of spiral dawn light." Fang Yuan threw an information path mortal Gu to Xia clan's stall.

Soon, Xia clan's response came: "Fang Yuan, my clan does produce spiral dawn light, but the production ground is inside first supreme elder's immortal aperture. There is none left in the clan's storage."

Fang Yuan was slightly dazed, this reply was beyond his expectations, but he sent a reply with a cold smile: "How could I not know this? Send three portions, no, send ten portions of spiral dawn light and I will take it as your clan's sincerity, then we can talk. Or else…"

"But spiral dawn light are extremely rare, there is no supply even in treasure yellow heaven. Three portions is okay, but ten, where would we find that much?"

"I don't care. That is your issue, not mine." Fang Yuan left a cruel reply.

Chapter 1610: Incomplete Form of Gu as Before

Shang clan.

"One hundred and fifty kilograms of eight-parts jade, I want it within three days at the latest." Fang Yuan demanded strongly.

Shang clan's immortal looked quite unsightly: "Eight-parts jade is a rank eight immortal material, treasure yellow heaven usually has transactions of only up to five kilograms. It is difficult for my clan to bring out so many at once."

"Hehehe, I believe in your great clan's strength. Who does not know that Shang clan is the richest force of Southern Border?" Fang Yuan sneered, no matter how Shang clan negotiated, the conditions did not change.

Ba clan.

"Where is my seven treasures water?" Fang Yuan urged.

Ba clan's immortal quickly responded: "We have already gathered the seven treasures water, we can trade the goods for person at the same time."

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan laughed heartily, "Good, good! To express my sincerity, I might as well hand over a batch first."

"This, what is this?" Ba clan's Gu Immortal was shocked and furious.

"You don't recognize it? This is the arm of your clan's Gu Immortal." Fang Yuan's voice was slow and unperturbed.

"Fang Yuan! What is the meaning of this?"

"Hmph! You want to take back your clan's Gu Immortal with just some seven treasures water? It won't be that easy, right? Or are you taking me for a fool? If you don't satisfy me, I will simply kill him. Oh, that's right, I will be sure to record the process of killing him and display it in treasure yellow heaven. Or maybe I can sell this person to Wu clan? Hehehe, hahahaha!" Fang Yuan laughed loudly.

Ba clan's Gu Immortal almost grinded his teeth into pieces. After a good while, Ba clan Gu Immortal squeezed out his words through clenched teeth: "Fang Yuan… we can talk this through."

"Sure we can talk, that is not a problem. First, hand over the seven treasures water to display your Ba clan's sincerity. With all due respect, your clan wants to overthrow Wu clan to become the number one force of Southern Border, how could you be so petty? Wu clan is not hesitating to pay any price for an external supreme elder. Meanwhile, your Ba clan's Gu Immortal is your own bloodline descendant, can you watch him die? What does your first supreme elder think? Can you truly be so cold and unfeeling?"

Fang Yuan's each word was piercing, causing the Ba clan Gu Immortal to be pale and furious, but also helpless.

Luo clan clan, Hou clan, Chai clan… these were Fang Yuan's second wave of extortion targets. As for Tie clan, Wu clan and others, he did not make a move on them yet.

Fang Yuan mentioned all kinds of demands to these clans, he naturally encountered resistance during the extortion, but Fang Yuan had hostages in his hands, and with his location being extremely secretive, unable to be deduced, he firmly held the initiative.

Southern Border's righteous path was helpless, and could only bitterly satisfy Fang Yuan's demands.

Among them, Xia clan's sincerity was the highest, those ten portions of spiral dawn light were the first to end up in Fang Yuan's hands.

Despite Xia clan's Gu Immortal shouting about how difficult it had been to gather these spiral dawn light, Fang Yuan knew how robust these super forces' foundation was. Satisfying his demands were within their capabilities, it was just that the difficulty was a little high.

Spiral dawn light, eight-parts jade, seven treasures water….

These immortal materials were either rank eight materials or rank seven but with high quantity, all these materials were successively sent to Fang Yuan.

Soon, Fang Yuan had most of the required immortal materials to construct year essence pool.

This efficiency was truly shocking!

If Fang Yuan had to gather these himself, he would need to spend at least a dozen years under the situation that he was lucky.

Fang Yuan's foundation was deep, but in terms of accumulating immortal materials, he was completely unable to compare to these super forces that had thousands and even tens of thousands of years of history.

Naturally, the immortal materials Fang Yuan requested were not just for constructing year essence pool.

Many of the immortal materials were in the preparation for Immortal Gu refinement.

At this moment, the time path clone arrived in front of an immortal formation.

"This is the last time, after this plunder, none of these Southern Border Gu Immortals will have any Immortal Gu left."

Southern Border's righteous path had thirteen super clans; Wu clan, Ba clan, Shang clan, Tie clan, Hou clan, Luo clan, Qiao clan, Chai clan, Xia clan, Yi clan, Chi clan, Yang clan, and Yao clan.

Fang Yuan could battle rank eight, if they could kill Fang Yuan, every clan would profit. So each clan had mobilized one of their Gu Immortal experts with at least rank seven cultivation and peak battle strength. Xia clan's first supreme elder had personally set to the task of leading these experts to prevent any internal conflicts.

Each of these Gu Immortal experts had at least two to three Immortal Gu, some had four or five Immortal Gu like Xia Cha. On average, each had three.

Fang Yuan had not finished looting but the total amount of Immortal Gu he had accumulated from them already broke the count of one hundred!

Immortal killer move — Great Thief Ghost Hand!

Looking at a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body drag out Yang Ku from the dream realm, Fang Yuan immediately got to work.

A rank seven Immortal Gu was looted, Fang Yuan was immediately exulted, it was soul search Immortal Gu!

This soul search Immortal Gu was a rank seven Gu which would be helpful to Fang Yuan in searching their souls.

"But this Gu can only be considered icing on the cake."

"Even without soul search Immortal Gu, I can use other soul path Immortal Gu to create a soul search immortal killer move. Just that, this process will be much more convenient with this Immortal Gu."

"It would be better if I had gotten devour soul Immortal Gu instead of this Soul Search."

Shadow Sect had once possessed devour soul Immortal Gu, if Fang Yuan had it at this moment, it would be much easier for him to extract these Southern Border Gu Immortals' souls out of their body. His current methods required him to go through a lot of trouble for this.

Yang Ku had three soul path Immortal Gu altogether, there was no devour soul Gu among the next two Gu, regretfully.

The final person was Wu clan's Liu Hao.

"This person had a method to restrain my Fixed Immortal Travel, let me take a good look at you." Fang Yuan repeatedly activated his killer move, finally stealing an Immortal Gu after a while.

"Eh!" Fang Yuan was stunned.

This Immortal Gu directly self-destructed the moment it was taken out of the immortal aperture.

"What is this situation?" Cold light flickered within Fang Yuan's eyes.

He continued to steal, but he could only take out remnant parts of Gu worms. Be it Immortal Gu or mortal Gu, they had self-detonated following the first Immortal Gu.

Fang Yuan carefully distinguished these Gu worms' parts, and soon discovered this was a clever refinement path method. As long as one of these Gu worms left the immortal aperture, every Gu would self-detonate simultaneously.

"There is actually such a method? This refinement path method is nothing ordinary, it is absolutely at the level of Long Hair Ancestor. Looks like this Gu Immortal being recruited by Wu clan is not simple, he is very likely to be a person of Heavenly Court!"

Fang Yuan immediately deduced the truth.

There were three great experts of refinement path in the Gu Immortal history, they were all supreme grandmasters. Besides Long Hair Ancestor from the Medieval Antiquity Era, there were Old Eccentric Tian Nan from Remote Antiquity Era, and Old Immortal Kong Jue from Olden Antiquity Era. And these two were humans, most of their true inheritances were collected by Heavenly Court. Fang Yuan had once disguised as Wu Yi Hai and infiltrated Wu clan, so he was extremely clear about Wu clan's foundation. Wu clan did not have such a refinement path method!

Fang Yuan's expression was slightly dark.

This method was beyond his expectation, catching him off-guard and causing him slight losses.

At the same time, he also realized: "I had intended to use years flow execution formation to lure and expose Heavenly Court's arrangement in the River of Time. But I had not expected Heavenly Court to infiltrate into Southern Border's team to hunt me down."

"Dangerous… based on Fairy Zi Wei's methods, she would not have just sent this person, she definitely arranged more backup plans. Fortunately, I left quickly back then and did not waste time on Lu Wei Yin."

"Wu clan is Southern Border's number one righteous path force, but it was actually so easily infiltrated by Heavenly Court? This is not so simple, mostly likely, Wu Yong brought in Heavenly Court to deal with me. Hmph, he is indeed a formidable character, unafraid of this matter being exposed and violating a taboo of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan's thoughts turned as he once again casted his gaze at the Immortal Gu carcasses in his hand.

"Gu as Before…" He softly mumbled.

Gu as Before was a concept he had envisioned before. He had thought about it because of Man as Before and Landscape as Before.

When a Gu worm was injured or destroyed, using Gu as Before could restore them to their previous state.

However, although this concept sounded good, the deeper one researched into it, the more they realized how impractical it was.

Mortal Gu had dao marks, Immortal Gu were the fragments of the Great Dao, to restore them, Gu as Before's might and level had to far surpass the target. This alone signified that Gu as Before would not be as practical as Man as Before and Landscape as Before. Not to mention the tremendous difficulty in using it.

But now, Fang Yuan could almost see a trace of Gu as Before in these Gu worm carcasses.

"These Gu worms are clearly of space path, but refinement path dao marks have been added, which when activated, would destroy them."

Since refinement path was specialized in refining Gu, it was naturally also proficient in destroying Gu worms.

"Maybe these Gu worm carcasses have more value to me than the stolen Immortal Gu." A sharp light flashed past Fang Yuan's eyes.

In the ambush before, Liu Hao had used fixed space Immortal Gu to restrain Fang Yuan's Fixed Immortal Travel.

Heavenly Court adopted such a contingency measure not just because they did not want fixed space Immortal Gu to land in Fang Yuan's hand. In fact, there were many methods other than fixed space Immortal Gu to restrain Fixed Immortal Travel.

"On the contrary, I might be able to find clues from these Gu worm carcasses to refine Gu as before Immortal Gu!"

Fang Yuan carefully stored these Gu worm carcasses.

In this case, there was a lot to learn and research upon.

Naturally, the better method was to directly refer to Heavenly Court's methods and inheritance.

But this possibility was practically impossible for Fang Yuan.

"I have absorbed the Long Hair true meaning, my refinement path attainment has reached quasi-supreme grandmaster. But in the history of refinement path, there are still two other monumental figures equal to Long Hair Ancestor, Old Eccentric Tian Nan and Old Immortal Kong Jue. Most of these two's inheritances have definitely been pocketed by Heavenly Court." Fang Yuan sighed inwardly.

He could clearly see the opportunity to refine Gu as Before, but Heavenly Court was like a heavenly moat obstructing Fang Yuan's path.

Chapter 1611: Zi Wei's Unease

Heavenly Court.

Countless halls shined with splendor.

Inside a hall, as Fairy Zi Wei slowly opened her eyes, a purple light flashed past her beautiful eyes.

She frowned slightly, her tone was free and natural as she mumbled: "Fixed space Immortal Gu has self-detonated."

After Fairy Zi Wei grasped Star Constellation Chessboard, she had become one of the top three wisdom path great experts of the present Gu Immortal world. This time, she sent Liu Hao and Jun Shen Guang to deal with Fang Yuan, how could she not have prepared for Fang Yuan's great thief ghost hand?

Becoming wiser through learning from mistakes, because Fang Yuan had stolen Fixed Immortal Travel from Feng Jiu Ge right under Fairy Zi Wei's eyes, she was not going to commit the same mistake twice.

"Yuan Qiong Du." Fairy Zi Wei contacted this newly recruited rank eight Gu Immortal.

"Lady Zi Wei." Yuan Qiong Du immediately responded.

"Go refine fixed space Gu." Fairy Zi Wei instructed lightly.

Yuan Qiong Du's expression immediately changed. It was him who had added the refinement path dao marks on fixed space Gu and the others, thus he knew the approximate situation.

Fairy Zi Wei's words no doubt meant that Liu Hao's situation was likely to be bad.

Liu Hao and Yuan Qiong Du came from the same ancient sect, Yuan Qiong Du hesitated a moment before asking: "Lady Zi Wei, Liu Hao…"

"He is most likely taken captive by Fang Yuan, but I would rather he was killed by Fang Yuan." Fairy Zi Wei's tone was indifferent, astonishingly similar to Fang Yuan's cruel extortion of Southern Border righteous path.

Yuan Qiong Du was stunned, before quickly realizing.

Fairy Zi Wei's words did not mean she hated Liu Hao and wanted Liu Hao to die, instead if Liu Hao was taken captive, it meant that other Southern Border immortals were also taken captive by Fang Yuan.

But if Fang Yuan killed Liu Hao, the other Southern Border immortals would likely not be an exception. With this, there would be a deep-seated hatred between Fang Yuan and the Southern Border righteous path, there would be no possibility for them to compromise or cooperate. Southern Border had suffered disastrous losses in the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain as well as the battle of dream realm, if their elite team was killed by Fang Yuan, their foundation would be truly damaged. Their overall strength would fall to the bottom among the five regions.

When the five regions chaotic war starts and regional walls disappear, Central Continent would be able to attack Southern Border first.

Southern Border could be devoured by Central Continent easily, and with two regions, Central Continent's originally high strength would immediately surpass the remaining three regions, gaining a huge dominance. The situation would also change, they would not be in an awkward situation of being besieged by four regions!

Compared to this grand situation, how significant was the sacrifice of a mere rank seven Gu Immortal like Liu Hao?

After realizing this, Yuan Qiong Du's shock vanished as he left: "I will go refine fixed space Gu."

Yuan Qiong Du had already made sufficient preparations, he was a rank eight Gu Immortal and with the help of Heavenly Court's grand refinement path formation, it was practically a certain matter for him to refine fixed space Immortal Gu and the other Gu.

However, there was still uneasiness in Fairy Zi Wei's heart.

For wisdom path Gu Immortals, such a feeling was like a premonition.

Wisdom path had three elements, thoughts, wills, and emotions.

To other Gu Immortals, the rise, change, and disappearance of emotions may be their own joy, anger, sorrow, or pleasure. But it had a different meaning for wisdom path Gu Immortals.

"Did I miscalculate? What is it that is making me feel this uneasy?" Fairy Zi Wei's mind was heavy, as she began to deduce while holding Star Constellation Chessboard.

After a good while, she slowly opened her eyes, revealing a trace of doubt.

The result of the deduction was the same as before.

"Fang Yuan could successfully ambush them because of the crucial starting step that let him lure Southern Border immortals into his time path formation."

"This is not his own accomplishment, it is a time path formation Shadow Sect had set up long ago near the tributary of the River of Time using natural dao marks."

Fang Yuan had formation path grandmaster attainment, he had to use immortal materials to set up immortal formations.

Only when one reaches formation path great grandmaster level, could they set up an immortal formation using just the natural dao marks in the outside world.

Shadow Sect naturally did not lack such experts, and had long ago set up a time path formation near the tributary of the River of Time, while heavily concealing this tributary of the River of Time.

Although such an immortal formation created from natural dao marks did not need to use Immortal Gu, it had its disadvantages.

The main disadvantage was that according to the composition and arrangement of the natural dao marks and other specific circumstances, the time path formations that could be set up were different.

When Gu Immortals set up this kind of immortal formation, not only did they need to have their own ideas, but also think according to the local condition. Time path dao marks of another area would not be able to set up such extremely concealed time path formation.

Thus, Fang Yuan could not replicate the terrifying success of ambushing the Southern Border immortals.

Fairy Zi Wei had paid a huge price along with crucial clues from Jun Shen Guang to make this deduction.

"Without the immortal formation's confinement, even if Fang Yuan detonated Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies, the dream realm's expansion speed is not fast, the Gu Immortals could easily escape."

"Were he to use an immortal battlefield, unless it is a dream path battlefield, battlefields of other paths would be the first to be corroded by the dream realm and crumble apart."

"So Fang Yuan's dream realm battle tactic does not possess much threat."

"So why am I feeling uneasy? Could it be Spectral Soul?"

Thinking of this, Fairy Zi Wei left the hall and moved towards a certain area of Heavenly Court.

Spectral Soul was here, Dang Hun Mountain's self-detonation had given him the opportunity to use the soul path dao marks to recover and resist.

But Heavenly Court had never lacked methods, when Fairy Zi Wei reached this place, a grand immortal formation had already been constructed and was operating while producing a buzzing noise.

This enormous immortal formation was like a huge mill that constantly destroyed the soul path dao marks here.

"Spectral Soul, you are still thinking of putting up a resistance? A pity for you, the soul path dao marks beside you are going to be completely ground down in another three days. Your action is only a brief dying struggle." Fairy Zi Wei entered the formation and sneered at Spectral Soul.

Spectral Soul was like a stone, giving no response.

Purple light erupted in Fairy Zi Wei's eyes and the Star Constellation Chessboard in her hands also let out a dense blue light that constantly scanned the whole immortal formation as well as Spectral Soul. After inspecting a few times, she was sure there was nothing odd about Spectral Soul and that he had no concealed methods to resist.

"There is no issue with Spectral Soul, looks like my unease did not come from here. Then where did it come from? Wait, could it be…"

Fairy Zi Wei's expression suddenly changed when she left the immortal formation, as she thought of a person.

She immediately set off with no hesitation, personally moving out of Heavenly Court and arriving in a certain nameless valley in Central Continent.

The valley was lush and green, and had a waterfall. Duke Long had built a cavern beside the waterfall, wholeheartedly teaching and guarding Feng Jin Huang.

Feng Jin Huang!

If someone could make Fairy Zi Wei feel unease, it was probably this Great Dream seed.

The waterfall crashed down, roaring and creating dense fog.

A dense dream realm could be seen before which young Feng Jin Huang was sitting with closed-eyes on a giant rock. Her skin was white as snow, her demeanor graceful and dignified.

A Gu Immortal whose aura was extremely constrained, with a pair of spiral dragon horns on his forehead and a well-built body, was quietly standing to the side like a giant pillar, observing Feng Jin Huang.

"Senior Duke Long." Fairy Zi Wei quietly approached and bowed in greeting.

Duke Long nodded, raising his hand slightly, signaling Fairy Zi Wei to maintain silence.

At the next moment, Feng Jin Huang suddenly opened her eyes, letting out a soft sound like the cry of a baby phoenix. She then lightly pointed her index finger at the dream realm and activated a killer move.

Whoosh.

A soft sound resonated, white light shot into the dream realm.

The dream realm suddenly froze, then with a shattering noise, like the breaking of a mirror, it completely crumbled apart, scattering everywhere.

"I have succeeded in learning break dream!" Feng Jin Huang raised her arms, exclaiming in joy.

Duke Long nodded with a satisfied expression.

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes involuntarily revealed her shock, Feng Jin Huang's progress in dream path was far beyond her expectation.

Any killer moves of old paths, even if they were of rank nine levels, or even if they were rank nine Immortal Gu Houses, were like stones thrown into a sea in a dream realm, unable to do anything to the dream realm.

But who could have thought Feng Jin Huang's mortal killer move, break dream, could actually be effective against the dream realm.

"Huang Er, you have trained for almost a day now, go take a rest." Duke Long looked at Feng Jin Huang amiably, there was no trace of his terrifying might when he had rampaged through the battlefield and captured Spectral Soul.

"Yes, master." Feng Jin Huang knew Fairy Zi Wei and Duke Long had things to discuss, so she obediently left.

After Feng Jin Huang had gone far, and when only he and Fairy Zi Wei remained, Duke Long spoke: "What is the reason for you to come here?"

"It is just that I have been feeling uneasy, but cannot find the reason." Fairy Zi Wei said, truthfully.

Duke Long immediately frowned: "With your wisdom path attainment, a feeling of unease is a huge matter, but you cannot find its cause?"

Fairy Zi Wei nodded: "I have deduced Fang Yuan and also checked Spectral Soul, but still could not let go of this unease, so I came here to take a look."

Duke Long smiled: "Since you're here, what do you think of this place?"

Fairy Zi Wei also smiled: "I was too anxious, with senior Duke Long's teachings, Feng Jin Huang's progress is really beyond imagination."

Duke Long shook his head: "I don't have any foundation in dream path, Huang Er was able to have such accomplishments all because of her own aptitude and intelligence. I am only looking after her, to prevent any accidents in her cultivation."

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes brightened, praising sincerely: "This child is truly the hope for Heavenly Court to unite the five regions."

Duke Long nodded his head as light flickered in his eyes: "I know where your unease is coming from."

"Oh? Please clear up my doubts, Lord Duke Long."

"My wisdom path attainment is immeasurably lower than yours, but there are only a few possible sources of unease after all. Since it is not Fang Yuan, Spectral Soul, or Feng Jin Huang, then that only leaves Red Lotus."

Red Lotus Demon Venerable!

Fairy Zi Wei's eyes immediately brightened: "You are talking about Red Lotus' true inheritance?"

Three Demon Venerables attacked Heavenly Court, but only Red Lotus Demon Venerable almost destroyed fate Immortal Gu. Even outsiders could realize the unresigned nature of Red Lotus, possibly, through the true inheritance left behind by Red Lotus Demon Venerable, he wanted the inheritor to completely destroy fate Immortal Gu!

"How is the progress in searching for Red Lotus' true inheritance?" Duke Long asked.

Fairy Zi Wei said: "Present and Past Pavilion has been in the River of Time all along, as long as Fang Yuan enters, we will definitely know. Eternal Yacht is almost completed and will enter the River of Time after a few days to search for Red Lotus true inheritance together with Present and Past Pavilion. I still plan to construct Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform and Shark Flow Lever. With these four time path Immortal Gu Houses, no matter how much Fang Yuan has grown, he will completely fail in front of this impassable barrier!"

Chapter 1612: Successfully Constructing the Year Essence Pool

A dreamlike wisp of dawn rays, bright and fresh, was constantly rotating above the palm of Fang Yuan's time path clone.

In Fang Yuan's surroundings, Ying Wu Xie and the rest were already prepared and ready.

"Let's start." Fang Yuan said. Auras of Gu worms suddenly rose from his body as his immortal essence expended rapidly, the rank eight immortal material spiral dawn light suddenly exploded, covering the surrounding hundred li.

Almost at the same time, Ying Wu Xie and the rest set to work, confining this spiral dawn light and not letting it spread farther.

Spiral dawn light was extremely stretchable, it expanded over the surroundings. Although its luster was no longer as transparent as a water wave, Fang Yuan could still feel the slight wind from the spirals at the central area.

Fang Yuan saw that the Shadow Sect immortals had already stabilized the situation, and took out the second portion of spiral dawn light, using it similarly.

Lumps of spiral dawn light erupted, dying the surrounding hundred li with illusory shadows that constantly flickered.

At this time, Fang Yuan took out seven treasures water.

This water was a plain grey color. All kinds of solid bumps that were like gold, silver, pearls, gems, jades, and agates formed naturally in the water. But the moment these solid bumps were extracted from the seven treasures water, they would turn into seven treasures water and splash down.

The time path clone lifted a portion of seven treasures water above his head.

The time path clone could only act as support in this next step, Fang Yuan's main body had to take the primary role. The reason being that Fang Yuan's time path clone was only rank six, thus unable to bear this responsibility.

The divine sense of Fang Yuan's main body had already covered this place, and could immediately sense if there was anything wrong.

At this moment, Fang Yuan activated his methods, immortal essence expending rapidly.

A white light landed on the seven treasures water, the seven treasures water quickly started burbling and boiling, with countless bubbles rising up to the surface.

The solid bumps in the seven treasures water were like snow encountering hot sun, they melted rapidly at a visible rate.

The seven treasures water's volume continued to expand, and soon, all those solid bumps disappeared.

After purifying the seven treasures water, another strange light shot into the seven treasures water.

The seven treasures water quickly turned into an ice block; cold air spread out from it, rapidly engulfing Fang Yuan's time path clone before spreading to the surroundings, covering one hundred li precisely.

When Ying Wu Xie and the rest saw this, they quickly threw the eight-parts jade in their hands into the dense fog.

Everything progressed smoothly…

Several days later in sovereign immortal aperture, a rumbling sound resonated within this area as an enormous one hundred li long pool formed completely.

"This is my rank eight year essence pool!"

Because of sufficient preparation and the advantage of his luck, Fang Yuan successfully constructed this year essence pool on his first try.

Fang Yuan carefully examined it repeatedly and confirmed there were no flaws before he activated time path methods to draw in a tributary of the River of Time.

In every immortal aperture world, as long as time passes inside, there would definitely be a tributary of the River of Time.

The tributary of the River of Time was usually invisible, it could only be targeted using special time path methods.

Bubble bubble…

The tributary of the River of Time in sovereign immortal aperture was much wider and rapid than in ordinary immortal apertures.

The tributary poured into year essence pool smoothly and flowed out from the other end of the year essence pool.

However, the tributary of the River of Time that flowed out was thin as a brook, no longer torrential as before.

The water surface of the year essence pool started to rise slowly.

In the following period of time, the whole sovereign immortal aperture's time flow would continue to slow down. The tributary of the River of Time that flowed out would be restored to its previous state when the year essence pool was completely filled; the flow of time in sovereign immortal aperture would also be restored subsequently.

The year essence pool was successfully constructed, Fang Yuan's time path clone and Shadow Sect's immortals were exhausted. They had been pouring all their energy and concentration into this task, without any rest for several days. They had also expended a lot of immortal essence.

Fang Yuan's main body's divine sense was still staying to observe it while the others left to rest.

Fang Yuan's time path methods gradually lost their effects, the year essence pool and the tributary of the River of Time also became increasingly dimmer till they completely disappeared after a while, deeply concealed inside sovereign immortal aperture.

The year essence pool was rather special, it had integrated with the tributary of the River of Time thus it was also concealed.

It was not just a resource point, but also had the effect of a dam.

For instance, draining the year essence pool's water or accumulating water in it could cause a change in the sovereign immortal aperture's rate of time.

Although Fang Yuan had immortal killer moves like days pass like years and so on, these moves expended immortal essence and every time they were used, they would have no more influence on the tributary of the River of Time for a set interval of time.

But with the year essence pool, this became much easier.

Many Gu Immortals, even if they did not cultivate time path, would construct this kind of essence pool in their immortal aperture to change their immortal aperture's rate of time.

Naturally, they mainly constructed rank six or rank seven year essence pools, and not a rank eight year essence pool like Fang Yuan.

The cost of a rank eight year essence pool was enormous, requiring huge investments, and also required formation path methods.

It was essentially an immortal Gu formation.

It was fortunate that Fang Yuan's formation path attainment level was at grandmaster, and could use the dao marks in the immortal materials to set up immortal formations.

Year beasts began to howl in joy.

The water level of the year essence pool was still low, only a small number of desolate level year beasts sensed it and dived in.

They were born in the River of Time, growing and also dying in it. The most suitable environment for them was also the River of Time. And the year essence pool imitated the environment of the River of Time, it was no wonder these year beasts were joyous.

Following the continuous pouring of the tributary of the River of Time, the year essence pool was slowly expanding.

Be it spiral dawn light, seven treasures water, or eight-parts jade, they all had excellent stretchability and were also merged into one, so they would not self-disintegrate.

When the year essence pool gets completely filled, this rank eight year essence pool would expand to a terrifying ten thousand li length.

What was even more amazing was that it was concealed deeply and was like an illusion, not occupying any space in the sovereign immortal aperture.

The year essence pool was like an independent small world where Fang Yuan could build a food chain, it had no relation to the sovereign immortal aperture.

What made Fang Yuan most satisfied was that the year essence pool could restrain year beasts, making them move around only in the essence pool and not escape outside.

With this characteristic, Fang Yuan could accommodate even more year beasts, and those year beasts could be completely wild, like wild immemorial year beasts.

Fang Yuan could only control seven immemorial year beasts currently, if any of these immemorial year beasts were killed in battles, Fang Yuan was unable to replenish them.

But if the year essence pool had other wild immemorial year beasts, the moment Fang Yuan lost one or two immemorial year beasts, he could temporarily enslave the wild immemorial year beasts to replenish his troops.

This would be extremely helpful in his plan in the River of Time!

After this period of recuperation, Fang Yuan's main body's injuries were completely healed.

"It is time to separate these Gu Immortals' souls and bodies, then soul search them one by one."

At the same time, Fang Yuan did not stop extorting Southern Border's righteous path forces.

However, he met with strong resistance this time.

Southern Border's righteous path forces had united to resist Fang Yuan.

The year essence pool's cost was too high, Fang Yuan's previous extortions had already made these forces bleed. Fang Yuan kept on asking Southern Border's righteous path to show their sincerity, while he himself did not show any sincerity. Southern Border's righteous path secretly ruminated over this, deciding to unite and jointly put pressure on Fang Yuan to force him to give in.

Several days later.

"If you don't show your sincerity, our Southern Border's righteous path will not give you any more resources!" A Shang clan Gu Immortal was chosen to represent the whole of Southern Border's righteous path to negotiate with Fang Yuan.

His words quickly shifted: "All our clans of Southern Border have already shown our sincerity, now it is your turn to show us yours. Only then can we discuss further, otherwise, even if you kill those Gu Immortals, we won't compromise!"

Fang Yuan sneered: "What sincerity do you want from me? Release a portion of the hostages?"

The Shang clan Gu Immortal quickly responded: "We won't make excessive demands of asking for the hostages immediately, we can move step by step, for instance, Immortal Gu. You don't need many of the Immortal Gu, you can first return these Immortal Gu to us, and as the price, we will give you the cultivation resources you need."

Southern Border's righteous path were not idiots. If they asked Fang Yuan to release a portion of the hostages, then the righteous path clans who got back their immortals might not put much effort in the next negotiations. So they would rather start bargaining with Fang Yuan starting from Immortal Gu, then immortal aperture resources, Gu Immortal physical bodies, finally the Gu Immortals' souls.

Like this, Southern Border's righteous path could unite, advancing and retreating together.

Chapter 1613: Threatening the Whole of Southern Border's Righteous Path

"You want to get back Immortal Gu? Impossible!" Fang Yuan laughed coldly.

Immortal Gu were unique!

They were the only one of their kind in the world. Fang Yuan possessing them meant others could not have them, thus their value was inestimable.

Even though Fang Yuan had once sold Immortal Gu to purchase a huge amount of eagle beasts, he was in fatal danger at that time and had no choice but to do so.

Fang Yuan possessed countless killer moves and Immortal Gu recipes, he could make use of almost all Immortal Gu.

The problem was the feeding burden.

Fang Yuan had basically solved this issue for his Immortal Gu. But now, there was an addition of a large number of Immortal Gu, however, the feeding resources for these Immortal Gu were almost all in the bodies of their respective Gu Immortals.

These Gu Immortal experts were trump cards of their respective clans and had deep foundation, how could they not be able to feed their own Gu worms? It was because they could provide the food for their Immortal Gu by themselves that their battle strength was stable, they enjoyed unlimited glory.

Currently, Fang Yuan indeed could not use a lot of the Immortal Gu, but what about the future?

The future was uncertain!

In the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain, Fang Yuan could turn around the situation not only because of the guidance of Star Constellation heaven's will, the crucial key was that he possessed change soul Immortal Gu.

Without this unassuming rank seven Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan would have already died. Shadow Sect would have succeeded in defying heaven.

The difference in having the Immortal Gu and not having it was as different as heaven and earth.

Who could say if, in the future, one of these Immortal Gu might be able to help Fang Yuan turn around the situation like change soul Immortal Gu.

Not to mention that if Fang Yuan sold these Immortal Gu, someone might make an unimaginable comeback like Fang Yuan back in the Battle of Yi Tian Mountain!

Fang Yuan refused the proposal of transacting Immortal Gu without hesitation.

Shang clan's Gu Immortal was not angry: "Then how about exchanging Gu?"

This new proposal interested Fang Yuan.

Southern Border's righteous path wanted to recover their losses as much as possible. Everyone knew Fang Yuan's viciousness and that he could very easily kill the hostages, so they were prepared for the worst.

Those Immortal Gu on the captives had enormous value to the respective clans. This was because they knew the usage methods, a lot of the Immortal Gu had even been taken away from the clan's storage, the clan also had respective killer moves. Many killer moves were even their trump card methods which would be difficult to use without the corresponding Immortal Gu.

As such, Southern Border's righteous path forces were willing to give up some Immortal Gu in their storage, as these Immortal Gu did not have too high of a value to them. It was more worthwhile for them to use these Immortal Gu to exchange for the Immortal Gu in Fang Yuan's hands.

Fang Yuan pondered for a moment, this deal was profitable to both sides, and was also very beneficial to him.

The Immortal Gu that the Southern Border clans could not use and were of less value to them could be of great importance to Fang Yuan.

"You have my interest. But what Gu worms can your clans bring out?" Fang Yuan asked.

Shang clan's Gu Immortal had already prepared for this, immediately sending a list to Fang Yuan through treasure yellow heaven.

Who knew that after Fang Yuan received the list, he said: "I need to look at this list properly. I also have lists here that I will send to your respective clans."

"Fang Yuan, I have already said it, unless you display your sincerity, our Southern Border righteous path won't be extorted by you any more!" The Shang clan Gu Immortal's tone immediately changed.

Fang Yuan smiled: "Your Southern Border righteous path wants to exchange Immortal Gu, sure. But my condition is that you will have to first send the immortal materials in my list to me. Only then will you have the qualifications to make an exchange."

"Fang Yuan, don't go too overboard. If you act like this, we won't continue our discussion."

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed, "The Shang clan Gu Immortal that I currently have captured is Shang Hu Zhang, right? What do you think will happen if I sell him to Fu Sheng Xian?"

Shang clan Gu Immortal was immediately stumped.

Fu Sheng Xian was a rank seven demonic path Gu Immortal of Southern Border who had a deep-seated hatred with Shang Hu Zhang. More than once, he had proclaimed that were Shang Hu Zhang to end up in his hands, he was going to flay the latter's skin and tear the tendons before crushing his bones into ash.

"I believe Fu Sheng Xian will definitely be very interested in buying Shang Hu Zhang." Fang Yuan said in a leisurely tone.

"Fang Yuan, you dare!" Shang clan's Gu Immortal erupted in anger.

"Haha, what would I not dare to do?" Fang Yuan retorted: "I even dared to offend Heavenly Court, why would I fear your mere Shang clan?"

"You, You!" Shang clan's Gu Immortal could not restrain his anger at Fang Yuan's response.

Fang Yuan continued: "Don't overestimate yourself, you are only someone who was chosen to negotiate with me. Did you really think you could represent the whole of Southern Border's righteous path? Let me give another example, Luo clan's Luo Fei is also among the captives. What if I tear all her clothes and throw her into a cesspit? Or what if I throw her into a group of giant apes in heat, and use information path Gu to record every scene, then put them for sale in treasure yellow heaven?"

Shang clan's Gu Immortal gritted his teeth, a deep disgust flashing past his eyes: "Fang Yuan, you are an infamous demon, the Reverse Flow River Lord, inheritor of Red Lotus, Spectral Soul, and many other inheritances, your name is renowned throughout the world, how could you be so shameless and despicable?"

"No, no, no, you are wrong." Fang Yuan shook his head: "I am not despicable, but your attitude is not correct. You have been trying to provoke me, even trying to drive a wedge between me and other clans by saying bad words about them, like how Luo clan is cursing me and wants to plot against me. I believed your words, so I took revenge against Luo clan."

Shang clan's Gu Immortal was unable to say a word, his whole body trembled, his face paled and cold sweat started dripping from his forehead.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Now, you still think you can represent the whole of Southern Border's righteous path?"

After a good while, the Shang clan Gu Immortal said with a tired expression: "Alright, you win, Fang Yuan. I will bring back your list, but I can't guarantee their response."

Fang Yuan laughed: "I don't need your guarantee, you also don't have the qualifications to give me a guarantee. Even if you could, I would not believe you. Go back, you can twist my words and add fuel to the fire when you relay the message to them. Oh, that's right, I need a satisfying answer within three days. If not, I will first sell Shang Hu Zhang to Fu Sheng Xian."

Shang clan's Gu Immortal immediately panicked: "Fang Yuan, you can't do this! I can represent Shang clan to discuss with you right now in private…"

"I refuse!"

"Fang Yuan? Fang Yuan! Damn it!!!" Shang clan Gu Immortal lost contact with Fang Yuan, veins popped out his forehead and pulsed like lightning.

Before the three days limit was reached, Southern Border's righteous path handed over all the materials in Fang Yuan's list.

With hostages in hand, Fang Yuan held too great of an initiative.

He did not need to use any methods and just needed to play some despicable tricks to destroy the tens of thousands of years of reputation that Southern Border's righteous path had, making them the greatest laughingstocks in the eyes of every Gu Immortal.

For the countless years that had passed, there were naturally cases where righteous path Gu Immortals had fallen into the hands of the demonic path.

But some of these demonic path Gu Immortals were not as crazy as Fang Yuan, while most of them did not have Fang Yuan's wisdom path methods.

Wisdom path Gu Immortals were rare, even if Southern Border's righteous path forces did not have a wisdom path Gu Immortal in their own clan, they could rely on relations to get help from a wisdom path great expert.

But when it came to Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan himself cultivated wisdom path and his emperor yama killer move could even defend against Fairy Zi Wei's deductions, when he hid himself, Southern Border's righteous path simply could not find his location. More importantly, Fang Yuan had the battle strength to fight rank eight, his nature was cruel and he was extremely cunning. What other options did Southern Border's righteous path have other than to accept Fang Yuan's conditions?

Naturally, this was because Fang Yuan's extortions had not yet reached the bottom line of Southern Border's righteous path.

If it truly reached their bottom line, Southern Border's righteous path would absolutely not be so nice.

"Fang Yuan, we can talk properly now, right?" The previous Shang clan Gu Immortal found Fang Yuan once again.

Fang Yuan smiled: "Are you truly so unpopular that you are still doing this troublesome job?"

The Shang clan Gu Immortal's face was gloomy, just like Fang Yuan said, this task was harming his reputation, but what could he do? He had no choice but to show up, Shang clan's first supreme elder had personally mentioned his name.

"Let's cut to the chase. We have already satisfied your condition, now…" Before he finished speaking, Fang Yuan interrupted.

"It is my turn to show sincerity. Here."

"What is this?"

Fang Yuan smiled: "This is an information path mortal Gu for Yi clan. I have used some blood path methods to create it, so only Yi clan's Gu Immortals can refine it. Even if others try to refine it, it will end up in failure. Even if they use some methods to refine it, they will not receive my exact message."

"This…"

"No more questions, take it back and you will know."

"Fang Yuan? Fang Yuan! Damn it, he left again!" Shang clan Gu Immortal was stifled, he could only hand over this Gu worm like Fang Yuan said.

Yi clan refined it, obtaining an address.

They were worried this was another of Fang Yuan's traps, so they gathered the other clans and moved together.

In the location, they saw Gu Immortal Yi Yang.

"Yi Yang! This is my clan's Yi Yang!"

"Oh my goodness, this scum Fang Yuan actually released a hostage."

In an instant, Southern Border's immortals were surprised and joyous, while also being unable to believe this.

"Wait a moment, don't get happy so soon. There might be an issue with this Yi Yang!" Without needing the reminder of other clans, Yi clan had already begun carrying out a comprehensive inspection.

The final result was this was indeed Yi Yang and not Fang Yuan's disguise. It was just that this was not the complete Yi Yang, but just his body.

Yi Yang's soul was still in Fang Yuan's hands.

Fang Yuan's action made Southern Border's Gu Immortals see hope of redeeming the captives. In the next meeting, Fang Yuan directly admitted: "I released Yi Yang's body so I can obtain even more benefits. Who is to say that I can't imprison the rest of you in the future, so I can't damage my reputation, right? Don't worry, as long as you can pay the price, I will release all the captives."

"This scum Fang Yuan…" Southern Border's righteous path did not know how they should respond.

The immortals felt mixed feelings, they were happy at seeing hopes of redeeming the hostages, but felt disgust, anger, hatred, and helplessness towards Fang Yuan, including a trace of unease and fear.

Fang Yuan could appear and disappear unpredictably, he had the ability to imprison lone righteous path Gu Immortals. As long as he succeeded, he could escape to an enormous distance once and Southern Border's righteous path would have no way to find his location.

The whole of Southern Border's righteous path was threatened by Fang Yuan, even rank eight Gu Immortals were feeling vigilant. Even they did not feel safe against Fang Yuan, Xia Cha was the best example after all!

Chapter 1614: Soul Search

Fang Yuan's words made Southern Border's righteous path furious and wary, but he had reached his objective of persuading them.

Although this frankness caused Southern Border's righteous path to feel even more hatred towards Fang Yuan, they chose to believe in Fang Yuan's 'sincerity'.

In fact, they were willing to believe in this sincerity.

Because losing a Gu Immortal would be an even greater loss to them!

It would not matter much if it were rank six Gu Immortals with ordinary abilities. The thing was, the captives were rank seven experts, trump cards of their respective clans. Xia clan's Xia Cha was even its first supreme elder.

Losing such experts would greatly affect the whole clan.

Spirit Affinity House had once lost Feng Jiu Ge; its resource points had immediately been coveted by the surrounding ancient sects, and they were under huge pressure.

The ten great ancient sects had the same superior — Heavenly Court, their relations were much closer than Southern Border's righteous path, but this situation occurred even then. Were the Southern Border righteous path forces to end up in such a situation, their state would no doubt be worse.

So be it if every Southern Border righteous path clan lost these Gu Immortals. What made them secretly worried was Fang Yuan killing some and releasing some.

Earth veins were stirring, all kinds of immortal materials and wild Immortal Gu appeared endlessly, it had already caused every Southern Border force to fight each other, they were almost at the point of killing for these resources.

There were many, many individual forces in Southern Border's righteous path, they were already filled with enough conflicts, and the movement of these earth veins had further intensified these conflicts.

If Fang Yuan killed some and released some, there was no doubt that the original balance between the righteous path forces would be broken, the whole of Southern Border's situation would once again be unstable.

The Southern Border righteous path forces were allowing themselves to be extorted by Fang Yuan, was it just because they were afraid of him or because they were worried about the captives?

It was not as simple as that.

They were also worried about themselves.

Whoever Fang Yuan released or killed could change the whole of Southern Border's situation.

They were indeed afraid of Fang Yuan despite them not admitting it. But they were even more wary of each other!

Fang Yuan could clearly see this political tension, and thus was able to unscrupulously extort Southern Border's righteous path.

"The righteous path assumes dignified airs, but is absolutely not ambiguous when taking action. Northern Plains' Hei tribe was an excellent example, Hei tribe weakened, and with the excuse of harboring a culprit of the destruction of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it was immediately besieged by all the Huang Jin tribes."

"Compared to lone, wandering immortals like me, no matter how much we extort, we can't take away territories and we also cannot quickly build a super force to occupy these territories. On the other hand, righteous path forces have a lot of manpower and have the instinct to expand, so the threat is even higher."

"Speaking of which, this is also because there are many Southern Border forces while lacking a powerful leader. If I were to do this in Central Continent, none of the ten great ancient sects would give any attention to me!"

"Southern Border, Western Desert, and Eastern Sea are filled with many individual forces, it is just that the conflicts are the deepest in Southern Border because of the movement in earth veins in this period of time. As for Northern Plains…"

A trace of a smile appeared on Fang Yuan's face.

Compared to his previous life, Northern Plains' Longevity Heaven had already appeared to the world ahead of time, and was now actively uniting the whole of Northern Plains' Gu Immortal world.

Previously, this plan was obstructed by Heavenly Court, who knew which pawn of Heavenly Court disguised as Fang Yuan to kill Cloud Gentleman, thwarting Longevity Heaven's plan to recruit Northern Plains' lone immortals.

But not long ago, Longevity Heaven had a turning point.

That was Lang Ya Sect seeking refuge.

Longevity Heaven absorbed the whole of Lang Ya Sect, moreover doing it with full publicity, letting the whole world know that they had taken in Lang Ya blessed land, giving Lang Ya blessed land an equal status according to the former agreement between Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and Long Hair Ancestor, also ensuring their safety.

This action of promoting their recruitment of a powerful force was truly spectacular!

All the Gu Immortals of five regions were shaken.

Lang Ya blessed land's Gu Immortals were all variant humans, but Longevity Heaven could actually be so generous. That meant their treatment of human Gu Immortals would definitely be even better.

Longevity Heaven thus successfully turned around people's hearts, changing the mindset of the Gu Immortals in the whole of Northern Plains. Their plan of recruiting lone immortals progressed rapidly, completely different from before.

"Speaking of which, Lang Ya land spirit was able to get help from Longevity Heaven, they were truly fortunate."

Longevity Heaven was actively taking action, Northern Plains would definitely bring even more trouble to Central Continent in the five regions chaotic war.

While Western Desert's Xiao clan and Southern Border's Chi clan were secretly receiving Fang Yuan's support.

This was not all, in this period of time, Fang Yuan was constantly mentioning the threat possessed by Heavenly Court in treasure yellow heaven; repeatedly mentioning the problem of the killer move star cast and fate Immortal Gu. Videos of the battle of Reverse Flow River, battle of the dream realm, the battle of Lang Ya Sect, were all displayed in treasure yellow heaven by Fang Yuan, constantly playing on loop, silently recounting Heavenly Court's ambitious and tyrannical way of meddling with the other four regions.

Such actions seemingly had no response. But Fang Yuan believed that there was no super force in the other four regions that did not detest Heavenly Court's actions! They were just temporarily restraining themselves.

Central Continent's ten great ancient sects accepted Heavenly Court because they were sub-sects of Heavenly Court, founded by the members of Heavenly Court.

Northern Plains' righteous path forces could accept Longevity Heaven because they descended from the same bloodline, and Longevity Heaven was Ancestor Giant Sun's grotto-heaven that represented the righteous path.

While Southern Border, Western Desert, and Eastern Sea were controlled by various super forces. They were used to abusing their powers, and none of them wanted a force to boss them around.

Days later, in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Immortal killer move — Soul Search!

Fang Yuan had already designed a killer move with the rank seven soul search Immortal Gu, taken from Yang Ku, as the core. Its efficiency was a dozen times higher than just activating the soul search Immortal Gu.

Under the effect of this killer move, all kinds of information was extracted out of every Gu Immortal's soul and sent to Fang Yuan's mind.

Fang Yuan saw the lifestyle of each Gu Immortal clearly, their cultivation secrets and techniques, factional disputes in their respective forces, secret storages, and so on.

Fang Yuan already had a good understanding of Southern Border. On one hand, there were records of it among Shadow Sect's true inheritances, while he had also learned a lot through Wu clan's information when he had infiltrated them as Wu Yi Hai.

With such a foundation, this first-hand information of many Gu Immortals was added, further deepening Fang Yuan's understanding of Southern Border's situation.

Even rank eight Gu Immortals like Wu Yong and Chi Qu You would not have such detailed understanding of Southern Border's situation.

"Looks like the Immortal Gu list they gave me is correct, except they have concealed some information."

Southern Border's righteous path forces wanted to exchange Gu, and gave Fang Yuan their list of Immortal Gu. Right now, Fang Yuan immediately understood each force's foundation by soul searching these Gu Immortals. Rank six or ordinary rank seven Gu Immortals probably would not have such information, but these rank seven Gu Immortals were experts of their forces. Strength meant authority, so every one of them was a core of their clan's higher-ups.

Fang Yuan was not surprised at the clans hiding information.

Because he knew that the Immortal Gu which were not mentioned were those that the clans were not willing to exchange with and that were very valuable to the respective clan. If Fang Yuan wanted to exchange for the Immortal Gu on the list, it could be done more easily.

In fact, he also wanted to exchange Gu.

"I need to construct an Immortal Gu House to be a base for me to rest and recuperate in River of Time. And, with an Immortal Gu House, Shadow Sect's immortals can also participate in the battle and lend me a hand."

Fang Yuan could exchange the Immortal Gu which he did not need. After all, if Southern Border's righteous path was strengthened, they would be able to resist Heavenly Court much more efficiently.

Naturally, Fang Yuan would not exchange those Immortal Gu which he had great use for.

Immortal Gu were unique, they were priceless, but even more important was the overall situation!

Heavenly Court.

Immortal formation rumbled loudly, Fairy Zi Wei looked at Spectral Soul while holding an iron dragonfish.

Scenes of relevant memories were surging out of Spectral Soul and playing in front of Fairy Zi Wei's eyes.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled: "With this portion of the food path true inheritance, Heavenly Court can also produce, iron, copper, silver, and gold dragonfish, we can change the situation in treasure yellow heaven. Spectral Soul, you are already done for. Dang Hun Mountain's detonation gave you some time to prolong your dying breath, but now, what can you rely on?"

Spectral Soul was condensed into a lump, silent like a dead object.

Chapter 1615: Continued Progress

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Immortal killer move — Soul Search!

A vast force shot at Xia Cha's soul fiercely, but Xia Cha's soul suddenly shined with time path dao marks that completely blocked Fang Yuan's soul search killer move.

But Fang Yuan did not give up, continuing to instill immortal essence without stopping.

A good while later, like a pair of hands lifting a corner of a stuck steel board, a gap appeared in the time path dao marks protecting Xia Cha's soul, allowing Fang Yuan's soul search killer move to finally take effect.

At the next moment, a huge amount of information was greedily absorbed by Fang Yuan. But the time path dao marks had not admitted defeat, the surrounding dao marks moved in to fill the gap.

As time passed, this gap which Fang Yuan had made after so much effort was once again filled in with time path dao marks. Furthermore, the defensive power of this area was even stronger than before!

Fang Yuan's soul search killer move thus stopped here.

"This Xia Cha is indeed worthy of being a rank eight Gu Immortal, she has such a robust foundation that even her soul is protected by a time path defensive method that can resist a rank seven soul search killer move."

"This defensive method also has self recovery and counterattacking abilities, it is truly wonderful."

After Fang Yuan stole all the Immortal Gu from the Southern Border immortal captives, he extracted their souls, separating them from their bodies.

At this state, the threat of these Southern Border captives had already fallen to a negligible level. It was then the process of searching their souls that no longer had the protection of a physical body.

The souls of Tie Qu Zhong, Shang Hu Zhang and others did not give much trouble to Fang Yuan, so all their memories and information were extracted by Fang Yuan.

But he encountered some trouble with Yang Ku. Yang Ku was a rank seven expert who primarily cultivated soul path, so he naturally had strong resistance towards soul search methods.

Yang Ku still could not be considered troublesome, even more troublesome was Liu Hao.

Liu Hao's fixed space Immortal Gu and other Gu were tampered by Heavenly Court, so Fang Yuan was not able to obtain them. Heavenly Court naturally did not forget about his soul, putting in layers of strong defensive methods on it.

But these two were still soul searched by Fang Yuan in the end.

If Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley were sacred lands of soul cultivation, Fang Yuan's Spectral Soul true inheritance was no doubt the number one soul path sacred scripture!

Fang Yuan had thus learned of Liu Hao's true identity, a spy of Heavenly Court.

However, Xia Cha's soul was still the most troublesome one.

Her soul was filled with time path dao marks which had formed into a tight defense that blocked any external attacks. Fang Yuan's soul search was naturally a kind of attack and was harmful to Xia Cha.

Fang Yuan tried all his methods, using Immortal formations to suppress the soul, modifying the soul search killer move, finally reaching the limit of the soul search killer move's power so that he could search Xia Cha's soul.

But this soul search was extremely difficult and did not progress smoothly.

Fang Yuan often had to use a herculean effort before he could open a tiny gap. But this gap would be covered again by time path dao marks, not long later.

Fang Yuan could only soul search in the limited duration of the gap. After this duration passed, the gap would be closed by even more time path dao marks than before, its defense increasing further.

Fortunately, the time path dao marks on Xia Cha's soul did not increase, an increase in time path dao marks in the gap meant there were few dao marks in other areas. This gave Fang Yuan even better chances for his next attack.

The others' souls were already searched completely, only Xia Cha's soul remained.

Fang Yuan continued to target Xia Cha's soul, while using the time path clone to go into each Gu Immortal's immortal aperture by using Fixed Immortal Travel.

Because he had obtained first-hand information from soul searching, Fang Yuan was fully aware of the landscape inside these Gu Immortals' immortal apertures. He could easily enter the immortal apertures by using Fixed Immortal Travel.

Furthermore, Fang Yuan was also aware of what resources these immortal apertures were hiding.

In a Gu Immortal's cultivation, the immortal aperture was an extremely important factor. All of these Southern Border immortals were experts with deep foundation, their immortal aperture management was naturally at a superior level with all kinds of good stuff inside.

But these Gu Immortals would be released by Fang Yuan.

Because the benefits from annexing their immortal apertures and absorbing their dao marks were far inferior to the benefits from extorting those super forces.

An increase in dao marks brought in an increase in foundation as well as a brighter future.

But no matter how beautiful the future was, it was nothing if he could not cross the present obstacle.

The present obstacle was naturally fate Gu, more accurately, he had to stop Heavenly Court from restoring fate Gu.

But Fang Yuan had made no progress in this, he was currently able to avoid Heavenly Court's pursuit, but fate Gu was protected in the depths of Heavenly Court, stopping Heavenly Court from restoring it was far beyond Fang Yuan's capability.

So Fang Yuan was thinking of every way possible to enter the River of Time and inherit Red Lotus' true inheritance.

In the history of humans, three great Demon Venerables had successively attacked Heavenly Court, but only Red Lotus Demon Venerable was able to break fate Gu, although he could not completely destroy it, he had indeed broken fate Gu. In the true inheritances left behind by Red Lotus Demon Venerable, there were likely to be plans targeted at destroying fate Gu.

To smoothly inherit Red Lotus' true inheritance and not be destroyed by Heavenly Court in the process, Fang Yuan needed to raise his time path strength. Other paths' methods were greatly weakened and not useful when fighting in the River of Time.

Year essence pool, time path Immortal Gu House, as well as many other things required Fang Yuan to transact with the Southern Border righteous path, his chips were naturally these Gu Immortal captives.

Several days later in the sovereign immortal aperture's time.

Roar—!

In the sky of Mini Southern Border, a dark green 'rock dragon' roared, its enormous and slender body twisting around.

Then, under the effect of Fang Yuan's killer move, the 'rock dragon' pierced into Mini Southern Border's ground. Loud rumbling noises resounded over the surroundings as this 'rock dragon' pierced into the depths of the ground until even its tail disappeared underground.

Fang Yuan let out a breath: "The matter of drawing in the mineral vein is finally finished."

This 'rock dragon' was not the rock dragon of the rockman tribe, but was the manifestation of a mineral vein. This mineral vein was constructed by using rank seven immortal material dark inkstone. Fang Yuan had moved it over from an earth path Southern Border captive's immortal aperture.

As for the method to move such a large mineral vein, Spectral Soul's true inheritance naturally had it, but the Immortal Gu and the killer move Fang Yuan used came from that captive.

The captive used to relocate outside world's dark inkstone mines into their immortal aperture. Fang Yuan was only imitating them.

"With this dark inkstone mineral vein, I can extract a batch every year and sell them in treasure yellow heaven."

This profit was not much, but it was a steady income.

Because the dark inkstone mineral vein would expand itself by absorbing the surrounding earth qi. As long as Fang Yuan extracted limited amounts, he would have a continuous flow of dark inkstones.

Although dark inkstone did not have a high price among rank seven immortal materials, it was still a rank seven immortal material, its price could not be neglected.

"Maybe… I can move in a batch of rockmen and breed them near the dark inkstone vein." Fang Yuan suddenly had a thought.

This was extremely beneficial to the rockmen.

The higher the quality of the mineral veins, the more helpful it would be for a rockman tribe's procreation, survival, and strengthening. What was even more amazing was that the rockmen could also nurture these mineral veins and increase their purity.

This was a win-win situation for both sides.

But this dark inkstone mineral vein was not suitable for mining yet, and moving in rockmen would only make it their new home.

Fang Yuan thought for a moment before deciding to bring in some rockmen.

The profits from mining the dark inkstone mineral vein was of no importance to him, what he was more interested in was the future benefits brought by the rockmen and the mineral vein.

Fang Yuan had not just obtained this one dark inkstone mineral vein from the Southern Border captives.

There were dozens of mountains in Mini Southern Border now.

Most of them were ordinary mountains, but were filled with dense earth path dao marks, they were treasure troves.

There were also some mountain ranges that reached the level of famous mountains!

For instance, Interior Rain mountain.

This mountain's peak was always shrouded by a layer of dark clouds from where light rain continued to fall.

The drizzling rain was not ordinary rainwater, but rank six immortal material interior rain!

Another example was Copper Seal mountain.

This mountain was red and had a squarish shape, it was like a large seal was standing upright in Mini Southern Border.

Copper Seal mountain did not have even a trace of soil, it was completely formed from all kinds of copper, mortal level copper like chaotic sky copper, pragna copper, snow flower copper, and so on, and immortal copper like profound gray copper and ascending dragon copper.

Naturally, the mortal level copper were of the highest amount and occupied the most space, while immortal coppers only occupied a small portion and were mostly rank six immortal materials. The highest level of the copper was a unique rank seven copper, the famous domination copper! With this copper present, it essentially could not support another rank seven copper.

Mountains, mineral veins, forests… as these Gu Immortal captives were from Southern Border, nearly half of the stolen resources were moved to Mini Southern Border. Because these resources were extremely suited to this environment.

The other half of the resources were split into the other four mini regions as well as the mini nine heavens.

For instance, in Mini Central Continent, there was now a phantom shadow flower garden and a large fertile land filled with an enormous amount of immortal farmer soil.

In Mini Northern Plains, there was now a heaven pillar wind. This wind's appearance was like a tall pillar, extremely tall and long. When it blows, it will not cause movement, only blowing on the spot, from outside, it resembled a giant pillar that extended into the sky.

In Mini Eastern Sea, there was a brand new sea area, wave flower sea area. The sea area was filled with turbulent waves, where countless magical flowers were formed during the moments where waves appeared and vanished. Because they had a short lifespan, they were hard to gather. Fang Yuan had been rather surprised when he obtained the method to nurture this resource from Yi Yang.

In Mini Western Desert, a dozen hibiscus trees were planted, every branch of this tree was an immortal material!

"The sovereign immortal aperture is too large, in terms of specific value, previously, the sovereign immortal aperture's development was only at three to four percent. Now, because of these resources, it has reached eight to nine percent. There are still many resources left in these Southern Border Gu Immortals' immortal apertures, and also Xia Cha's grotto-heaven! With all of them added, the development will definitely pass ten percent." Fang Yuan heaved a sigh.

These resources were either on large or small scale, and a lot were large scale resource points and economic pillars of each Southern Border Gu Immortal!

Heavenly Court had already made a move in treasure yellow heaven, selling copper dragonfish, iron dragonfish and silver dragonfish at heavily reduced price, causing a great impact to Fang Yuan's dragonfish business.

But so what?

These dozen newly added economic pillars would support his continued progress!

Chapter 1616: Request to Fang Clan

Sovereign immortal aperture, Mini Southern Border.

Rumble!

The ground shook violently for a moment, before the dense radiance of an earth path killer move covered the surrounding one hundred li.

Like a large formless hand molding soft mud, the surrounding terrain began to sink in while the land in the periphery began to protrude out, forming a circular valley.

This sunken land was surrounded by mountains, forming an environment that was isolated from the outside.

There was no vegetation in this sunken land, soil was also scarce, it was instead covered by a large amount of steel.

This was white steel bowl valley.

Fang Yuan extorted the production method of the white steel extract resource point as well as corresponding construction materials from Shang clan.

White steel bowl valley was a medium sized resource point, after its construction, it would coagulate rank seven immortal material white steel extract at the center of the valley.

With this immortal material, Fang Yuan could feed rank seven edge Gu by himself.

Previously, when he had plundered Tie Qu Zhong's immortal aperture, he did not find resources to feed edge Gu, but after soul searching him, Fang Yuan realized he had intended to construct this resource point and had already discussed the price with Shang Hu Zhang.

Fang Yuan directly extorted Shang clan, constructing white steel bowl valley without paying any price.

After this task was done, Fang Yuan's time path clone immediately moved towards Dang Hun Mountain.

A lofty and large crystal mountain, pink throughout, was emitting illusory radiance.

Fang Yuan threw soul cores into Dang Hun Mountain, not long later, a large amount of guts Gu was produced on the surface of the mountain.

Dang Hun Mountain had finally recovered, looking close to its complete state!

Ninety-nine percent restoration was already enough. Fang Yuan could not restore it completely, as Heavenly Court already knew Dang Hun Mountain's appearance in its complete state. Although Fixed Immortal Travel was in Fang Yuan's hand, who could say Heavenly Court did not have an immortal killer move that could produce the effect of Fixed Immortal Travel.

"From now on, I can produce a large amount of guts Gu and restart my guts Gu business once again." Fang Yuan let out a breath of air.

It had not been easy to reach this state, Fang Yuan had expended a massive amount of immortal essence!

Dang Hun Mountain had been destroyed before as well, but it had been destroyed by gruel mud Immortal Gu, it had turned into mud but still retained soul path dao marks.

And this time, Fang Yuan only had a small piece of Dang Hun Mountain, most of the soul path dao marks had been destroyed with the destruction of Dang Hun Mountain.

Through this process of restoring Dang Hun Mountain, Fang Yuan deeply experienced the power of the killer move orderly well.

Spectral Soul Demon Venerable had used this rank nine immortal killer move himself, its effect was magical and peerless. Fang Yuan could not have restored Dang Hun Mountain without its help.

"With my guts Gu business, Heavenly Court is unable to limit my income any further."

"But with so many resource points taken from the Southern Border immortals, I can continue to cultivate without relying on guts Gu business."

"It is better to use these guts Gu for my own soul path cultivation."

Fang Yuan's soul foundation had previously broken into one hundred million man soul level, but had greatly fallen now.

Cultivating and raising his soul foundation once again meant Fang Yuan could enslave even more immemorial year beasts!

"Such a pity that my development plan for green ghost desert did not succeed. Qing Chou has escaped, Suan Bu Jin's identity was also exposed, I can no longer continue the plan of hunting soul beasts."

"However, I might be able to borrow Fang clan's help…"

Fang Yuan considered it.

He wanted to cultivate his soul so he naturally needed more guts Gu, which also meant expending a lot of souls. The souls of the Southern Border Gu Immortals could not be used here, it would be a waste of their value. Soul cores were most suitable.

Where could he get a large amount of soul cores?

The price of soul cores had already gone up in treasure yellow heaven, it was especially high during this recent time.

Fang Yuan knew this was Heavenly Court's doing.

Fang clan.

Discussion hall, all the supreme elders had gathered.

"Everyone, have a look at this letter." At the main seat was an old man, he was tall and sturdy, with long white hair spreading around his head like a lion's mane, he was Fang clan's first supreme elder, Fang Gong.

Fang clan's second supreme elder, wisdom path great grandmaster Fang Di Chang, third supreme elder Fang Hua Sheng, as well as Fang Zhi, Fang Chen, Fang Leng, and Fang Yun were all present.

Everyone glanced through the letter and had different expressions.

Fang Chen gritted his teeth: "I had already sensed that Suan Bu Jin was not a good person, but had not expected him to be Fang Yuan in disguise. Heavenly Court has exposed his identity, and is even blaming us Fang clan for colluding with a demonic person. Right now, our clan is being ostracized by other righteous path forces, it is all because of this demon Fang Yuan! And he wants us to supply him with soul cores? Hehe, he is truly dreaming!"

Fang Chen had married into Fang clan, he once had a verbal dispute with Fang Yuan. He immediately showed his stance right now, not willing to associate with the demon Fang Yuan.

Rank seven poison path Gu Immortal Fang Zhi glanced at Fang Chen, saying coldly: "So Fang Chen, you want to reject Fang Yuan's request?"

Fang Chen was stunned: "Is our Fang clan afraid of Fang Yuan? Right now, every large righteous path force is pressuring our Fang clan, their reason being that we colluded with a demonic path member. If we now make a deal with Fang Yuan, they will have an even bigger excuse to isolate us."

Fang Zhi was silent.

In the trip to green ghost desert, Fang clan had beaten back Heavenly Court's rank eight Gu Immortal Chen Yi, succeeded in capturing Divine Bean Palace, and also forcibly subdued two rank seven lone immortals, Old Ghost Bai Jun and Eagle Concubine, to be Fang clan's slaves. Their harvests were huge.

But while they had made gains, Fang clan had also paid a considerable price. Their three Immortal Gu Houses had suffered serious damage, and they still had no ways to refine Divine Bean Palace.

Fang clan's strength had thus fallen greatly, Heavenly Court exposed this matter, causing Fang clan to be immediately met with difficulties from other Western Desert righteous path forces.

But were they truly going to reject Fang Yuan?

This question had already been lingering in the minds of Fang clan Gu Immortals.

Could Fang clan afford to reject him?

Fang clan was being troubled by every clan, they were in a precarious situation from the enormous pressure. And, they were going to offend Fang Yuan at such a crucial time?

At present, who in the world did not know how vicious and crafty Fang Yuan was. He also had powerful battle strength to boot, even Heavenly Court was without options against him.

And such a person happened to be all alone in the world with no fetters of relatives and loved ones, no territories or organization, Fang clan simply had no way to bargain against him!

Fang clan's Gu Immortals started recalling past information, how Fang Yuan had used Fixed Immortal Travel to move around and continuously wreck the resource points of Southern Border's Chi clan.

If Fang clan truly refused Fang Yuan, and Fang Yuan troubled them like he dealt with Chi clan, what should they do?

Chi clan was a righteous path force of Southern Border, when they had been attacked by Fang Yuan, they did not receive support from any other clan. Fang clan's situation would be much worse than Chi clan's.

Not only would Fang clan fail to receive reinforcements, they might even be pincer-attacked by other righteous path forces! If they were not careful, Fang clan would become the next Hei tribe from Northern Plains, their headquarters captured and their clan exterminated.

"Fang Leng, Fang Yun, what are your opinions?" Fang Di Chang suddenly broke the silence.

Fang Yun was stunned, they were only rank six, they normally could only listen from the side and had no qualifications to speak on this kind of occasion. Now, he was suddenly being asked, and was caught off-guard: "This… I also don't know what we should do. After all, Fang Yuan saved my life, he is my benefactor. Moreover… haven't we made an agreement with him? It should be alright to give him soul cores as the compensation. Ah, of course, I will listen to lord father, you can just deduce it."

Fang Di Chang's expression was slightly dark, he took a glance at his adopted son before looking towards Fang Leng.

Compared to the flippant Fang Yun, Fang Leng had a steady nature and was well thought of by many Gu Immortals of Fang clan, believing him to be the future hope of Fang clan.

Fang Leng thought deeply before speaking: "I wonder if everyone has noticed that Fang Yuan did not use the name of Suan Bu Jin in this letter, but directly used his own name?"

Fang Chen snorted: "It is because Heavenly Court already exposed it, it is useless for Fang Yuan to use Suan Bu Jin's identity. He might also be thinking of threatening our clan. By using his name, he is trying to say: I am Fang Yuan, if your Fang clan does not follow my request, you shall face my, Fang Yuan's, anger and vengeance!"

Fang Leng smiled: "There is indeed this meaning. Fang Yuan is confident he can create trouble for our Fang clan. I also believe he can do this, so I think we should agree to Fang Yuan's request."

"What?!" Fang Chen's voice rose, his eyes widened as he tried to rebuke.

But, Fang Di Chang waved his hand: "Let him continue."

Fang Chen did not dare to speak any more.

Fang Leng took a deep breath before continuing: "Everyone, our clan has landed in a precarious situation and is being troubled from all around. Is it truly because we collaborated with the demon Fang Yuan?"

"That is not the case! The true reason is that our clan obtained Divine Bean Palace, once we absorb our gains properly, the top spot among Western Desert's righteous path forces will probably belong to our Fang clan. Strength represents power and authority, and even more importantly, benefits. Our clan's rise will naturally be through stepping on other clans. This is why the other great clans are not tolerating us and are jointly pressuring us."

"If our clan does not satisfy Fang Yuan's request and makes a clean break with him, will the other righteous path forces let us go? That is impossible! On the contrary, we will have made enemies with Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan has rank eight battle strength, if such a demonic overlord takes revenge, it will probably cause endless headache to any super force."

"And by satisfying Fang Yuan's request, not only can we fulfil the previously set agreement, we can also improve our relationship, and even might be able to use his strength to deal with other super forces."

"Of course, we will send the soul cores secretly to him, and after discussing with him, we can act like we have completely broken off our relationship with him. What does it matter if we lose those rank six and rank seven soul cores? They are only immortal materials, as long as our Fang clan can get past this difficulty, what immortal material would we lack in the future?"

The immortals fell into silence.

Fang Di Chang chuckled.

Fang Gong laughed heartily: "Good, we will do it like this then. Fang Yun, you get in touch with Fang Yuan."

"What? Huh!" Fang Yun was dazed, it was clearly Fang Leng who had analyzed and made the proposal, why was he the one to execute it? But first supreme elder's command had to be obeyed, Fang Yun could only accept it.

"This Fang Leng has sound judgment, he sees the overall situation clearly. First and second elder are painstakingly nurturing him into the future successor of Fang clan. How could such a person have a stain of colluding with a demon? So Fang Yun was ordered to take the task." Fang Chen glanced at the ignorant Fang Yun with a pitying look.

This pity also had sympathy.

Why was Fang Yun made to do this task?

That was because Fang Yun was Fang Di Chang's adopted son.

The two biggest factions in Fang clan belonged to first supreme elder Fang Gong and second supreme elder Fang Di Chang.

As for Fang Chen himself, he was extremely aware of the situation. Unfortunately, he was an outsider married into Fang clan, his talents were useless because of his status, he could only be a superficial stepping stone for Fang Leng!

Chapter 1617: Crucial Tribulation

Soul cores with the size of a chicken egg, dark blue to the point of being black, rained down on Dang Hun Mountain.

The soul core contained all of the essence of a soul beast, after the soul beast died, its corpse would turn into smoke and scatter, leaving behind only its soul core.

Soul cores condensed a large amount of soul path dao marks, they were a top tier Gu material.

Soul cores could be found in all sizes, an ordinary soul beast's soul core was the size of a rice grain, and would only be the size of a chicken egg when they reached rank six. Those of rank seven were slightly larger, while a rank eight immemorial soul beast's soul core was as large as a horse carriage.

After a round of discussion, Fang clan finally agreed to Fang Yuan's request, secretly sending him a large amount of soul cores. These soul cores were almost all rank six Gu level, with few being rank seven soul cores, and as for rank eight soul core, there was not even one.

Fang Yuan had two rank eight soul cores but he was storing them, not wanting to use them for producing guts Gu on Dang Hun Mountain.

Rank eight immortal materials were normally used to refine rank eight Immortal Gu or to construct a large formation. Using them for producing guts Gu would be somewhat of a waste of their value.

The radiance of Dang Hun Mountain shook as the soul cores scattered into powder, sprinkling their essence into Dang Hun Mountain. Within moments, guts Gu started condensing with rapid speed.

Fang Yuan nodded inwardly at this scene: "My soul path cultivation can get back on track again and progress swiftly."

Soul path foundation was extremely important to Fang Yuan.

Enslaving immemorial year beasts required it, moreover the deeper the soul foundation, the more immemorial year beasts Fang Yuan could enslave.

Emperor yama expended soul foundation, whenever a wisdom path Gu Immortal made deductions about Fang Yuan, emperor yama would activate to conceal Fang Yuan while expending a portion of Fang Yuan's soul foundation.

Burning soul bursting luck also depended on soul foundation. There was also lead soul into dream, Fang Yuan had already studied this killer move completely, it had a chance of failure. But if Fang Yuan's soul foundation was higher than the target, the killer move's success rate would be much higher.

Fang Yuan had directly used his name in the letter, abandoning Suan Bu Jin's name, Fang clan's response was not beyond his expectations.

To a super force, a lone force like Fang Yuan could not seize their territories, at most he could steal some resources. But other super forces were different, they could forcibly occupy territories and seize entire resource points by sending in their manpower.

The greatest threat to Fang clan were the other righteous path forces that were glaring at it covetously.

"Moreover, Western Desert is somewhat special. Western Desert Gu Immortals compromise a little more easily than those of the other four regions."

This was not because Western Desert Gu Immortals were soft, it was because of the environment.

Different from other regions, Western Desert was filled with boundless deserts and oases. If an oasis was destroyed in a battle between Gu Masters, they would have no foundation for survival and could easily perish together. On the other hand, different oases produced different resources, Gu Masters would need each other's help to make up for what they lack in their cultivation. So Gu Masters often formed caravans and moved a long distance which was usually quite dangerous and exhausting. Thus, there were many collaborative relationships between Gu Masters as well as different forces.

So, since long ago, Western Desert's Gu Masters were molded to compromise and make concessions for the survival of both sides.

Any Gu Immortal had cultivated step by step from Gu Master stage. This habit had sunk deep into their bones and was already a part of the nature of Western Desert Gu Immortals.

In his first life, Fang Yuan had roamed around Western Desert for some time and was well aware of the nature of Western Desert's people.

Had Fang Yuan captured Western Desert Gu Immortals, the Western Desert righteous path forces would have compromised quicker than Southern Border, their attitude would also be more realistic and proper.

Had Fang Yuan captured Northern Plains Gu Immortals, it would be a different situation. Northern Plains Gu Immortals were often valiant and unafraid of death, they might even think it was a disgrace for them to be saved. Fang Yuan would suffer a headache with those captives.

In the following days, Fang Yuan resumed his soul path cultivation while continuing to extort Southern Border's righteous path forces and soul searching the captives.

Fang Yuan's soul search target was Xia Cha.

Although it was rather difficult to search her soul, he was not without any progress. Fang Yuan's immortal aperture's time was very fast, under continuous effort over time, he had made many gains.

Soon, Xia Cha's immortal killer moves were plundered by Fang Yuan.

Xia Cha was worthy of being Xia clan's first supreme elder, she had developed two sets of killer moves involving Spring, Summer, Autumn, and Winter, these four Immortal Gu, each set had four moves.

The first set of killer moves was mainly used for battle, spring scissors, summer fan, autumn perception, and winter coat.

Among them, Fang Yuan had already seen spring scissors and summer fan. These two killer moves were extremely ferocious, fully displaying rank eight might.

Autumn perception was an investigative killer move which greatly made up for Fang Yuan's shortcoming in the investigative aspect.

Winter coat was a defensive killer move with extraordinary effect.

The second set of killer moves was used for managing the immortal aperture, spring ploughing, summer hoeing, autumn harvest, and winter storage.

Every move was ingenious and profound, the more terrifying part was when these four moves were used in unison, their might would be amplified and have extraordinary effect in managing the immortal aperture.

Besides these, there were of course other moves as well, used for healing, movement, or evasive maneuvers, they were all exquisite but could not compare to these two sets of killer moves.

In fact, conceptualizing immortal killer moves was a difficult process, there was a high requirement for the ability and talents of Gu Immortals.

Central Continent's Vicious Lightning Fiend spent a few years in closed cultivation before he was able to deduce the killer move lightning deity. And this was when he had blood deity's Immortal Gu recipe as reference.

Under a normal situation, without any help of wisdom path methods, a Gu Immortal would on average need five to six years of time to deduce and conceptualize a killer move.

Choosing suitable Gu worms out of myriads of Gu worms was not easy. There were even countless choices in combining Gu worms. Even if a killer move was conceptualized, it was useless if it did not have practical value, and also could not be used if the side effect was too severe. After completing a killer move, it still had to be tested and improved which was even more difficult.

Naturally, five to six years was not referring to a Gu Immortal whole-heartedly concentrating on deducing the killer move without doing anything else.

If the Gu Immortal had reference materials like Immortal Gu recipes or inheritances of predecessors, they could further shorten this time.

But the time taken was normally measured in years.

Fang Yuan seemed to be easily deducing and modifying killer moves, the main reason was the light of wisdom, after all, rank nine wisdom Gu was nothing to scoff at. There was also another important reason, that was his deep attainment level in all kinds of paths.

The Immortal Gu and immortal killer moves obtained from Xia Cha greatly supplemented Fang Yuan's strength in terms of time path, he could be said to have made huge progress, like the eruption of a volcano.

But Fang Yuan was facing a rather awkward issue.

"Spring and Summer are both rank eight Immortal Gu, they can only be activated with rank eight immortal essence. I am only a rank seven Gu Immortal, I don't even have the qualifications to refine them without using other methods."

"So I still need to advance my cultivation to rank eight!"

"Then, not only can I use Spring and Summer, there is also wisdom sword Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan started deducing matters regarding his advancement to rank eight.

Several days later, his deduction was finished.

Putting aside heavenly tribulations and earthly calamities, rank seven needed to pass through three grand tribulations to advance to rank eight, and these three grand tribulations would get increasingly powerful.

Fang Yuan was currently very close to the third and final grand tribulation.

The threat of the grand tribulation was not high to him.

Even if heaven's will strengthened it to the greatest limits, Fang Yuan already held firm initiative with his exposing heavenly secret killer move.

What Fang Yuan was worried about was not the grand tribulation, but a possible human calamity.

To face the grand tribulation, he must place his immortal aperture and connect to the outside world to absorb heaven and earth qi.

At that time, Fang Yuan's location would be directly exposed to heaven's will, while also sharply increasing the difficulty in defending against others' deductions.

Heavenly Court absolutely would not let go of this opportunity, they should already have some estimations of Fang Yuan's cultivation level.

If Fang Yuan underwent the tribulation in Southern Border, when Southern Border's Gu Immortals learn of the information, they would rush to kill Fang Yuan even if the captives were with him!

Because if they got rid of Fang Yuan, they would have no more future trouble, and looking at the long term, the benefits they could gain would be even larger.

Fang Yuan's dragonfish business was already obstructed by Heavenly Court, his income falling massively. This showed Spectral Soul was unable to hold on and Heavenly Court was making a lot of progress in soul searching him. As time passed, Heavenly Court would gain more information while Fang Yuan would be put into an increasingly passive situation as all kinds of methods in Spectral Soul's true inheritance continued to lower in value.

"At present, Heavenly Court is my main enemy. The crucial key in the fight against Heavenly Court is fate Gu."

"If Heavenly Court completely restores fate Gu, I will have no more chance at victory. If I can destroy it, I will be able to continue to fight with them."

"And the crucial key to destroying fate Gu lies in Red Lotus' true inheritance." Fang Yuan had already deduced that it was very likely for Red Lotus' true inheritance to hold the method to destroy fate Gu.

"And to inherit Red Lotus' true inheritance, I will have to fight in the River of Time, whether I can break through Heavenly Court's defense line will depend on this third grand tribulation."

"If I can pass it, I will become rank eight, and will be able to use Spring, Summer, and wisdom sword Immortal Gu. My battle strength will soar rapidly, I will have a chance at the battle in the River of Time."

"If I can't pass it, it will be my death. Even if I survive by chance, the opportunity and timing will be lost. After I fall by one step, I will continue to fall behind continuously, unless Heavenly Court makes a serious slip up, they won't give me another chance to make a comeback."

Fang Yuan's mind was cool as ice, well aware of his situation.

The important thing now was to plan on how to pass the third grand tribulation and become a rank eight.

In the following days, besides cultivating his soul, soul searching Xia Cha, and managing his immortal aperture, Fang Yuan focused on exploring dream realms, practising the new immortal killer moves as well as modifying the old killer moves.

It was necessary to modify the old killer moves, especially his soul path killer moves which needed to be greatly improved. Otherwise, if the soul path killer moves were countered or restrained by Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan would be in an extremely passive situation.

As for practising new killer moves, Fang Yuan was mainly practising Xia Cha's methods. He was only rank seven currently, but autumn Gu and winter Gu were also only rank seven, he could practise their corresponding immortal killer moves.

Normally, there were two main difficulties in practising killer moves.

One was the high chance of getting injured. But Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal body which had non-conflicting dao marks and also had Man as Before, so this was not difficult to overcome.

Second was the expenditure of immortal essence. If immortal essence was expended quickly, immortal essence stones had to be refined into immortal essence. Fang Yuan was low on funds before, but he had a lot of businesses now, so he did not lack the capital!

Chapter 1618: Do You Believe In Fate?

Sovereign immortal aperture, an illusory dream realm.

Fang Yuan entered the dream realm.

Under the setting sun.

"Do you believe in fate?"

A human female immortal with skin as fair as snow, wearing a yellow robe, with arched eyebrows and a pair of beautiful eyes shrouded in mist, was looking sadly at the beautiful afterglow of the sun.

Fang Yuan was a rockman Gu Immortal in this dream realm, but it was not under his control.

The dream realm played by itself, the rockman Gu Immortal spoke in a low, muffled voice: "I, Tu Ji, cultivate rule path and naturally believe in fate. Fairy Ruo Li, ever since I saw you, I knew you were my fated partner, you are the person that I will pursue for love over my entire life!"

Fairy Ruo Li smiled slightly, her brows, however, furrowed a little. She looked at the rockman Gu Immortal standing beside her: "You are right, we are fated to be an immortal couple."

"Ah… wha, what? I, I, I…" The rockman Gu Immortal was astonished before becoming exulted, as he shouted in disbelief: "Fairy Ruo Li, have you accepted me?!"

Fairy Ruo Li nodded her head gently.

"Oh heavens, oh heavens! Hahaha! I am not dreaming right? Oh my heavens!" Tu Ji waved around his arms towards the sky and shouted: "I finally succeeded after failing over three thousand times! Hahaha! Fairy Ruo Li, from today onwards, you are my wife."

"Yes, you are my husband."

Tu Ji's body trembled with excitement, the trembling was so intense that rock fragments began to fall from his body.

Second scene.

Ruo Li was gently lying in Tu Ji's arms, soft like a white feather.

She looked at the sky where the clouds were moving across quickly, her eyes were clear as water.

Tu Ji's eyes however were dazed, he had not shifted his gaze at all from Ruo Li's face.

He mumbled: "It has already been twelve years, but I still feel like everything is a dream! Oh Ruo Li, my wife, I swear I will love you and protect you, if you have any wish, tell me, I will do everything to satisfy you."

"Is that so?" Ruo Li asked softly.

"Of course!" Tu Ji replied without any hesitation.

Ruo Li's face showed a rare look of hesitation, after a long while, she said with some difficulty: "Then kill someone for me."

"Kill who? Even if it is a rank eight existence, trust me, I will stake my life to kill them." Tu Ji agreed readily and seriously.

"An infant who was just born." Ruo Li smiled, her smile containing bitterness.

Tu Ji was stunned: "An infant?"

Ruo Li took a deep breath: "Do you believe in fate?"

"I cultivate rule path, I have to believe in the rules of this world. All things have their own ordained path of which is fate." Tu Ji replied.

Ruo Li continued: "Then I will tell you, this baby will become a future Gu Venerable, called Reckless Savage. And in the future, I will definitely die at his hands."

"What?!" Tu Ji was shocked: "Ruo Li, how many times have you checked this prophecy?"

Ruo Li gave a bitter smile: "Only once is enough, but I checked it many times indeed, every result was the same. Do you know why a wisdom path Gu Immortal's prophecy is so accurate? That is because fate is always fixed. I will die at Reckless Savage's hands, that is my fate."

Tu Ji's mouth became dry as waves surged and ebbed in his heart.

But shortly, soaring killing intent suddenly surged out of his body as he stood up: "Then I shall kill him! Although this is fate… I don't believe that I, the grand Tu Ji, a rank eight Gu Immortal, can't kill an infant!!"

Fang Yuan's soul foundation continued to fall as the third scene started.

Tu Ji was heavily injured when he appeared in front of Fairy Ruo Li. His lips shook and his expression was ashamed as well as shocked: "I…"

Fairy Ruo Li smiled: "I know, you encountered your fated enemy on the way there, and he just happened to have made a breakthrough."

Tu Ji was surprised: "You deduced it?"

Fairy Ruo Li nodded: "The moment you got attacked, I deduced it."

Tu Ji was dazed, he hesitated for a moment but still asked: "Then, Ruo Li, since you already deduced it, why didn't you come to help me? If we, husband and wife, joined hands, we could have definitely killed that scumbag!"

Ruo Li shook her head: "You still don't understand? This is fate's arrangement. If I didn't tell you my deductions, you would not have gone to kill that infant. If you didn't go to kill that infant, you would not have encountered your old enemy. Anyone who tries to change fate will be met with fate's punishment. Your injuries are the punishment now. If I had gone to help you, another obstruction would have appeared."

Tu Ji blinked his eyes several times before saying in joy: "So it was like that. That's good, your decision was correct. I won't let you get injured, I would rather be torn apart than see even a hair of yours get damaged."

Ruo Li gave a bitter smile as she looked at Tu Ji: "You understand the power of fate now? You don't need to try anymore, stay with me and quietly accompany me in my final moments. I believe I will be blessed with you by my side."

"No!" Tu Ji's body shook as he said resolutely: "Absolutely not! I won't stand by and watch this happen, I won't let you die. I promised to love you and protect you with my life."

"But my death is fate's arrangement. Oh Tu Ji, my husband, you said it yourself, that you believe in fate." Ruo Li said meaningfully.

"Then… then I will stop believing in it!" At first, Tu Ji struggled and hesitated, but when he finally said it, he could not restrain his roar, his anger soared to the skies.

Fourth scene.

Tu Ji went to look for that infant once again, but an earthly calamity suddenly appeared, there was a landslide, villagers ran everywhere, the infant also disappeared. Tu Ji could only kill some mortals, but he ran into several righteous path immortals. After a huge battle, Tu Ji killed a few of them, but he ended up becoming a major wanted criminal by the human Gu Immortals.

Fifth scene.

Several years later, the tribulation was strange and of unsurpassed strength, Tu Ji almost died undergoing the tribulation. When he was lying in the bed, unable to move, he heard that Ruo Li had finally deduced the specific location of that infant.

"I will go kill him!" Tu Ji struggled to stand up, but when he had just walked a few steps, he fell unconscious.

When he woke up, he saw Fairy Ruo Li had lost lifespan, her hair had turned completely white, he sobbed: "It is all my fault, all my fault, Ruo Li, you went through such painstaking efforts and finally deduced it after several years of closed cultivation… if not for my inability…"

Fairy Ruo Li smiled warmly, consoling: "No problem, I can deduce it again."

Sixth scene. They encountered a beast tide.

Seventh scene. Fairy Ruo Li's deduction failed, suffering backlash, her youth was spent and she became an old lady. She rested in Tu Ji's embrace, smiling bitterly: "Look at what I have become, I must look pathetic, right?"

Tu Ji gently stroked her hair, his gaze still containing deep love: "No, no matter what you look like, you will still be my beloved Fairy Ruo Li."

This special dream realm continued, Fang Yuan could only observe from the start.

Regardless of how Tu Ji and Ruo Li chased, all their attempts were met with failure. One time, he captured the infant, but the baby escaped by some unexpected mishap. Three times, he caught up to the infant, but whenever he tried to make the fatal attack, by some strange factors and coincidences, the baby was able to escape.

That infant was gradually growing up, becoming a Gu Immortal.

The situation moved firmly along the path decided by fate, finally nearing the day of Fairy Ruo Li's death.

Tu Ji became increasingly tense, he knew the most crucial time had arrived. He planned every day and cultivated bitterly, using anything that could increase his strength no matter what the risks were.

On the contrary, Fairy Ruo Li had loosened up, she no longer deduced ceaselessly. She persuaded Tu Ji not to risk his life. Tu Ji did not listen, getting more anxious. Sometimes, she would accompany Tu Ji, lying in his arms, then look at him warmly for a long time as if she could not savor it enough.

Finally, the eighth scene.

The fatal attack was blocked by Tu Ji with his body, he even counterattacked, forcing back that great enemy.

Tu Ji was on the verge of death, he fell in Fairy Ruo Li's arms, saying joyfully: "We… we finally won against fate. Ruo Li… my wife… I did it, I really did it, cough cough cough…"

He wanted to shout and cheer in joy, but he was too weak and coughed incessantly.

He knew he was no doubt going to die and did not have much time; using this final period of time, he grabbed Fairy Ruo Li's hand with difficulty, looking at her with incomparably deep love as he said in a solemn tone: "After I die, you must continue to live on, live well…"

Clear crystal-like tears flowed down Fairy Ruo Li's eyes, sliding down her face.

She tightly embraced Tu Ji, whispering in his ear: "Do you know? Although I cultivate wisdom path, I don't believe in fate. I had deduced fate's arrangement for me, but who would want to die? So I looked for you, actually, our marriage was not even part of the arrangements of fate. I did not love you and only wanted to use you."

Tu Ji smiled, responding in an extremely faint voice: "I knew that, but so what? I love you… I am happy and fully willing to be used by you. Thank you for giving me an opportunity to be used by you… I had once believed in fate, but I don't anymore. Look, you are still alive, fate has already been changed, this is wonderful…"

Tu Ji was no longer able to lift his heavy eyelids as they closed slowly, he no longer responded.

Fairy Ruo Li wept loudly, she had never lost her composure like this before in her life, she repeatedly shook her head and sobbed: "I did not used to believe in fate, but now I do!"

Her whole body started to let out a pure-white light that slowly entered the rockman Gu Immortal Tu Ji's body.

Tu Ji's aura gradually began to recover from its weak state, while Fairy Ruo Li's body became increasingly frail and illusory.

The rockman Gu Immortal opened his eyes once again, when he saw what was happening, he shouted in shock and panic: "No, stop, I don't want to be healed. You will die, you will die!!"

Unfortunately, he did not have any strength left and was unable to stop it.

Fairy Ruo Li's figure had already become illusory, she revealed a smile, saying with incomparable warmth and a trace of craftiness: "You are aware of it, my killer move cannot be stopped once it is activated."

"I want to say one final thing to you, the thing you wanted to hear the most."

"You silly rock… I…"

"I love you."

Once she said that, Fairy Ruo Li faded like an illusion, vanishing from the world.

"No! No——!" Tu Ji roared like an injured beast filled with anger and sorrow, he was powerlessness and in pain.

Chapter 1619: I Do Not Believe!

Gorgeous lights slowly dissipated from the stone room. Feng Jin Huang took a deep breath, staring forward without blinking, with her sharp eyes flickering with light.

A cocoon-like lump of light, the size of a millstone, was quietly floating in front of her.

"The final step." Feng Jin Huang took another deep breath, suddenly pinching all her fingers.

Her ten fingers then opened like blossoming flowers, endless bright lights flickering from them, shining upon the whole stone room!

Feng Jin Huang's movement was so skilled even refinement path grandmasters would show a solemn expression.

Feng Jin Huang was already a refinement path great grandmaster, it was not strange for her to have such exquisite Gu techniques.

What Feng Jin Huang was using was a dual metal and fire path refinement technique, she had found this method to be the most suitable for her.

Boom!

After a while, a loud sound erupted, the cocoon, however, did not explode and was instead rapidly shrinking.

The pure-white cocoon surface gradually turned into dark blue color, while the cocoon gradually turned firmer with some metallic luster.

"I finally succeeded after failing many times!" Feng Jin Huang's eyes flashed with joy. Her mind was calm the whole time, she was already starting to display the demeanor of a refinement path great expert.

The rank five Gu worm was refined, but it still needed to be processed with proper technique.

Feng Jin Huang opened her mouth, carefully breathing out wisps of cold air.

As the cold air blew on it, the blue cocoon slightly trembled and let out a buzzing noise. Large amounts of hot air rose up from the cocoon, filling the whole stone room with hot fog.

Using dual metal and fire path refinement techniques created such a residual effect, the temperature of the Gu worm would become too high and if it was not cooled down in time, it might not die, but it would be severely injured and difficult to use.

Gu refinement was an extremely deep and broad subject with countless techniques. Any Gu refinement technique had its advantages and disadvantages. If an ice refinement method was used to refine this Gu worm, the residual effect could not be treated with cold air, the Gu had to be nourished in warm water for some time.

Feng Jin Huang stopped her techniques and slowly stood up from the cushion.

The rank five Gu floated to her hand, she tested it carefully, her solemn expression bloomed like flowers as she let out a dazzling smile.

She left the secret room and walked out of the cavern.

The moment she opened the door, the huge rumbling noise of a waterfall, the sounds of birds, and the rustling of tree leaves entered her ears.

Outside of the extremely quiet secret room, the world had once again sprouted to life.

The verdant green mountains, birds singing, fragrance of the flowers, the bright sunlight, everything was tranquil and beautiful.

Feng Jin Huang looked around and saw Duke Long sitting quietly on a giant rock beside a pool.

The lights from the mountain delighted the birds, the shadows on the pool set the heart at ease.

"Master, master, take a look! I refined this dream pillow Gu." Feng Jin Huang ran over to Duke Long while holding the newly refined rank five Gu and spoke with a dazzling smile.

Duke Long slowly opened his eyes and took a glance at dream pillow Gu, he nodded his head slightly and said in a mild voice: "Not bad, not bad."

Feng Jin Huang slightly pouted: "How can it only be not bad? Master, you don't know how many times I failed in refining this Gu worm before succeeding this once. With this dream pillow Gu, mortal Gu Masters can enter dream realms if they sleep while laying their heads on it. It will be an enormous help to my Spirit Affinity House and the whole of Central Continent."

Ever since Feng Jin Huang took Duke Long as her master, she had devoted herself to cultivating. Duke Long did not instruct her in cultivation, but taught her of the situation of the whole world and his experiences, expanding her vision and knowledge.

With Duke Long's meticulous teaching, Feng Jin Huang was no longer the same as before, she now had a strategic vision and considered issues in terms of the overall view.

Feng Jin Huang's dream pillow Gu seemed ordinary but because it was a mortal Gu, it could be used by most Gu Masters. As long as this Gu was mass-produced, Central Continent's Gu Masters could easily enter their own dream realms and extract dream path Gu materials from them, gaining an early advantage in the great era.

This Gu was able to raise a whole region's strategic dominance, its significance was beyond ordinary!

Duke Long, however, showed no surprise: "It is only natural for you to have such accomplishments. Huang Er, you are the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable…"

Before Duke Long finished speaking, Feng Jin Huang interrupted with a trace of discontent: "Alright, alright, you are saying this again. Are you saying that I obtained all these accomplishments only because I am the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable?"

Duke Long chuckled as he looked at Feng Jin Huang, suddenly changing the topic: "Huang Er, do you believe in fate?"

Feng Jin Huang's brows furrowed: "Master, are you talking about fate Gu?"

Duke Long nodded: "Right, it is the fate Gu recorded in <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, and also the fate Gu that Heavenly Court is about to restore completely."

<<The Legends of Ren Zu>> stated that Ren Zu had spent enormous energy and effort to gather Gu materials, even sacrificing his own two hands to finally refine wealth Gu.

He brought his son, Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance, and daughter, Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence, to the feathermen's residence.

But strangely, all the feathermen had disappeared with no traces left.

"What's going on?" Ren Zu was puzzled.

"That is because I arrived here, those feathermen are afraid of me, all of them ran away." A black and white spider walked towards Ren Zu leisurely.

"Who are you?" Ren Zu asked.

The spider smiled: "Human, you have walked through the road I created in the Door of Life and Death, you still don't know who I am? I am fate Gu."

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence added: "Fate Gu, you are not even the size of my palm, why would those feathermen fear you?"

Fate Gu chuckled: "Because they pursue freedom, but I, Fate, bind and restrict them."

Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance grumbled: "So your intention was the same as us. You are really a failure, not capturing even one featherman, while hindering us as well."

Fate Gu laughed loudly: "Who said I failed? The feathermen are pursuing freedom, but what do they know? Their escape is only on the superficial level, I have already bound them. The road towards their freedom was all arranged by me, but they think they succeeded, not knowing anything. You are also the same, look at yourselves."

Ren Zu, Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance, and Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence looked at their bodies.

They discovered that white spider silk had stuck to their limbs and body for some unknown time.

They also discovered that not just themselves, even the surrounding flowers, grass, trees, rocks, water, everything was bound by the spider silk.

These spider silk gathered together to form into a spider web which spread out endlessly in the sight of Ren Zu and his children.

"This is the web that I weaved, it is called all-encompassing web. Everything in the world is bound by this web, to be arranged and controlled by me, Fate. Everyone you encountered and all the things that have happened are all controlled by me." Fate Gu said.

Ren Zu and his children felt a chill in their hearts and began to struggle fiercely.

Fate Gu smiled: "It is useless, you cannot escape. Fate cannot be altered."

Ren Zu glared at fate Gu furiously: "Oh Fate, why do you have to manipulate and toy with us? From what you said, all the hardships and misfortunes I encountered were all your doings. The loss of my children was also due to you!"

Fate Gu said calmly: "Human, I know you want to save your eldest son Verdant Great Sun, but he is already dead. Death is a necessary fate of humans, you simply cannot save him. Moreover, you want to rely on wealth Gu to save your daughter Boundless Forest Samsara, that is also impossible."

As Fate willed, a thread of spider silk bound Ren Zu's wealth Gu and dragged it in front of fate Gu.

"Release it, that is our Gu worm!" Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance shouted.

Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence's eyes reddened, sobbing: "Father sacrificed his own hands to painstakingly refine this wealth Gu. How dare you take it away?"

Ren Zu struggled fiercely, but the spider silk continued to become tighter, firmly binding them.

Fate Gu laughed loudly: "Life and death is decreed by fate, prosperity is up to heaven. Human, you are fated to be poor and menial, tormented and humiliated till you become insane, and in the end, you will also die. Although you refined wealth Gu, you don't have the fate to enjoy it. If you are fated to be poor, even if you dug out gold, it will turn to copper, if you are fated to be rich, even if you pick up paper, it will turn to silk. All these things are under my control."

Ren Zu, Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance, and Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence started cursing fate Gu furiously.

Fate Gu was not the least bit angry, still carefree and at leisure: "Many have cursed me, but so what? Humans, no matter how you curse me, it won't change anything."

Fate Gu suddenly moved the spider silk, throwing Blazing Glory Lightning Brilliance and Myriad Gold Wondrous Essence far away, completely out of Ren Zu's sight.

"My children!" Ren Zu howled.

Fate Gu said darkly: "Human, don't blame me, this is your fate. Not just you, loneliness is the fate of every person. Even if they are your own children, they will not accompany you for life and will eventually leave you. Every encounter is temporary, separation is normality."

Ren Zu, however, kept on struggling, but the more he struggled, the tighter the spider silk bound him.

Ren Zu felt an increasingly enormous pressure pushing him down to the point of suffocation.

He panted heavily, he gradually lost the strength to struggle.

Ren Zu started crying, tears rolling down his cheeks: "Why does my fate have to be so pitiful!"

Fate Gu was silent.

But at this time, a voice emerged from the depths of Ren Zu's heart. The voice belonged to self Gu: "Human, believe in your own strength rather than blaming your fate!"

Ren Zu stopped crying as he suddenly realized: "Right, although I don't have strength Gu, self Gu has taken a bite of strength Gu, I have my own strength now. Self Gu, I can only rely on you."

Self Gu then erupted with a dazzling light as it attempted to break the spider silk.

Some spider silk was torn, but even more came to bind Ren Zu.

"My own strength is not enough?" Ren Zu was anxious: "Right, self Gu, you have also taken a bite of love Gu. If strength does not work, let us rely on love instead."

Thereupon, self Gu let out a gentle light as it attempted to break the spider silk, but this also failed.

Fate Gu said: "Oh human, why can't you understand? Love is a type of fate, I arranged it to make Verdant Great Sun fall in love with Desolate Ancient Moon, I also arranged it to make the rockman fall in love with Desolate Ancient Moon. I also arranged success and failure in their lives, so they eventually ended up dead."

"No! No——!" Ren Zu screamed and bawled.

Fate Gu listened quietly.

Ren Zu gradually lost the strength to cry, he mumbled powerlessly: "I understand now, I know why the feathermen pursue freedom."

Fate Gu smiled: "Human, you also want to pursue freedom?"

Ren Zu nodded: "Yes, if I have freedom, I will be no longer be bound by you."

Fate Gu: "But look at those feathermen, even though they pursue freedom, aren't they still under my control?"

Ren Zu shook his head: "My freedom is different from them. I will pursue absolute freedom."

Fate Gu laughed loudly: "A person's absolute freedom is insanity. Oh human, see for yourself, you are seeking freedom but you are actually moving towards insanity. I already said this earlier, you will lose your mind. That is the road I arranged for you, you cannot escape my control."

"No! I don't believe you! I will use my own strength and wisdom to obtain freedom. I don't believe your words, I will escape your control!" Ren Zu retorted.

Fate Gu's laughter became louder: "Oh human, you are truly going crazy, you are already deranged. Did you forget? Your self Gu has only taken a bite of strength Gu and love Gu, so you only have your own strength and love, but not your own wisdom. Oh human, when you think you are intelligent, it will be the sign that you are going crazy."

"Hahaha, hahaha." It was Ren Zu's turn to laugh: "I don't believe you, oh fate Gu, I don't believe you! I don't believe that this world has fate."

Fate Gu was silent for a moment before saying: "Even if you don't believe it, I will still exist."

Ren Zu rebuked: "No, that is not true. When I stop believing in you, you will stop existing. I refuse to believe in fate, fate does not exist! Hahaha!"

Fate Gu shook its head, sighing: "Truly pitiful, oh human, you have already fallen into insanity."

Ren Zu scratched his hair and skin, his tears and mucus mixed together, he struggled, he knelt on the ground as he rolled around.

It was like how Fate declared, he had become insane.

…

Time flew by rapidly as a scene of the past suddenly appeared in Duke Long's mind.

A million years ago.

"Do you believe in fate?" Duke Long was standing and looking at his disciple warmly.

His disciple was only a youngster with a glossy forehead, handsome appearance and bright eyes. He had long black hair that reached his waist, there was a lifelike red lotus birthmark on his forehead.

Duke Long continued: "Red Lotus, you are the future Immortal Venerable, you will definitely lead us humans towards the greatest prosperity and glory. You will certainly succeed, creating your own Gu worms and techniques, you will become the pride of your parents, become invincible in the world, and your name shall be marked in history. You will join Heavenly Court, become the leader of humanity, and bring blessings to all beings, your glory will shine throughout time and space."

Young Red Lotus blinked his eyes before smiling, exposing his dazzling teeth: "There does not seem to be anything bad with this. I believe in fate!"

Duke Long returned to reality after the slight trance.

He looked at Feng Jin Huang and said solemnly: "Huang Er, you need to understand that you are the future Great Dream Immortal Venerable who will surpass all the past venerables! You will create dream path and be invincible in the whole world. Your glory will shine and spread for ages, becoming the eternal symbol and support of humanity. Don't fear, don't hesitate, take each success to press forward indomitably until you reach the supreme peak of this world!"

Feng Jin Huang's eyes got brighter and brighter as she listened. She smiled with unparalleled beauty.

Duke Long also smiled.

Feng Jin Huang said: "If all this is predestined by fate, then… I do not believe in fate!"

"What?" Duke Long's smile froze on his face.

Chapter 1620: Southern Alliance

Heavenly Court.

The large formation let out buzzing noises as glaring light pierced deep into Spectral Soul's body like sharp needles.

Despite him curling up and defending with all his strength, he was still hard-pressed to resist the formation's power.

Fairy Zi Wei was concentrating fully on controlling the large formation while also absorbing all kinds of information extracted from Spectral Soul.

Only when the formation let out breaking noises did Fairy Zi Wei stop while feeling unsatisfied. She gave a deep glance at Spectral Soul.

Even if they were enemies, Fairy Zi Wei could not help but admire Spectral Soul's tenacity.

He was clearly in a desperate situation with no trace of hope, but he was still resisting to the end. He was indeed worthy of being an invincible Gu Venerable.

Fairy Zi Wei left without saying anything.

Returning to her hall, she immediately began to concentrate on deducing. The use of Star Constellation Chessboard pushed her deduction ability to the peak of the world.

Countless thoughts emerged and faded in her mind like the flickering of countless stars. Her thoughts constantly collided with each each other, even flying out of the body, turning into countless purple light specks that covered Fairy Zi Wei's body before spreading to fill the whole vast hall.

A long while later, the purple thoughts gradually drew in, dissipated and finally calmed. Fairy Zi Wei took a deep breath, stopping her methods as she slowly opened her eyes.

A layer of thin sweat had formed on her forehead, her brows were furrowed into a tight knot and she looked mentally exhausted.

"Fang Yuan, where in the world are you going to undergo tribulation?" Fairy Zi Wei muttered.

She had been working hard, repeatedly extracting various internal details of Shadow Sect from Spectral Soul. She was especially interested in Shadow Sect's arrangements left in the five regions.

Because Fang Yuan had used Shadow Sect's arrangement to capture the pursuing team of Southern Border righteous path in one go. If Fang Yuan was to undergo tribulation, he was very likely to once again rely on these arrangements. It would make no sense for him to not borrow this help.

Fairy Zi Wei had been closely paying attention to Fang Yuan's cultivation progress. After the battle in Lang Ya blessed land, she clearly deduced Fang Yuan was not far from rank eight.

Rank seven and rank eight were two completely different levels!

In the absence of rank nine, rank eights were the peak of the world.

Once Fang Yuan advances to rank eight, he would truly become difficult to suppress, and would become an enormous obstacle for Heavenly Court.

"Fang Yuan's final grand tribulation is the crucial point. If we can kill him here, it would be greatly beneficial to Heavenly Court and people all over the world."

Fairy Zi Wei was not going to let go of any chance to kill Fang Yuan, but she found this matter was extremely troubling.

Because she could not tell the specific time and location of Fang Yuan's tribulation for sure.

Fang Yuan possessed emperor yama, which had strong defensive properties, not giving her any chance to make deductions against him.

Fang Yuan also had plentiful time path methods to alter the rate of time in the immortal aperture, so it could not be estimated when he was going to undergo the final grand tribulation.

Fang Yuan also had Fixed Immortal Travel and could undergo his tribulation anywhere in the world. How could Fairy Zi Wei make arrangements like this?

The most she could do was rule out black heaven and white heaven.

Because a blessed land would absorb a slightly higher amount of earth qi when undergoing tribulation, so it was usually done in the five regions.

Naturally, the possibility of undergoing tribulation in black or white heaven was small but not zero, there were several areas which were special and had abundant earth qi.

But what about the five regions?

The River of Time was only a secluded domain of heaven and earth, so Fairy Zi Wei could arrange Immortal Gu Houses in it and guard it heavily.

But when it came to the huge area of the five regions, even thousands of Immortal Gu Houses would not be enough. Let alone when Heavenly Court did not have enough manpower to assign to every area of five regions to interfere with Fang Yuan's tribulation.

Fairy Zi Wei heaved a sigh, she did not have any good solutions.

The plan now was to use all her strength to extract valuable clues from Spectral Soul and use them to deduce the possible locations where Fang Yuan could undergo tribulation. Meanwhile, she would actively contact the righteous path forces of five regions and release the news of Fang Yuan undergoing tribulation. Heavenly Court did not have control over the other four regions and was only able to borrow their strength.

The news that Fang Yuan was about to undergo tribulation quickly spread throughout the five regions.

Not only the righteous path clans and sects, even demonic and lone immortals heard about it.

Currently, Fang Yuan was already renowned throughout the five regions. Although he only had rank seven cultivation, his battle accomplishments were so amazing that he was already recognized as the number one person below rank eight. The Gu Immortal world acknowledged that even Feng Jiu Ge was inferior to him, he was the strongest new star of the demonic path in the last hundred years, his growth was so shockingly fast that when the Gu Immortal world reacted, he had already become a demonic path overlord.

So the news of Fang Yuan undergoing tribulation quickly created a heated discussion in the Gu Immortal world of the five regions.

"If this demon passes the final grand tribulation, he will become a rank eight Gu Immortal, how can we ignore this?!"

"Demons are rising while the righteous path is weakening, what else can we do?"

"This person is extraordinary, he possesses Spring Autumn Cicada, is someone who has been reborn, and also has obtained the inheritances of multiple venerables. A grand tribulation cannot stop him."

"I have a different opinion. As the saying goes 'one who commits many injustices is doomed to failure', this demon is too arrogant, he wants to undergo tribulation, but he has to first see if Heavenly Court or the entire world's righteous path are allowing it or not."

Some were optimistic about Fang Yuan while some were pessimistic. But, one point was clear, the absolute majority of the Gu Immortals did not want to see Fang Yuan succeed in his tribulation.

"This demon brought chaos to the world when he was just rank six and even more disaster when he is rank seven, would he topple the world if he advances to rank eight?"

"I don't care if Fang Yuan undergoes tribulation in other places. But if he undergoes tribulation in Southern Border, my Tie clan will not allow it!"

While the Gu Immortal world was in fervent discussions, Southern Border's righteous path forces were also actively holding meetings or frequently contacting each other to discuss about how to deal with Fang Yuan.

Despite there still being hostages in Fang Yuan's hands, if they were able to take this chance to eradicate this disaster, Southern Border's righteous path forces would be more than happy.

The reason was simple: benefits!

Ignoring Fang Yuan and letting him grow stronger meant he would increasingly become a bigger threat and shroud over Southern Border's righteous path, like a dark cloud. There might even be a day where one of them might face a calamity under his hands.

More importantly, Fang Yuan had an extremely huge amount of Immortal Gu, Immortal Gu recipes, inheritances, and all kinds of cultivation resources, he was simply a moving treasure trove. They might be able to obtain enormous benefits by killing him. Even if his immortal aperture was destroyed, as long as a fragment of his soul remains, these righteous path forces could soul search and might obtain some venerable's incomplete inheritance. Just this alone was enough for these righteous path forces to go after him like a flock of cranes.

Wu Yong said in a heavy voice: "The headquarters of Shadow Sect are in Southern Border, there are bound to be many arrangements put in place here. Previously, Fang Yuan used one of the arrangements to capture many immortals. There is a high probability of Fang Yuan undergoing tribulation in Southern Border!"

Prior to saying this, Wu Yong had secretly received information from Fairy Zi Wei and knew of several arrangements Shadow Sect had put in Southern Border.

Wu Yong was fully aware Fairy Zi Wei was making use of him to deal with Fang Yuan. But Wu Yong was willing to be used. Because Fang Yuan had heavily toyed with him by disguising as Wu Yi Hai, Fang Yuan being alive was the greatest disgrace to the whole of Wu clan and him, Wu Yong!

"Lord Wu Yong's analysis is sound." Qiao clan Gu Immortal immediately added: "Fang Yuan captured Gu Immortals from every clan, he is also an inheritor of Shadow Sect, the current sect leader, he definitely has powerful soul path methods. After soul searching the captives, he will be clear of the situation of our Southern Border righteous path."

"Moreover, our Southern Border has been through all kinds of large changes in these recent years, be they lone or demonic immortals, they have all suffered severe losses, especially our righteous path. If that demon undergoes tribulation here, he will face the least obstruction."

"Even if Fang Yuan undergoes tribulation in Southern Border, how can we keep a lookout? Southern Border is so large, he could very well undergo tribulation in some corner, how would we know?" A Gu Immortal asked.

"We can know it by investigating." Xia clan Gu Immortal replied, "Once he places his immortal aperture and connects to the world, he has to maintain this state till he finishes the tribulation. He will no longer be hidden in this period of time, and we will be able to trace him. Even without others' help, our Xia clan's wisdom path Gu Immortals will be able to deduce his specific location with the help of our formation."

"Of course, if there are many wisdom path Gu Immortals helping us, we will have even more certainty in deducing Fang Yuan's location, and also much more quickly." Another Xia clan Gu Immortal continued, "The true difficulty is not in deducing his location but how we can reach there in time. There is also a premise here that we must have gathered a considerable number of Gu Immortals to deal with Fang Yuan."

Southern Border's Gu Immortals fell into silence.

Since ancient times, the Southern Border righteous path forces were numerous and divided, no one submitting to others. And to eliminate Fang Yuan, these Southern Border forces had to work with full cooperation and unity.

This could be considered an unprecedented event.

Fang Yuan was currently able to fight rank eight, but he was one person in the end. Any single super clan of the righteous path could make sure Fang Yuan had more trouble than he could handle during the tribulation, causing him to fail his tribulation and even die.

Because these righteous path forces either possessed rank eight Gu Immortal or had Immortal Gu Houses that could fight rank eight. Most of them had managed their territories and resources for thousands of years or even tens of thousands of years, so they had incomparably robust foundation. In contrast, Fang Yuan had developed for a considerably shorter time.

But was it possible for one super clan to use all their strength against Fang Yuan?

Impossible.

This was a jungle, every righteous path clan was a fierce beast who ruled over a territory. If this fierce beast left its territory to attack another fierce beast, even if the latter was not fully developed, it would still have claws and fangs.

This risk was too large.

Even if it killed the other, the fierce beast could very likely be injured and if its injuries were too severe, other fierce beasts would be attracted to invade.

Of course, the invasion would be under the cover of justice. They would find all sorts of excuses, with so many conflicts between Southern Border righteous path forces over the years, would they be worried about not finding an excuse?

Even if they really had no excuse, they could offer to 'help'. For instance, take the initiative to help for the 'prosperity of Southern Border'. Look at how passionate I am to help you. Do you dare to refuse? Do you have the strength to refuse?

So, the true difficulty in dealing with Fang Yuan did not lie in Fang Yuan himself.

Was Fang Yuan strong?

Indeed, being able to fight rank eight with rank seven cultivation was extremely rare even in history.

But what if he was compared to a super force?

Fang Yuan was not strong, he could not compare to a group's strength. After continuous conflicts, Fang Yuan would start bleeding.

Some Southern Border Gu Immortals could only smile bitterly because they knew: The current situation was ironic. The ones binding them were themselves. They were wary of each other and kept each other in check. They divided their forces to guard their large territories to defend against each other.

The silence lasted a long while, until a Tie clan Gu Immortal suddenly spoke: "Actually, there is a way to resolve a portion of this issue. Everyone knows of the Immortal Gu House Beacon Tower of my Tie clan."

Southern Border Gu Immortals maintained their silence, but it did not last long when another voice spoke: "I agree with Tie clan in building Beacon Towers."

Everyone was shocked, because this person was none other than Wu clan's first supreme elder Wu Yong!

Even that rank six Tie clan Gu Immortal who had spoken just now was surprised. Wu Yong actually supported Tie clan in building Beacon Tower?

While everyone was still in shock, Wu Yong spoke again, his voice was low and deep, his every word landing in the immortals' minds like a giant rock.

He said: "It is time to make a change. Have you still not realized? The wave of the great era is already upon us, the five regions' regional walls have also started to thin. If we don't start changing now, we will be submerged by this wave of the new era."

The immortals fell into silence.

Another person stood up, he was Ba clan's first supreme elder who had always wanted to seize the number one position from Wu clan.

He rarely spoke and thus startled everyone: "My Ba clan supports Wu Yong. We need to look ahead, Central Continent has Heavenly Court, Northern Plains has Longevity Heaven, what does our Southern Border have?"

He paused for a moment before making a logical point: "We have many forces but every force is independent, we will be taken down by the other regions eventually. So I support Wu Yong and also agree to Tie clan building Beacon Towers."

Not long after him, Chi clan's first supreme elder Chi Qu You expressed his support.

Then, Luo clan, Hou clan, Chai clan, and so on also expressed their strong intent to unite.

Southern Border's immortals suddenly realized that this event was of an extreme importance and would be recorded in the history of Southern Border!

Never had such a situation appeared where Southern Border's righteous path forces joined hands. This was not just a superficial proclamation, but a true close cooperation!

The atmosphere was heated like never before, waves rose in Southern Border Gu Immortals' minds as they felt an excitement at participating in a historical moment!

"Let Fang Yuan be the first sacrificial offering to our Southern Alliance, then… the other four regions!" Wu Yong did not conceal his ambitions.

Chapter 1621: Fang Yuan's Tribulation

Several months later, Southern Border.

In a nameless ordinary valley.

"Hah!" Rank six female immortal Ba Tao gave a loud shout as auras surged out from her body. She lifted her hands like she was bearing thousands of kilograms of weight, her face quickly reddened and her body started trembling in exhaustion.

"Quick." Ba Tao urged.

A Gu Immortal who was standing at the side activated a killer move.

This person was a young looking rank six Gu Immortal from Tie clan. He was Tie Yi, son of Tie Qu Zhong.

Red light spheres started rising up, suddenly with a loud sound, the spheres turned into a soaring red light pillar that shot towards the skies.

But at this time, an old looking Gu Immortal revealed himself, he was standing on clouds. With a wave of his hand, he suppressed this red light pillar.

The red light pillar dissipated, revealing a seven floored pagoda that looked like it was forged from bronze. A fire was quietly burning on top of the pagoda.

"Done." Tie Yi let out a breath of air, revealing a satisfied expression: "Another Beacon Tower is built."

"So exhausting." Ba Tao breathed a sigh of relief as she sat on the ground, panting.

The old looking Gu Immortal slowly floated down, at the same time, countless Gu worms gathered and went inside his sleeves.

This was a small group tasked to build Beacon Towers.

There were three people, Tie clan Gu Immortal Tie Yi was in charge of building the Beacon Towers, Ba Tao was supporting him, while the old Gu Immortal was in charge of setting up a formation to disguise the process. After all, the commotion of the Beacon Tower's construction was huge and could easily be known by others.

There were still more than a dozen of such groups. After Southern Border's righteous path forces agreed to collaborate, these small groups rushed everywhere to build Beacon Towers.

"Beacon Tower is indeed worthy of being Tie clan's signature Immortal Gu House, it is truly unbelievable for a Gu House formed from mortal Gu to be able to transport Gu Immortals!" The old Gu Immortal sighed while gazing at the Beacon Tower.

Tie Yi helped Ba Tao stand and replied to the old Gu Immortal: "The true terror of Beacon Tower is that the higher the number of Beacon Towers built, the greater their overall power. To reach an Immortal Gu House's power, there needs to be at least one hundred Beacon Towers. Right now, the number of Beacon Towers in Southern Border is already over one thousand and can transport rank seven Gu Immortals. But to transport rank eights, we need at at least ten thousand Beacon Towers."

"Many thanks for clearing my doubts." The old Gu Immortal expressed his thanks.

Tie Yi and the old Gu Immortal glanced at each other and smiled.

If it were before, this secret of Beacon Tower absolutely could not be mentioned. But because Southern Border's righteous path was uniting, the Gu Immortals' attitude towards each other was gradually changing.

"If we had a Beacon Tower near that tributary of the River of Time, our Southern Border righteous path could have mobilized our troops and saved my grandfather in time." Ba Tao mumbled in a daze while looking at the Beacon Tower.

"Ba Tao, we still have hope. Wasn't Yi clan's Gu Immortal released by Fang Yuan? This demon Fang Yuan just wants more cultivation resources." The old Gu Immortal consoled.

Tie Yi did not speak, his mind was, however, in a disorder.

His situation was similar to Ba Tao, his father Tie Qu Zhong had also been captured by Fang Yuan.

He was of course furious and hated Fang Yuan, but he had to admit that if Fang Yuan had not captured so many Southern Border Gu Immortals and made Southern Border righteous path feel pain, would Southern Border righteous path forces have united so quickly?

Between comfort and pain, the latter was able to move people's hearts much more easily.

Sometimes, Tie Yi felt this situation was ironic. Beacon Tower's plan had been Tie clan's dream since long ago, but it had come to fruition because of a demonic path overlord. Naturally, there was also another important reason, the impending great era. But regardless, Fang Yuan's actions had played a key role.

Whoosh whoosh.

The Beacon Tower suddenly let out a strange sound, even slightly shaking for a moment.

"What's going on?" This sight immediately attracted the old Gu Immortal's attention, he frowned and looked at Tie Yi.

Ba Tao also casted her gaze at Tie Yi.

She had participated in building many Beacon Towers, but had never seen this scene before. Were there some flaws in the construction of this Beacon Tower?

Tie Yi's frown was even deeper: "You don't need to worry, this scene is not because of an issue with this Beacon Tower, it is because one of the Beacon Towers spread throughout the Southern Border has been completely destroyed."

"Oh? So it was like that." The old Gu Immortal slightly relaxed.

Ba Tao snorted coldly.

This scene was within the expectations of Southern Border's righteous path. Although the construction of Beacon Towers had obtained the approval of Southern Border's righteous path, Southern Border's Gu Immortal world had demonic cultivators and lone cultivators as well.

Beacon Towers were under the control of Tie clan, it represented the benefits of Tie clan and other Southern Border super forces, which had no relation to these demonic and lone cultivators.

It was extremely likely for a Beacon Tower to be destroyed by these Gu Immortals if they discovered it.

"Investigate who attacked, we will kill them as a warning to the others!" The old Gu Immortal's killing intent soared, this was one of the methods, discussed by the Southern Border righteous path forces, to deal with such matters.

However, at the next moment, Beacon Tower's anomaly shocked the three immortals.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh.

A series of strange sounds resounded for a while. The newly constructed Beacon Tower trembled non-stop like an epileptic patient.

"What happened?"

"This… does this mean many Beacon Towers are being destroyed successively?"

Ba Tao and the old Gu Immortal once again looked at Tie Yi.

This time, even Tie Yi was puzzled as he mumbled: "Strange, does this Beacon Tower really have an issue?"

But at the next moment, their doubt was removed.

The three immortals' expressions changed because they had received astonishing news at almost the same time.

The mad destruction of Beacon Towers was caused by only one person, it was none other than the nefarious and unpardonable demonic path overlord Fang Yuan!

"Fang Yuan has outstanding wisdom path methods, it is not difficult for him to deduce the location of these Beacon Towers. He also has Fixed Immortal Travel and can move anywhere freely. It is not strange for him to be able to do this." Tie Yi's expression was gloomy.

"Damn it! That incompetent Heavenly Court, they actually let Fang Yuan steal Fixed Immortal Travel!" Ba Tao said furiously with clenched fists.

The old Gu Immortal was steady and cautious: "We should return to our clans. Since Fang Yuan is moving about, it is not safe outside."

Tie Yi and Ba Tao tensed up as they thought of Fang Yuan's methods, having no intention to stay behind.

At the same time, Wu Yong, Chi Qu You and other clan leaders were in an urgent meeting.

"Fang Yuan probably noticed the threat of Beacon Towers so he is taking an early action to destroy them! Look, my clan's Beacon Tower has already made him feel unease." Tie clan's first supreme elder said.

"Hmph, just let him destroy. The construction of Beacon Towers is quite difficult and requires Gu Immortals to personally do it. But they are only constructed with mortal Gu, so their cost is low, we can just let him destroy them." Shang clan's first supreme elder laughed coldly, showing the aura of a wealthy force.

Wu Yong, however, frowned, he had slightly more understanding of Fang Yuan: "Fang Yuan is crafty, we cannot look down on him. I feel like his action has another deep meaning, it is not as simple as it looks."

Wu Yong's words immediately attracted other Gu Immortals' attention.

One of them spoke: "Would this be possible? Fang Yuan is going to undergo tribulation in Southern Border, and one of these Beacon Towers is extremely near to the location where he will undergo tribulation. So he took action and destroyed a large amount of them."

"It is reasonable!"

"Quick, gather wisdom path Gu Immortals to make deductions!"

"As long as Fang Yuan makes a move, he will leave behind all kinds of clues. Right now, he is making a big commotion, we will definitely have more gains in our deductions."

After a round of deductions, there were indeed great results.

Southern Border righteous path obtained three locations which had the greatest possibility of being the areas where Fang Yuan would undergo tribulation.

"Quickly investigate."

"These three areas should be emphasized and guarded heavily."

Similar commands were passed down, Southern Border's Gu Immortal world moved with an unprecedented and united pace, all to kill their common enemy.

A moment later, shocking news reached every Southern Border force — there was an unusual disturbance of heaven and earth qi in the five regional mountain range and its range was extremely large!

Chapter 1622: Besieging Fang Yuan

"Five regional mountain range?" Jun Shen Guang's thoughts flickered.

Fang Yuan's unbridled destruction of Beacon Towers caused a huge commotion, even Heavenly Court, which had very weak influence in Southern Border, was able to detect it.

Southern Border's righteous path forces had gathered many wisdom path Gu Immortals and deduced three locations, which also included the five regional mountain range.

While in Heavenly Court, Fairy Zi Wei deduced alone but had found out about five regional mountain range a step earlier.

Jun Shen Guang immediately moved towards the five regional mountain range.

At the same time, all kinds of relevant information about the five regional mountain range appeared in his mind.

This five regional mountain range was not a naturally formed mountain range, but was man-made. The person who could create such a mountain range was naturally not ordinary, he was rank eight restriction path Gu Immortal Tao Zhu.

This person had extraordinary attainment level and was called Restriction Expert. He had done deep research regarding the five regional walls, he attempted to find a way to allow Gu Immortals to travel through the regional walls easily.

Unfortunately, even until his death, there had been no progress. But this five regions mountain range was left behind and became a special area in Southern Border.

"Senior Thunder Ghost True Monarch was beaten by Fang Yuan when she chased him into the regional wall, this battle revealed the secret of Fang Yuan receiving almost no suppression in regional walls. The regional walls can even be said to be his natural territory."

"Unfortunately for him, it is almost impossible to draw in heaven and earth qi in regional walls, he definitely can't undergo tribulation in the regional walls. But five regional mountain range is different, this area is man-made and has ample earth qi since it is in Southern Border, heaven qi is also not scarce in it, it is also able to provide some territorial advantages for Fang Yuan!"

Jun Shen Guang was extremely fast, he had already crossed tens of thousands of li while all kinds of thoughts moved rapidly in his mind. He could already see the five regional mountain range on the horizon.

Jun Shen Guang was able to so quickly rush to the scene because he had been lurking near this area.

Everyone knew of the five regional mountain range, it was not a secret.

Months ago, Fairy Zi Wei had deduced some locations where Fang Yuan might undergo tribulation. Five regional mountain range was among the top possible locations.

As such, the five regional mountain range was one of the heavily observed locations by Heavenly Court.

This time, to deal with Fang Yuan, Fairy Zi Wei did not hesitate to transfer many rank eight Gu Immortals into the other four regions. Southern Border had two, Jun Shen Guang was one of them, the other was a rank eight Gu Immortal, Wei Feng, who was rather far away but was currently rushing towards the location with all haste.

Jun Shen Guang reached close to five regional mountain range and activated a killer move to hide himself before carefully moving forward.

Swoosh swoosh!

Endless amounts of heaven and earth qi, like giant river waves, were drawn in and gathered in the central area of the five regional mountain range.

That area was covered in shadows and bright light, nothing could be seen. That area was like a bottomless hole that endlessly devoured the enormous amount of heaven and earth qi.

"This scale, it is truly terrifying…" Jun Shen Guang felt a chill from the sight. He quickly activated his unique investigative methods.

After Fang Yuan successfully trapped and captured the group of Southern Border Gu Immortals, Jun Shen Guang had appeared to inspect the battlefield.

Right now, Jun Shen Guang was vigilant and did not dare to rashly move ahead even though he was a rank eight Gu Immortal, a rank higher than Fang Yuan. If by any chance, he rashly entered the five regional mountain range and discovered it was Fang Yuan's trap, it would be truly miserable.

After Jun Shen Guang inspected properly, he confirmed someone was indeed undergoing tribulation.

But whether it was Fang Yuan or not was unknown.

Jun Shen Guang was extremely patient and used other methods, after a while of investigation, he confirmed an otherworldly demon was undergoing tribulation.

As such, Jun Shen Guang was almost one hundred percent sure this was where Fang Yuan was.

"He is truly undergoing tribulation here!" Jun Shen Guang mumbled, his gaze holding some disbelief.

But he quickly reacted, smiling at himself: "The truth sounds fake while the lies sound real, Fang Yuan is clearly here but I actually don't dare to believe it."

Northern Plains' Hei tribe had unique methods that could detect otherworldly demons. Heavenly Court naturally also had similar killer moves.

Back when Fairy Zi Wei had tried to persuade Fang Yuan to surrender, she had revealed: Heavenly Court is the Heavenly Court of humanity, even otherworldly demons would be accepted in it. Heavenly Court had indeed recruited otherworldly demons before but there were no clear records in history, so others were unaware.

It was not strange for Heavenly Court to possess such methods.

Jun Shen Guang was currently using this method.

"The probability of Fang Yuan taking such methods into consideration and deceiving us is too low. After all, even if he has reborn, this method was specially modified by Lady Zi Wei recently."

"I've heard that after Yuan Qiong Du joined Heavenly Court, besides being in charge of restoring fate Gu, he has also been refining Immortal Gu targeted towards dealing with Fang Yuan."

There were cases in history where rank eight demonic path Gu Immortals caused havoc in the world.

When Heavenly Court became unable to restrain them easily, they would refine Immortal Gu to deal with such demons. This kind of Immortal Gu were specially meant to subdue specific demons, and as such had extraordinary effect.

Fang Yuan was only rank seven but was already thought so highly by Heavenly Court, a case like this was unprecedented even in history.

"There could be another reason, he is no longer able to delay the grand tribulation and must undergo the tribulation!" Jun Shen Guang's eyes flashed with sharp light.

Someone was undergoing tribulation here and that person was an otherworldly demon; it was clear that person was Fang Yuan.

If it were someone else, who would come to this place to undergo tribulation?

Adding on the scale of the heaven and earth qi, and the otherworldly demon identity, who else could it be other than Fang Yuan?

"Good, good, good. Fang Yuan, my Heavenly Court has finally caught you!" Jun Shen Guang's face shined with increasing excitement.

Fang Yuan had already started his tribulation and could not move casually during this time, he had become a live target.

Even if he had Fixed Immortal Travel, how could he use it?

This could be said to be Fang Yuan's weakest moment.

Jun Shen Guang's expression slowly calmed down, turning serious as a deadly and murderous aura moved around his body.

"If I kill Fang Yuan, I will make a world-shaking contribution!" Jun Shen Guang's heart was set on fire, it was truly lucky that he could encounter such a good opportunity!

"No wonder Lady Zi Wei once told me that I had abundant luck, although it is not a match for Fang Yuan's, I won't be suppressed by his luck as long as I don't make the first move. If I stalk from behind like an oriole, waiting for Fang Yuan's luck to weaken, I have a chance to win."

Jun Shen Guang's eyes were already burning with killing intent.

"So what if it is the five regional mountain range? It is only an imitation of the regional walls, even if Fang Yuan was undergoing tribulation in the regional wall, I, Jun Shen Guang, would forcibly enter and kill him!"

Rumble!

A sonic wave suddenly erupted as an Immortal Gu House charged into the five regional mountain range like lightning.

Jun Shen Guang's heart immediately chilled: "Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building? These Southern Border immortals arrived really fast! Sure enough, the Beacon Towers helped them a lot. Even my Heavenly Court does not have such methods to gather troops so quickly. When we invade Southern Border in the future, we must first get rid of these Beacon Towers."

Jun Shen Guang was actually somewhat happy to see these Southern Border righteous path forces. He wanted these people to spearhead the attack, wearing down Fang Yuan's battle strength and luck.

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building rose to the sky, Wu Yong and the Southern Border righteous path immortals were looking at the whole five regional mountain range from within the bamboo building.

Many Gu Immortals felt puzzled and stunned at such a scale of heaven and earth qi.

Some wisdom path Gu Immortals deduced together, and soon, one of them excitedly said: "It is almost certain that Fang Yuan is undergoing tribulation here!"

"Great!"

"Wonderful, wonderful."

"Fang Yuan is a heinous demon with deep sins, we will avenge our Southern Border righteous path's brethren by taking his head today."

"We are saving the world by killing this demon, we will bring blessings to the people of the world!"

"Hmph, this Fang Yuan really thinks my Southern Border righteous path is a pushover? He is really undergoing tribulation in Southern Border."

"Hehehe, he probably thought we will be afraid because he has our members in captivity. Little could he imagine how firm our Southern Border righteous path is in defending our values!"

The Southern Border immortals were full of battle intent.

Xia clan's second supreme elder Xia Zhao and third supreme elder Xia Chen Yuan looked at each other with helplessness. They really wanted to save their first supreme elder Xia Cha, but they had no choice but to go with the flow in this atmosphere.

Southern Border's righteous path forces were already suppressing deep anger from being extorted by Fang Yuan. It was just that they were not able to find Fang Yuan's location, after calculating the benefits, they chose to be extorted to protect the hostages.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan was in front of them, as long as they killed him, they might be able to obtain inheritances of multiple venerables, countless cultivation resources, and several secluded domains of heaven and earth!

The soaring hatred and the enormous benefits made these Southern Border Gu Immortals' eyes turn red.

"Our Southern Border righteous path alliance is newly established, we need to establish a name for ourselves using an infamous demon, Fang Yuan is perfect for this. Everyone, this damned demon is undergoing tribulation, we have limited time, we will attack from all sides and make his death anniversary exactly a year from now!" Under Wu Yong's command, Southern Border righteous path immortals rushed out.

They had a powerful group of immortals: Chi Qu You, Shang Wu Jie, and other rank eight Gu Immortals; seniors with high authority like Xia Zhao and others, rank seven experts like Yao Du, Hou Teng, Ba De and so on. Even Jun Shen Guang who was hiding inwardly clicked his tongue. This was almost the full force of Southern Border's righteous path, there were probably only some minor rank six immortals left to guard their headquarters.

At this moment, inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Heaven qi was surging rapidly, boundless lumps of lights condensed into dozens of giant beams of light and shot towards Fang Yuan.

Earth qi solidified, restraining Fang Yuan's movement.

Fang Yuan was austere, his attention was not on the tribulation, but outside his immortal aperture.

"Oh wow, quite a number of people have showed up. Southern Border's righteous path really hates me, of course the wealth I possess is also extremely attractive. Besides them, there definitely have to be Heavenly Court's Gu Immortals lying in ambush, but I am not able to find them for now."

He had captured many Southern Border Gu Immortals and soul searched them, gaining deep understanding of Southern Border's righteous path, but he did not dare to have any hint of carelessness right now.

Southern Border's righteous path had robust foundations and hidden trump cards. Especially some deeply hidden trump cards, even the clan's first supreme elder might not be aware of them, let alone the captives in Fang Yuan's hands.

"The Beacon Towers are troublesome indeed." Fang Yuan heaved a sigh.

"I destroyed so many, but it is extremely easy for them to construct more again. In my first life of five hundred years, Southern Border was defeated repeatedly before they finally began constructing Beacon Towers on a large scale. In this life, because of me, the construction of the Beacon Towers has been brought forward. Those holding high positions are indeed not simple, they cannot be underestimated."

Chapter 1623: Eight Ears Monkey

The Southern Border immortals immediately felt strong forces of repulsion and attraction when they entered the five regional mountain range.

They activated their killer moves to move forward while maintaining defensive methods, their immortal apertures shook constantly as they suffered backlash from their immortal killer moves.

"This demon chose quite a good place!" Some Southern Border Gu Immortals said with hatred.

"Even if my immortal aperture is destroyed, I will get rid of this demon!" Many Gu Immortals instead became filled with battle intent as their thoughts of killing Fang Yuan became even more firm.

Fang Yuan was so crafty and vicious, he was audacious and arrogant, having no fear of even Heavenly Court let alone of the other regions' righteous paths.

This person was only rank seven but had ambushed Southern Border's righteous path immortals and taken them captive for ransom, if he was allowed to advance to rank eight, how disastrous would that be?

If Fang Yuan was a righteous path member, it would be fine.

Righteous path had to abide by rules. But he was of the demonic path, a lone individual, he killed or robbed others for the cultivation resources he needed. This was an irreconcilable conflict!

Moreover, Fang Yuan not only had terrifying battle strength to kill and loot, he could even defend against deductions, this was too frightening.

This calamity must be eradicated as early as possible!

"Kill! Charge in!! Avenge our clansmen."

"Whoever kills Fang Yuan will be heavily rewarded by me, Shang Wu Jie!"

"I, Chi Qu You, will personally set up an immortal formation for them!"

"My Wu clan will open the treasury and let the person who kills Fang Yuan choose three Immortal Gu!!"

The morale of Southern Border's Gu Immortals soared crazily in front of the great rewards. They split into various groups and moved to every area of the five regional mountain range, creating a perimeter around the central area before charging in.

Caw caw!

A series of chicken cries was heard, a giant immemorial year chicken suddenly appeared and blocked Shang Wu Jie's group.

Fang Yuan had naturally made arrangements, spreading immemorial year beasts in all directions to block the enemy.

This immemorial year chicken charged ferociously towards the Southern Border Gu Immortals.

The accompanying rank seven Gu Immortals felt a chill in their hearts and were about to defend with all their strength when they suddenly heard Shang Wu Jie's snort.

"A little chick trying to block me!" Shang Wu Jie shouted, directly activating a rank eight killer move.

Boom!

The immemorial year chicken was sent flying, it crashed into a mountain and fell unconscious immediately.

The rank seven Gu Immortals gasped at this sight, their gaze towards Shang Wu Jie had already changed.

"Shang Wu Jie might be a rank eight Gu Immortal but he was never famous for his battle strength, I didn't imagine his offensive move to be so fierce!"

"An immemorial year chicken is still an immemorial year beast, but was knocked unconscious by Shang Wu Jie without even a chance to retaliate."

"Ferocious, too ferocious!"

"Shang clan is ranked among the top five super forces of Southern Border, but the strength Shang Wu Jie showed is too powerful."

Shang Wu Jie's performance was extremely shocking. No matter how weak the immemorial year chicken was, it was still at rank eight level, who could have thought it would be get done in by just one move.

"Oh? He brought weak chicken Gu with him…" Fang Yuan was observing the situation outside while undergoing the tribulation.

The immemorial year chicken's poor performance made Fang Yuan recall a famous transaction in his previous life. Ba clan rank seven Gu Immortal Ba Ji paid an enormous price to obtain rank eight weak chicken Gu from Shang clan. Because of some special method, he was actually able to use this Immortal Gu and increase his strength greatly, successively raising a huge storm in the five regions chaotic war.

"Currently, Gu Immortal Ba Ji is still in closed cultivation, he is not famous and is hardly regarded by anyone. Weak chicken Gu is still with Shang clan and was brought by Shang Wu Jie to deal with me."

Shang Wu Jie's battle strength was not outstanding among Southern Border's rank eights, but he created a great sensation with weak chicken Gu.

Fortunately, that immemorial year rooster was only unconscious and not killed, it could still be saved.

Fang Yuan immediately sent an immemorial year snake to attack Shang Wu Jie's group.

The two sides confronted, Shang Wu Jie was immediately obstructed, his previous momentum coming to an abrupt stop.

Several other groups were also facing Shang Wu Jie's situation, and they all had rank eight Gu Immortals. Fang Yuan was clearly prioritizing defending against these rank eight existences.

These immemorial year beasts were not the match of the rank eight Gu Immortals in one-on-one combat, but they could block them for some time.

Moreover, it was different in the five regional mountain range.

The difficulty of using any immortal killer move increased greatly and the Gu Immortal would even suffer the backlash. There were also attraction and repulsion forces that constantly disturbed the Gu Immortals. They not only had to concentrate on the fight, but also had to constantly pay attention to these constant attraction and repulsion forces.

These attraction and repulsion forces became greater on those with higher cultivation. Rank eight Gu Immortals would face great difficulty to make any move, this was also why, under normal situations, rank eight Gu Immortals traveled through black heaven or white heaven, detouring around this path.

But in the end, the five regional mountain range was only an imitation of five regions' regional walls, so its obstruction towards rank eight Gu Immortals was not as powerful as the true regional walls. Even so, it still greatly restricted the actions of rank eight Gu Immortals.

For a moment, even Wu Yong had to use all his strength to fight the immemorial year beast, unable to move any further.

These immemorial year beasts came from the River of Time and were not born in the five regions, so they suffered no restrictions.

As for Immortal Gu House Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, it was a consolidated immortal killer move and would be severely restrained in the five regional mountain range. Wu Yong had already stored it inside his immortal aperture and did not dare to rashly take it out.

"This demon's scheme is truly sly, no wonder he chose this place to undergo tribulation!" A Gu Immortal coughed out blood and shouted.

"Forget us, charge in and disturb Fang Yuan's tribulation. We can't let him pass this tribulation!" Chi Qu You shouted.

Fang Yuan had arranged all the immemorial year beasts, but their numbers were not as high as the Southern Border Gu Immortals.

While the immemorial year beasts were restraining the Southern Border immortals, they were also being restrained at the same time. Many Southern Border Gu Immortals passed around the immemorial year beasts and charged towards Fang Yuan.

"Formation, rise!" Fang Yuan was not panicked, under his command, a large immortal formation suddenly activated in the surroundings.

Instantly, the Southern Border Gu Immortals lost their five senses, dense fog appeared before them making them lose their direction.

"This demon had a backup plan indeed!"

"Don't be afraid, Immortal Gu Houses can't be used easily in the five regional mountain range, the same applies to immortal formations. Once enough time passes, it will collapse by itself, at that time, Fang Yuan will have to bear the backlash of the collapse!"

"No, this is exactly that demon's plan. As long as he can hold out for this time and pass the tribulation, even if the formation collapses and he suffers backlash, he can use Fixed Immortal Travel to escape."

The Southern Border Gu Immortals rapidly conversed with each other, immediately realizing Fang Yuan's delaying tactic.

"We need to break this formation as soon as possible!"

"Do you have such methods?"

"Not good, Chi clan's Gu Immortals are all obstructed, none of them came."

"Damn it, this demon did it deliberately."

"Hahaha." Suddenly, a Gu Immortal's laughter could be heard.

Everyone's gaze was attracted towards the source, they saw a person with a large head, small body, and crafty eyes. Someone immediately asked: "Friend from Hou clan, why are you laughing?"

Hou clan Gu Immortal Hou Zi Shua stopped laughing and said: "No need to be worried, everyone, I found that this formation has no space path ability, it is only confusing our senses and causing us to fail to detect the correct direction. I have a beast that can be used for this. Come out!"

Just as he finished speaking, a strange light shot out of Hou Zi Shua's immortal aperture and landed on his shoulder, turning into a monkey.

This monkey was small, covered with dense amount of silver fur, it had eight ears, four on the left and four on the right.

A Gu Immortal gasped in shock: "Could this be an immemorial desolate beast eight ears monkey?!"

Hou Zi Shua laughed loudly: "You are exactly right!"

Ear monkey was a strange and precious beast, it was an information path beast. Even ordinary mortal ear monkeys were scarce, an immortal ear monkey was even rarer.

When the ear monkey has six ears, it is a desolate beast. Seven ears meant ancient desolate beast. And eight ears meant an immemorial desolate beast!

Instantly, the Southern Border immortals' gazes towards Hou Zi Shua changed.

Hou Zi Shua only had rank seven cultivation, he neither had great battle strength nor was famous, who could have thought he was actually hiding an immemorial desolate beast!

He had really hidden it deeply, he might not have showed this trump card if not for this expedition to kill Fang Yuan.

"Monkey, monkey, where is the enemy?" Hou Zi Shua stroked the eight ears monkey's small head and softly commanded.

The eight ears monkey, an immemorial desolate beast, was actually so tame that it obediently listened to Hou Zi Shua's words. It immediately tilted to the side and listened for a moment, before screeching and pointing towards a direction.

Everyone followed its direction, immediately making continuous breakthroughs.

Suddenly, the immortal formation changed, the eight ears monkey immediately screamed loudly; it listened once again before pointing to another direction.

Fang Yuan frowned, if this went on, he would not be able to block these Southern Border Gu Immortals even if he repeatedly changed the formation.

"It is actually an eight ears monkey! Although Hou clan has always focused on raising and enslaving monkeys, I didn't think they had such a rare divine beast." Jun Shen Guang's killing intent rose.

Killing Fang Yuan was of great importance, Jun Shen Guang hesitated for a moment before deciding to take the risk. When the Southern Border Gu Immortals had entered the five regional mountain range, he had already quietly activated a killer move to conceal himself and enter.

The other Heavenly Court Gu Immortal, Wei Feng, was rapidly approaching as well.

"Beasts like eight ears monkey can perceive everything in the surroundings, when Central Continent invades Southern Border, most of our concealment methods will be useless. Killing it will be greatly helpful to my Heavenly Court's plan!"

A trace of killing intent appeared in Jun Shen Guang's eyes when he looked at the eight ears monkey.

The eight ears monkey immediately reacted, giving a sharp panicked screech.

"This beast is quite sensitive!" Jun Shen Guang quickly retracted his gaze and looked ahead: "Forget it, I will spare it for now. The urgent task is still Fang Yuan."

"Don't be afraid, don't be afraid!" Hou Zi Shua comforted the eight ears monkey.

Right at this time, their vision suddenly cleared up, some Gu Immortals shouted: "We have broken out!"

Whoosh whoosh whoosh.

The sovereign immortal aperture's entrance was wide open as it endlessly devoured the surging heaven and earth qi.

"This is Fang Yuan's immortal aperture?"

"We are close now!"

Their enemy was in front of them, but the Southern Border immortals were dazed, looking at each other, none dared to move forward.

Fang Yuan's terrifying might made these rank seven Gu Immortals feel uneasy.

"Hmph, the Southern Alliance might have been established, but can the overall situation be changed instantly? These people are still a disorderly band!" Jun Shen Guang sneered.

He continued to move ahead while concealing himself, he was trying to enter Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

"Once I enter Fang Yuan's immortal aperture, he will be in a passive state and will have to hold back for fear of destroying his own resources."

"I don't even have to fight Fang Yuan, I just need to move around while destroying his resources, Fang Yuan definitely would not be able to bear it."

"Even more perfect is that Fang Yuan's grand tribulation has yet to form, if I disturb him from the side, he will make a mistake trying to deal with everything and I might really be able to kill him."

"But for more assurance, I should continue to hide inside his immortal aperture, and after Fang Yuan has fought the tribulation and Southern Border immortals for a while, I can make a fatal move. Hahah! I can't wait to see his expression when he realizes a powerful enemy has entered his immortal aperture."

Jun Shen Guang possessed extremely powerful concealment methods, this was one of his specialties.

Naturally, he knew there was also a possibility of him being seen through and discovered by Fang Yuan.

But if he did not grasp such a great opportunity, he would miss a chance at victory! Moreover, the probability of Fang Yuan seeing through his concealment was low.

What did not carry risk? Let alone when it would be a fierce battle.

Jun Shen Guang was a high and mighty rank eight Gu Immortal, but he had never lost the courage to stake his life. It was just that he had a clear understanding of when he should take the risk and when he should not.

"Now is the time to stake my life!" Jun Shen Guang's eyes shined with bright light as he activated his immortal killer move. He endured the backlash and entered the sovereign immortal aperture along with heaven and earth qi.

The Southern Border immortals had all been maintaining investigative killer moves but none of them detected Jun Shen Guang.

Chapter 1624: This is a Trap!

The immortal aperture's entrance was wide open, but the scale of the absorption of heaven and earth qi had already decreased by a lot.

"What is this? The enemy is in front of you and you are all hesitating?" A Tie clan Gu Immortal shouted at the Southern Border immortals.

Many became red with shame, they immediately came to their senses and someone yelled: "Let's charge in together!"

"Fang Yuan is still undergoing tribulation, we will win this battle! Whoever runs away will be the biggest disgrace of Southern Border's righteous path!"

"That's right, let's charge into his immortal aperture. Even if we die, we will make sure this demon has huge losses!"

"Hehehe, why so pessimistic? This demon has extorted so many things, his immortal aperture definitely has wondrous and rare resources, not to mention he also has a few secluded domains of heaven and earth!"

"My clan's Gu Immortal is still in his captivity, I wonder where he is putting the captives."

"I have already checked, there are no immortal formations around us." Hou Zi Shua assured while stroking the eight ears monkey's small head.

The Southern Border immortals immediately put their hearts at ease.

Fang Yuan's formation had made Southern Border's righteous path suffer huge losses. After this problem was removed, their morale soared, charging into the entrance of the immortal aperture one after the other.

Buzz buzz buzz!

But right at this moment, there was a change.

Ear-piercing buzzing sounds resounded throughout the battlefield, almost bursting the immortals' eardrums.

At the same time, an extremely dazzling light burst out; many Southern Border Gu Immortals were caught off-guard, their vision was covered in white as they temporarily lost sight.

The Southern Border immortals were shocked, they defended in panic while sending out countless killer moves towards the center of the light.

The person inside the light was not Fang Yuan, but Jun Shen Guang!

He was furious and shaken: "This killer move of mine is fright light, it will activate automatically when I face fatal danger and I don't need to control it. Fright light was activated when I tried to sneak into Fang Yuan's immortal aperture! What's going on?! Could there still be a trap?"

He was a rank eight Gu Immortal, he retreated rapidly while blocking the bombardment of the Southern Border immortals.

"Hehehe, you have great methods, but since you have arrived, why be in a hurry to leave?" Fang Yuan's leisurely laughter reached Jun Shen Guang's ears.

Jun Shen Guang's mind jolted, crying out: "Oh no!"

He immediately sensed a formless attraction force pulling him, trying to drag him into Fang Yuan's immortal aperture.

Immediately, Jun Shen Guang's doubt completely disappeared, he was certain that this was Fang Yuan's trap!

Jun Shen Guang roared and without regard for the backlash from the five regional mountain range, he crazily activated his immortal killer moves to resist the formless attraction force.

Jun Shen Guang used his main method to turn into a ray of strange light once again and tried to shoot out of the battlefield.

But although the killer move succeeded, the strange light's speed was so slow, to the point of being like a snail or a tortoise.

"Damn it, this is a time path method!" Jun Shen Guang immediately identified it because this time path method had slowed down his time by close to one hundred times.

Jun Shen Guang was extremely shocked: "I am a rank eight Gu Immortal with rank eight dao marks, why am I being slowed down so much? Fang Yuan's time path method is actually at rank eight level, this is completely beyond the previous information, how did he achieve this?"

"What happened?"

"I have been struck!"

"Time is extremely slow, it is like I am trapped in a swamp, quickly think of some way!"

Like Jun Shen Guang, the nearby Southern Border immortals were also in the same situation.

"Hehehe, you all came uninvited, I should naturally pay such enthusiasm a hundredfold in return." Fang Yuan descended on the battlefield.

They saw a Gu Immortal wearing a loose white robe, with black hair fluttering in the wind, his face was handsome to the point of being beautiful. A pair of deep abyss-like eyes with a gaze filled with coldness and terrifying killing intent.

The Gu Immortals here were all too familiar with this appearance, such that their bodies started shaking and their faces paled in fright.

Someone among the Gu Immortals said with a trembling voice: "Fang Yuan!"

Fang Yuan ignored these rank seven Gu Immortals and looked at Jun Shen Guang.

Jun Shen Guang's face was red as he used all his strength to get rid of the time path restraints. He had plenty of methods and they were showing good effects under his efforts, the time path restraints on him were decreasing and his speed was subsequently increasing.

Fang Yuan smiled, slowly extending his left arm.

His pristine jade-like hand spread open elegantly, like the blossoming of a white lotus.

Soul path aura surged out and instantly shrunk fiercely, condensing into an illusory figure in Fang Yuan's left palm.

This illusory figure looked like the real Luo Po Valley, but shrunk by countless times.

Luo Po Valley's illusory figure leisurely rotated while Fang Yuan's left hand began to slowly close.

Jun Shen Guang's mind rang madly with warning signals, an unprecedented sense of danger had shrouded his whole body and mind. His eyes opened wide, almost about to rip open from the nervousness.

"What is this killer move?! Terrifying, too terrifying! My feeling is not wrong, I will not survive if I get hit by this move! Escape, I must escape!!"

Jun Shen Guang's face turned completely red, his thin brows trembled madly as his previous grace completely disappeared.

Immortal killer move — Sun Deity's Radiance.

With a shout, he directly used his strongest method. His whole body turned into a lump of light, endless light erupted, it was like a small sun had appeared in the battlefield!

The scalding white light had inexhaustible might, wherever it went, Fang Yuan's time path methods crumbled apart.

The Southern Border immortals had just freed themselves when they were engulfed by the endless glaring sunlight.

The imitation regional wall that spread over every mountain dissipated completely under the illumination of the powerful sunlight. The whole five regional mountain range began to shake, especially the center of the battlefield where large amounts of mountain rocks began to crumble and fall.

The aftereffects of sun deity's radiance even affected other battlefields.

Southern Border's groups with rank eights, who were fighting with immemorial year beasts, were heavily disturbed by this.

"This is a rank eight Gu Immortal of Central Continent?"

"Hmph, this is probably a person of Heavenly Court!"

The light dissipated, the scene at the central battlefield became extremely clear. Suddenly, a Gu Immortal cried out in shock.

"Wait, that immortal aperture… that is my clansman's immortal aperture!"

"What? It is not Fang Yuan's immortal aperture?!" Everyone was terrified.

"This is a trap!" Jun Shen Guang shouted as he forcibly concentrated and retreated madly.

"Escaping?" Fang Yuan suddenly appeared above Jun Shen Guang.

Jun Shen Guang's heart shook fiercely as he stared at Fang Yuan rigidly with narrowed eyes. In that instant, he suddenly realized that rather than saying Fang Yuan was ambushing Southern Border Gu Immortals, it was more accurate to say he was specially ambushing Heavenly Court's members like himself!

"So your true target was me!"

"Hmph, you have already exposed that move, I am now already on guard. Your trap has also collapsed, can you still restrain me?"

"A mere rank seven… I am a rank eight Gu Immortal! I also have Wei Feng rushing here now."

"Unless this group of Southern Border Gu Immortals teamed up with you, do you think you can kill me?"

Jun Shen Guang breathed heavily, countless rays of light flowed around him like liquid, protecting him heavily.

Sure enough, the Southern Border immortals attacked at the next moment.

Their target was Fang Yuan!

Wu Yong took the lead, while Chi Qu You and Shang Wu Jie followed closely behind. They attacked Fang Yuan, disregarding the attacks of the immemorial year beasts. Following them, large numbers of Southern Border Gu Immortal experts used their main techniques.

Jun Shen Guang laughed heartily: "Fang Yuan, you demon, you have brought your own doom by committing so many sins! You still want to kill me? Your death is certain today!"

"Is that so?" In the brink of danger, Fang Yuan was still calm, the corners of his lips even rose slightly to reveal a mocking smile.

Boom!

At the next moment, his rank seven aura suddenly changed. An incomparable aura soared to the skies and shot in all directions.

Everyone at the scene was greatly shocked.

"What?!"

"Rank eight aura!"

"Impossible!!"

Fang Yuan's body paused slightly before he lightly pointed his finger.

Immortal killer move — Spring Scissors!

Next, he folded his hands, his sleeves fluttered and formed a fan.

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

"This is?!" Chi Qu You and Shang Wu Jie were dumbstruck at this scene.

"This is Lady Xia Cha's…" Several of Xia clan's rank seven Gu Immortals cried out, an extremely bad feeling shrouded everyone's hearts.

Rumble!

Spring scissors attacked Jun Shen Guang, immediately suppressing him, while summer fan which was in Fang Yuan's hand waved rapidly, blocking all killer moves of the Southern Border immortals.

At this moment, Fang Yuan's demonic aura surged as he fought the whole group alone, it was a grand spectacle!

Chapter 1625: Luo Po Seal

Shock!

All the Gu Immortals present at the scene felt shocked at seeing Fang Yuan fight against everyone.

They had come to obstruct and disturb Fang Yuan from passing his tribulation, to prevent him from becoming rank eight.

But none of them had thought that when they saw him, he was already rank eight.

This unexpected result caught all of them off guard.

"When did he advance to rank eight?!" Chi Qu You's eyes were wide open in disbelief.

"It is not strange for him to be able to use spring scissors and summer fan, the important thing is that these killer moves have been amplified by time path dao marks and are able to obstruct all the attacks. Even if Fang Yuan advanced to rank eight, how could he have gained so many time path dao marks in such a short period of time? I think he has likely possessed Xia Cha's body and used familiar face to deceive us and make us think he has already passed the tribulation." Shang Wu Jie forced himself to calm down and analyzed.

"No! First supreme elder's Spring and Summer are both rank eight Immortal Gu and can only be activated by rank eight immortal essence." Xia clan's second supreme elder Xia Zhao shouted.

"Then…" Shang Wu Jie immediately hesitated.

Immortal essence contained the Gu Immortal's will and had to belong to themselves, if they died, their heavenly spirit or land spirit could use their immortal essence.

The only exception was Immortal Gu Houses as immortal essence from any source could be used in them. But the killer moves Fang Yuan used were clearly not Immortal Gu Houses.

If Fang Yuan was only rank seven with red date immortal essence, he would not be able to activate rank eight Immortal Gu Spring and Summer, even if he possessed Xia Cha's body and obtained her immortal essence.

"No use in thinking much, we will know after killing Fang Yuan." Wu Yong called out.

He flew forward, the immemorial year beast behind him collapsed to the ground, unable to get up.

At this crucial moment, Wu Yong displayed powerful battle strength, he first killed Fang Yuan's immemorial year beast and then used all his strength to attack Fang Yuan.

"Fang Yuan!" Wu Yong's gaze was cold as his battle intent surged wildly, "Even if you have truly advanced to rank eight, you won't escape your doom today. This five regional mountain range, which you carefully chose, will be your graveyard!"

Just as he finished speaking, the whole mountain range began to tremor violently.

The ground quaked, the mountains shook, and debris flew everywhere.

"What's happening?" The immortals were stunned.

Wu Yong's voice traveled to everyone's ears: "Don't panic, this is a backup plan I arranged, it can change the alignment of the earth vein under the five regional mountain range and destroy the mountain range!"

The immortals were even more puzzled.

So what if the earth vein's alignment changed?

But soon, they had a pleasant surprise, as the mountain range gradually crumbled, the five colored lights unique to the five regional mountain range were also rapidly dissipating.

"This?!" Even Jun Shen Guang was astonished.

"Amazing. Without these shackles, our battle strength will recover and we will no longer be restrained!" Southern Border's Gu Immortals were rejoicing.

"Wu Yong is indeed different from Wu Du Xiu, he still had another card up his sleeve!" Shang Wu Jie's eyes flickered with sharp lights.

"How can Wu clan be so familiar with five regional mountain range? There cannot be this level of effect just by changing the alignment of the earth vein. They also would have to know the arrangements made by Tao Zhu back then!" Chi Qu You's thoughts were fluctuating rapidly.

The large formation, set up by Wu clan's and Qiao clan's Gu Immortals in the periphery of the five regional mountain range, was constantly rumbling, it was the source of the change in the entire five regional mountain range.

Qiao Si Liu, Wu Yu Bo and some others were in charge of this formation.

Wu Yu Bo chuckled coldly while looking towards the battlefield: "This demon Fang Yuan wants to rely on the five regional mountain range, now that we have destroyed his territorial advantage, how will he defend against our Southern Border righteous paths' attacks?"

Qiao Si Liu was silent, her expression was slightly complicated.

She had once been quite close with 'Wu Yi Hai' and had even believed she and he would get married. But the outcome was shocking beyond her imagination. Wu Yi Hai was actually Fang Yuan in disguise. She felt a chill every time she thought of how close she had been with a great demon like Fang Yuan.

She did not have any feelings left for Fang Yuan, her complicated emotions were because of the five regional mountain range.

Everyone thought Tao Zhu's research of the regional walls did not succeed. But that was not quite true.

Qiao clan had by chance obtained clues to Tao Zhu's inheritance and had been secretly exploring the clues to excavating the inheritance.

But they had not expected Wu Yong to know of this information, and under his pressure, Qiao clan had to offer their findings which were then used now.

It was because of such clues that Wu Yong had a deep understanding of the five regional mountain range and could make the lights of the five regions disappear by changing the earth vein. If it were any other who tried to change the earth vein without knowledge, unless they were extremely lucky, the lights would still exist for the most part.

"Oh! This is a rank eight Gu Immortal's inheritance, but it is all used up here, and with the destruction of the five regional mountain range, there is no hope in exploring the inheritance anymore." Qiao Si Liu sighed.

She seemed to have had many thoughts, but a very short time had passed.

Jun Shen Guang's fright light activated as he was chased by Fang Yuan, the Southern Border immortals attacked Fang Yuan but their attacks were blocked by Fang Yuan who revealed rank eight cultivation, Southern Border immortals conversed rapidly, while Wu Yong made the first move, the five regional mountain range crumbled, removing Fang Yuan's terrain advantage.

All these changes happened in an instant.

Fang Yuan endured the Southern Border immortals' attacks while still chasing after Jun Shen Guang even when Wu Yong was nearing him.

Jun Shen Guang had used his trump card, his aura had already fallen to an extreme point. His sun deity's radiance killer move was extremely powerful, but it not only expended a huge amount of white litchi immortal essence, it also permanently decreased his light path dao marks. It was a move that dealt damage to the enemy as well as to himself. Moreover, he had activated it inside the five regional mountain range and had already suffered a powerful backlash. Although he managed to escape for the moment, he was seriously injured.

But now, the lights of the five regions were rapidly weakening, Jun Shen Guang felt like a huge load was removed from his back, he felt more at ease in his movements as his greatest concern was removed.

Looking at Wu Yong rushing towards Fang Yuan, a thought appeared in Jun Shen Guang's mind: "Should I cooperate with the Southern Border Gu Immortals to kill Fang Yuan?"

This thought had just emerged when it was immediately rejected by Jun Shen Guang.

"Continue to escape!"

The current situation was extremely complex, he was not a Southern Border Gu Immortal. More importantly, Fang Yuan was chasing him, if he managed to escape, it would mean Fang Yuan's failure.

Jun Shen Guang prioritizing his escape was a very wise move.

Fang Yuan was still chasing him closely, disregarding Wu Yong.

At this time, there was another change.

A powerful aura suddenly emerged. Enormous pillars in five colors soared to the skies, a loud voice reverberated throughout the five regional mountain range: "Junior, you did well, you actually passed my final test of destroying the five regional mountain range. Now, my five regions inheritance is yours! Cultivate properly and you can move unrestrained and unhindered over the world in the future, don't let down my name."

In the middle of the five colored light pillars, a smoke-like will condensed into the vivid appearance of a Gu Immortal.

Many gazes were inevitably attracted towards this. Someone recognized this appearance: "This looks like old man Tao Zhu."

"This can't be, right?" At the periphery of the mountain range, Qiao Si Liu heard the voice from within the pillars and felt strange: "Tao Zhu's final test was to destroy the five regional mountain range? This accidental action actually activated Tao Zhu's inheritance!"

Tao Zhu's will heard someone calling him old man and immediately felt unhappy, speaking arrogantly: "What old man, since you are inheriting my inheritance, how could you be so disrespectful?"

Rumble!

Wind blew rapidly, heaven and earth roared.

Replying to him was Wu Yong's rank eight killer move, but it was targeted towards Fang Yuan and not him.

Fang Yuan's immortal robe shook and ripples appeared on it, it was the immortal killer move reverse flow protection seal!

This move reflected the attack, Wu Yong continued to close in while enduring the reflected attack.

Fang Yuan's speed was immediately restrained.

The move Wu Yong used had an extremely wide range, so reverse flow protection seal only reflected back a portion that had struck Fang Yuan. Fang Yuan continued to fly while reflecting the attacks back, although he was completely safe, his speed was greatly reduced.

Fang Yuan had already used reverse flow protection seal many times, how could Wu Yong not have prepared specific restricting methods?

"What!" Tao Zhu's will was stunned, he quickly looked around and saw several rank eight Gu Immortals fighting, there were also many rank seven experts present on the scene. He almost broke down from the shock!

"What, what's going on?" This was completely different from his original expectation, there was no respectful junior in front of him, there were only vicious and fierce Gu Immortals!

"Ignore him, he is just a dead man."

"The inheritance is here, we can take it after the battle!"

"The urgent thing now is to kill Fang Yuan! Not to mention Tao Zhu's inheritance, I would even give up a Gu Venerable's true inheritance to kill Fang Yuan!!"

The immortals shouted in fury, their attention once again focusing on Fang Yuan's body.

Tao Zhu's will: "…."

He was stupefied, this was completely out of his expectations.

Shortly afterwards, he shook as he reacted: "Who in the world is that person being chased by so many Gu Immortals? To kill him, they can even give up a Gu Venerable's true inheritance?"

Tao Zhu's will looked towards Fang Yuan but did not recognize him.

"Who is this person? Someone who became a Gu Immortal after my main body's death?"

Right at this time, Fang Yuan had finally caught up to Jun Shen Guang.

Jun Shen Guang's whole body was soaked in sweat from the nervousness, intense warning signals caused his heart to beat like a drum!

He escaped with all his strength while cursing internally: "Wu Yong, you bastard! What killer move did you use, even trapping me?"

Wu Yong's killer move had an extremely wide range, even Jun Shen Guang received its 'care'. Wu Yong's exquisite method was not so easily broken, Jun Shen Guang's strength fell sharply, his speed fell even more than Fang Yuan's.

"It's over." Fang Yuan mumbled lightly as he attacked with no change in his expression, calm like an ancient well.

The illusory figure of Luo Po Valley in his palm was slowly rotating. Suddenly, Fang Yuan's fingers clenched it tightly.

A gray light shot out from the gap between the fingers.

Fang Yuan then opened his palm and slapped towards the distant Jun Shen Guang.

The light shot out with extreme speed, Jun Shen Guang dodged it frantically like a headless housefly.

Wu Yong, who was chasing from behind, had a sinister look in his eyes.

A wild wind suddenly blew around Jun Shen Guang, obstructing him heavily.

"Wu Yong, I curse your grandmother!" Jun Shen Guang did not even have time to complete his curse when Fang Yuan's gray light struck him.

In an instant, his flight came to an abrupt stop. His physical body had no injuries, but his soul was heavily injured to the point it was almost extinguished!

Immortal killer move — Luo Po Seal!

While Jun Shen Guang was in a daze, an Immortal Gu House suddenly appeared beside Fang Yuan. Inside the Immortal Gu House, Ying Wu Xie attacked Jun Shen Guang with a killer move he had prepared for a while.

Immortal killer move — Lead Soul Into Dream!

Jun Shen Guang could not react, instantly falling into a dream realm, unable to extricate himself.

The Immortal Gu House was shadowy and faint, it immediately absorbed Jun Shen Guang and flew to Fang Yuan's side.

Wu Yong paled from fright!

He had disturbed Jun Shen Guang because he wanted to test the power of Fang Yuan's move. After all, Jun Shen Guang was not a Southern Border Gu Immortal, why not make use of him once?

But Wu Yong had never expected Fang Yuan to capture Jun Shen Guang in one move!

Previously, Fang Yuan had captured the Southern Border immortals by trapping them in a meticulously laid out time path formation. But now, he captured Jun Shen Guang with just a few methods!

Such an increase in battle strength was simply horrifying.

"What killer move is that, it feels like it only targets the Gu Immortal's soul? It has such terrifying might, I must defend against it!"

"There is also the Immortal Gu House! What is that Immortal Gu House, it almost cannot be detected when it is concealed!"

Southern Border's rank eights rushed over with surging momentum.

But when they witnessed Fang Yuan capturing Jun Shen Guang, they were shocked and bewildered as their battle intent fell sharply.

Chapter 1626: Wu Yong's Loss

Fang Yuan's actions shocked Tao Zhu immensely!

Where did this soul path Gu Immortal come from? He severely injured a rank eight Gu Immortal with just one attack! Such imposing demonic might, even Spectral Soul was merely at this level when he was young.

"I didn't expect this young man, who looks so delicate, to be so vicious and have such peerless methods. He must have committed many sins, or else why would Southern Border's righteous path attack him on such a scale?"

Noticing this, Tao Zhu's will became frightened.

For the first time, he felt that the pillars of light around him were so glaring.

"My main body had made this arrangement for the convenience of the inheritor. Oh, who could have expected this situation to happen at the moment the inheritance activated."

"What did I do to deserve this? Was it easy for my main body to make such a painstaking arrangement?"

Tao Zhu's will immediately felt lonely and helpless. In this situation, let alone him, a mere will, even his main body would have to stay away from this conflict.

The implications were too deep and troublesome, he could not rashly get involved!

Tao Zhu's will was frightened, dejectedly curling inside the pillars while mumbling: "Don't look at me, don't look at me…"

Why would the Gu Immortals have the time or mood to look at him?

Fang Yuan had captured the rank eight Gu Immortal Jun Shen Guang in front of everyone, such terrifying battle strength made the rank seven Gu Immortals have parched mouths, and even the rank eights were dazed.

"How can we defeat such a powerful enemy?"

"If I stake my life and something unexpected happens, what will happen to the clan? Other rank eights will keep their lives while I will be wasting mine for them."

When Fang Yuan was rank seven and could fight rank eight with reverse flow protection seal, Southern Border's rank eight Gu Immortals could accept this level of battle strength.

But it was completely different now!

Fang Yuan was not only a rank eight Gu Immortal, he also possessed a mysterious and powerful method that seemed to be a soul path method. And it made a great combination with lead soul into dream.

Jun Shen Guang's example was right in front of them, the Southern Border rank eight Gu Immortals could also very well fall to Fang Yuan's vicious methods!

At the crucial moment, the deep-seated problem for Southern Border's righteous path emerged again. They were forces who had prioritized themselves for too long, a heavy wariness against each other was already ingrained deep in their bones, even if they realized the necessity of an alliance, faced with a choice at this time, these rank eight Gu Immortals all felt hesitation.

These Southern Border rank eight Gu Immortals hesitated, but Fang Yuan had no hesitation.

He laughed loudly as he turned around and charged towards Wu Yong.

"Wu Yong! What did you say earlier? This is my graveyard? Hahaha! I think it is the opposite, this is your graveyard. Come, come, let's settle the score once and for all!"

Fang Yuan gave a loud shout, his voice resounding throughout the five regional mountain range like thunder.

His white robe and hair fluttered in the wind, his demonic aura and surging killing intent shocked the immortals.

Chi Qu You, Shang Wu Jie and other rank eight Gu Immortals looked at Fang Yuan targeting Wu Yong, feeling complicated. They were tense but also could not help feeling a slight relief as all kinds of thoughts lingered in their minds.

Fang Yuan might be powerful but he was only one man in the end. Moreover, Chi Qu You had transacted with Fang Yuan before.

In the current Southern Alliance, the alliance leader's position was empty and Wu Yong was undoubtedly the number one choice for it. If he became the alliance leader, who knew how he would treat the other clans.

Southern Border had always been divided, the biggest problem in working together were the mental hurdles and self-interest of the respective Gu Immortals.

When two tigers fought, one was definitely going to be injured.

Whether the injured one was Fang Yuan or Wu Yong, it was beneficial to other clans.

Moreover, it could not be said we had not come to aid, aren't we being hindered by immemorial year beasts?

"Useless bunch!" Wu Yong inwardly cursed when he saw no one coming to his aid.

But he did not fear Fang Yuan, instead his courage and battle intent were stirred!

"Let me see what method you used to capture a rank eight Gu Immortal!" Wu Yong took out Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and controlled this Immortal Gu House to charge straight at Fang Yuan.

Although Fang Yuan had a mysterious Immortal Gu House, it absolutely would not be able to survive a collision with Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building, his eyes flashed with a sinister light as he suddenly changed his direction and flew down.

Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building's momentum was too fierce and fast as it missed its target.

"Wu Yong, you are safe with the Immortal Gu House to protect you. In that case, how about I kill these rank seven immortals, can you save them? Hahaha!" Fang Yuan laughed madly.

"Damn it!" Wu Yong quickly changed the direction of Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building and chased after Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan continued: "Wu Yong, you have such a huge ambition, you established the Southern Border alliance to become its leader, right? Let's see if you will still have the face left to become the alliance leader after I kill these people!"

Fang Yuan had not actually made any real attacks at Wu Yong, but his words were like blades that stabbed deeply in Wu Yong's heart.

Wu Yong had led the Southern Border immortals to besiege and kill Fang Yuan, on one hand, it was because he had deep hatred towards Fang Yuan, on the other hand, it was to accumulate reputation to pave the road to the position of alliance leader.

But if he let Fang Yuan kill these rank seven Gu Immortals while he remained safe inside Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building without being able to do anything to Fang Yuan, his reputation was sure to take a huge hit and he would be even further from the position of alliance leader.

Wu Yong was anxious and furious, almost pacing around in Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building. Although Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building was extremely fast and was rapidly catching up to Fang Yuan, Fang Yuan had already reached those rank seven Gu Immortals.

"Persevere!"

"Am I going to die?"

"Not necessarily! There are many Gu Immortals here, we still have hope of survival!"

Fang Yuan had yet to attack but these rank seven Gu Immortals' morale had already dissipated, they did not have any thought of counterattacking and were only thinking of how to preserve their lives.

The scene of Fang Yuan capturing a Central Continent rank eight Gu Immortal was truly horrifying.

"Go die! Hmm?" Fang Yuan's shout suddenly stopped.

At the moment of danger, a dense yellowish-brown radiance suddenly appeared under the Southern Border immortals and firmly protected them.

This was a rank eight defensive killer move!

"Fang Yuan, why commit more murders? You kill me, I kill you, this cycle is too pitiful and miserable. You are an outstanding person of this era, why can't you see through this?"

Lu Wei Yin's figure appeared not far away.

"Hmph! You again!" Fang Yuan gazed fiercely at Lu Wei Yin.

Boom!

At the next moment, Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building flew over like a meteor and carried with it Wu Yong's intense hatred and anger, heavily collided with Fang Yuan's back.

Immortal killer move — Reverse Flow Protection Seal!

Fang Yuan was completely safe, the attack was reflected back to Clear Jade Dripping Wind Tiny Bamboo Building.

But the enormous collision force sent Fang Yuan flying like a cannonball.

Wu Yong was suddenly at ease, he had sent Fang Yuan away from these rank seven Gu Immortals and it would be even more difficult for him to attack these people.

But soon, Lu Wei Yin's voice reached him: "Not good! This is Fang Yuan's plan, he is escaping!"

Wu Yong's expression immediately turned ashen as he helplessly looked at Fang Yuan smoothly charging into that immortal aperture.

The moment he entered, the immortal aperture's entrance loudly closed.

"Fang Yuan is too crafty, since he put an ambush here, how could he not have arranged an escape route? He entered the immortal aperture because he must have a way to escape, like Fixed Immortal Travel!"

Veins popped up on Wu Yong's forehead, he felt extremely stifled.

Immortal apertures had always been easy to defend and hard to attack, especially an immortal aperture that had its entrance closed. Naturally, Southern Border's righteous path group could break into this blessed land. But Fang Yuan already had enough time to escape!

Wu Yong had gathered such a large team but still failed, not only was he unable to harm a single hair of Fang Yuan, a Central Continent rank eight Gu Immortal was captured right in front of everyone!

This was simply a kick to Wu Yong's face.

"What is more insufferable is this guy…" Wu Yong's dark gaze stared at Lu Wei Yin.

He suddenly spoke: "Lu Wei Yin, why didn't you stop him?"

Lu Wei Yin quickly greeted as he said slowly: "I am ashamed! I already used all my strength to protect these Southern Border friends, I truly did not have strength left to obstruct him."

Lu Wei Yin was instantly swarmed with countless expressions of gratitude from the Southern Border Gu Immortals.

Wu Yong breathed heavily in anger, his fists were tightly clenched but he could do nothing to Lu Wei Yin.

Lu Wei Yin had a terrifying background of being Paradise Earth's inheritor and was the competitor who possessed the greatest threat to Wu Yong's dream of taking the alliance leader position.

Wu Yong had led the immortals to besiege Fang Yuan but had left Lu Wei Yin behind so he could more easily accumulate prestige.

But the result was: Fang Yuan escaped while Wu Yong gained nothing, his reputation suffered while Lu Wei Yin was the complete opposite!

Wu Yong's gaze shined sharply as if lightning sparks were flashing inside.

After a while, he sighed and let his body relax, the anger on his face completely disappeared while his battle intent soared inwardly. A faint smile appeared on his lips as he clapped, thinking: "Fang Yuan, Lu Wei Yin, you two are truly something! I lost this round entirely because of you two…"

Chapter 1627: Zi Wei's Lingering Fear

"How could this be? How could this be…" When information of the Southern Border battle reached her, Fairy Zi Wei kept on mumbling in perplexity.

The vast and bright hall was now filled with doubts.

Fang Yuan had not only passed the tribulation, becoming rank eight, he had even laid a trap in the five regional mountain range and captured Heavenly Court Gu Immortal Jun Shen Guang!

Fairy Zi Wei already knew of the Southern Border Gu Immortals being captured by Fang Yuan, but she had never imagined the same fate would befall her Heavenly Court so quickly.

A Heavenly Court Gu Immortal was actually captured alive!

How long has it been since this happened?

The instant she learned of this news, Fairy Zi Wei had subconsciously thought of the impressive battle achievements of multiple Demon Venerables.

Her brows showed her worry and there was even nervousness.

Despite her estimating Fang Yuan highly, his growth had still greatly surpassed her expectations.

"Ever since Fang Yuan gained reverse flow protection seal, he has been huge trouble. Now that he has become rank eight, along with Xia Cha's methods, regardless of using the terrain advantage in the five regional mountain range to weaken his enemies, he indeed possesses a threat to Heavenly Court Gu Immortals!"

Fairy Zi Wei heaved a deep sigh.

She had already expected such a day. So she had tried all ways to eliminate this danger beforehand, but who could have expected Fang Yuan's progress to be so fast!

"Fang Yuan's progress is getting faster and faster, it seems like the quantitative change is becoming a qualitative change. But how in the world did he become a rank eight without any commotion?"

Fairy Zi Wei did not understand.

She had always thought Fang Yuan's extremely fast cultivation progress was because he had used time path methods to quicken his immortal aperture's rate of time.

But looking back over it, Fairy Zi Wei suddenly realized Fang Yuan also had a peerless method that could raise his cultivation level!

"Then… what is this method?"

Fairy Zi Wei did not continue deducing, instead she left the hall and arrived at Spectral Soul's confinement area.

The large formation rumbled into motion, after a long while, Fairy Zi Wei returned to her hall with a shaken expression.

"Sovereign immortal fetus Gu! Sovereign immortal aperture… so it was like this!" Fairy Zi Wei muttered to herself, she was dazed and her soul was shaken.

Spectral Soul's ambition shocked her.

What made her even more fearful was that sovereign immortal fetus Gu had been refined and obtained by Fang Yuan!

An intense bitterness emerged in her heart.

Spectral Soul had really hidden it too deeply!

If not for Fang Yuan revealing clues this time which made Fairy Zi Wei doubtful and use a specialized soul search, she would still have been in the dark.

"No wonder Fang Yuan's cultivation speed is so fast! This time, he should have annexed many Southern Border Gu Immortals' immortal apertures to skip tribulations and become a rank eight."

"He could activate Xia Cha's killer moves and confront other rank eights head on, this means he has annexed Xia Cha's immortal aperture. Only then would he have enough time path dao marks to amplify Xia Cha's killer moves."

"Immortal apertures can only swallow smaller immortal apertures, but the sovereign immortal aperture is special. But devouring Xia Cha's rank eight grotto-heaven would require time path great grandmaster attainment, how could Fang Yuan have it?"

"Wait!"

Suddenly, Fairy Zi Wei's expression became extremely unsightly.

All kinds of clues merged in her mind and removed her previous bewilderment.

"Fang Yuan has dream path methods and can raise his attainment level through dream realms!"

"No wonder he entered Southern Border and plundered dream realms. His time path great grandmaster attainment was definitely gained from dream realms."

"Gasp…"

Thinking of this, even Fairy Zi Wei, who held a high status and was very experienced, could not help taking in a cold breath.

Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal aperture and could devour apertures to skip calamities and tribulations.

And the biggest obstacle in devouring apertures was the attainment level of the respective paths.

It was extremely difficult to raise attainment level and often required hundreds of years. But Fang Yuan could quickly raise his attainment level through dream realms.

Like this, he could create a beneficial cycle, his cultivation speed could rise to a level where it could raise a terrifying wave even in the entire history of human cultivation.

"No, more accurately, what is terrifying is Spectral Soul. Fang Yuan was only a chess piece of heaven's will to destroy Spectral Soul's heaven defying plan, it was just that he escaped heaven's will's control in the end."

Fairy Zi Wei felt a chill.

Heavenly Court had already confined Spectral Soul and Fairy Zi Wei would also frequently torture and soul search to extract important information from Spectral Soul.

But despite this, Fairy Zi Wei was feeling deep lingering fear.

If Spectral Soul had truly succeeded, he would have great grandmaster attainment level in all paths. With his extreme killing nature, he could continue devouring apertures and along with Shadow Sect and Zombie Alliance's resources, he could totally go straight to rank eight!

At this level, Spectral Soul would have pseudo-venerable battle strength.

More importantly, when the five regions chaotic war starts and dream realms appear everywhere, Spectral Soul might even be able to progress further. His huge ambition could be felt just by looking at lead soul into dream! He had already made countless preparations in this aspect. If he truly reached this step, his dominance would be too large. Even the Great Dream seed Feng Jin Huang might have no chance to mature.

"Fortunately, he was not able to make the breakthrough during the most important juncture. Currently, Fang Yuan is taking his place in this plan, so it is more accurate to say that he did not succeed but he did not completely fail either."

Fairy Zi Wei frowned deeply when she thought of Fang Yuan.

"Fang Yuan gave up on those Southern Border Gu Immortals and instead prioritized capturing Jun Shen Guang. His action is similar to me soul searching Spectral Soul, he wants to get the location of Heavenly Court from Jun Shen Guang's soul."

"Oh no… the River of Time!"

The tumultuous river was always flowing.

It was so vast that its ends could not be seen.

From inside an Immortal Gu House, Fang Yuan quietly looked at the ebb and flow of the river and its countless dazzling ripples.

The River of Time!

After entering the immortal aperture and gaining some free time, Fang Yuan used an immortal killer move made with Fixed Immortal Travel to escape the battleground.

Not long later, he entered the River of Time.

Right now, Jun Shen Guang's soul was facing constant soul searching inside his sovereign immortal aperture.

Know yourself and your enemy, and you will never be defeated.

Fang Yuan urgently needed to know what arrangements Heavenly Court had made in the River of Time!

"I laid an ambush in the five regional mountain range and fought a large battle, although I captured Jun Shen Guang, I revealed too much information."

Fang Yuan wanted to catch Heavenly Court off guard and not give them enough time to respond, so he directly entered the River of Time in this short time period.

"This Lu Wei Yin is not simple. His action was too timely, saving those Southern Border rank sevens at the most critical time. He was probably hiding nearby all along."

"Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable had a merciful and compassionate nature, he restored peace to the chaotic world and repaired the damage done by Spectral Soul in all five regions. In the five regions, and especially Southern Border, among the ten venerables, his reputation is the highest."

"As his current inheritor, Lu Wei Yin has inherited this reputation as well. This person is going against me, but his true goal does not look to be so simple and is hidden in a layer of fog."

"Unfortunately, there is no such person in the memories of my previous life!"

The more he thought, the more Fang Yuan felt his five hundred years of memories were not reliable.

Naturally, there was also the possibility that the butterfly effect of his rebirth had spread until it involved Lu Wei Yin.

Fang Yuan slightly shook his head, forgetting about Lu Wei Yin for the moment, and thought of Tao Zhu's inheritance.

He felt a huge regret.

Tao Zhu's true inheritance was definitely related to the five regions' regional walls.

The five regions' regional walls would disappear without a trace in the future and the five regions would merge into one, Tao Zhu's research in crossing the regional walls would look like a joke.

But think about it carefully.

Tao Zhu could construct the five regional mountain range, couldn't this method of imitating the regional walls be used to defend oneself?

Especially for Fang Yuan, fighting in regional walls was extremely advantageous.

"It is a pity, a true pity. The situation did not allow me to take this inheritance, I had missed this true inheritance of Tao Zhu by a hairsbreadth."

Fang Yuan's wisdom path attainment was not low, he had a strong premonition that missing this chance to obtain Tao Zhu's inheritance was a severe loss to him.

Chapter 1628: Present and Past Pavilion, Four Xunzi

"Tao Zhu's true inheritance…"

If this was months ago, Fang Yuan might be able to use the Southern Border Gu Immortals to exchange for this inheritance.

But now, the Southern Border captives that he had were already annexed, he had already killed the hostages.

These Southern Border Gu Immortals were all rank seven Gu Immortal experts, while Xia Cha had rank eight cultivation level. The sovereign immortal aperture annexed them as well as the immortal aperture blessed lands in City Well, Fang Yuan's cultivation level rose rapidly, he went from rank seven to rank eight, skipping the final rank seven grand tribulation.

Fang Yuan originally planned to continue capturing Southern Border Gu Immortals in the five regional mountain range before extorting them. But because of Lu Wei Yin, Fang Yuan's plan was disrupted.

Not only did his cultivation level rise, because the sovereign immortal aperture could annex his enemies perfectly, Fang Yuan's dao marks also rose in huge numbers!

Using perceivable dao Immortal Gu to check them, Fang Yuan's current dao mark accumulation was extremely deep.

He originally had very little time path dao marks, almost at the bottom, but it had emerged to become his number one path, having seventy-three thousand dao marks. Almost all of it was Xia Cha's contribution, he had truly 'become wealthy from one single robbery'.

With so many time path dao marks, Fang Yuan's time path killer moves could be amplified by seventy-four times. Along with the rank eight Gu Spring and Summer, his battle strength was extremely high now. Within the five regional mountain range, he managed to block the attacks of many Gu Immortals at once.

Of course, he had made use of the territorial advantage of the five regional walls' trait, the Southern Border Gu Immortals could not work together well and conflicted with each other.

The second was water path dao marks, reaching sixty thousand.

He had a lot of water path accumulations, Fang Yuan had killed lone immortals Zhou Li, Wu Yi Hai, You Chan, and others, while many of the Eastern Sea lone immortals in City Well were also water path cultivators.

Third was transformation path, having fifty thousand. It was originally first place, but had fallen to third place now.

Fourth was soul path at thirty thousand. The immortal aperture's own dao marks, as well as the yellow spring ghost martial statue earthly calamity and green lightning divine martial statue heavenly tribulation, along with other accumulations, added up to twenty-nine thousand. The remaining hundreds were obtained from Fang Yuan's soul cultivation. According to Spectral Soul's true inheritance, after million man soul, ten million man soul, hundred million man soul, and desolate soul… after reaching desolate soul, there would be a thousand dao marks on the soul.

Next were ice and snow path, rule path, metal path, wood path, fire path, wind path, and other common paths, they had about twenty thousand.

After that were dark path, light path, strength path, qi path, luck path, sound path, blood light, and others, being around ten thousand.

And finally, food path, phantom path, and others were in the thousands and hundreds category.

Next, the dream realms.

Fang Yuan had already explored all of his dream realms in these few months, all of his different paths had grown to certain extents.

The highest was still refinement path at quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment level!

Second were theft path and time path at great grandmaster level.

Third were blood path, strength path, star path, wisdom path, and others, they were all at grandmaster level. Rule path and soul path also entered this category.

The paths below that will not be explained in detail.

Unlike dao marks, attainment level was harder to raise as it got higher. The ones with the most evident growth were time path, soul path, and rule path.

Other than dao marks and dream realms, Fang Yuan's development of the sovereign immortal aperture had also risen greatly due to his annexing of immortal apertures, it had reached fifteen percent development.

And worth noting was that in Xia Cha's immortal aperture, Fang Yuan found a year essence pool!

This way, Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had two year essence pools.

Other than these, Fang Yuan's greatest gains were two things.

One was Luo Po seal.

Fang Yuan had always been trying to create this immortal killer move, he only succeeded recently.

The other was an incomplete Immortal Gu House.

Fang Yuan had wanted to build his own Immortal Gu House long ago, so that Hei Lou Lan, Bai Ning Bing, and the rest could fight in battle with him.

To create this Immortal Gu House, Fang Yuan took reference from Secluded Residence, Cloud City, Dark Flow Giant City, Profound Ice House, Unbreakable Iron Fortress, Blood River Chariot, Nightmare Castle,Green Wave Pavilion, Weaving Cocoon Manor, Golden Altar, Regret Pool, Sacred Feather City, Bai He Palace, and other Immortal Gu Houses, while the skeleton of the design was based on Graceful Chaotic Duel Stage.

Several months ago, while extorting Southern Border's righteous path to exchange Gu for Gu, Fang Yuan obtained many crucial Immortal Gu that allowed him to create the skeleton.

This Immortal Gu House was created by Fang Yuan himself, it was unprecedented. Because he needed to enter the River of Time, it mainly used time path Immortal Gu, it had a comprehensive range of abilities and most excelled in concealment.

Even though it was only a skeleton now, it had great battle strength in the five regional mountain range. Ying Wu Xie and the rest relied on this to cooperate with Fang Yuan, successfully capturing Jun Shen Guang.

In the River of Time, waves rose and fell, water splattered everywhere, creating beautiful rainbow light.

Fang Yuan rode in the incomplete Immortal Gu House as he traveled slowly in the river.

The rank six time path clone had already emerged from the sovereign immortal aperture, standing beside him as he shut his eyes, sensing internally.

Red Lotus Demon Venerable had left behind many true inheritances scattered in the River of Time, Spring Autumn Cicada was the key to finding them.

But the River of Time was extremely huge, in order to find the several stone lotus islands, other than luck, he also needed lots of time and energy to explore.

"It would be best if we could find a Red Lotus true inheritance in this exploration of the River of Time."

"But most importantly, we need to test Heavenly Court's arrangements and catch them off guard, if possible, we need to destroy their arrangements!"

Fang Yuan thought as he searched Jun Shen Guang's soul in the sovereign immortal aperture.

Jun Shen Guang's soul originally had light path dao marks to protect it, but after Fang Yuan's Luo Po seal struck, the defense was destroyed, at the same time, Jun Shen Guang's soul was injured, he was on the verge of death.

Precisely so, after Ying Wu Xie used lead soul into dream, Jun Shen Guang was directly hit and fell asleep.

The condition to use lead soul into dream killer move was to sense the soul and compare the strength between the enemy's soul and the user to determine the success.

Being able to deal such damage to a rank eight Gu Immortal, it showed how powerful Luo Po seal was!

However, compared to reverse flow protection seal, and seeing how Fang Yuan used Luo Po Valley as the core of this move, it was not very surprising that it had such power.

Right now, Jun Shen Guang's soul was extremely weak, he could not defend against Fang Yuan's method, information was obtained by Fang Yuan continuously.

"What arrangements did Heavenly Court make? Jun Shen Guang must know about them."

A moment later, Fang Yuan's brows eased as he found something: "Oh? Time path Immortal Gu House Present and Past Pavilion…"

He had just thought of this when the water in front of him rose up, a huge pavilion was riding the waves and approaching.

This pavilion was not covered on all four sides, it was very simplistic. The cover was made of yellow grass, the pillars were grey white rocks that were not polished. There was a folding screen[1] in the pavilion, it was the most elegant decoration in there. Four Gu Immortals stood in the pavilion, they all had rank seven cultivation level, looking at Fang Yuan's incomplete Immortal Gu House, their eyes flashed with a dangerous light.

"This Present and Past Pavilion is a pure time path Immortal Gu House, it can inspect the past and present, it is best at investigation. Heavenly Court placed it here, the moment I entered, they noticed. Amazing, amazing!" Fang Yuan's heart sank a little, but he praised on the surface, explaining to Ying Wu Xie and the rest.

Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing, and the rest frowned lightly or had dark gazes.

They understood something, Fang Yuan's incomplete Immortal Gu House was best at concealing traces, to think that Present and Past Pavilion would be able to find them. This was like their advantage getting countered, even before fighting, they had gotten into a passive situation.

Present and Past Pavilion got to Fang Yuan and the rest before stopping, staying a thousand steps away from the incomplete Immortal Gu House.

Someone spoke coldly from within the pavilion: "Central Continent's Four Xunzi are here to guard the river, demon, don't think of advancing."

A person behind him said: "That's right, you'll have to step over our corpses if you want to pass!"

"Four Xunzi…" Fang Yuan directly soul searched Jun Shen Guang and quickly got the information of these four people.

It turned out that these four were time path Gu Immortals, they were quadruplets, found by Spirit Butterfly Valley when they were young and specially nurtured. They comprised three older brothers and one younger sister, they were Shang Xunzi, Zhong Xunzi, Xia Xunzi, and Xun Guo Zi respectively.

[1] Just google chinese folding screen and you'll see. Back

Chapter 1629: Great Power of Time Path

According to Jun Shen Guang's information, the Four Xunzi had the same rank seven cultivation level, they had a combination technique with extraordinary power, even against rank eight Gu Immortals, they could contest against them.

Of course, they were only able to fight with that one move. After a few rounds, they would definitely lose to the rank eight Gu Immortal.

They were not like the past Fang Yuan or Feng Jiu Ge with battle strength that could rival rank eights.

Even so, they were quite impressive. After nurturing the Four Xunzi, they had been kept hidden by Spirit Butterfly Valley, they were not easily deployed.

"Heavenly Court wants to make arrangements in the River of Time, Spirit Butterfly Valley had to comply. Four Xunzi… four time path experts with great cooperation, they are indeed the best candidates to control Present and Past Pavilion."

Fang Yuan frowned slightly.

The Four Xunzi and Present and Past Pavilion were not out of his expectations.

Rank eight Gu Immortals that were also time path were very rare. Heavenly Court originally had Lord Huang Shi, but he had died in the River of Time last time after Fang Yuan made use of the stone lotus island.

In order to deal with Fang Yuan and obstruct him in the River of Time, they had to choose people who were rank seven time path Gu Immortals, unless more antiques woke up from Heavenly Court's immortal graveyard.

What made Fang Yuan more concerned was that other than Present and Past Pavilion, Heavenly Court also had another time path Immortal Gu House, Eternal Yacht.

"Present and Past Pavilion excels at investigation, it is nearby so it was the first to obstruct me. I cannot stay here, once the Four Xunzi delay long enough, Eternal Yacht would arrive to help it, it will be disadvantageous for me to face two enemies at once."

Heavenly Court had a huge advantage in this, even though they did not have time path rank eights, they had members of other paths, along with two Immortal Gu Houses, Present and Past Pavilion and Eternal Yacht.

In contrast, Fang Yuan only had one incomplete Immortal Gu House, even though he became rank eight, Hei Lou Lan, Bai Ning Bing, and the rest were very weak.

Fang Yuan immediately opened his immortal aperture's entrance, letting out a second batch of immemorial year beasts.

He had used the first batch of immemorial year beasts in the five regional mountain range, they were injured or killed by Southern Border's righteous path, Fang Yuan did not manage to retrieve them.

But it did not matter, Fang Yuan had a second batch.

After annexing Xia Cha's immortal aperture, Fang Yuan obtained a second year essence pool, there were two immemorial year beasts inside. Furthermore, throughout the months, Fang Yuan had been using immemorial year beast fishing formation to lure immemorial year beasts to him, before capturing them inside the year essence pool.

Thus, Fang Yuan obtained two batches of immemorial year beasts, the second batch had a total of nine immemorial year beasts.

The only flaw was that Fang Yuan did not manage to collect all twelve types of immemorial year beasts to form the ancient battle formation.

He had tried to collect them during this period, but when he actually tried, he realized that getting a full set was very hard to achieve. He got the most number of immemorial year chickens, because recently, the River of Time was producing this type of year beasts[1].

In Fang Yuan's second batch of immemorial year beasts, he had five chickens, more than half of the entire group.

Nine immemorial year beasts roared as they charged towards Present and Past Pavilion.

Inside Present and Past Pavilion, the Four Xunzi had grim expressions, they activated Present and Past Pavilion's power together.

Pew!

A huge wave that was ten meters tall crashed towards the nine immemorial year beasts.

Immemorial year beasts were beasts that belonged in the River of Time, Present and Past Pavilion's waves could not obstruct their movement. Instantly, they charged through the obstacle, creating countless splashes as they approached Present and Past Pavilion.

The surface of Present and Past Pavilion shined with brilliant light, the light shot up like a huge pillar.

Swish swish swish…

Waves came after waves, they were like moving walls that could attack or defend, constantly crashing into the immemorial year beasts.

At Fang Yuan's will, the immemorial year beast were instructed by him to cooperate, they shot out like an arrow, going past many walls of waves and reaching Present and Past Pavilion.

But all of a sudden, the Four Xunzi shouted as the folding screen in Present and Past Pavilion turned into misty green fog.

The green fog flew into the battlefield as the immemorial year beasts got affected, their speed fell as if they had landed in a marsh.

The green fog settled and fused into the water of the River of Time, turning the surface of the water in this area jade green.

Present and Past Pavilion shook intensely, the huge pillar of light faded and turned into green sparkles that enveloped the surroundings.

The sound of crashing waves became even louder and more imposing, they were many times larger than before, thirty meters tall now. Not just that, tens of spirals formed on the surface of the River of Time, they became excellent traps to restrain the immemorial year beasts.

The nine immemorial year beasts were originally gathered together, but after the obstruction of the waves, their formation broke apart as they fell into their own respective battles.

At once, Present and Past Pavilion stood at the center and controlled the situation. Fang Yuan's immemorial year beasts were all at a disadvantage.

The Four Xunzi's expressions relaxed.

Shang Xunzi let out a breath of air: "We finally got past the initial period, this demon did not break through."

Xun Guo Zi smiled: "Present and Past Pavilion has control of the situation now, even though Fang Yuan has many immemorial year beasts, he cannot gather them, he is not a threat."

"That's right." Xia Xunzi stroke his beard: "Even though Present and Past Pavilion is not his match anyway, as long as we can stall until Eternal Yacht arrives, by then our strength will surpass him, we will be able to win."

Zhong Xunzi had a deep gaze: "The demon is crafty, we cannot be careless, let's play safe."

He had just spoken when the immemorial year monkey closest to Present and Past Pavilion suddenly jumped up and used an immortal killer move.

It held a huge fan in its hands as it waved towards the front.

Rank eight immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Instantly, intense winds whipped, sweeping away everything, the entire battlefield became dark and gloomy.

The huge waves resembling thick walls that were in front of the immemorial year monkey completely broke apart and collapsed due to summer fan.

The immemorial year monkey snickered as it dived down.

In Present and Past Pavilion, the Four Xunzi were shocked, they noticed that Fang Yuan was disguised as the immemorial year monkey.

"That demon has joined the battle!"

"Impossible! We have the investigative killer move from Lady Zi Wei, we can expose familiar face, how did he manage to deceive us?"

Fang Yuan sneered internally, he had spent the last few months to its fullest, using all of his time and energy without any waste, he had naturally modified familiar face.

Fang Yuan finally got to the Four Xunzi.

Present and Past Pavilion burst out with brilliant light once again, while Fang Yuan relied on the immemorial year monkey's tough physique to punch with its strong fists, but Present and Past Pavilion remained unmoving despite a loud sound.

"It is useless, right now, Present and Past Pavilion is anchored here in the River of Time, how can you move it?" Xun Guo Zi said with a nervous tone.

"Is that so…" Fang Yuan's eyes shined with brilliant light, he used immortal killer move spring scissors at the next moment.

Clip, clip.

Spring scissors cut continuously, Present and Past Pavilion was able to defend itself initially, but soon, the brilliant light on it was unable to last as spring scissors cut away a corner of the roof after five to six snips!

"This is a rank eight time path killer move, but how can it be so powerful?"

"Even Present and Past Pavilion cannot match it? How can this be!"

The Four Xunzi were frantic.

Fang Yuan's eyes were filled with cold flickering lightning.

He originally had over seventy thousand time path dao marks, it was at rank eight level. Now that he became an immemorial year monkey, his transformation path dao marks also turned into time path dao marks, adding another fifty thousand.

Thus, he had over a hundred and twenty thousand time path dao marks now!

Ordinary rank seven Gu Immortals would only have less than thirty thousand dao marks. A hundred and twenty thousand dao marks was not common for rank eight Gu Immortals, they normally would have to pass one myriad tribulation to get such an accumulation.

He could amplify any time path killer move by a hundred and twenty times its power!

And Fang Yuan was already using two rank eight immortal killer moves.

Even though Present and Past Pavilion had the territorial advantage, Fang Yuan's killer move was also boosted by the environment of the River of Time.

Thus, his time path battle strength soared to the extent that even Present and Past Pavilion could not endure his attacks!

Fang Yuan's two killer moves forced Present and Past Pavilion back time and time again.

The Four Xunzi tried to keep their stability in Present and Past Pavilion, while attacking sometimes, but Fang Yuan did not even need defensive killer moves like winter coat, with just the immemorial year monkey's body, he could endure them.

"Hold on!" A huge yacht was riding the waves, approaching them from afar. Several Gu Immortals were shouting and having nervous expressions.

Eternal Yacht was nearby.

"Too late." Fang Yuan snickered, he waved the summer fan and whipped up some tornadoes, Present and Past Pavilion was shaking from the impact, it was about to collapse.

Spring scissors flew towards it and snipped again!

A pillar in Present and Past Pavilion broke as it collapsed entirely.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly as he jumped above Present and Past Pavilion, stomping with his huge immemorial year monkey feet.

Boom!

The whole of Present and Past Pavilion broke apart into pieces, the Four Xunzi were either dead or injured, they were all kicked into the River of Time.

Fang Yuan and the incomplete Immortal Gu House left with ease.

When Eternal Yacht arrived, it was already too late. The Gu Immortals in the yacht hesitated, should they save the Four Xunzi or chase after Fang Yuan.

[1] Chicken banner rates up. Back

Chapter 1630: Stone Island Trap

"Cough, cough." Shang Xunzi sprawled on the deck of Eternal Yacht as he coughed, he had drunk a lot of water, he was drenched.

Beside him, Xia Xunzi had already fainted, his injuries were severe, his situation was not looking good.

Rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye walked over and looked at Shang Xunzi calmly: "The other two have been swept away by the River of Time, we cannot find them."

Shang Xunzi breathed roughly for a while, he forcibly stood up, taking a glance at Xia Xunzi before speaking with a pale expression: "They have already died, that demon Fang Yuan is very powerful! How is the salvaging of Present and Past Pavilion going?"

The Four Xunzi were siblings with deep kinship, but right now, Shang Xunzi was more concerned about Present and Past Pavilion, he did not pay attention to the dying Xia Xunzi nor did he display anger or sadness.

Qing Ye smiled: "The core Immortal Gu have not been destroyed, we have recovered all of them."

"That's good!" Shang Xunzi let out a breath of air, his expression easing.

Qing Ye nodded: "I have already prepared the room for you."

Shang Xunzi: "Thank you, I will go and revive my siblings now."

It turned out that these quadruplets, with their very close bloodline, managed to create a unique killer move. Even if three of them died, as long as one remained, they could use the killer move to rapidly revive the other three.

Precisely so, Shang Xunzi did not feel any sadness.

A moment later, the Four Xunzi returned to the deck with no injuries, entering battle once again.

Fang Yuan's second batch of immemorial year beasts were surrounding Eternal Yacht, attacking from all sides, desperately drawing their attention…

The river water was turbulent, sounds of waves crashing could be heard by Fang Yuan.

Right now, he had returned to his original appearance, he entered the incomplete Immortal Gu House to rest.

With this incomplete Immortal Gu House, Fang Yuan had a base, it was very useful.

"Eternal Yacht did not chase us…" After leaving the battlefield for a while, Fang Yuan relaxed his mind slightly.

The speed of the incomplete Immortal Gu House could not match Eternal Yacht, its specialty was in concealing its traces when moving.

With Present and Past Pavilion around, the incomplete Immortal Gu House could not move stealthily. But Eternal Yacht could not detect the incomplete Immortal Gu House, otherwise, why would it not pursue him with such an advantage in speed?

"We are temporarily safe." Ying Wu Xie breathed out deeply, feeling some lingering fear: "It was quite dangerous earlier."

"Indeed, if sect leader did not destroy Present and Past Pavilion, we might have fallen into a tough battle and would not be able to escape." Fairy Miao Yin smiled.

Bai Ning Bing was silent at the side.

Hei Lou Lan looked outside the Immortal Gu House, at the grand River of Time.

Fang Yuan's time path clone was frowning with his eyes shut. He was trying to track the islands, but his vital Gu Spring Autumn Cicada had no reactions.

In fact, according to Spectral Soul Demon Venerable's deduction, the higher Spring Autumn Cicada's rank was, the larger the range of its detection to find Red Lotus' true inheritance.

Fang Yuan's Spring Autumn Cicada was only rank six, even though he had many Immortal Gu recipes, Fang Yuan's multiple attempts at refining it ended in failure.

It was regrettable, but Fang Yuan had done his best already.

For the last few months, he had put in all his effort to cultivate soul path, explore dream realms, modify killer moves, extort Southern Border's righteous path, plot for the overall situation, defend against deductions, annex immortal apertures, and so on, he had expended his time and energy.

It was already a miracle that he could squeeze out some time to refine Spring Autumn Cicada. But the real miracle did not happen, Fang Yuan's refinement attempts failed.

"Even though Spring Autumn Cicada is rank six, I have already made up for the flaws in other aspects." Fang Yuan's eyes shined with deep confidence.

He had planned deeply before entering the River of Time. Fang Yuan had already used luck path methods like burning soul bursting luck, he had only stopped after reaching the limit.

In this vast River of Time, finding one or two stone lotus islands was purely dependent on luck.

Roar—!

The river water suddenly became turbulent as sounds of beast growls entered their ears.

"There are two immemorial year beasts fighting ahead!" After inspecting it, Ying Wu Xie alerted.

Looking at it closely, these two immemorial year beasts had already fought for some time, they were near their limit.

Fang Yuan laughed, wasn't this the work of luck path?

He flew out of the incomplete Immortal Gu House and activated familiar face, becoming a part of the river water as he blended into the River of Time.

Next, he opened a trace of his immortal aperture's entrance and activated the immemorial year beast fishing formation!

The two immemorial year beasts detected the delicacy, their movements stopped, they charged towards Fang Yuan like they were competing in a race.

They did not find any enemies, but they sensed a tributary of the River of Time under the river water.

The immemorial year beasts did not think much, they charged into this tributary of the River of Time.

This was naturally Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture.

If it were in the past, Fang Yuan would not dare to lure these immemorial year beasts, they would cause huge destruction to the sovereign immortal aperture if they went in.

But now, times were different, Fang Yuan had year essence pools, two in fact!

The year essence pools were connected to the tributary of the River of Time like huge dams.

The immemorial year beasts were lured by the formation, following the tributary of the River of Time until they rushed into the 'dam', becoming trapped.

Fang Yuan smiled heartily as he stopped the transformation killer move, he flew back into the incomplete Immortal Gu House.

Those two immemorial year monkeys were trapped in the year essence pools, they could not find any food and sensed something amiss, but how could they return to the River of Time now?

Fang Yuan used his enslavement path methods and quickly subdued these two immemorial year beasts.

The incomplete Immortal Gu House moved stealthily as it searched for a stone lotus island.

Fang Yuan met many year beasts along the way, he took in all of them, luring them into the year essence pools and subduing them.

Soon, Fang Yuan's number of immemorial year beasts rose to six.

And even more ancient and desolate level year beasts.

Other than year beasts, there were other lifeforms like day beasts, month beasts, or dark web spiders in the River of Time, Fang Yuan had chosen to ignore them all.

The use of the year essence pools was amply displayed here!

With th, Fang Yuan could lure immemorial year beasts while keeping sovereign immortal aperture very safe. Without their restriction, the immemorial year beasts would be able to move along the tributary of the River of Time and go to anywhere in the sovereign immortal aperture. Because the tributary was present all over the whole sovereign immortal aperture.

"Wait!" After moving for a while, Fang Yuan's time path clone opened his eyes, bursting with bright light.

He seemed to have found something!

The time path clone quickly shut his eyes as he frowned deeply, trying to sense it.

Next, he pointed in one direction: "There seems to be something there, Spring Autumn Cicada shuddered a little."

The time path clone spoke with uncertainty.

But this was the only clue, Fang Yuan manipulated the incomplete Immortal Gu House and changed directions, going towards that place.

As the distance shortened, Fang Yuan's clone felt increasingly happy: "The feeling is getting stronger, our luck is really not bad, we found it so quickly!"

A while later, in the vision of Fang Yuan and the rest, a thin layer of fog appeared.

The incomplete Immortal Gu House halted for a moment before rushing into the fog with no hesitation.

The fog was extraordinary, it could obscure one's sense of direction and confuse them, but using the key Spring Autumn Cicada, Fang Yuan's clone could move in the proper direction.

The fog got thicker, the river water also moved slower due to its effect, it was not as turbulent as the water outside.

Vaguely, the silhouette of an island appeared before Fang Yuan and the rest.

"Stone lotus island! Red Lotus true inheritance!!" Ying Wu Xie stared wide and shouted loudly.

Bai Ning Bing and the rest also started to breathe roughly.

When the incomplete Immortal Gu House got to the periphery of the stone lotus island, the island shot out a white light that hit the incomplete Immortal Gu House directly.

"What is going on?!" Fairy Miao Yin screamed.

"Oh no! This is a trap." Fang Yuan's eyes shined with a sharp light, it was too late to escape now.

The entire incomplete Immortal Gu House shook intensely, it could not resist the strong attacks outside.

"Demon, I have been waiting for you for a long time!" A rank eight Gu Immortal with a tall muscular body appeared on the stone lotus island.

At the next moment, his killer move that had been prepared for a while hit the incomplete Immortal Gu House.

Boom!

The incomplete Immortal Gu House broke apart at once.

Chapter 1631: Verdant Sun Flame Cloak

Fang Yuan's incomplete Immortal Gu House did not excel in defense, after it was struck, it broke apart.

Fang Yuan and the rest quickly defended themselves inside the Immortal Gu House.

A huge amount of flames moved like poisonous snakes and burned all of the Gu worms in their way, before they gathered towards Fang Yuan in an encircling movement.

Fang Yuan shouted as he used immortal killer move winter coat, his body was immediately covered by a layer of snow-white frost.

The frost not only protected him, at this crucial moment, it spread out and protected the time path clone, Hei Lou Lan, Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing, and the rest.

In this regard, winter coat was better than reverse flow protection seal.

Because reverse flow protection seal only defended himself, it could not help others, but winter coat was able to affect other people.

Winter coat killer move blocked the fire snakes' attacks, but at the next moment, the old man on the stone lotus island shouted: "By the power of flames, snakes turn into dragons!"

Whoosh!

The flames burst out with incredible heat, the snakes coiled around each other, turning into a huge flame dragon that was a hundred feet long, possessing huge claws and fangs.

The bright red flame dragon slashed through winter coat before charging at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan wanted to open his immortal aperture's entrance to store the immortals back in his aperture, but this fire snake killer move actually had a variation, with the old man's deep experience, Fang Yuan had no time for that.

The flame dragon opened its mouth as its soared down from above.

Fang Yuan and the rest looked up as their faces were red from the light of the flames, the intense heat felt like it was going to grill them alive!

Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, and the rest all revealed looks of despair on their faces.

This flame dragon was not an ordinary rank eight killer move, it had extraordinary power, even Bai Ning Bing's Bai Xiang killer move could not escape from it.

Their only hope was Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's ears, nose, and eyes were bleeding!

Winter coat killer move was broken, Fang Yuan suffered a rank eight killer move backlash. A large number of mortal Gu were killed, thankfully his core Immortal Gu were still alive, they were damaged but still usable.

Fang Yuan was in a difficult situation.

The time path clone, Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, and the rest were behind him, their cultivation level was too low, they could not block the flame dragon. If they had the incomplete Immortal Gu House, they could still participate in the fight, but the old man was too perceptive, he destroyed the incomplete Immortal Gu House from the start.

If Fang Yuan stayed and protected them, not only did he have no good methods now that winter coat was broken, even if he did, it would be too dangerous!

Because the other party wanted to force Fang Yuan to fight them, once he protects them and fights, the old man's plan would succeed.

Fang Yuan was almost certain that the other party still had killer moves prepared. Once Fang Yuan fights with the flame dragon, the old man would grasp the tempo of the battle, he would control the battle's flow from now on.

Instantly, Fang Yuan made up his mind, he moved out like lightning, dodging the flame dragon.

The old man laughed frenziedly: "A true demon indeed! Then burn to death!"

The flame dragon ignored Fang Yuan, it charged down.

Fang Yuan snorted coldly, he turned around and attacked the old man.

The old man diverted his gaze at Fang Yuan, seeing that he was approaching, the old man smiled and revealed a sinister expression.

Fang Yuan's heart sank, he attacked so that the old man would divert attention to defend himself but the old man was similarly courageous and did not fear a frontal assault. Most possibly, he still had arrangements on this stone lotus island, he was extremely confident.

Fang Yuan stretched out his finger, his hard work over the last few months had not been in vain, spring scissors was unleashed and shot towards the old man.

The scissors was very sharp, but when it landed on the old man, his hair started to burn as it turned into a flame cloak, protecting him all around and blocking spring scissors.

"Hahaha, I named this move verdant sun flame cloak, I made it from the inspiration I gained from Verdant Great Sun's flame hair from <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>, it is my proudest creation. To speak the truth, even though I am a fire path Gu Immortal, I am more skilled in defense than offense! Not just spring scissors, even summer fan is useless against me." The old man laughed loudly.

But at the next moment, the old man's smile faded.

It turned out that the flame dragon had returned empty-handed, be it Fang Yuan's time path clone, Bai Ning Bing, Hei Lou Lan, or others, they were still alive.

The old man's eyelids twitched, he licked his dry lips as he said darkly: "This is a dream realm?"

It turned out that while Fang Yuan dodged the flame dragon, he did not abandon his clone or the other Gu Immortals, he had ordered Ying Wu Xie to self-detonate at the crucial moment.

After the five regional mountain range, Ying Wu Xie had changed bodies, using a body with the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique again. Precisely because of the dream path dao marks on the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique, he was able to use lead soul into dream and successfully affect rank eight Gu Immortal Jun Shen Guang.

Now that the Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body self-detonated, Ying Wu Xie's soul was trapped in the dream realm. The other immortals were very close to him, they were covered by the dream realm.

With the manifestation of the dream realm, all other paths could not affect it. The old man's flame dragon had great power, but against the illusory dream realm, it was useless.

"Hmph, you are truly a scheming demon, but you will die today!" The old man stomped his feet, flying up into the sky as the stone lotus island below him scattered into dust and sand.

The old man wore a flame cloak as he approached Fang Yuan like a blazing meteor. Spring scissors followed after him as it attacked, but the flames defended against them and the old man was completely unharmed.

Fang Yuan flew backwards as he used summer fan.

Intense winds blew, the old man's flame cloak was flickering, but it seemed like the fire was growing with the wind, becoming even larger.

The old man smiled as he exposed his sharp teeth: "How about that! My verdant sun flame cloak is unparalleled, have you felt despair yet? Hahaha!"

Like what the old man has said, summer fan and spring scissors were useless against verdant sun flame cloak.

Not only that, as they got closer, an intense feeling of drunkenness assaulted Fang Yuan.

But soon, Fang Yuan used his wisdom path killer move and regained clarity in his mind.

Verdant sun flame cloak not only contained the extreme profundity of fire path, it also mimicked the effects of human path and food path. As the old man got closer to him, the greater the feeling of drunkenness would be.

Fang Yuan tried his best to retreat, wanting to pull some distance from the old man, but against his wishes, the enemy's speed surpassed him by quite a bit.

"Demon, you are trapped in the formation, where can you run to? Obediently accept your death!" The old man shouted.

Earlier, the stone lotus island was merely an illusion, its true essence was a super time path immortal formation set up in the River of Time!

This formation was very powerful, even Fang Yuan could not notice it. As it activated now, a formation space was created, Fang Yuan was trapped inside, restricting him from using Omni-directional Travel, Fixed Immortal Travel, and other similar methods.

Fang Yuan had used a time path formation earlier to ambush Southern Border's righteous path. Now, Heavenly Court did the same against Fang Yuan.

But Heavenly Court put in much more effort than Fang Yuan!

Fang Yuan could not create such a time path formation in the River of Time. With his current strength, he could only create a time path immortal formation near a tributary of the River of Time in the outside world.

Even for time path great experts in history, few could create immortal formations inside the River of Time.

The person who could achieve this to the limit was Red Lotus Demon Venerable. This person had already surpassed the realms of time path immortal formations, he could directly create artificial secluded domains of heaven and earth, stone lotus islands, to influence segments of the River of Time and take control of it.

Heavenly Court had been looking for the stone lotus islands and had yet to find one, but they were not without gains. This time path immortal formation was one of their achievements.

The formation restricted Fang Yuan, making him unable to evade or dodge.

The old man got closer, Fang Yuan snorted, instead of retreating, he charged at the old man.

The old man was slightly surprised, but he quickly reacted as he waved his hands, sending waves of flames towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan had no fear, he rammed forward.

The huge flames reversed and went back to attack the old man.

It was the immortal killer move — Reverse Flow Protection Seal!

The old man was a little flustered, he defended against his own killer move, but at this moment, Fang Yuan had already arrived in front of him.

Fang Yuan was ruthless, he slammed his body into the old man.

Reverse flow protection seal against verdant sun flame cloak!

At the next moment, Fang Yuan and the old man both flew backwards, they were nearly evenly matched in this contest.

The old man had lost by a slight bit, but soon, his flame cloak burned again as he returned to his peak condition.

Reverse flow protection seal was extremely effective against attacks. But verdant sun flame cloak was a defensive killer move, the reflected damage was quite little.

"This is reverse flow protection seal? Heh, he found out so quickly." The old man's gaze flickered eerily.

It turned out that this time path immortal formation created an isolated inner formation space, there was a core effect, it was that this environment weakened time path.

Heavenly Court's original intention was to use this formation to deal with the stone lotus islands of Red Lotus' true inheritance. These islands were artificially created time path secluded domains of heaven and earth, once the formation encapsulates them, they would be weakened.

Precisely so, Fang Yuan's spring scissors and summer fan killer moves were so ineffective against verdant sun flame cloak.

Verdant sun flame cloak was very powerful indeed, it was the peak creation of fire path, and even extended to contain the profundities of human path and food path.

In terms of intricacy, reverse flow protection seal was very roughly made and straightforward. In contrast, myriad self comprised both enslavement path and strength path, it was on par with verdant sun flame cloak in this aspect.

Summer fan and spring scissors were ordinary, they only contained rank eight Immortal Gu and were amplified by time path dao marks to gain such great power. They could not break verdant sun flame cloak but could have caused great damage. Yet in this environment, they had a mild effect.

Fang Yuan realized this and daringly dispelled winter coat, instead using reverse flow protection seal to regain his footing in the battle.

Chapter 1632: You Lied!

Immortal killer move — Myriad Dragon!

Howl…

At once, myriad dragons flew in a sea of silvery scales, attacking the old man like a tidal wave.

After understanding the effect of the time path formation, Fang Yuan gave up on his strongest time path methods, he started to use other methods. In this aspect, Fang Yuan had many useful methods comparatively.

The old man snorted, showing no surprise on his face.

Before coming here, he had already made ample preparation, he knew about Fang Yuan's myriad dragon killer move.

"Slippery eels, what can they do to me?" The old man stood arrogantly in the sky, instead of dodging, he watched as the myriad dragons approached him.

His verdant sun flame cloak was blazing, his entire body was covered, resembling a huge fireball.

The myriad dragons appeared before the old man, but they started to screech weirdly, the sword dragons were all drowsy as they randomly flew around, their ferocious attacks had been stopped.

When each sword dragon's drunkenness got to a certain level, they would start to blaze up with a loud sound.

The sword dragons turned into a pile of flames before rapidly vanishing.

Looking at the field, the old man was unmoving while the myriad dragons burned to death. Even though there were countless dragons, the moment they got close to the old man, they died, they were of no threat to him.

"Immortal killer move verdant sun flame cloak!" Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, he finally saw the power of this move. It was both offensive and defensive, it was a counter to Fang Yuan's myriad dragon killer move.

"Then let's try Luo Po seal." Fang Yuan thought to himself.

He had already used familiar face to disguise as a sword dragon, he blended into the army of dragons, getting closer to the old man.

Next, he pretended to be drunk as he got closer and unleashed Luo Po seal.

Fang Yuan got exposed when the killer move had just activated, Luo Po seal's aura was too great, it could not be hidden.

The old man's gaze shot like lightning as he charged at Fang Yuan without fearing Luo Po seal.

Boom boom boom!

The old man attacked Fang Yuan in a frenzy but reverse flow protection seal kept him safe.

Fang Yuan did not speak, he endured the old man's attacks until Luo Po seal was finally ready to strike.

The old man was on guard now, the situation was not good for Fang Yuan. Eventually, he barely managed to use Luo Po seal, but it scraped past the old man's shoulder, only half landing!

The old man immediately felt a sense of emptiness in his heart, at the same time, the blazing cloak on his back weakened by forty percent!

"This move is amazing, but it cannot break my verdant sun flame cloak!" The old man laughed loudly as he retreated, using methods to heal himself.

His speed was faster than Fang Yuan, it was hard to land consecutive hits on him.

The old man found time to catch a breather despite having the disadvantage, a moment later, his injuries healed mostly and his aura regained its peak state, the verdant sun flame cloak also started to blaze up again.

Luo Po seal had terrifying might but the old man was very alert, he did not give Fang Yuan any more chances.

His verdant sun flame cloak's defenses were superb, Fang Yuan could sense that in battle, it was like how his enemies felt when facing reverse flow protection seal.

"This old man's soul is not his weakness." Even though he only grazed past him, Fang Yuan obtained valuable intel.

Luo Po seal was targeted at the enemy's soul, but this old man was an experienced rank eight Gu Immortal with deep foundations, he did not have any evident weaknesses, his soul's defense was quite tight.

Fang Yuan estimated that even if Luo Po seal hit directly, it could not kill the old man in one move.

Luo Po seal had to be paired with lead soul into dream to deal with Heavenly Court's rank eight Gu Immortals.

But at the start of the battle, the old man destroyed Fang Yuan's incomplete Immortal Gu House, causing Ying Wu Xie and the rest to slumber in the dream realm.

If the incomplete Immortal Gu House was still around, Fang Yuan would have Ying Wu Xie's lead soul into dream to help him, he would have the advantage against this old man.

But the old man had ambushed and destroyed the incomplete Immortal Gu House, not only were Fang Yuan's losses severe, he lost his initiative and was kept on the back foot for a long time.

This situation was naturally very dangerous for Fang Yuan, he had fallen into an ambush, he had to escape quickly.

Immortal killer move — Myriad Dragon!

Fang Yuan continued to activate myriad dragon as more sword dragons filled this formation space.

The old man had the advantage but he did not relax his mind or become careless.

He squinted a little as Fang Yuan hid among the sword dragons again. At this time, should he use an investigative method to find Fang Yuan or eliminate these sword dragons first?

If he did not kill Fang Yuan, there would be an endless stream of sword dragons, but the old man had clear awareness, he thought: "I'm afraid my investigative method cannot expose familiar face, Fang Yuan is so crafty, he must have other plans!"

The old man had the initiative now, he spoke arrogantly and wildly, but his mind was extremely calm and composed.

He knew that when opponents of his and Fang Yuan's level fight, with such rich battle experience on both sides, even though he had the initiative now and could hold the advantage, if he made a mistake, Fang Yuan would turn the situation around.

The old man roared as flames started to burn around, spreading out like a sea of fire.

The sword dragons melted in candles within the flame.

The old man's decision made Fang Yuan quite troubled.

He hesitated for a while before persisting with his tactic, he controlled the myriad dragons to charge at the formation space.

This formation was clearly controlled by Central Continent Gu Immortals. Seeing that the myriad dragons were attacking, they wanted to retaliate but the old man quickly transmitted to them: "Don't move! Fang Yuan has very high time path and wisdom path attainment levels, the more the formation activates, the more flaws he will notice. I will handle these eels, don't be anxious."

The old man did not want to give Fang Yuan any chances, the sea of fire killed the sword dragons at a rapid rate.

Fang Yuan smiled coldly, he suddenly appeared in front of the dream realm.

Immortal killer move — Pure Dream Reality Seeker Transformation!

He quickly gathered the dream realm and turned the lump of dream realm into a Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique body.

"Oh no, this demon is so scheming!" The old man's expression changed, Fang Yuan used many feints and tactics, it was hard to see through his plans after all.

Fang Yuan opened a sliver of his immortal aperture's entrance, wanting to send the time path clone, Ying Wu Xie's soul, Hei Lou Lan, and Bai Ning Bing inside.

But at this moment, the old man screamed angrily behind him: "Demon, forget about it!"

Boom!

A killer move was used, bursting out with immense strength and sound.

Fang Yuan felt a chill, he did not need to turn around to know that this move was the old man's strongest offensive method.

"I won't make it!" Fang Yuan did not have enough time to react, his heart sank to rock bottom.

At the crucial moment, he went all out!

His time path killer move was used as the time around suddenly became faster.

He placed the immortals into the immortal aperture, and at the same time, he felt like a giant had landed a punch on his back, the huge force sent him flying like a cannonball, he lost fifteen percent of Reverse Flow River's water! The impact made Fang Yuan's head dizzy, he directly spat out a mouthful of blood.

He was only able to save a portion of them, Fairy Miao Yin could not be reached. She was still unconscious earlier, after being engulfed in the huge flames, she was burned to ashes, not a bit of her body remained.

Fang Yuan shouted loudly as he used myriad dragon, charging around the place, while he started to act and destroy the formation.

The old man was a bit nervous now, he started to attack Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan had reverse flow protection seal to defend him, he ignored the old man and only targeted the formation.

"Fang Yuan, don't think of getting out, that is merely a delusion!" The old man roared as his flames engulfed Fang Yuan.

"Hahaha, you are simply struggling at death's door." The old man got behind Fang Yuan and slammed them on his back like two huge tablets, Fang Yuan was sent flying.

Fang Yuan was bleeding from all seven orifices, it was quite a pathetic sight, yet his eyes were still cold as ice, he continued to attack the time path formation.

"It is useless! How can you break such an amazing formation? Look at your Reverse Flow River, it is about to be fully expended." The old man mocked, he attacked with greater intensity, killing intent surged as he behaved in a frenzied manner.

Even though Reverse Flow River could reflect attacks, the old man also had his verdant sun flame cloak. He endured the reflected attacks as he continued to expend the Reverse Flow River water.

He was not wrong, Fang Yuan's Reverse Flow River had gone through many battles, a lot of it was used up already. As he continued to attack, the river water level fell, Fang Yuan's robe also started to become thin and flimsy.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan roared as he stopped attacking, preparing Luo Po seal again.

The old man's pupils shrunk, his attacks changed, he started to prepare his defenses against Luo Po seal.

Fang Yuan completed the preparation as he flicked his palm, instead of attacking the old man, he shot it towards a corner of the formation.

"Guh!" With a shocked voice, a rank seven Gu Immortal controlling the formation was hit by Luo Po seal, he died on the spot.

"How?!" The other Central Continent Gu Immortals were also shocked and lost for words.

Fang Yuan was able to find a formation core in such a short time and kill the person inside.

Luo Po seal was very powerful even against rank eight Gu Immortals, not to mention these rank sevens.

"Quick, that formation core has been destroyed, quickly move and fix the hole!" A Gu Immortal shouted.

On the other end, the old man grunted as he attacked Fang Yuan again.

Fang Yuan used the extremely depleted reverse flow protection seal to defend himself while attacking the formation himself.

With many of his methods used, Heavenly Court's meticulously created time path immortal formation collapsed area by area, it could not hold up against Fang Yuan's unraveling.

"How can this be?!" Fang Yuan's speed of deduction was extremely shocking to everyone.

"Quick, over there!" Someone shouted.

A loophole formed in the formation, connecting with the outside world.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Bye."

"You cannot leave!" Flames swept over, turning into the old man. He hid the loophole behind himself desperately.

The other Central Continent Gu Immortals also let out a sigh of relief.

But Fang Yuan shot out like an arrow towards the old man, saying coldly with deep killing intent: "Get lost."

The old man snickered: "It is useless, you cannot deal with my verdant sun flame cloak!"

The distance between them shrunk!

Central Continent's Gu Immortals quickly changed their formation, someone shouted: "Block Fang Yuan, we only need five breaths of time to change the formation! This is a complete change, it would be ten times as difficult as before to deduce it afterwards!"

The old man scoffed: "Not just five breaths, even if… hmm?"

His eyes suddenly widened, his face turned stiff, he looked at Fang Yuan's killer move preparation with deep disbelief.

Fang Yuan's aura was completely concealed, not a bit leaked out.

He clapped both hands together in front of his chest. Next, his right hand which was in contact with his left hand moved, it was like he was trying to pull out something precious, as his right palm slowly clenched into a fist.

Afterwards, his left hand was still at the original position, but his tightly clenched right fist was lifted, above his chest and shoulder, above his head, until it was fixed right above his head.

"This, this move is…" The old man no longer smiled, there was nervousness in his eyes and even some fear.

Indeed, this was the immortal killer move — Five Finger Fist Heart Sword!

Time passed, at the first breath.

First finger!

Fang Yuan had a cold expression as he raised the thumb of his right hand.

From the right fist that he held high in the air, a sword light shot out.

Fast! Fast! Fast!

The speed of the sword light was beyond belief!

The moment it was shot out, it pierced the old man's forehead.

The old man shuddered, the flames on the verdant sun flame cloak on his body weakened by half.

Second breath.

Second finger!

The old man reacted, he roared as the verdant sun flame cloak started blazing again.

But the sword light landed again, weakening the verdant sun flame cloak.

Third breath.

Third finger.

The old man's expression turned pale, he wanted to grit his teeth, the verdant sun flame cloak on his back had expanded like a fireball, earlier it was the size of a horse carriage, but now it was the size of a house.

The old man roared: "This is the peak condition of my verdant sun flame cloak! Come, your attacks cannot break through."

The moment he said that, the sword light landed as the verdant sun flame cloak burst like a balloon, it returned to its former condition.

Five finger fist heart sword got stronger as it progressed.

Fourth breath, fourth finger!

The old man desperately blocked the fourth sword, his expression was pale, he took a huge step back, verdant sun flame cloak was like a flickering candle, it was extremely thin now.

Fifth breath.

Fang Yuan snickered: "What cloak, it is laughable. Li Huang, you can start preparing your funeral. It is over, the fifth sword!"

The old man's heart jumped, his eyes were filled with terror: "No, Bo Qing, don't even dream of killing me!"

The flame blazed, he turned into dozens of figures as he flew in all directions.

Fang Yuan ignored him, he flew outside the loophole, escaping into the River of Time.

He had just flown out when the time path formation changed completely, the earlier loopholes were fixed, it had become whole again, securely locking the formation space inside.

But Fang Yuan had already escaped, the time path formation was completely silent inside.

The Central Continent Gu Immortals controlling the formation were all dumbfounded.

The flame clones dissipated slowly, until only the old man's main body remained.

At this moment, his face was flushing red and white; anger, fear, humiliation, hatred, and killing intent, they filled his heart entirely, turning his expression distorted and filled with terrifying hatred.

Suddenly, the old man raised his head and roared.

"There, there was no fifth sword!"

"Fang Yuan!!"

"You lied!!!"

Chapter 1633: Cutting Edge Slays Enemies

After a tough battle of brains and brawn, Fang Yuan finally got out of Heavenly Court's ambush and escaped into the River of Time.

Once he left the formation, Fang Yuan felt the difficulty of using reverse flow protection seal raise by several times, he quickly stopped it and changed to the time path killer move winter coat.

Immortal killer move — Familiar Face!

At the next moment, Fang Yuan turned into an immemorial year beast.

Because he had transformed in the River of Time, transformation path was also greatly suppressed. Even though he managed to use the move, his immortal essence expenditure was tens of times as much as usual!

Thankfully, familiar face's core was attitude Gu, it only expended mental energy. Thus, on the whole, familiar face used very little immortal essence, Fang Yuan could sustain it.

Plop.

Fang Yuan turned into an immemorial year snake as he went into the River of Time, slithering away.

"We are finally out of the encirclement, escaping the time path formation." Fang Yuan felt a little glad.

The earlier situation was quite dangerous. The longer it dragged on, the more tight Heavenly Court's defenses would be, and the lower chances Fang Yuan would have of survival.

This time, there were two reasons why he could escape.

Firstly, Fang Yuan had made the time path clone use the light of wisdom to break the formation. Because of the light of wisdom, Fang Yuan's wisdom path abilities far exceeded Heavenly Court's imagination, he could catch them off guard.

Secondly, he used five finger fist heart sword. Fang Yuan had rank eight cultivation level, with his own white litchi immortal essence, he could use wisdom sword Immortal Gu. This Immortal Gu was one of the core of five finger fist heart sword to begin with, thus, Fang Yuan could use the fourth sword of five finger fist heart sword. This was his current limit, to use the fifth sword, he would need other core sword path Immortal Gu.

"I expended a lot of rank eight immortal essence." Fang Yuan inspected his immortal aperture, his immortal essence storage had fallen to a dangerous level.

Even though Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had a fast time flow and could accumulate white litchi immortal essence rapidly, he had gone through fierce battles consecutively, especially earlier against the old man Li Huang, he had expended a lot when breaking out of the time path formation.

"I should escape first!" In this situation, Fang Yuan only had one thought.

This was the wisest decision, a frontal face-off was the most stupid idea.

"Fang Yuan, where are you going!" An angry growl could be heard behind him.

Fang Yuan turned around and his heart jumped.

Three Immortal Gu Houses were chasing after him with threatening auras.

The left one was Eternal Yacht, it was tall and rode with the wind. On the deck, rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye, the rank seven Gu Immortals Four Xunzi and others were standing with a righteous aura.

The middle one was Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform, it was elegant and grand, the orange roof resembled cranes with their wings spread out. The Immortal Gu House was radiating three layers of autumn light, it was quite extraordinary.

The right one was Shark Flow Lever, the huge lever was white like jade, a rank eight Gu Immortal was standing on it, he wore a suit of blue star armor and had a rough appearance. There were seven huge sharks in front of the lever, they had sharp teeth and were dragging the huge lever ahead.

"Three rank seven Immortal Gu Houses, at least three rank eight Gu Immortals, with many rank seven Gu Immortals…" Fang Yuan's heart continued to sink, at this moment, he could see Heavenly Court's huge determination to get rid of him!

Even though Fang Yuan became an immemorial year snake, his speed was not fast. With the destruction of the incomplete Immortal Gu House, he could not conceal himself.

Both sides continued to shrink in distance, the three Immortal Gu Houses attacked from afar.

Fang Yuan used autumn perception killer move as eyes seemed to grow on his back, he managed to evade agilely.

If he could not dodge, he would use winter coat to endure the attacks forcefully.

Winter coat was amplified in the River of Time, together with Fang Yuan's time path dao marks, it displayed incredible defensive power, even though it was not as amazing as reverse flow protection seal, it was on par with it here.

"This cannot go on!" The situation was getting worse, Fang Yuan tried to find a solution.

Luo Po seal took a long time to activate, in the River of Time, the duration would be even longer, and the overall strength would be weaker. Heavenly Court would be fully on guard against him, he could not rely on Luo Po seal to turn the situation around.

Myriad self, myriad dragon, strength path giant hand, emperor yama, and others, they were the same.

Fang Yuan could only rely on summer fan, spring scissors, and other time path methods.

But the three Immortal Gu Houses after Fang Yuan were strong as fortresses, spring scissors and summer fan were unable to do anything to them.

As they continued to fight, Fang Yuan's immortal essence storage fell continuously, the situation was getting worse.

Heavenly Court chased after Fang Yuan with rising morale, their expressions were very optimistic.

Suddenly, at the river ahead, a change occurred, huge fountains were starting to burst out.

"Oh no, this is the sudden spring river segment!"

"This demon excels in luck path, he has incredible luck, he is very hard to kill. As expected, something occurred here!"

"Follow him, don't let him escape."

Heavenly Court's side shouted, showing nervous expressions on their faces.

Fang Yuan dived into the sudden spring river segment.

The sudden springs were very dangerous, they carried the might of time path. If the scale was large enough, they would definitely be able to take the lives of rank eight Gu Immortals.

In most situations, Fang Yuan would avoid them, but now, this sudden spring river segment was his hope of escaping.

The immemorial year snake slithered in the river, sudden springs erupted around Fang Yuan time and time again, but they were not much of an obstacle for him.

Fang Yuan had luck inspection Immortal Gu, while the sovereign immortal body had non-conflicting dao marks, he could evidently sense that his luck was falling rapidly.

Luck path usually could not be sensed, but at this moment, it displayed its incredible power.

Heavenly Court's three Immortal Gu Houses had a hard time chasing him.

The moment they entered the sudden spring river segment, Eternal Yacht and Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform were hit by sudden springs immediately, pushed up forcefully.

They spent a lot of effort to dive down, even Shark Flow Lever was hit.

Fang Yuan often encountered rank six or seven level small to mid sized sudden springs, while Heavenly Court faced rank eight level big sudden springs.

Even though Fang Yuan met many obstacles and was often obstructed by the sudden springs, Heavenly Court's group was more like a bunch of sick people climbing a mountain. Their encounters were clearly contrasted, Heavenly Court's members had dark expressions, they felt deeply vexed, wanting to spit blood in anger.

"It seems that Feng Jiu Ge is not part of the group." Fang Yuan had a realization.

In the battle of Lang Ya, Fang Yuan saw how strong Feng Jiu Ge's luck was, he could not suppress the latter.

If he was here, Heavenly Court would not face such troubles now.

Without much danger, Fang Yuan managed to get out of the sudden spring river segment.

Behind him, Shark Flow Lever and Three Autumn Yellow Crane Platform were already far behind, only Eternal Yacht could barely catch up with him, it had left the sudden spring river segment as well.

Without obstacles now, Eternal Yacht's speed rose, it reduced the distance between Fang Yuan and itself.

"I cannot escape like this!" Fang Yuan's eyes shined with lightning, he made up his mind and stopped to face the enemy.

Seeing that Fang Yuan was not escaping, Eternal Yacht's Gu Immortals were overjoyed, but soon, they exposed wary expressions full of alertness.

Xun Guo Zi shouted: "Everyone, be careful, the demon is fighting instead of running, he must have some vicious plans!"

She had just spoken when Fang Yuan's killer move activated.

Immortal killer move — Time Cutting Edge!

This move was still rank seven level, but Fang Yuan's time path dao marks amplified it to a hundred times of its power, at the same time, it was inside the River of Time, its power rose to nearly rank eight.

At once, the leader, rank eight Gu Immortal Qing Ye, sensed a fatal threat, his hair was standing on ends, his heart shrunk as he quickly dodged.

But time cutting edge was too fast, even faster than five finger fist heart sword, the moment Fang Yuan used it, it had already reached Qing Ye.

Eternal Yacht had its defenses of course, but time cutting edge was thin as paper, it easily penetrated it!

"Isn't this move lost in history? How can he use it! Am I going to die here?!" Instantly, Qing Ye was filled with shock as he fell into deep despair.

"Let me!" At the dangerous moment, Xun Guo Zi jumped out, standing in front of Qing Ye.

Crack!

Xun Guo Zi's body shook intensely, she was hit by time cutting edge, her eyes stared widely as she fell down on the deck.

"Huff huff!" Qing Ye breathed roughly, he was covered in sweat, having barely kept his life.

"Xun Guo Zi…" Qing Ye's expression was pale as he showed a deeply moved expression.

The other three Xunzi looked at each other with calm expressions.

They thought: Xun Guo Zi blocked the blade for Qing Ye and died for him, it was definitely worth it to gain the favor of this rank eight Gu Immortal.

"Lord Qing Ye, don't worry about it. We have a unique method to revive our sister." Shang Xunzi smiled and expressed his sincerity.

But Qing Ye shook his head, showing a grim expression: "I can somewhat understand the profundities behind your method. I am afraid it will not work this time."

The three Xunzi were shocked, they asked: "Lord, what do you mean? Please explain it to us."

"This is Bo clan's killer move, it had once threatened the whole of Central Continent, it is called time cutting edge." Qing Ye said with a complex expression, unable to conceal his fear.

"What?"

""There is such a move!"

The three Xunzi's expressions changed, they all started to tremble as they became fearful and panicky, no longer as calm as before.

"No, impossible, isn't this move gone already?" Shang Xunzi shook his head, refusing to believe Qing Ye.

"But the truth is so, stop chasing him." Qing Ye breathed in deeply with a pale expression.

"Lord!" The remaining rank seven Gu Immortals shouted, Fang Yuan was right in front of them, it was a great chance to kill this demon, they would gain an incredible amount of contribution credits! If they let him go, they would definitely be reprimanded and punished.

But Qing Ye made up his mind.

"Among the three Immortal Gu Houses, Eternal Yacht is the fastest but has the weakest defense. You've all seen how time cutting edge could not be blocked!"

"If we pursue him, as long as Fang Yuan kills us one by one, he will gain this Eternal Yacht instead. Plus, even though I have a phantom aperture, you all have a lifetime of accumulation, we cannot give them all to this demon."

If at this moment, other than Eternal Yacht, the other Immortal Gu Houses were around, Qing Ye might pursue him.

But right now, if they chased after him, there would not be any chance of victory.

Chapter 1634: Attack and Defend

"Huff…" Fang Yuan let out a breath of air and suddenly opened his eyes.

This was an underground cave, there were dim flames lighting the walls, creating a natural formation. Even though it was not strong, it could alert him.

Fang Yuan was ambushed by Heavenly Court in the River of Time, he had fought desperately for a way out after an intense struggle.

After getting away from Qing Ye and the rest, Fang Yuan followed the tributary of the River of Time and got to the outside world of Southern Border.

Southern Border was the headquarters of Shadow Sect, Purple Mountain True Monarch had set up many eerie fire caves at many locations. Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel to randomly go into one and rest, recovering from the fight.

Even though he had reverse flow protection seal, he was not using it the entire time, he had to rely on winter coat. Let alone the battle with Li Huang, just during his escape, Fang Yuan was hit by the three Immortal Gu Houses multiple times, his injuries were not light.

Fang Yuan inspected his sovereign immortal body before standing up slowly.

After a few days of recovery, he had already healed. Most importantly, because the sovereign immortal body had non-conflicting dao marks, his healing effects were very effective.

His rank eight white litchi immortal essence had also increased, but it was still in the red zone.

Fang Yuan paced around in the cave with his arms behind his back. While considering the situation, his frown got deeper.

This time, he had suffered greatly in the River of Time. It was no exaggeration to say that he had 'barely survived'.

Fang Yuan did not feel much fear or joy, such a case was within his expectations.

Heavenly Court's foundation was simply too deep!

Fang Yuan's growth was simply nothing compared to the long history of Heavenly Court.

With such immense foundation, they only had to put in some effort to give Fang Yuan huge problems. The battle in the River of Time was a good affirmation to this.

Earlier, Fang Yuan had an advantage against Heavenly Court, it was because he sneak attacked and caught them unprepared. Because he was able to stay hidden, Heavenly Court could not do anything. Fang Yuan had always been exerting all his effort and using all his time to grow stronger and make Heavenly Court's plans fail each time.

But as Heavenly Court learned more about Fang Yuan, they placed more emphasis on him, when it finally came to a frontal assault, Fang Yuan's strength was just too little.

Heavenly Court was not just strong in foundation, the biggest advantage was their unified mindset.

Southern Border's righteous path also had immense strength, but all of the clans were focused on their individual benefits, they could not effectively deal with Fang Yuan.

But Heavenly Court had always been pressuring Fang Yuan.

If not for his schemes and plots, any other demonic path Gu Immortal would have been captured or killed already.

As time passes, Heavenly Court's arrangements in the River of Time would get more elaborate, the chances of getting Red Lotus' true inheritance would become slimmer.

Against such a strong enemy, what could Fang Yuan do?

"I have expended almost all of my white litchi immortal essence."

"Reverse Flow River also has barely any water, Li Huang expended too much of it, I can't use it anymore."

Unlike Dang Hun Mountain and Luo Po Valley which had rank nine killer move orderly well and could be repaired using Landscape as Before rapidly, Reverse Flow River was very different.

Fang Yuan did not lack the methods to restore it, but any method would incur huge costs!

For the foreseeable future, Fang Yuan would not be able to use his reverse flow protection seal anymore.

Even without reverse flow protection seal, Fang Yuan had gotten to rank eight and obtained Xia Cha's methods, on the whole, his strength had still risen by quite a lot.

"But this time, I exposed too many methods."

Immemorial year beasts, spring scissors, summer fan, and other killer moves were exposed, they were part of Fang Yuan's plan. But the reveal of time cutting edge was truly a shame.

There was no choice, in that battle, if Fang Yuan did not use this method, he might have died already.

"But I am not without gains."

Fang Yuan also managed to probe Heavenly Court's foundation.

They had a mysterious method to cause the resonance of Spring Autumn Cicada!

Fang Yuan had not expected this.

But now, thinking about it, Fang Yuan could understand that the time path formation in ambush was not targeted at him, but Red Lotus' true inheritance instead.

And Spring Autumn Cicada was the key to opening Red Lotus' true inheritance.

How could Heavenly Court not research Red Lotus' true inheritance using Spring Autumn Cicada as the starting point? Even though they could not refine Spring Autumn Cicada, they could mimic it to a great extent.

"Li Huang, Qing Ye…" New rank eight Gu Immortals showed up.

Heavenly Court ruled Central Continent and could take in rank eight Gu Immortals from the ten great ancient sects as new members. From time to time, a few experienced experts would wake up from the immortal graveyard.

Having been created since the Remote Antiquity Era, all the way until now, nobody knew how deep Heavenly Court's foundation truly was.

Precisely with such foundations, during the five hundred years of Fang Yuan's previous life, Heavenly Court ruled Central Continent and fought against four other regions, for a long time, they held the advantage and even many super clans were destroyed.

Perhaps because of this, even though Spectral Soul managed to defy heaven, he did not dare to attack Heavenly Court directly, he continued to lurk and infiltrate it slowly.

"And those three Immortal Gu Houses… no, the one I destroyed earlier did not lose many Immortal Gu, even if they were destroyed, Heavenly Court could still refine it. I am afraid that next time, I will have to face four or more Immortal Gu Houses!"

Rank eight time path Gu Immortals were not easily found, even for Heavenly Court.

But time path Immortal Gu Houses could be assembled using parts of other Immortal Gu Houses, or using Immortal Gu that various Gu Immortals had in their possession or inventory.

After assembling these time path Immortal Gu Houses, Heavenly Court could place a large number of Gu Immortals from different paths inside, allowing them to seal off the entire River of Time.

Any plan of luring the enemy away would not work.

Heavenly Court was the number one grotto-heaven in the five regions, there was no concerns over its safety. Even if Fang Yuan attacked Heavenly Court directly, not only would he be unable to find the entrance, even if he got in, he would incur Heavenly Court's wrath, a few rank eight great experts from the immortal graveyard could wake up and take his life.

And if Fang Yuan attacked the ten great ancient sects, he would not be able to topple Heavenly Court's rule either, and it was extremely risky to do so. After all, they had the wisdom path great expert Fairy Zi Wei.

Fang Yuan's gaze was cold as ice, he knew clearly that to find Red Lotus' true inheritance, he would need to face off against Heavenly Court!

The more defenses Heavenly Court placed in the River of Time, the more important Red Lotus' true inheritance was, and the greater Fang Yuan's hope to destroy fate Gu rested in it.

"I need to be fast!"

Heavenly Court had all sorts of methods, they might find Red Lotus' true inheritance before him. Thus, he needed to get past their layers of defense into the stone lotus island before Heavenly Court succeeds, and obtain the most crucial things left by Red Lotus Demon Venerable.

As for what they were, Fang Yuan had no idea, even Heavenly Court might not know.

Guarding the River of Time was an open scheme by Heavenly Court, because they had the tactical advantage, they were not afraid that Fang Yuan would not come.

Fate Gu was about to recover, Fang Yuan needed to get past Heavenly Court and obtain Red Lotus' true inheritance to have a chance of destroying Fate. Even if he had to take huge risks, even if he had to risk his life, even though there was an ambush, he had to go!

"There are no special tactics or shortcuts, I need to raise my strength and continue to grow, surpassing Heavenly Court's defenses to break through these obstacles and obtain Red Lotus' true inheritance!"

Once Fang Yuan achieves this goal, he would have the qualification and ability to continue challenging Heavenly Court.

Chapter 1635: Logistics

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

Mini Western Desert.

All the surroundings were covered in a snow-white color. Fang Yuan's time path clone traveled here as he grabbed a handful of sand, looking at it.

The sand particles were all clear as crystal or ice, having a feeling of coldness in them.

Right now, the skies were bright and sunny, Mini Western Desert was quite a warm place, but this desert was very cool and refreshing.

Fang Yuan's clone put a bit of snow-white sand into his mouth, after his saliva came into contact, it melted and gave off a salty taste.

This was salt sand.

In human history, salt sand had a very long story.

A million years ago, during the Olden Antiquity Era, even though humans created Heavenly Court, the other four regions were still filled with strong variant human forces, they enslaved and suppressed humanity.

In Western Desert, there was a human city, it was ostracized and suppressed by the variant humans.

The variant humans joined up and pretended to be bandits, robbing all of the caravans that tried to head to the human city. As time passed, the human city lacked essential resources and was slowly unable to survive.

The human city lord feared for the safety of his people, he had to seek help from a variant human group, marrying his beloved daughter to them in exchange for peace.

The city lord's daughter knew what was more important, for the sake of the humans in the city, she sacrificed herself.

The group soon set off from the city, escorted by the human city lord himself.

While traveling in the desert, they met an old man who had fainted.

The old man was heavily injured and was on the verge of death, his entire body was covered in abscesses, the smell was repulsive. The city lord saw that he was a human, he quickly saved him and gave the old man some clean water.

The old man woke up slowly, he said to the city lord: "Oh city lord, since you saved me, why don't you provide me some more help, give me your robe and steed so that I can leave on my own."

The city lord's subordinates started to laugh, the clothes were so precious, how could they give them to such a lowly beggar?

But the city lord waved his hand: "The value of a robe cannot match a person's life. I have other clothes with me, you can have this. But my steed can only be ridden by a strong Gu Master, if I give it to you, I will be causing you harm."

Saying so, the city lord gave his robe as well as a large amount of water and food to the old man.

Next, the city lord ordered his men to bring over a mild tempered camel to the old man.

The old man sighed deeply: "City lord, I have long heard of your kind reputation, it is truly not a lie. Since you want to do a good deed, why don't you help me fully. The abscesses on my back have been troubling me for years, only a virgin girl who is born in the yin year, yin month and yin day[1] can heal me by using her mouth to burst them."

Just as the old man said that, the city lord's subordinates started to rebuke in anger, they wanted to kill this old man.

The city lord was a little angry, because everyone knew that his daughter was a virgin girl born in the yin year, yin month and yin day.

The city lord said: "Old man, stop making fun of me. Even though I am a city lord, I am also a pitiful father. I love my daughter, but I have no choice but to send her to the vicious feathermen, and let her become their slave concubine."

"Father, if my sacrifice can save the entire city, I will accept that fate." At this time, the city lord's daughter arrived. The clamor had drawn her attention, she understood the situation from the description of others.

She walked towards the old man as she nodded: "Old sir, let me see your abscesses."

"You are willing to heal my injury?" The old man asked.

"Yes. Even though I am the city lord's daughter and everyone says I am of noble blood, how noble can I truly be?" The city lord's daughter smiled bitterly: "Only when the entire human race is noble can our statuses truly rise, I have no hope left, I am going to be a slave concubine of the variant humans. In that case, why shouldn't I save you? We humans are too weak now, the recovery of one person is better than nothing."

The city lord and the others heard her words and felt very moved, they did not stop her.

The abscesses on the old man's back were ugly and disgusting, they were filled with pus and had an overbearing smell, people would want to puke upon seeing them.

The city lord's daughter was slightly dazed, but she held in her disgust and used her teeth to burst the abscesses on the old man's back.

Once they burst, a white-silver liquid flowed out.

The liquid landed on the desert and emitted a thick fragrant smell, making the caravan group feel refreshed mentally.

The old man's body vanished, only his voice was left, he said: "Oh city lord, you are a person worthy of my help. Humans cannot just rely on Gu Immortals, you Gu Masters are the hope of the future. I will entrust this desert to you, make good use of it."

The city lord and the rest realized at this moment, the old man was a human Gu Immortal, they quickly knelt on the ground.

And this desert was changed by the white-silver liquid, becoming the snow-white salt sand. After obtaining this huge desert, the city lord sold the salt sand as edible salt, he did not lack revenue and managed to revive his city, becoming stronger in time.

Currently, salt sand was no longer a unique product of Western Desert, it was available in all five regions.

Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had salt sand too, he had obtained it from annexing a Southern Border Gu Immortal's immortal aperture.

After inspecting it, Fang Yuan's clone gained a deeper understanding of the desert, he returned in satisfaction.

"Right now in treasure yellow heaven, Heavenly Court has started to sell silver dragonfish. They must have gotten the method to produce it from Spectral Soul, in time, golden dragonfish will also appear in the market."

Fang Yuan's dragonfish business was feeling a huge impact.

In the short term, because he had obtained immense market share, his dragonfish still provided huge profits. But he definitely would gradually lose his profits to Heavenly Court.

But it was not a problem, after annexing the Southern Border immortals, the sovereign immortal aperture had gained over ten blessed lands, and even a grotto-heaven.

Forget about salt sand, it was an ordinary Gu material. But he gained a lot of immortal material resources, there were at least five to six resource points that could match the dragonfish business, Xia Cha grotto-heaven's year essence pool was one of them.

Thus, Fang Yuan was still earning a lot of profits, his immortal essence stones were accumulating at a faster pace than before.

Due to his development in the past, he did not lack any food production for the feeding of his Immortal Gu. Even though he obtained some Immortal Gu as loot from battle, he also obtained the respective Gu Immortals' immortal apertures, he completely moved their resource points over to himself.

"The feeding of Immortal Gu still has some flaws, but that is not an issue." The time path clone looked at the salt sand desert one last time before using Fixed Immortal Travel.

This salt sand desert was the second last resource point that he visited.

At the next moment, Fang Yuan's clone went to City Well.

Inside City Well, there was already a sizable group of hairy men.

These hairy men were obtained from the immortal apertures of the Southern Border Gu Immortals, almost all of them had a certain number of hairy men raised to refine mortal Gu.

Hairy man slaves were the most popular ones in treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan gathered the hairy men in all these immortal apertures and placed them into City Well to live.

Currently, raising hairy men was most helpful to Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan gave some dream path Gu recipes as well as cultivation methods to these hairy men. Their task was to enter their own dream realms and gather dream path materials to refine dream path mortal Gu for Fang Yuan's use.

Fang Yuan's unravel dream killer move expended a lot of dream path mortal Gu.

Earlier, Fang Yuan was exploring dream realms and used up all of his accumulated dream path mortal Gu. If not for these hairy men refining dream path mortal Gu to replenish his supply, Fang Yuan might not have been able to explore all of his dream realms.

Fang Yuan's clone came to City Well as the sky turned dark, even though there was no sun or moon, it seemed to be evening currently.

After Fang Yuan became rank eight, the blessed land became a grotto-heaven, it had astronomical changes now. Because the sovereign immortal aperture had a lot of time path resources, the changes was very precise, almost like the five regions.

Fang Yuan's clone was about to find out the situation of the hairy men when his body froze, a bright light flashed across his eyes: "The main body has already found the location of the Five Xiang's seal!"

Fang Yuan rested in his eerie fire cave for a while before leaving and going to white heaven.

His immortal aperture was well operated, the logistics were clear and orderly, he did not need to waste time in recuperating, his immortal essence storage rose continuously.

He did not want to waste time, he headed to white heaven immediately. Right now, the Five Xiang's seal was opening, the ancient bet was undergoing again!

[1] Something to do with the Chinese calendar. Back

Chapter 1636: Demon King!

Immemorial white heaven.

A tall gatehouse suddenly emerged in the sky that was originally empty.

The gatehouse had a tall roof and two statues at the side of the gate. There was a huge plaque above the gate, writing the words 'Five Xiang's Bet Entrance'.

The entire gatehouse seemed to be made of bronze, it radiated a majestic aura. Initially, it was only a phantom image, but as time passed, it became solid and clearer.

Qi clan had six Gu Immortals in total, they were all standing outside the gatehouse now, waiting for it to materialize entirely.

The leader was an old Gu Immortal, he had a thin body but strong spirits, his eyes radiated with brilliance, he stood up straight like a spear. He was Qi clan's first supreme elder Qi Fa.

On his left was Qi clan's second supreme elder Qi Cai, he stroked his beard as he said: "I have experienced many openings of the seal, but this time, I feel very impatient, I almost cannot wait!"

Third supreme elder Qi Jin laughed: "This bet has been going on for thousands of years, we are finally going to end it today. As descendants of Qi clan, we can proudly face our ancestors, we are the eventual victors of this bet!"

As they spoke, the gatehouse formed fully, a huge area of clouds gathered to hold up this gatehouse.

The door started to shine in five colors, representing the strength of the Five Xiangs.

First, red light shined down, causing the clouds to turn bright red.

This was Xue Xiang's Xue clan, because they cultivated blood path, they had been wiped out. Thus, after the red light shined around the place, it faded away.

Next was yellow light.

It was Chi Xiang's Chi clan, even though they had descendants, because they lived in the immortal apertures of their ancestors and did not work hard, they were living like livestock, not a single Gu Immortal emerged from among them.

Next, a brown light appeared.

Ni Xiang's Ni clan had Gu Immortals in the past, even though the numbers were small, they were all elites. Especially Ni Er, someone deduced that his refinement path attainment level was at the point of quasi-supreme grandmaster! He was the one who fused Immortal Gu into the bloodline of Ni clan members, he wanted to assist his descendants but right now, Ni clan's villages were controlled by Qi clan, they could not win.

After the brown light came white light.

"Our turn." Qi Cai became very alert, he could not wait anymore.

"Let's go." Qi Fa said with a firm tone, he led the four Gu Immortals behind him as they went to the gatehouse, bathing in the white light.

The white light flickered for a moment as it got stronger, sweeping around the five Qi clan Gu Immortals' bodies as it returned to its original intensity, continuing to shine.

But Qi clan's Gu Immortals were all here already.

Without any additional descendant of Qi Xiang, the white light faded away.

There was a white light spiraling above the heads of the five Qi clan Gu Immortals, they had passed the test of the Five Xiang's seal, they were qualified to enter for the bet.

"Bai clan is the last one." Qi Jin spoke, unable to conceal his nervousness.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals were all above the clouds, they had not entered the door yet, they were alert and looked around.

They knew of the existence of Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing had inherited Bai Xiang grotto-heaven, she even learned the immortal killer move Bai Xiang, displaying great power in a few battles.

Heavenly Court had exposed intel on Fang Yuan, that involved the Shadow Sect members as well. Even though Bai Ning Bing was not part of Shadow Sect, her information was also exposed.

Even though Qi clan was secluded and did not mix with the circles of Gu Immortals, they still had their collection of information regarding the outside world.

Blue light shined for a while but nobody showed up, it was about to weaken and fade away.

Qi Cai let out a breath of air: "Good, Bai Ning Bing did not show up. Our Qi Cai will definitely win…. hmm!"

He had just spoken when two figures approached at a rapid speed, in the blink of an eye, they arrived in front of the gatehouse.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals looked over and saw a boy and a girl.

The girl had silvery hair that flowed down to her waist. Her pale blue dragon eyes emitting a cold aura to the outside world. Her skin was white as snow, her expression was cold, her beauty was simply divine. And the most eye-catching thing was the pair of small coral-like dragon horns on her forehead.

Seeing this female immortal, Qi clan's Gu Immortals all thought of a name — Bai Ning Bing.

"Bai Ning Bing came after all, damn it!"

"Who is that beside her?"

Qi Jin first noticed Bai Ning Bing before turning his gaze towards the other Gu Immortal.

This Gu Immortal was a young man with similarly long hair that was black and smooth, he had a sharp and tall nose, his face was extremely exquisite, his eyes were deep like the abyss, resembling the darkness that existed since the beginning of time, able to devour anything in its way.

Seeing this young looking Gu Immortal, Qi Jin shook like he had been hit by lightning, his heart turned cold, he gulped as he said in a hoarse voice with great difficulty: "Fang, Fang Yuan…"

He was already the most composed one, the Qi clan Gu Immortals around him were shaking, their legs were trembling as they had sweat pouring down their foreheads.

Bai Ning Bing was Fang Yuan's henchman, the five regions' Gu Immortals knew that.

If Bai Ning Bing appeared and participated in the Five Xiang's bet, Fang Yuan was likely to come too.

Qi clan had known this and were mentally prepared for it before coming here.

However!

When Fang Yuan truly appeared in front of them, they found that their mental preparations were all in vain. Fear, panic, chaos, all sorts of emotions filled their hearts, they felt like they had fallen into an icy river.

This was Fang Yuan!

He had been reborn using Spring Autumn Cicada.

Refining an Immortal Gu on Three Kings Mountain as a mortal, snatching Hu Immortal blessed land from the Central Continent ten great ancient sects.

He went to Northern Plains and destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, nobody knew how great his gains were.

He inherited a true inheritance of Thieving Heaven and cooperated with Lang Ya blessed land and the other variant humans, becoming a traitor of humans.

He disguised as Wu Yi Hai and deceived Wu Yong like a fool.

During the dream realm battle, he toyed with the entire righteous path of Southern Border and became the leader of Shadow Sect.

Southern Border's righteous path chased after him and Heavenly Court hunted him, but he remained free and got stronger and stronger.

At the regional wall, he fought against the rank eight Gu Immortal Thunder Ghost True Monarch as a rank seven and pummeled her, leading to a fall in Heavenly Court's reputation.

When Lang Ya blessed land was invaded by Heavenly Court, he stole Fixed Immortal Travel and left freely!

Several months ago, he ambushed Southern Border's righteous path and kidnapped many Southern Border Gu Immortals, extorting all the super forces.

Not long ago, Heavenly Court had distributed the intel in treasure yellow heaven, the battle in the River of Time had been exposed. The entire world of the five regions was shocked! Fang Yuan had become a rank eight Gu Immortal silently, obtaining killer moves like spring scissors, summer fan, and five finger fist heart sword, most amazingly, he even had the long lost method, time cutting edge.

Seeing that his intel was exposed, Fang Yuan returned the favor and exposed all of Heavenly Court's methods as well.

The Gu Immortal world was in a huge commotion!

Heavenly Court's foundation and methods were shocking.

But the scarier thing was, Fang Yuan managed to escape regardless.

Heavenly Court had set up a super time path formation in the River of Time, there were multiple rank eights and many Immortal Gu Houses, but they could not do anything to Fang Yuan!

Even though Fang Yuan lost, in fact running away like a dog, after this battle was exposed, his reputation soared and left a deep impression in everyone's hearts.

Not only because of his schemes and ferocity, but also due to his opponent being Heavenly Court.

It was created since the Remote Antiquity Era, Heavenly Court which had three million years of history and had withstood the multiple invasions of various Demon Venerables, the number one human force created since the beginning of human history!

After so long, this Heavenly Court could actually do nothing to a demonic path Gu Immortal?!

This was a really rarely seen situation.

Even throughout the entire history of Heavenly Court, it was rarely seen.

Countless Gu Immortals and super forces were watching, waiting to see how Heavenly Court would capture Fang Yuan. How long could Fang Yuan really last?

Because of all these emotions, Fang Yuan's reputation was at its peak.

Rank seven Fang Yuan could resist rank eight.

Rank eight Fang Yuan was the king of demonic immortals, shaking the world!

He had grown like a shooting star, the speed was simply unthinkable. This meteor was currently like the blazing sun, he was bright and dazzling, countless people could not even look up at him.

Demon King Fang Yuan!

Qi clan's Gu Immortals started trembling even more fiercely, Fang Yuan's mere entrance had already intimidated all these people.

His demonic might was unstoppable.

Chapter 1637: He Cheated!

"Everyone, don't panic." Qi Fa said in a dry voice. His tall body was like a bamboo in the wind, wavering slightly.

Nobody laughed.

Qi clan had three rank seven and two rank six Gu Immortals, they were not Fang Yuan's match even if they joined up. They were meat on the chopping block, they were completely defenseless.

After Qi Fa spoke, he mustered his courage and continued: "We have already obtained the acknowledgement of the gatehouse, we can explore that grotto-heaven, we are also protected by the gatehouse. If Fang Yuan wants to kill us, he will need to pass the gatehouse, but if he destroys it, he will break the rules of the bet and would not reach the other side."

Qi Fa's words calmed everyone down.

Fang Yuan looked at Qi Fa with slight surprise as he smiled, praising: "He is quite smart."

Qi Fa's words were said to Qi clan's Gu Immortals, but was also meant for Fang Yuan. Qi clan was able to become the eventual winner of the Five Xiang's bet, it was not without reason. These last years, Qi clan had developed while suppressing or enslaving the other four clans, they also kept a low profile and hid themselves deeply. Even Southern Border's righteous path did not know or attempt to find the Five Xiang's treasure, this was due to Qi clan's abilities.

But no matter how amazing they were, against Fang Yuan, they were doomed to fail.

Fang Yuan's smile was terrifying in their eyes, his pearly white teeth were like sharp daggers aiming at them.

Fang Yuan took a look at Qi clan's Gu Immortals before looking over at Bai Ning Bing.

Both of them had already negotiated earlier, Bai Ning Bing nodded at Fang Yuan before flying towards the gatehouse.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals were slightly stirred, but they could do nothing but watch.

Once Bai Ning Bing entered the blue light, this icy light shook for a moment before stabilizing.

Fang Yuan nodded to himself, he was afraid earlier that Bai Ning Bing's dragonman status would affect it, after all, dragonmen were variant humans and were not traditional humans. But now, it seemed that the gatehouse only cared about Bai Ning Bing's bloodline, regardless of her status as human or variant human.

After a few breaths of time, Bai Ning Bing gained the acknowledgement of the gatehouse and was sent up into the clouds by a formless and mild force.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals had flickering gazes, they all showed a look of regret.

"It seems that Bai Ning Bing is not under Fang Yuan's enslavement, otherwise, the gatehouse would not acknowledge her."

"It is a pity…"

"Damn it, Bai Ning Bing was allowed to enter the world beyond the gatehouse too!"

Bai Ning Bing was found by Old Man Yan Shi last time, but she was never enslaved, all they did was cooperate.

After joining Fang Yuan, Bai Ning Bing was not targeted by Fang Yuan's enslavement methods either.

This was all due to this gatehouse.

Bai Ning Bing landed on the cloud and inspected the area, before saying to Fang Yuan: "Getting onto the clouds would be the same as getting the gatehouse's acknowledgement, Gu Immortals cannot fight each other here."

"Okay." A bright light flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes, seeing his following actions, Qi clan's Gu Immortals all gasped in shock.

Fang Yuan actually flew towards the blue light.

The blue light flickered for a moment before stabilizing.

Even though Fang Yuan was in his original appearance, he had activated immortal killer move familiar face already. He had modified this move, adding in blood path Immortal Gu to disguise his own bloodline. Initially, he had used this against Wu clan, disguising as Wu Yi Hai and mixing into the righteous path.

But before Fang Yuan got happy, the four other lights appeared on the gatehouse.

These four lights represented the power of the other four Xiangs.

Fang Yuan was slightly surprised, earlier, he had allowed Bai Ning Bing to enter first in order to inspect the blue light. After he flew in, he managed to deceive the blue light, but to think that the other four Xiangs unleashed their power.

Boom!

The gatehouse shook, Fang Yuan was pushed out of the light by a strong force.

"Familiar face cannot deceive it?" Fang Yuan's heart shook slightly.

Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs!

This strong force that had once taken leadership of Southern Border's Gu Immortal world had displayed its immense power.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals all sighed in huge relief, great joy appeared on their faces.

Fang Yuan's actions were simply too shocking, but this result was the best for them.

"So close, Fang Yuan could not get in!"

"We have hope! This way, Fang Yuan is kept outside, we only need to deal with Bai Ning Bing."

"Her Bai Xiang killer move is troublesome, but our Qi Xiang true inheritance is not weak either."

Fang Yuan focused as he looked at the gatehouse.

Indeed, he had underestimated the gatehouse. Or rather, Shadow Sect and Bai Ning Bing's information was not sufficient regarding this gatehouse.

To deceive it, familiar face was not enough.

Fang Yuan did not want Bai Ning Bing to explore it alone.

She was unreliable, and even if she was reliable, she could not deal with Qi clan's Gu Immortals alone.

Even though Fang Yuan had encountered an obstacle earlier, his determination to get in had not wavered.

"Qi Xiang, Bai Xiang, Xue Xiang, Ni Xiang, Chi Xiang, these are the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs. This gatehouse was created by all five of them, their power was fused into one."

Fang Yuan went into rapid contemplation.

Qi Xiang, Bai Xiang, Xue Xiang, Ni Xiang, and Chi Xiang; they were in qi path, ice path, blood path, earth path, and food path respectively.

Fang Yuan had high attainment in blood path and earth path, he was confident.

In terms of food path, even though his attainment level was not high, Fang Yuan had Spectral Soul's true inheritance, it contained the original food path inheritance in this world. With such a foundation, Fang Yuan had an immensely deep amount of information to work with.

His qi path and ice path attainment levels were very low. But ice path was not a problem, he had Bai Ning Bing's Bai Xiang true inheritance that was used to deceive the blue light already.

"So, my only obstacle is Qi Xiang's power." Divine brilliance flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes.

Fang Yuan did not have qi path attainment level or sufficient qi path inheritances, because it was already on the decline for a long time.

"No issue, I have the light of wisdom."

Fang Yuan wanted to use the light of wisdom to force his way through!

Qi clan's Gu Immortals conversed.

"What is he doing?"

"He seems to be deducing… didn't Heavenly Court announce it, this demon has very extraordinary wisdom path methods."

"Hehe, it is useless, how can he deduce the Five Xiang's arrangements in such a short time?"

Qi clan's Gu Immortals were very confident about this.

They had tried to break the power of the Five Xiangs long ago, but they had no success. This was the failure of generations of Gu Immortals that had tried time and time again.

They had failed too many times against the Five Xiang's seal, how could Fang Yuan possibly succeed?

"Or maybe Fang Yuan's wisdom path methods are above us. But he is simply dreaming if he wants to deduce it now. This difficulty is like deducing an unknown immortal killer move that he has just seen for the first time in battle, he needs to deduce and unravel it. He is too naive!" Qi Fa shook his head, as he said that, his courage appeared again, his fear was fading.

Boom!

At the next moment, Fang Yuan attacked the gatehouse.

The gate shook intensely, the expressions of Qi clan's Gu Immortals also changed.

"This, this, this!"

"The demon attacked, he actually attacked the gatehouse. He wants to destroy the teleportation entrance, does he not want to enter?"

"He failed the deduction so he got angry instead?!"

Bam bam bam…

As Fang Yuan attacked fiercely, the entire gatehouse started to shake. Qi clan's Gu Immortals also shook as their footing became unstable, they were like candles in the wind.

Shock and fear was shown on their faces, some even began to tremble.

Once the gatehouse gets destroyed, they would lose their protection, it would be up to Fang Yuan whether he wants to kill or capture them.

"It must hold against him!" Qi clan's Gu Immortals were all praying in their hearts.

Fang Yuan gradually stopped attacking.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals breathed roughly, they were all wet with sweat. The feeling of almost dying was too terrible, they had never been so nervous.

But eventually, the gatehouse still remained standing.

"The demon did not succeed, great!" Qi Jin cheered, while the other Qi clan Gu Immortals had joyful expressions on their faces.

Fang Yuan glanced at them as he showed a mocking smile: "Oh? Why do you think I stopped?"

Saying so, he activated an immortal killer move, there was no flashy light or commotion, his entire body's aura underwent a profound and mystical change.

Next, Fang Yuan landed and bathed in the blue light, easily gaining its acknowledgement and landing beside Bai Ning Bing.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals were all dumbfounded, some opened their mouths and froze like statues.

Shock was expressed on their faces, some beliefs in their minds had been completely shattered by Fang Yuan's success!

"This, this demon actually succeeded!"

"This must be a dream! How can this be?"

"How could he succeed in such a short period of time?"

Qi clan's Gu Immortals felt incredibly confused, before a strong cold feeling entered their hearts.

Fang Yuan's battle strength was ridiculously high, but his wisdom path attainment was even beyond the understanding of the Qi clan Gu Immortals.

Such a monster made even Heavenly Court without options. How could they deal with him?

"Gatehouse! Oh ancestor! This Fang Yuan is an outsider, he cheated!!" Qi Cai screamed, his face was full of fear and also anger.

But the gatehouse was silent, the Five Xiang's seal started to gather power. Soon, a strong aura emerged from the gatehouse as five lights started to shine brightly.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals saw this as their faces turned to despair.

They knew that the gatehouse had activated not because it exposed Fang Yuan's identity, but because the teleportation was beginning.

Chapter 1638: Ultimate Treasure of the Bet

The glaring light faded gradually.

Fang Yuan looked around, the environment had changed, he was already inside the small world past the gatehouse.

Bai Ning Bing was beside him, their distance was the same as before the teleportation.

Suddenly, Bai Ning Bing's expression changed, mysterious information was transmitted into her mind. She looked at Fang Yuan, seeing that he was completely expressionless, she hesitated for a moment before saying: "This is a public grotto-heaven, the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs had once donated a portion of their grotto-heavens each to form this place. The entire grotto-heaven has five segments, they are not directly connected to each other, only the most central mountain range is shared among the five. The treasure of this bet is at the center of the grotto-heaven, as long as a Gu Immortal is acknowledged by the gatehouse and is teleported inside here, they can go after the treasure. Along the way, the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs have also set up some resources, stronger experts can try to take them away, but it is recommended that they do not take everything, so as to allow the resources to grow again in the future."

Bai Ning Bing obtained this information, but Fang Yuan did not.

"It seems that even though I used the light of wisdom to deduce a killer move and disguise my identity, it was too roughly made in a rush."

Fang Yuan had a deep gaze as he looked afar: "This means that we are very far from Qi clan's Gu Immortals, and our areas are not connected. After disguising as a Bai Xiang descendant, I can only move about in this Bai Xiang grotto-heaven region?"

Fang Yuan wanted to try using Fixed Immortal Travel, but he did not know the appearance of Qi Xiang's territory.

He had once killed Qi clan's Qi Zai, but this person only became a Gu Immortal in the last thousand years, he did not enter this place or have any memories of it.

"According to my experience of getting past that gatehouse's inspection, this place has a very strict level of defense, space path methods are likely to be restricted. I am afraid that even if I use Fixed Immortal Travel, there is a low possibility of success."

Fang Yuan looked at the situation now, soon, he made up his mind.

"Let's go to the center!"

The entire public grotto-heaven had five areas, they were all connected to the center which contained the ultimate treasure of this bet. In that case, Fang Yuan would directly target it, he did not need to find Qi clan's Gu Immortals. Not only would he waste time, he might not be able to find them after all.

Once they got to the mountain range, they would meet Qi clan's Gu Immortals anyway.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing flew rapidly, crossing mountains and valleys.

Bai Xiang cultivated ice and snow path, this area was contributed by Bai Xiang grotto-heaven, thus even though there were mountains and valleys here, they were covered in thick snow, it was a field of white.

"Look there!" Bai Ning Bing suddenly said.

She was looking at a mountain, it was extremely steep and dangerous, at the peak, there were a hundred ice mirror snow lotuses growing.

This was a rank six immortal material containing ice path and wood path dao marks.

Near the snow lotus, there were many snow monsters and even desolate level snow monsters. If anyone went there and wanted to get the ice mirror snow lotuses, these snow monsters would stop them.

In fact, Fang Yuan had discovered it long ago, he only took a glance before flying away with Bai Ning Bing.

Even though these desolate level snow monsters were not his match, Fang Yuan did not want to waste time here, he headed straight for the center of the public grotto-heaven!

Ice mirror snow lotus, hundred years profound ice, thousand years profound ice, mystical frost water, heaven craft divine jade… along the way, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing saw many resource points, even though they were small to mid sized resource points, they had plentiful storage.

The deeper they went, the more valuable the resource points in the grotto-heaven. Of course, the beasts or plants defending them were also increasingly stronger. The Five Xiangs had specially created this arrangement to test their descendants.

Even though Fang Yuan's current strength was enough to sweep through everything, he ignored these small benefits in front of him, his mind was completely on the center of the mountain range.

Howl—!

Howling of beasts could be heard continuously as they emerged from the valleys to attack Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

They were jade frost antelopes.

The large ones were huge like palaces, the small ones were the size of three houses, their eyes were fully jade green in color without irises. Their horns curled upwards, even without wings, they could float and travel in the air. Each time they jumped, their hooves would emit white frost that would produce a clear chiming sound.

These jade frost antelopes appeared very peculiarly, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing's expressions quickly changed.

Fang Yuan snorted as he waved his hand, grabbing a fan that appeared out of nowhere.

Immortal killer move — Summer Fan!

Whoosh!

Summer fan whipped up strong winds that turned into tornadoes, they resembled winds but were actually filled with time path's power.

The beasts that approached with a great momentum were engulfed by the winds and rapidly died. Their corpses fell from the sky like dumplings, crashing onto the snow and creating loud noises.

This large group of jade frost antelopes died in an instant, not just that, Fang Yuan's fan also caused the snow mountain below him to crumble, creating a huge crater filled with rocks.

Fang Yuan flew down rapidly, slamming down as the rocks scattered.

He looked at a huge rock wall and inspected the aura on it, his expression turning cold.

There was a Gu formation here that Fang Yuan destroyed, it had the style of qi path.

"It seems that the restriction of five independent regions cannot restrict those Gu Immortals from Qi clan." Fang Yuan said to Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing nodded: "Understandable, they have already been coming here so many times, they must have a deep understanding of the place. A lot of the Five Xiangs' restrictions cannot stop them anymore. This also means that our journey is not going to be smooth."

Fang Yuan smiled coldly: "Qi clan's Gu Immortals are trying to obstruct us, they must be trying to delay for time to obtain the treasure first. We will not stay here, we will move rapidly."

The two continued to fly, along the way, as Bai Ning Bing had expected, many beast groups obstructed them.

But these beast groups were all slaughtered easily by Fang Yuan's methods, they could barely delay his advancement.

"Fang Yuan's methods are truly terrifying! Our beast tides are simply thin as paper!"

"No, he is simply killing them like killing ants, this is too scary."

"They are coming, they are near the central mountain range!"

"Don't panic, there is a layer of defense at the mountain range, there is an immemorial desolate beast there."

"The defenses were broken through, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing are arriving!"

Qi clan's Gu Immortals continued to converse, the atmosphere was tense, when Fang Yuan arrived, Qi clan's Gu Immortals were all panicking, their nervousness could be felt from afar.

The area that stored the treasure was very obvious, Fang Yuan could see it the moment he entered the central mountain range.

At the peak of the highest mountain, there was a palace, it was decorated in the same style as the gatehouse.

This was an Immortal Gu House!

Fang Yuan successfully got into the Immortal Gu House, he saw that at the center of the hall, there were five Qi clan Gu Immortals sitting around the ultimate treasure.

Next, his gaze turned towards the treasure of the bet.

This mysterious treasure was a white crane.

This white crane has one leg, it was covered in snow-white feathers that had no dust or dirt on it. Its long beak was red in color, its wings were tucked in as its eyes were shut tight.

Fang Yuan's brows furrowed rapidly, he could tell that this white crane was extraordinary.

It was not a real living being, it was also not an Immortal Gu, yet it emitted a rank nine aura!

"Amazing!" Fang Yuan laughed: "So the ultimate treasure of the bet is a rank nine killer move!"

Fang Yuan's laughter made the Qi clan Gu Immortals shudder.

They were fearful and also furious.

Qi clan had painstakingly protected this ultimate treasure of the Five Xiangs bet, but an outsider was here now trying to take it!

Qi clan has already treated the treasure as their possession. Fang Yuan wanted to take it, it meant that the great animosity between Qi clan and Fang Yuan was unresolvable.

Fang Yuan's gaze was cold, he did not speak, he pointed his finger as a sword light flew out, attacking a Qi clan Gu Immortal.

The five Qi clan Gu Immortals had instilled their wills into the white crane killer move, they did not move and allowed the sword light to approach them.

At the crucial moment, the five lights of the hall shined as the sword light was dispelled soundlessly.

"As expected." Fang Yuan felt no surprise.

This hall could gather the power of the entire public grotto-heaven, it was also the place where the Five Xiang's seal was the strongest. With this power overseeing the area, Fang Yuan and Qi clan's Gu Immortals could not fight each other.

Of course, Fang Yuan could act forcefully, but he had to suppress the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs' power, he would also cause great damage to the entire public grotto-heaven.

"No wonder Qi clan's Gu Immortals are not moving! But since they have the qualification to refine this ultimate treasure, so can I!" Bai Ning Bing had her own thoughts, she got close to the killer move.

Next, she mimicked the five Gu Immortals from Qi clan as she sent her own will into it.

The five Qi clan Gu Immortals had nervous expressions while Bai Ning Bing's body shook, she shouted to Fang Yuan: "Hurry up!"

Even without her reminder, Fang Yuan had already arrived beside her, he instilled his will into the killer move as he understood the entire situation.

At the same time, some information originating from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable also entered his mind!

"People of the future, I am Ben Jie Sun, also known as Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable."

"When exploring the immemorial white heaven, I by chance found a mysterious existence, it was like the heavenly spirit of a grotto-heaven. It was incredibly agile, I only managed to capture it after spending a lot of effort. After researching it, I found that it was incredibly profound, it involved the deepest mysteries of this world. It corresponded with the details in the latter half of <<The Legends of Ren Zu>>."

"I temporarily named it the natural heavenly spirit, it could not be brought out of white heaven or placed into one's grotto-heaven. It was filled with heaven's will that was constantly replenished at all times. Even I could not use my human will to refine it forcefully."

"After thinking long and hard, I found a solution, I forcefully condensed it and created an immortal killer move, I called it — Heaven Form!"

Chapter 1639: Contest Over Heaven Form

"Heaven form?!" Fang Yuan was surprised, but soon understood what happened.

Everything was clear now.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable was an otherworldly demon, he was skilled in space path and created theft path, he also had great ability in refinement path.

His entire life was dedicated to finding a way to leave the Gu Master world and return to his homeland.

He was the richest venerable, he searched for immortal materials all around the world and refined many Immortal Gu. He had also traveled the most, having explored almost the entire five regions and two heavens.

One day when exploring white heaven, he by chance found a mystical existence, after searching on it, he named it natural heavenly spirit.

Even with his Demon Venerable strength, he could not refine the natural heavenly spirit.

It was not hard to understand this.

According to Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's words, this natural heavenly spirit could not be brought out of immemorial white heaven, and inside white heaven, it was replenished by heaven's will endlessly. When Gu Immortals refine Immortal Gu, they have to use their own will to get rid of the wild will in the Immortal Gu, eventually refining it into their tool.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable wanted to refine the natural heavenly spirit, even though the steps were different, in essence it was the same. The Demon Venerable's will was strong, but against the natural heavenly spirit filled with heaven's will, that was constantly replenished, he could not succeed.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable failed but was not dejected, man was the spirit of all living beings, he found a method, that was to combine the heavenly spirit with other Gu worms to form a rank nine immortal killer move.

This made Fang Yuan think of the ghostly concealment killer move that he had, it was also a rank nine killer move. It was paired with divine concealment, even though Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had used it long ago, these two moves still remained until now.

This seemed to be a specialty of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable.

The problem was, even if Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable found a way to turn the natural heavenly spirit into a rank nine immortal killer move heaven form, he could not manipulate or use it.

Because he did not manage to refine the natural heavenly spirit.

But this was part of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's plan, he knew that he could not refine the natural heavenly spirit in a short period of time, therefore he turned the heavenly spirit into an immortal killer move.

This way, the natural heavenly spirit would be replenished with heaven's will at a far lower rate.

After Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable created heaven form, he did not use it. Before he vanished mysteriously, he left behind many Thieving Heaven true inheritances, he did not forget heaven form either.

"Heaven form killer move has not been truly refined, I cannot complete it alone, it needs a long period of time and generations of wills to cleanse. One day, it will be truly refined by a Gu Immortal, by then, it would be usable."

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable also said that even though he left this killer move behind, it could not be controlled and was not a Thieving Heaven true inheritance, it needed more work from people in the future, it was only half a Thieving Heaven true inheritance.

Fang Yuan could deduce the future developments himself.

One day, when the Heaven Surveying Five Xiangs explored immemorial white heaven, they happened to find this half Thieving Heaven true inheritance.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had said it clearly already, this rank nine killer move could only be used by one person, because all Five Xiangs wanted it, they argued and did not manage to come to a consensus, due to their internal conflict, their group fell apart.

The Five Xiangs tried but just the five of them could not refine this killer move, eventually, they set up the bet and agreed to use this to decide the owner of the immortal killer move.

Time passed mercilessly, countless events occurred throughout the ages.

Eventually, the Five Xiangs died, generations of Gu Immortal descendants of the Five Xiangs appeared and disappeared. Until today, Qi clan obtained the decisive advantage, and after years of hard work by their predecessors, they were finally about to succeed.

But Fang Yuan interfered!

It was understandable why the Qi clan Gu Immortals were so furious and filled with hatred.

Since the first generation of the Five Xiangs, they had worked so hard throughout the ages, their efforts were finally about to bear fruit, and now, he was here to snatch it away!

How shameless!

Too shameless, too despicable!

These emotions were the fuel that Qi clan was using to face Fang Yuan at the moment.

Fang Yuan was only a rank eight Gu Immortal, they believed that as long as they obtained the rank nine killer move, they would be able to defeat Fang Yuan, or at least, make him wary of their battle strength, they would be able to negotiate.

Fang Yuan came to Bai Ning Bing's side as he instilled his will into the heaven form killer move.

Inside the heaven form killer move, there was a lump of stubborn heaven's will that remained steady as a fortress, having the greatest defense.

Below this heaven's will fortress were countless wills.

A vast sea of wills!

The bet had been undergone time and time again, a large number of Gu Immortals had left their wills behind. There were strong rank eight Gu Immortals like the Five Xiangs, there were also rank seven elites like Ni clan's Gu Immortal Ni Er.

Such an accumulation was not strange.

But what made Fang Yuan surprised was that these wills were not moving, they seemed dead like rocks, staying completely still.

Only these newly entered wills were moving around like dragons, fighting above the sea of wills.

Three of the five Gu Immortal wills of Qi clan went to deal with Bai Ning Bing's will. The remaining two attacked the heaven's will fortress at the top.

"That is the central area of the killer move heaven form, whoever refines it will become the owner of heaven form!"

"Demon Fang Yuan's will also came in!"

"Persevere, we cannot relax now, we are about to succeed."

"This is the hard work of our Qi clan after countless years, for this moment, we have sacrificed too much, we cannot let the outsider Fang Yuan win!!"

The Qi clan Gu Immortals conversed, they spurred each other on, their morale was at its peak.

Actually, they had no other choice, Fang Yuan's ruthless nature was known to all, if they did not manage to refine this rank nine killer move, they would definitely end up in pitiful states.

Without hesitation, Fang Yuan's will charged up.

His will gathered into a lump and moved like a soaring dragon.

The wills of three Qi clan Gu Immortals cooperated, but they could not resist Fang Yuan's fierce assault, they were retreating continuously.

They were just qi path Gu Immortals after all, while Fang Yuan had a huge advantage in this aspect.

"Persevere, regardless of the price we have to pay, we need to stall for time!"

"Quickly attack and take down the central control area!"

"As long as we can obtain this killer move, we might be able to kill this supreme demon king and eradicate him for good. We might be able to obtain a large number of venerable true inheritances…"

"Even if we cannot stop him, we need to expend his will so that he cannot take down the heaven's will fortress at the top."

Chapter 1640: Traitor Bai

Qi clan's Gu Immortals were all standing together, resisting Fang Yuan desperately and courageously while feeling anxiety, fear and panic.

Fang Yuan frowned, he found that his will could not be instilled endlessly, after reaching a certain amount, he could not send any more.

Furthermore, when his will was instilled, his main body could only watch as the wills fought. Thus, his vast number of wisdom path methods could not work here.

Heaven form was rank nine, while Fang Yuan's wisdom path methods were just rank eight at best. Even if they could affect the killer move heaven form, Fang Yuan did not want to try them, if he triggered the counterattack of the killer move, that would be a problem. Even if there was no counterattack, destroying heaven form would also make him lose the greatest treasure here.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals needed heaven form to deal with Fang Yuan and protect themselves. Fang Yuan also wanted heaven form greatly, because he needed more strength to deal with the obstacles from Heavenly Court in the River of Time.

Thus, both sides had to compete using the most basic form of attacking through their wills.

In this regard, Fang Yuan was deeply experienced. After suffering at the hands of Mo Yao, he had practiced tirelessly to remove this weakness, it was his advantage now.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals were not Fang Yuan's match, but they had strength in numbers, their cumulative will was much greater than Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing.

As time passed, Fang Yuan's advantage grew, but he could not turn this advantage into victory. The Qi clan Gu Immortals were resisting him stubbornly, they were outperforming themselves.

In fact, Fang Yuan still had one worry left, it was Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing had once backstabbed him, she was an unstable element in this situation.

But thankfully, the heaven's will fortress at the top was very strong and did not waver, no matter how Qi clan's Gu Immortals attacked it, there were no traces of it breaking down.

Fang Yuan started to feel troubled, at this rate, even if he got past or destroyed the Qi clan Gu Immortals' wills, he might not have enough will left to deal with the heaven's will at the center.

Time and again, Qi clan's wills retreated while Fang Yuan's will moved like a dragon, coiling around Qi clan's wills, encircling them.

Qi clan's wills were shocked, if Fang Yuan destroyed their encircled wills, they would be in deeper trouble, they would not be able to stop Fang Yuan from leaving.

Thus, the wills that had just dispersed gathered together again as they charged at Fang Yuan.

"Bai Ning Bing, block them." Fang Yuan rapidly ordered.

Bai Ning Bing's will was like an ice wall, it stabbed into the battlefield, but it defended Qi clan's wills as it started to attack Fang Yuan!

Qi clan's wills were greatly shocked, at the crucial moment, Bai Ning Bing had betrayed him.

Fang Yuan's will was caught off guard by Bai Ning Bing, he was very angry.

Qi clan's wills observed for a moment and became very happy, they attacked Fang Yuan from another direction.

Fang Yuan's will continued to reduce in size, he had to give up on taking down Qi clan's wills.

"Bai Ning Bing, you traitor, I will not forgive you!" Fang Yuan's will roared, but the outcome was decided, he had to escape with his remaining will.

"Fang Yuan, with your personality, after getting heaven form, won't you deal with me? I am the descendant of Bai Xiang, heaven form killer move is my fortuitous encounter. Hahaha!" Bai Ning Bing's will laughed maniacally: "This is a great chance, after defeating you here, my entire life will become dazzling and hopeful as a result."

Bai Ning Bing did not want to let Fang Yuan's will off, she chased after him.

Fang Yuan's will could only escape.

"What are you all waiting for? Come and help!" Bai Ning Bing's will roared at Qi clan's wills.

Qi clan's wills were also heavily damaged, after thinking for a bit, Qi Fa's will shouted: "Don't move, there might be a trap, let them fight it out."

Fang Yuan's will was attacked by Bai Ning Bing's will and was terribly damaged, it was much smaller than Bai Ning Bing's will now. Eventually, she encircled him and fought until he was completely exterminated.

"To think that the demon Fang Yuan would be the first to fall!"

"No matter how vigilant he was, he could not defend against an internal threat."

"Hahaha, this is the rise of our Qi clan, this is a great opportunity. Let's go, we must exterminate Bai Ning Bing's will too!"

Qi clan's wills attacked again, even though Bai Ning Bing's will resisted stubbornly, two fists could not rival four palms, she was eventually wiped out as well.

"We succeeded!"

"Heaven form is ours!!"

Qi clan's wills were drowning in joy, now that they had no enemies left, they gathered and attacked the heaven's will fortress.

Boom!

At once, an explosion occurred at the heaven's will fortress, a large amount of heaven's will gushed out like uncaged beasts, attacking Qi clan's wills.

All along, this heaven's will had been defensive in nature, Qi clan's wills were deceived and forgot that it could move freely.

Heaven's will's retaliation was a huge surprise to Qi clan's wills, they suffered huge losses.

"How can there be so much heaven's will?"

"Impossible!"

"Heaven's will is crafty, it deceived us of its strength, I am unresigned!"

"Quickly resist it, we cannot afford to lose!"

Qi clan's wills were determined and went all in, from a dangerous situation, they gradually stabilized it and eventually managed to gain the advantage over heaven's will, when there was little heaven's will left, the core was exposed, awaiting its new owner.

"We finally won!" A moment later, Qi clan's wills were about to cry from joy. They only had a bit of will left, but heaven's will was finally gone.

"I'm afraid not." Suddenly, Fang Yuan's will appeared again.

Qi clan's wills were shocked, they started shouting.

"You, you were already eliminated right?"

"Impossible! You already used up your will, normally, you will need a thousand years before you can send your will in again."

"Did you unravel this rank nine killer move? No, no way, this is a rank nine killer move originating from Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable!"

Fang Yuan's will snickered but he did not explain, he attacked.

Qi clan's wills were like tiny rabbits, Fang Yuan attacked them like a fierce tiger, easily getting rid of them without much obstruction.

And next, Fang Yuan's will replaced heaven's will and went into the core area.

He was the final victor!

Opening his eyes, he saw the five Qi clan Gu Immortals escaping in a panic.

Fang Yuan did not stop them, this Immortal Gu House and public blessed land had the Five Xiang's arrangements, they would definitely stop him if he attacked.

Bai Ning Bing stood by Fang Yuan's side motionlessly, she did not have any intentions of escaping.

Everything that happened was part of Fang Yuan's plan.

He purposely orchestrated a show, having Bai Ning Bing betray him. He wanted to deceive not just Qi clan's Gu Immortals, but also heaven's will.

Fang Yuan had much more experience against heaven's will than Qi clan's Gu Immortals. he deduced that heaven's will had a lot of battle strength remaining, even if he defeated Qi clan's wills, he would not be the match of heaven's will.

Thus, he purposely backed off and hid away a portion of his will.

Of course, Bai Ning Bing's will was truly wiped out. The advantage of this was that other than tricking Qi clan's Gu Immortals, he could prevent her from doing anything at the most crucial moment.

The wills of Qi clan's Gu Immortals were already weakened by Fang Yuan earlier, because they were facing huge problems and pressure, they were unable to see through Fang Yuan's plot.

It was difficult indeed.

When wills thought about things, they would be expended. The smaller the will, the less it could think. Qi clan's Gu Immortals also had to ensure that they had enough strength left to deal with heaven's will.

The outcome was as Fang Yuan predicted, he was the final winner.

Heaven form was under Fang Yuan's control, at this moment, he did not inspect, he turned to look at Bai Ning Bing with a deep gaze.

"Oh Bai Ning Bing… are you really not going to run?" Fang Yuan's eyes burst out with killing intent.

Bai Ning Bing's value had been squeezed out, she was not like Shadow Sect's members, she was not under Fang Yuan's control.

Since he obtained heaven form, it was time to settle this problem.

The atmosphere was tense, Fang Yuan's killing intent was rising.

They were about to fight at any moment.

Evidently, Fang Yuan was not someone Bai Ning Bing could defeat at the moment. Even though the killer move Bai Xiang was a powerful move that had once terrorized Southern Border's Gu Immortal world, Bai Ning Bing's cultivation level was too low now, her foundation was far weaker than Fang Yuan.

If they fought, Bai Ning Bing would die for sure!

Chapter 1641: Very Interesting

Facing Fang Yuan's immense killing intent, Bai Ning Bing smiled as she looked towards Fang Yuan straight in the eye, asking in return: "Why should I run?"

After pausing for a moment, she said: "Qi clan's Gu Immortals escaped, that is because they don't know you. We are both from Qing Mao Mountain, with my understanding of you, how could they escape? Hehe, since I cannot escape, what's the point of running? Not only will I not escape, on the contrary, I will join Shadow Sect."

Fang Yuan frowned: "I had thought of that, but your Bai Xiang killer move is too amazing, it can free you from almost any alliance agreement."

The uniqueness of Bai Xiang was that it turned the Gu Immortal into a unique existence, even a tiny fragment could regenerate and be reborn.

The essence of alliance agreements were information path dao marks, Bai Ning Bing could make use of Bai Xiang to self-mutilate and get rid of her information path dao marks, negating her alliance agreements.

Thus, Bai Xiang was also used for healing, to get rid of unwanted dao marks in the body.

"Indeed." Facing Fang Yuan's deep wariness, Bai Ning Bing laughed, not caring about her own safety: "But isn't that more exciting?"

Fang Yuan snorted, saying in displeasure: "I am not you, Bai Ning Bing."

Bai Ning Bing nodded, she stopped smiling as brilliance flashed in her dragon eyes: "Indeed, I have been pursuing excitement all along. This is why I admire you, Fang Yuan, your life is truly exciting, it is so thrilling! Every time you plot, every time you succeed, or even every time you fail, they are filled with excitement. Especially earlier when you were ambushed by Heavenly Court and had to escape like a dog, it was truly the most thrilling experience!"

"The other Shadow Sect members cannot understand my feelings. Some just want to save Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, some feel fear and panic, some feel immense pressure, but what I feel is excitement and thrill. The bigger the problems, the bigger the troubles, the more exciting life is, isn't that right?"

"Others might not know me, but I am sure that you understand me, right?"

Bai Ning Bing stared at Fang Yuan's eyes with a bright gaze.

Fang Yuan was silent.

Back then on Qing Mao Mountain, he had deduced that Bai Ning Bing was a true demon. He was not wrong, that was exactly who she was. To pursue the excitement of life, she could give up anything, even her life. The values and moral concepts of normal people, the complexities of love and hatred, they were all unrelated to her.

She was different from the norm, her world view was vastly different, she only walked on her own path. She followed her own desires, she did not care about life and death.

In fact, Bai Ning Bing and Fang Yuan were very similar, they were the same kind, only that they pursued different goals.

Fang Yuan pursued eternal life, he was willing to sacrifice anything including himself. Even if he failed and died along the way, he would feel happy and content, because he lived pursuing his dreams, he felt a sense of satisfaction and enjoyment towards life.

Bai Ning Bing said that Fang Yuan understood her, she was absolutely right, it was the same as how she understood Fang Yuan.

The saying goes, heroes admired each other, it was the same for demons.

Fang Yuan's killing intent gradually faded away.

His killing intent was only a facade, the truth was, he did not really have much killing intent.

Why should he kill Bai Ning Bing?

Fang Yuan's strength far surpassed Bai Ning Bing, her threat was very low to Fang Yuan.

Sometimes, when he saw Bai Ning Bing, Fang Yuan could see his own reflection. True demons like them were too rare, meeting one was a form of luck, it was a form of affirmation towards their goals.

Because of their similarity, they recognized each other, they acknowledged each other.

Thus, back then, when Bai Ning Bing gave up her life to save Fang Yuan, she said her final words — asking Fang Yuan to live in her place and witness the excitement of life. Bai Ning Bing had felt that Fang Yuan could take her place to a certain extent.

Sometimes, Fang Yuan thought about it, if he and Bai Ning Bing exchanged identities, would he have made the same choice as her?

"Hahaha." Bai Ning Bing suddenly raised her head and laughed: "I can give all of Bai Xiang grotto-heaven's resources to you. But I want the Gu worms from Bai Xiang's true inheritance, I am willing to join Shadow Sect because facing Heavenly Court is truly exciting! This was your excitement, but it will become mine as well."

"In that case, there are three possible outcomes." Bai Ning Bing squinted, excitement flashing in her eyes, there was a light of insanity.

"The first possibility, you get killed by Heavenly Court. With your strength, even if you get killed, it will be in an incredible manner, your struggle before death will definitely be a climax. By witnessing your death, it will be the greatest experience of my life."

"The second possibility, Heavenly Court gets defeated or even destroyed by you. That is definitely exciting beyond belief, the number one force of human history falling like a crashing meteor, it will create the greatest sparks in this world."

"And the third possibility, the one I anticipate the most, because it is the most thrilling! You and Heavenly Court get into a deadlock, both sides suffer losses. In that case, I will stay by your side, I will have the supreme chance to find an opportunity. I might even emerge as the victor, both you and Heavenly Court will become my stepping stones."

Fang Yuan looked at Bai Ning Bing calmly, he said with a cold and expressionless face: "If I kill you now, all three possibilities will vanish."

"Yes, yes…" Bai Ning Bing frowned, she became a little dejected, her gaze flickered and her tone became heavy: "That is true. If I die now, even though I will resist to the utmost, our strength is too vastly different, there will be little excitement in the battle."

"But if that is your choice, I will accept it." She smiled, shrugging: "I am just too weak, I have to accept that fate. This cruelty of life is also exciting, isn't it? Hehehe."

Death was not scary for Bai Ning Bing.

She was a lunatic, but also logical and calm. Such a person was the scariest.

But someone even scarier than her was standing right in front of her.

It was the demonic path overlord Fang Yuan who made both heaven's will and Heavenly Court helpless to deal with.

Fang Yuan smiled as he laughed "Very interesting."

Bai Ning Bing was a very interesting person.

Right now, Bai Ning Bing was weak and was subject to Fang Yuan's mercy, she did not try persuading him to spare her, she said the opposite, even exposing her own threat to Fang Yuan.

This was because she understood Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was a person who kept a clear mind, he had already analyzed the benefits and costs of keeping her life. Once he made up his mind, it was useless no matter what was said.

Even without Bai Ning Bing's words, Fang Yuan knew that he needed all the strength he could get to face Heavenly Court and obtain Red Lotus' true inheritance. Bai Ning Bing was a precious source of battle strength, even if she was given a chance to betray him, so what?

A blade was naturally able to harm oneself. But if he threw this blade away and fought empty handed, was that not a stupid move?

It was up to Fang Yuan's abilities to make good use of this blade and prevent her betrayal.

"If I am too useless and Bai Ning Bing's betrayal succeeds, I can only blame myself, isn't that right?"

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan laughed: "Oh Bai Ning Bing, you are truly someone I admire, I will not kill you now. Follow me, witness my failure or success. If I die at your hands, that will be quite a show. But now, display your worth to me, bring me the heads of Qi clan's Gu Immortals, and also… their Qi Sea grotto-heaven."

Chapter 1642: Blood Revenge

Inside rank nine killer move heaven form.

Fang Yuan's will moved like a dragon, coiling in the air as he charged down abruptly.

Rumble!

Fang Yuan's will descended like a meteor, crashing into the bottom of the sea of wills, exterminating a large amount of them in an instant.

However, this sea of will was truly huge, Fang Yuan's attack only destroyed a small portion of them.

"Even though I won and occupied the killer move's core area, this place is filled with the wills of the Five Xiangs' descendants. Only after I exterminate them all can I truly activate this rank nine killer move."

This sea of will was colossal. And the bigger problem was, these wills were affected by the rank nine killer move and were as sturdy as rocks. Many of Fang Yuan's methods could not work on them, under the influence of the rank nine killer move, he had a limited number of methods to use.

Fang Yuan suddenly had a thought as he instilled a new tide of will.

Swoosh swoosh swoosh!

The will gathered into swords as countless will swords shot down like rain, stabbing into the sea of wills and creating huge pits.

In a while, a layer of this sea of wills was eradicated.

Compared to the earlier will dragon, this rain of will swords had far more terrifying power.

Fang Yuan saw this and sighed deeply: "As expected of rank eight Immortal Gu Wisdom Sword!"

He had rank eight cultivation level now, he could use this Gu. Even though it was a sword path Immortal Gu, it was closely related to wisdom path.

Fang Yuan used it as the core to deduce a simple move that could summon a large amount of sword will.

Using these sword wills to attack the sea of wills was the most effective method that Fang Yuan had tried.

But if he did that, his investments would be very high. Wisdom sword Immortal Gu was a rank eight Gu, it expended white litchi immortal essence and the immortal killer move with it would cause a lot of immortal essence expenditure.

But Fang Yuan calculated and found that he could accept this expenditure.

After all, he was affluent, his immortal aperture management was a rising gold mine.

During the battle in the River of Time, even though Fang Yuan escaped and ruined Heavenly Court's plan of killing him, his losses were severe. The destruction of the incomplete Immortal Gu House was extremely painful to him, even now.

This incomplete Immortal Gu House was created by Fang Yuan after capturing many Southern Border Gu Immortals and obtaining their Immortal Gu, he went through transactions and negotiations with Southern Border's righteous path, eventually extorting enough Immortal Gu for the assembly.

Fang Yuan had spent a lot of effort to do this, even though he spent so much time on it, it was destroyed.

"I hope this heaven form killer move can be of use to me."

Fang Yuan was deeply anticipating what heaven form could bring to him.

For ordinary killer moves, Fang Yuan could investigate and deduce their abilities. But this killer move was rank nine, it was too profound, Fang Yuan could not comprehend it.

This was Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's creation, he was specialized in space path and theft path, even if this was not an offensive move, it had an incredible effect for sure.

Even though Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable did not explain anything about this move, Fang Yuan could deduce some things from other aspects.

Like Shadow Sect's attitude.

Shadow Sect's Old Man Yan Shi specially helped Bai Ning Bing for the sake of getting heaven form.

"Old Man Yan Shi was a wisdom path great expert, he might have found out something, this heaven form killer move must be very useful to Shadow Sect."

Fang Yuan was the current leader of Shadow Sect, this heaven form killer move was definitely going to be beneficial to him.

Other than getting rid of the sea of wills, Fang Yuan also broke the Five Xiang's seal and obtained the Immortal Gu House at the peak of the mountain, as well as this public grotto-heaven.

This grotto-heaven only opened once in a thousand years, it had abundant resources. Qi clan's Gu Immortals were too busy fleeing, they could not obtain any of these resources, so they all became Fang Yuan's resources.

Boom—!

The huge explosion tore Bai Ning Bing to pieces.

But at the next moment, her Bai Xiang form gathered again and charged at Qi clan's Gu Immortals.

Qi clan's Gu Immortals had ugly expressions, they saw how terrifying the killer move Bai Xiang was!

Bai Ning Bing had this move active, she was almost undying. Even so, right now, she was not fighting alone, Ying Wu Xie and Hei Lou Lan were also helping her.

Even though Fang Yuan wanted Bai Ning Bing to kill these Qi clan Gu Immortals, he knew her limits. She did not even have the most crucial immortal battlefield killer move.

Fang Yuan had already set up an immortal formation in ambush, ever since he captured the Southern Border righteous path immortals, he started to love this method.

Once Qi clan's Gu Immortals entered, they were stripped of their freedom by the immortal formation, they could not escape, they had to fight Bai Ning Bing.

"Ah—!" With a painful scream, the youngest Qi clan Gu Immortal was fatally injured by Bai Ning Bing and died.

"My turn." Ying Wu Xie was already prepared, he immediately moved and captured the Qi clan Gu Immortal's soul, trapping it in the formation.

The remaining Qi clan Gu Immortals shouted in anger as they retaliated fiercely.

Bai Ning Bing was broken into fragments again, but she revived in a few breaths of time, reforming into Bai Xiang again.

Even though there were many Qi clan Gu Immortals who had high battle strength, they all revealed expressions of despair now.

Because they knew that Bai Ning Bing could not be killed, while they were trapped here, they would eventually lose in this battle of attrition.

"What do we do?"

"Bai Ning Bing is too troublesome to deal with, and most importantly, this Fang Yuan is too vicious, he actually set this formation near the entrance of our Qi Sea grotto-heaven!"

Qi clan's Gu Immortals had been very vigilant but when they were near their base, they were captured.

They did not know that Fang Yuan had killed Qi Zai. Even though he did not enter the Five Xiang grotto-heaven, he knew the details of Qi Sea grotto-heaven.

This Qi Sea grotto-heaven was the immortal aperture of Qi Xiang in the past, after being placed in white heaven, it could not move anymore, it had stayed there all along.

Fang Yuan used this intel to set up the immortal formation secretly, managing to trap the Qi clan members.

"At this rate, we are bound to lose!"

"Stall! I don't believe that her Bai Xiang killer move is so strong, does it not have any cost or backlash?"

"Don't forget about Fang Yuan, if he gets here, we are not in the Immortal Gu House, the Five Xiang's seal cannot stop him."

"We cannot break out of the immortal formation, we need to let Qi Ping Su come out and cooperate with us to break this formation."

"No! Qi Ping Su is the only person left in the base, if he comes out, he will need to open the entrance, Shadow Sect would be able to use that chance."

"Fang Yuan might be nearby waiting for the grotto-heaven to open already, so that he can charge in!"

Fang Yuan did not come.

But his fearsomeness and craftiness was etched into everyone's hearts, the Qi clan Gu Immortals felt deep pressure and started to be flustered.

At the same time.

In Central Continent, a young man was standing quietly, looking at the Immortal Gu in front of him.

This young man had a mature and experienced expression, it showed that he had gone through many hurdles in his life.

This was none other than Gu Yue Fang Zheng.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng was originally going to be executed by Immortal Crane Sect, but Fang Yuan plotted and faked his death, making him live in Lang Ya blessed land.

Fang Zheng lived in a place where he was ostracized by hairy men, he had experienced a long period of wars and conflicts, being in danger at all times, he was also often in situations where his life was on the line.

After all of these experiences, he was no longer the same as before, he had truly matured.

After that, when Heavenly Court attacked Lang Ya blessed land, because of Gu Yue Fang Zheng's unique identity, he was saved by Feng Jiu Ge.

After that, he returned to Central Continent.

"If I am not wrong, this is a blood path Immortal Gu?" Fang Zheng looked at the Gu Immortal before him as he showed a mocking smile: "You want me to cultivate blood path, become a demonic path Gu Immortal and deal with Gu Yue Fang Yuan? This is the decision of Immortal Crane Sect, a righteous path sect?"

Immortal Crane Sect's rank six Gu Immortal Fan Xi Liu frowned slightly as he chuckled: "Regardless of what strength it is, if you use it righteously, it is righteous, if you use it for evil, it is demonic. Don't you understand this? For example, I cultivate poison path but I can still help the people of this world. You can do the same with blood path."

Gu Yue Fang Zheng shook his head: "Me cultivating blood path is only for the sake of dealing with Fang Yuan effectively. After all, we are blood brothers!"

Even though Fang Yuan had the sovereign immortal body, his time path clone was still blood related to Fang Zheng.

Fan Xi Liu nodded: "That is the case indeed. Don't you want to take revenge? After all, he slaughtered all of your clansmen in Gu Yue village."

Gu Yue Fang Zheng sighed deeply, even though he had a young face, his gaze was deep with the vicissitudes of life.

"So many years have passed. To speak the truth, even though I still hate him, I understand him already."

"I have thought about it, I was very childish and ignorant when I was young, Fang Yuan had taken care of me greatly. In contrast, my uncle and aunt had treated me as a pawn and made use of me. Should I take revenge for such people? I do not want to."

"Of course, the clan leader and Gu Yue Qing Shu had taken good care of me, they helped to nurture me, I am very willing to take revenge for them."

"But I am tired now… sigh, the cycle of killing each other continues endlessly over time… I do not want revenge anymore."

Fan Xi Liu's expression did not change: "It seems that these years, you have truly experienced a lot of things."

Gu Yue Fang Zheng looked at him, his mocking smile became wider: "The irony is that when I wanted to take revenge, the sect did not support me and even wanted to eliminate me. But when I gave up on revenge, you all saved me and supported my revenge."

Speaking of this, Gu Yue Fang Zheng looked at the blood path Immortal Gu, having an eerie gaze: "And I know that I have no choice, I can only accept this."

Fan Xi Liu assessed Fang Zheng once again, a surprise flashed in his eyes as he smiled lightly: "Is it really fine to speak so openly about this?"

"Does it really matter? I know that with your methods, I cannot hide any thoughts from you, isn't that that right?" Saying so, Fang Zheng stretched out his arm, holding that Gu as he asked: "What is this Gu's name?"

"Blood Revenge."

Chapter 1643: Grotto-Heaven Changes Owners

"Bai Ning Bing, don't go overboard!" Qi clan's Gu Immortal leader Qi Fa shouted in anger.

Bai Ning Bing was laughing coldly in her mind.

Bai Xiang tore through the sky, flashing past Qi Fa as Qi Jin's corpse was left behind, frozen in ice. His expression of fear before dying was perfectly preserved, vividly shown within the ice.

Boom boom boom!

Qi path killer moves burst out endlessly, Bai Xiang dodged a portion of them, some were intercepted by the immortal formation, while the rest tore Bai Xiang to shreds.

But immediately, it regenerated to perfection.

This scene made the Qi clan Gu Immortals feel a deep chill down their spines.

After an intense battle, three of the five Qi clan Gu Immortals had died, only Qi Fa and Qi Cai were left.

"Damn it, Bai Xiang is too powerful, we cannot deal with it in this situation!" Qi Fa gritted his teeth.

"This super immortal formation is the biggest problem, without it, we would have escaped already." Qi Cai looked at Qi Fa with bloodshot eyes, pointing out the truth.

Qi Fa was silent.

Qi Cai was right, even though the killer move Bai Xiang was strong, couldn't they simply run from it if they could not beat it? The sky was vast, there was no need to face Bai Ning Bing directly.

But it was too difficult to break out of this immortal formation. At least for Qi Fa and Qi Cai, they had been trying since the start, but had obtained no fruits of success.

Qi Fa sighed: "You are right, let's call Qi Ping Su to help."

Qi Ping Su only had rank six cultivation level, he was staying behind to guard Qi clan's base, Qi Sea grotto-heaven. But now, they had to ask him to come out and join forces with them, as long as they could destroy a bit of this immortal formation, they would be rescued.

But if they did that, they would fall into Fang Yuan's trap.

Fang Yuan had purposely made sure the immortal formation did not block transmissions, he wanted to lure Qi Ping Su out of the grotto-heaven.

Qi Fa knew this so for the entire duration of the battle, he did not want to get help from Qi Ping Su. But now, they were in a desperate situation, if they did not ask him to come out, they would lose their lives!

Qi Ping Su was already waiting to move, once he received orders, he opened the immortal aperture's entrance.

Bai Ning Bing was overjoyed: "They finally did it!"

Saying so, she teleported away using the formation, rushing into the immortal aperture's entrance.

"Oh no!" Qi Ping Su had just wanted to go out when Bai Ning Bing charged in, without a choice, he had to retreat.

Qi Sea grotto-heaven was huge, it was covered in white clouds and had strong winds.

The moment Bai Ning Bing entered, she felt a strong pressure, her strength was heavily suppressed by the vast qi path dao marks in this place.

But Bai Xiang was still extremely powerful, Bai Ning Bing and Qi Ping Su fought intensely and she soon gained the upper hand.

Qi Ping Su only had rank six cultivation level, his legs were crippled and he had injuries in his body. He could not beat Bai Ning Bing, he quickly retreated with his territorial advantage in this place, he soon vanished into the white clouds.

Bai Ning Bing furrowed her brows.

The situation was slightly troublesome, she did not kill Qi Ping Su earlier, how could she find this person in this huge grotto-heaven now? Even if she found him, what if he runs away again?

"Hmm?" Suddenly, Bai Ning Bing raised her head, she saw that a thick sea of clouds had formed above her head.

An intense sense of danger alerted her in her mind.

"A fatal danger!" Instantly, Bai Ning Bing understood the severity of the situation.

She quickly flew down like a falling meteor, descending rapidly.

In her vision, the yellowish ground was getting larger and larger.

Bai Ning Bing's expression became solemn, the sense of danger in her heart was intensifying.

Intense winds blew around her, she turned to look at the sky only to find the cloud sea expanding into the horizons, an intensely powerful killer move was nurturing from within it.

At the same time, Qi Ping Su who was in the cloud sea looked at Qi Sea heavenly spirit as he said joyfully: "Qi Sea heavenly spirit, you are awake! This timing is truly impeccable."

Qi Sea heavenly spirit had the appearance of a snow-white fawn, its eyes were golden in color, extremely dazzling.

"I was roused and woke up."

"Since the last time I got injured, I needed to seal myself to stabilize my injuries."

"But this time, I sensed that an incredibly evil and strong existence is coming after the grotto-heaven. I had to wake up as a result, but this intruder is not that existence that I felt."

Qi Ping Su was stunned: "I know who that is, it must be Fang Yuan. Heavenly spirit, you have sealed yourself for years, you do not know that a terrifying demonic path Gu Immortal had emerged, his name is Fang Yuan, even Heavenly Court was helpless against him."

Qi Sea heavenly spirit was shocked: "Even Heavenly Court was helpless? It must be him."

Qi Ping Su pointed at Bai Ning Bing, saying in extreme anger: "This is Fang Yuan's subordinate, she has already killed three of our clan's Gu Immortals."

Qi Sea heavenly spirit was enraged, killing intent surged in its golden eyes: "An eye for an eye, they killed our Qi clan's bloodline, we will end her life as well."

Saying so, an intense sound resounded as a huge white qi pillar slammed down towards Bai Ning Bing at a rapid speed from the cloud sea.

At this instance, Bai Ning Bing was shocked to find that there was a force all around her immobilizing her. She had all sorts of thoughts in her mind but her body was unmoving, like a bug trapped in amber.

"So powerful!"

"Even with all my strength, I cannot escape."

Bai Ning Bing raised her head, a white qi pillar was slamming down at her like a giant mountain.

This attack was clearly at rank eight level, even if Bai Ning Bing had Bai Xiang, she could not escape, she was bound to die.

But at this moment, a jade light sparkled out of nowhere, it burst out into countless spreading jade fireflies, dancing around the area.

From within the jade green light, Fang Yuan emerged.

"It's him!" Instantly, Qi Sea heavenly spirit shook intensely, shouting in shock.

"Indeed, he is Fang Yuan." Qi Ping Su gulped, swallowing his saliva while feeling extremely nervous.

Against the white qi pillar, Fang Yuan's expression did not change, he only stretched out his finger.

Swoosh!

With a shrill sound, an intensely sharp and huge sword will surged up and pierced the white qi pillar, cutting it into two.

The white qi pillar dissipated, Qi Ping Su opened his mouth as he felt deeply shocked.

"I'm saved." Bai Ning Bing was dazed before her lips curled up, she flew into the air and stood beside Fang Yuan.

"What move is this?" Bai Ning Bing looked up above her, saying hesitantly: "Don't tell me…"

"It should be Qi Xiang's signature killer move — Unlimited Qi Sea. This move is grand and vast, it is complex and ever-changing, capable of attacking and defending, Qi Xiang was renowned back in the day because of it." Fang Yuan agreed, having a solemn expression.

Unlimited qi sea was a rank eight killer move, it used many qi path Immortal Gu as the cores, with tens of thousands of supplementary Gu worms. It could absorb all kinds of qi in the world to increase its power.

This killer move was quite unique, it had potential for growth on its own. After Qi Xiang created this move, he collected all sorts of qi and stored them inside the immortal aperture, increasing the power of this move.

Thankfully, Qi Xiang had died long ago, even though unlimited qi sea was left in Qi Sea grotto-heaven, because it was too powerful and without any rank eight Gu Immortals in Qi clan, the huge quantity of qi had gradually dissipated.

Until now, Fang Yuan was after Qi Sea grotto-heaven, it alerted Qi Sea heavenly spirit and it barely managed to activate unlimited qi sea, after so many years, it had finally been used again.

"Even though this move is powerful, Qi Xiang had died long ago, how much power can the heavenly spirit unleash with it? Hehe." Fang Yuan snickered, suddenly flying into the sky, straight towards the cloud sea.

Bai Ning Bing gritted her teeth, she wanted to fight alongside Fang Yuan but she quickly stopped herself wisely, showing regret on her face.

She was too weak, she could not participate in a battle of such magnitude.

Rumble…

Bai Ning Bing looked at the sky, the cloud sea was rumbling, after Fang Yuan went in, the waves became more turbulent, as if a tsunami had occurred in the white clouds.

At the same time, thunderous explosions resounded endlessly.

"Life qi, death qi, sword qi, blade qi, dusk qi, dawn qi…" Bai Ning Bing was dazzled from this view, all sorts of qi gathered into countless forms, they were like plants, blades, swords, halberds, beasts and birds, they were all gathering right outside the qi sea, before charging in towards Fang Yuan for an intense battle.

Fang Yuan initially felt huge pressure, he could barely move, but soon, he unraveled some of the mysteries of this killer move. Within the sovereign immortal aperture, his time path clone was sitting in front of wisdom Gu, using the light of wisdom to deduce the information of unlimited qi sea rapidly.

After fighting for a while more, Fang Yuan's brows eased as he laughed heartily, starting his counterattack.

Everywhere he went, all sorts of obstacles were taken down and destroyed, he was unstoppable, he charged all the way until he reached the heavenly spirit.

Qi Sea heavenly spirit had a tough requirement for ownership, Fang Yuan could not achieve it, that information was obtained from Qi Zai's soul. Meanwhile, blood light spirit suppression could not work against a rank eight level heavenly spirit.

Thus, Fang Yuan went ahead to kill Qi Sea heavenly spirit.

The moment Qi Sea heavenly spirit died, the unmanned unlimited qi sea killer move immediately stopped.

"I surrender!" Qi Ping Su's body shivered, he was completely subdued by Fang Yuan's overwhelming demonic aura.

Fang Yuan looked at him coldly: "You are quite smart, alright, if you want to live, get Qi Fa and Qi Cai to surrender too. Otherwise, you can all die together."

"Yes, yes." Qi Ping Su was filled with pressure, he was sent into the formation.

Qi Fa and Qi Cai learned that Qi Sea grotto-heaven was taken down, they lost all their motivation, after some hesitation, they surrendered with pale expressions, stopping their resistance.

And now, from the Five Xiang's Bet, the prized rank nine killer move heaven form, the public grotto-heaven of the Five Xiangs, as well as Qi Sea grotto-heaven were all obtained by Fang Yuan!

Chapter 1644: Big Family Qi

Qi Sea grotto-heaven.

"Come!" Fang Yuan's main body shouted as he stretched out his right arm, his five fingers grabbing at the unlimited qi sea in front of him.

Immediately, an orange-yellow qi flowed out of unlimited qi sea.

This qi was extremely special, it was shiny and lively, moving with a long trail behind it, the tip of the qi had auspicious clouds circling around it.

This was luck qi.

A type of immortal material.

Unlimited qi sea had all sorts of qi in it, luck qi was one of the rarer ones. Because even in the five regions and two heavens, luck qi of such a scale was rarely seen. If a Gu Immortal could find some, they were very lucky.

Fang Yuan was dismantling the killer move unlimited qi sea now.

This killer move was Qi Xiang's greatest trump card, it was similar to Fang Yuan's Luo Po seal and reverse flow protection seal, this unlimited qi sea killer move also used immortal materials, they were the myriad forms of qi that he gathered.

The more types of qi gathered on large scales, the stronger unlimited qi sea was. Of course, not only would this move expend immortal essence, it also used up the stored qi. Even if they were not used, as time passed, these qi would naturally dissipate slowly.

Thus, Fang Yuan had faced the unlimited qi sea killer move earlier when it was not at its peak.

It was the fifth day now.

Ever since he succeeded in taking down Qi Sea grotto-heaven, he had been resting here. Two days ago, he collated all of his gains, he also made enslavement agreements with the three Qi clan Gu Immortals, Qi Ping Su, Qi Fa and Qi Cai. Some of the resources that could be moved into the sovereign immortal aperture were also dealt with by Ying Wu Xie and the rest. Meanwhile, his own focus was on the killer move unlimited qi sea.

This was a qi path killer move, it was not usable for Fang Yuan. Dismantling it would give him a vast amount of qi, that was quite valuable. And most importantly, Fang Yuan could only deal with these Gu worms after dismantling the killer move, otherwise, if he refined them rashly, he might face the backlash of the killer move, after all, this move was complete and extraordinary.

"I will need three more days to extract all of the qi at this rate."

"After that, I will refine these Immortal Gu."

Fang Yuan planned inwardly.

There were many mortal Gu worms used to construct unlimited qi sea killer move, but Fang Yuan did not really care about them.

His focus was on the Immortal Gu.

There were six Immortal Gu that made up this killer move, one was a rank eight Immortal Gu, called Big Qi, it was the core of the killer move.

Other than that, there were some rank seven and six Gu worms. Fang Yuan was paying the most attention to a rank seven Immortal Gu, it was called Big Family Qi.

This qi path Gu worm could store all sorts of qi, including the qi of tribulations!

The final point was crucial.

Fang Yuan had once used many small family qi Gu to store his tribulation qi and help him to pass tribulations. As an Immortal Gu, Big Family Qi had a much stronger ability in this aspect.

"With this Immortal Gu, I will be able to store and release tribulation qi, that is a superb method to deal with tribulations."

"If the calamities and tribulations are powerful, I will use this Gu to absorb the tribulation qi and weaken it. If it is weak, I will release tribulation qi to allow myself to gain more dao marks in the end."

"Using this Gu, I can even absorb the heaven and earth qi of the outside world and store it. When the sovereign immortal aperture needs it, I can release this qi, this prevents me from needing to place my immortal aperture in order to absorb heaven and earth qi and stabilize the sovereign immortal aperture."

Different situations gave rise to different needs.

It was not that a higher ranked Immortal Gu was necessarily more helpful to the Gu Immortal. In this case, rank seven Big Family Qi was much more helpful to him than rank eight Big Qi.

Refining these qi path Immortal Gu would expend Fang Yuan's time and energy.

But there was no difficulty thanks to Fang Yuan's quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment level in refinement path and theft path great grandmaster attainment level, as well as great thief ghost hand and other methods

Like what Fang Yuan anticipated, a few days later, he absorbed all of the qi here, these qi were all stored in different ways, those that Fang Yuan could not keep were sold in treasure yellow heaven directly

Not only these qi, some of the resources inside Qi Sea grotto-heaven and the Five Xiang's public grotto-heaven were sold by Fang Yuan to exchange for resources he needed.

Normally, he traded goods for goods, there were few transactions involving immortal essence stones.

Because Fang Yuan had advanced to rank eight, he had white litchi immortal essence now.

One bead of white litchi immortal essence was in some sense a hundred beads of red date immortal essence, which was ten thousand beads of green grape immortal essence.

That was to say, ten thousand immortal essence stones could be converted into one white litchi immortal essence bead, the conversion rate was simply too bad.

Thus in most cases, rank eight Gu Immortals produced their own beads of immortal essence and stored them.

Fang Yuan's sovereign immortal aperture had abundant time path resources, he could produce beads of white litchi immortal essence rapidly, he did not need external replenishment from immortal essence stones. Especially when this replenishment came at such a high and inefficient cost.

Fang Yuan's cultivation resources were mostly traded for immortal materials, because he was going to mass refine Gu now.

Right when Fang Yuan was focusing on refining the qi path Immortal Gu, Ying Wu Xie secretly went to find him.

He was no longer in a female body, he had changed to a body belonging to a Gu Immortal from Southern Border's Yang clan, they had compatible soul path dao marks. In battle, Fang Yuan would also create some Pure Dream Reality Seeker Physique bodies for him to use.

Ying Wu Xie said cautiously: "Sect leader, you have already refined all of the three Qi clan Gu Immortals' Immortal Gu, but you returned and rented them out, that is a good way to control them. But why don't you use it on Bai Ning Bing? Even though she is very useful to you now, that is only temporarily, your ice and snow path attainment will increase in the future. Furthermore, Bai Ning Bing possesses the killer move Bai Xiang, it is very powerful and threatening. Even if she joins Shadow Sect and undergoes the alliance agreement, she can easily break it without a problem. I might be out of line, but you seem to be too… lenient with Bai Ning Bing."

Fang Yuan smiled as he shook his head.

"That is because you don't understand her."

"She is a person who does not fear death. If I try that on her, she would rather die than surrender."

"Even though I have methods to retain most of her Immortal Gu, what is the use of that?"

"You've already seen it in the battle of Reverse Flow River, I need manpower to restrain Heavenly Court's members. With your current strength, none of you can help me in this."

"Bai Ning Bing who has the killer move Bai Xiang is very valuable."

"With her identity and circumstances, she cannot turn towards Heavenly Court. At the same time, she needs me to refine yin yang rotation Immortal Gu and restore her male body."

Fang Yuan had refinement path quasi-supreme attainment level while Bai Ning Bing had no confidence in refining the Immortal Gu herself!

"We are too useless." Ying Wu Xie lowered his head.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "I understand your other intention. I will take care of you guys and raise your battle strength."

In the past, Fang Yuan only had rank seven cultivation level, he had to prioritize himself. But now, he was rank eight, raising Ying Wu Xie, Hei Lou Lan, and the others' battle strength was icing on the cake for Fang Yuan.

Of course, there were other reasons. In the past, Fang Yuan had no time or energy for this, but now as a rank eight, even though he was weak against Heavenly Court, ordinary people could no longer find trouble with him, they even had to avoid him. And with Fang Yuan's powerful methods in blocking deductions, as long as he did not go to the River of Time, he was safe.

In such a situation, Fang Yuan could calmly strengthen his subordinates.

He had a strong feeling that these people would be useful in the future.

Furthermore, raising their cultivation level was easy, he could mainly use time path methods to accelerate the time in their immortal apertures. Even if they had calamities and tribulations, he could help them to pass.

Ying Wu Xie obtained Fang Yuan's promise and left happily.

Next, in his free time, Fang Yuan called Hei Lou Lan over.

"I'll show you someone." Fang Yuan took out the captive Gu Immortal Hei Cheng.

Hei Lou Lan stared with wide opened eyes, she was furious, wanting to tear Hei Cheng to pieces.

Even though Hei Cheng was her father, they had deep hatred between them.

Hei Lou Lan did not act out of line, she watched as Fang Yuan stored Hei Cheng back into his immortal aperture, she breathed roughly with bloodshot eyes as she gritted her teeth and said: "So Hei Cheng was in sect leader's hands the entire time! Are you thinking of recruiting him?"

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Don't worry, compared to him, I hold you in higher regard. As long as you cultivate hard and accumulate some contributions, I am sure you will be able to take revenge one day."

"I understand!" Hei Lou Lan looked at Fang Yuan, by now, she had already been far exceeded by him, this difference made her feel extremely helpless.

Chapter 1645: Rank Seven Spring Autumn Cicada

Inside the sovereign immortal aperture.

The Gu refinement was at its most crucial point.

The huge cicada was floating in the air, about five feet from the ground.

The cicada's surface was not smooth, it was hairy and rough, while also having a metallic texture.

Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, using his killer move that had been prepared for a long time.

Instantly, winds blew around the cicada, dark clouds rumbled in the sky, gathering into one lump and turning the surroundings dim.

Howl howl howl…

Amidst waves of ghostly wails and the ground that was rotting into a pale white color, dark ghost hands emerged from the ground, they were thick and menacing, grabbing at the cicada.

The ghost hands grabbed the cicada but they were only illusory, the ghost hands moved around and took something out of the cicada before clenching into fists and retreating.

Hundreds of dark ghost hands continued to extend from the ground, grabbing the cicada and removing the impurities from within it.

The cicada was only a half completed product, it was unstable and became smaller as the ghost hands grabbed at it, the surface slowly became smoother as the metallic surface became sharper and brighter.

Fang Yuan had been paying attention deeply, upon seeing this, he felt greatly satisfied.

This method was his unique creation, it used rank eight Soul Beast Token as the core Immortal Gu.

"In the last few times I refined Spring Autumn Cicada, flaws appeared here, the materials were not processed properly. By doing this now, I can get rid of the impurities, but some flaws will be left behind."

The dark winds had stopped blowing, the dark ghost hands shrunk in number until none were left.

The dark clouds in the sky became thicker and denser, the cicada was already half of its original size, its body was shining in a metallic light, giving off a cold feeling.

Fang Yuan took out a huge lump of fire calmly.

This was the rank eight immortal material phoenix song flame, it was red and yellow in color, with two layers. The outside layer was yellow while the inside was red. The inner layer was shaped like a phoenix, it flew around while singing loudly, as the flames continued to burn, it emitted a crisp and wonderful melody.

"Go!" Fang Yuan grunted as he tossed a basin-sized phoenix song flame onto the cicada's surface.

Whoosh.

A soft sound echoed as the flames spread, surrounding the entire cicada and setting it ablaze.

At this moment, phoenix cries resounded in the clouds.

Next, the sounds went soft but the flames became brighter, burning the cicada intensely.

Fang Yuan held his breath, staring at the cicada without looking away.

Traces of ghost qi started to emerge from the cicada's surface but they were destroyed by the flames.

This Gu refinement step was very difficult, the precision needed was extremely high and hard to manage.

But Fang Yuan was sufficiently calm and patient, he waited until all of the ghost qi was destroyed and the surface of the cicada melted before he started the next method without panicking.

Dragon roars resounded, a huge dragon-shaped blizzard landed on the surface of the cicada.

The cicada's flames resisted it but this dragon blizzard was too huge, because it had Fang Yuan's support, it quickly gained the upper hand and suppressed the cicada in the middle of it.

The phoenix song flame on the cicada was very stubborn, it only dissipated after a few hours.

Meanwhile, the dragon blizzard transformed into a piece of ice and sealed the cicada.

Currently, the cicada had shrunk to the size of only a palm.

When the blizzard stopped, Fang Yuan carefully retrieved the frozen cicada, next, he breathed out some warm air as the ice melted, revealing the cicada inside.

The cicada seemed to be a work of art, it was very exquisite. Fang Yuan pinched the cicada with his fingers.

Crack crack.

The cicada's surface started to crack, next, a rank seven Spring Autumn Cicada awakened and flew out.

Fang Yuan's gaze flashed with joy.

"It had not been easy!"

"After so many failures, I've finally refined Spring Autumn Cicada to rank seven."

At this point, Fang Yuan had modified almost all of the refinement methods already. The ghost hand purification method was created by fusing great thief ghost hand killer move and Soul Beast Token. Even though this method had great effect, it would easily leave ghost qi behind. Thus, Fang Yuan chose the rank eight immortal material phoenix song flame to get rid of the ghost qi and also temper the cicada. Eventually, he used the dragon blizzard which was also not normal, it was actually a modification of the slumbering lightning python killer move.

Refinement path had four publicly recognized strongest immortal killer moves to deal with immortal materials. One of them was slumbering lightning python.

Fang Yuan modified it into a dragon blizzard, it suited him more and was better for the Spring Autumn Cicada refinement.

With all these reasons, his hard work paid off in the end, Fang Yuan succeeded in obtaining rank seven Spring Autumn Cicada.

"With rank seven Spring Autumn Cicada and my time path great grandmaster attainment level, I can totally use Spring Autumn Cicada as the core to deduce an immortal killer move and prevent getting into Heavenly Court's trap!"

Fang Yuan's gaze flickered with uncertainty.

Last time, when he entered the River of Time, he was ambushed by Heavenly Court because they had used a method to deceive Spring Autumn Cicada.

Back then, Spring Autumn Cicada was only rank six, now it was rank seven and if he had a relevant immortal killer move, even if Heavenly Court used a rank eight method to deceive Spring Autumn Cicada, they would not succeed easily.

"The best situation is to use rank seven Spring Autumn Cicada as the core, along with a supplementary rank eight spring Gu, to create a rank eight immortal killer move. When I enter the River of Time, I will not fear Heavenly Court's trap while also expanding my search range."

Of course, the most straightforward way was to raise Spring Autumn Cicada to rank eight.

But it was too hard.

Currently, Fang Yuan could not refine rank eight Immortal Gu.

On one hand, even though he had extremely high refinement path attainment level, his foundation was shaky, his refinement path methods needed practice.

On the other hand, he lacked finances. Back then, Old Ancestor Xue Hu had expended all his wealth and the entire foundation of Snowy Mountain before he was able to try and refine rank eight Immortal Gu Fortune Rivalling Heaven.

Of course, Fang Yuan's foundation was very deep now. Not to mention his countless fortuitous encounters, just his wealth after extorting the Southern Border experts and the inheritance of the Five Xiangs, it could be said that his foundation rivaled some super forces now.

He had many Immortal Gu, even though he lost the incomplete Immortal Gu House, he still had dozens of them left. He had ample cultivation resources too of varying types, he did not just focus on one path.

The only shortcoming was his weak subordinates.

When Hei Lou Lan and the others reached rank seven, along with the three enslaved Qi clan Gu Immortals, Fang Yuan would finally match a true super force! Even though he could not compare to Southern Border's Wu clan or Western Desert's Fang clan, he would still be first rate, surpassing ordinary super forces, leagues above Chu Du's Chu tribe.

"I can give some rank six and seven resources to Ying Wu Xie and the rest."

"Other than nurturing them, I need to refine Immortal Gu next!"

Most of the Immortal Gu that Fang Yuan was using extensively were still at rank six.

For example, Self Strength, Pulling Mountain, Pulling Water, Strength Qi, Unravel Mystery, Dog Shit Luck, Qi Luck, Luck Inspection, Connect Luck, Time Luck…

And most importantly for now, Landscape as Before, Man as Before, and day Gu.

If he raised the ranks of these three time path Immortal Gu, Fang Yuan's battle strength in terms of time path would surge greatly.

His current focus was truly on time path.

Even though sword path, soul path, wisdom path, and others had huge room for improvement, when he fought in the River of Time, he would need time path methods.

"It is a pity that Lang Ya Sect went to Longevity Heaven, my refinement path methods still need lots of work. If those hairy man Gu Immortals can help me refine Gu, I can save a lot of time and energy."

Fang Yuan expressed deep regret towards this.

He had made use of Lang Ya Sect too conveniently in the past, now that they were gone, he had to work hard and expend great effort, even though Fang Yuan did not mind the trouble, too much of his time was used, he was no longer as free as before.

"And refining Gu has a problem, the success rate!"

The refinement to raise an Immortal Gu's rank had low success rate, the higher the rank, the higher the chances of failure.

Fang Yuan wanted to refine rank seven Gu, it would be harder than creating rank six.

Once he fails, the original rank six Immortal Gu might even be destroyed, in that case, he would need to start over and refine the rank six before trying for seven again. If the Immortal Gu is refined by someone else during the period of its destruction, he would truly lose everything.

Chapter 1646: Fang Zheng's Immortal Ascension

Central Continent.

The sky was dark and gloomy, there was no wind.

Gu Yue Fang Zheng stood at a mountain peak, looking at the sky, he felt a bit of nervousness thinking about his upcoming immortal ascension tribulation.

Sensing his emotion, Fang Zheng laughed to himself, thinking: "Why am I nervous? Immortal Crane Sect should be the nervous one, or rather, the Heavenly Court behind them."

"On the surface, there is only one rank six Gu Immortal in charge of guarding my ascension, but there must be many eyes watching me in secret, with these people around, what is there to worry about?"

Even though Fang Zheng did not know why Central Continent wanted to support him, he had confirmed that he was valuable and of use to them.

In the past, he would not accept being a pawn like this. Back in Qing Mao Mountain, Fang Yuan had hinted that he was used by his uncle and aunt as the tool to fight for the inheritance, this made Fang Zheng very angry.

But now, Fang Zheng no longer felt anger towards this.

In the last decade or so, Fang Zheng had experienced the war in Lang Ya blessed land's three continents. In order to nurture the most elite hairy man Gu Immortals, the black haired land spirit disregarded the price and made the hairy men of the three continent fight in an intense war, Fang Zheng was implicated.

Surrounded by schemes and plots, bloodshed and war, Fang Zheng had made use of people, and was also made use of.

He gradually understood that sometimes, becoming someone's pawn and being used was not a bad thing. At the very least, it proved his worth. If a person did not have value to even be a tool, then he was in danger, he would be discarded like a faulty tool.

Of course, even though Fang Zheng had rank five Gu Master strength, he also had experiences of being abandoned and betrayed. As a human living among the hairy men, it was natural to be ostracized and isolated.

"We can begin." At this time, Fan Xi Liu's voice resounded in Fang Zheng's ears.

Fan Xi Liu had rank six cultivation level, he was sent over by Immortal Crane Sect to help Fang Zheng undergo tribulation.

Fang Zheng nodded, he calmed down and looked inside him.

His aperture was quickly seen, it was filled with primeval essence that showed his A grade talent, but his walls were filled with cracks. Anyone would feel nervous upon seeing it, after all, the aperture was the basis of a Gu Master's cultivation. With so many cracks, it was definitely a severe issue!

Fang Zheng was relatively calm now, his nervousness had vanished.

In fact, during a battle in Lang Ya blessed land, he had used a forbidden technique while in a desperate situation, even though he survived, his aperture was severely damaged and filled with cracks, his A grade aptitude fell to B grade.

Fang Zheng was saved by Feng Jiu Ge, after returning to Central Continent, his injuries in the aperture were healed, he returned to having A grade aptitude. But the cracks in his aperture walls still remained, it was not that Heavenly Court could not heal him, but they left those for him to undergo his immortal ascension tribulation more easily.

Fang Zheng observed his aperture, he had once felt extremely proud of his A grade talent, but after these life experiences, he no longer cared about aptitude so greatly. Right now, his gaze was stuck at the cracks in his aperture.

To him, these were his achievements, he had gained these wounds from bloodshed and war, it was his glory.

"Goodbye, my aperture." Fang Zheng muttered.

As he willed, the primeval essence in his aperture surged and crashed into the surrounding walls.

There were cracks in his aperture to begin with, it was not sturdy, soon, the cracks intensified as holes formed.

The complete aperture finally connected to the outside world, a mysterious power was forming.

This power drew in the heaven and earth qi of the outside world, at once, dark clouds rumbled in the sky, the earth was shaking, dust clouds were forming.

At the same time, a formless heavenly power held up Fang Zheng and allowed him to float into the sky.

"Heaven's will!" Fan Xi Liu who was watching in concealment sensed abundant heaven's will.

Fang Zheng's tribulation had drawn the attention of heaven's will, far beyond normal!

The calamities and tribulations started forming, a large amount of blood qi was converted from the heaven and earth qi, the dark clouds in the sky were quickly dyed red, the scale was huge, they could be seen from an enormous distance.

"Blood path tribulation…" Joy flashed in Fan Xi Liu's eyes, the blood path tribulation was what the higher-ups wanted to see.

Fang Zheng's aura started to spread out.

This was his human qi.

Every person had their own human qi, the scale was decided based on their foundation, talent, and abilities.

Fan Xi Liu observed Fang Zheng carefully, soon, he had a look of surprise on his face.

Fang Zheng's human qi was extremely dense, it showed how much life experiences and foundation he possessed.

Heaven qi was raining down while earth qi was bubbling up, both intertwined in the air with human qi.

Fang Zheng had a solemn expression, he tried to control the three qi and balance them.

The three qi had just started interacting and now was the best time to get used to controlling them. Fang Zheng had received Fan Xi Liu's guidance, he was aware of this.

But at this time, the calamities and tribulations were completed, a large amount of rain fell.

These raindrops were all blood droplets, they were extremely bloody. As the blood rained down, white fog started to appear in the air. The white fog was quickly dyed red by the rain, turning the entire mountain into an eerie red color.

Fang Zheng started to undergo tribulation. He put up his defenses and activated Gu worms to resist the blood rain.

At this time, whenever he used a Gu worm, he would suffer a backlash. Soon, his Gu worms died from the backlash.

This was also why Gu Masters would often lose all of their Gu worms after immortal ascension.

But Fang Zheng was supported by Heavenly Court and had deep preparation, he did not lack Gu worms.

He calmed down and defended himself, not panicking.

During Lang Ya blessed land's wars, he had experienced far more dangerous situations, he was adequately prepared for this.

Fan Xi Liu was much more nervous than Fang Zheng.

He stared at Fang Zheng without blinking.

Rank five Gu Masters usually had a lot of difficulty in their immortal ascension. Because they not only had to deal with the calamities and tribulations, but also control the three qi and maintain balance between them.

"I can help you to block this blood rain tribulation for a while, but the balancing of the three qi will depend on you, Fang Zheng! Before the tribulation, I had given you ample training, you cannot fail at the crucial moment." Fan Xi Liu thought to himself as he started to disrupt the blood clouds, affecting their size and influence.

Even though this blood rain tribulation was huge, it was not too overbearing, it seems that heaven's will had done this intentionally.

Fang Zheng's tribulation was peaceful, be it internally or externally.

The three qi fused properly, scenes of the past flashed in his mind as his body became tempered and elevated.

Next, during the heaven and earth resonance, he entered the most crucial moment of this immortal ascension. During this period, he could gain natural inspiration and communicate with heaven and earth.

This communication was extremely beneficial to any Gu Master.

Fang Zheng realized at this moment that blood path really suited himself.

Time passed, the three qi condensed and formed into a lump of qi.

Fang Zheng suddenly opened his eyes, he breathed in deeply and tossed a rank five blood path Gu into the lump of qi.

Boom!

A shocking sound exploded around him, the qi lump burst out and turned into an immortal aperture.

Instantly, Fang Zheng's mind became blank, he was completely defenseless at this moment.

A moment later, he regained his senses, he started to put his vital Gu and important Gu worms into his immortal aperture. The first one he put in was blood revenge Immortal Gu of course, followed by a large number of blood path mortal Gu.

Within the immortal aperture, the three qi were conditioned and balanced, the world gradually stabilized.

He obviously gained a high grade blessed land!

There was also a lot of heaven and earth qi remaining.

Fang Zheng was overjoyed, these heaven and earth qi could raise his vital blood path mortal Gu into an Immortal Gu!

Even though this was dangerous and there would be following calamity or tribulation, Fang Zheng was courageous enough to choose this option.

"Fang Zheng, quickly let me in, I will help you with the tribulation!" Fan Xi Liu transmitted.

"Hmm?" Fang Zheng frowned, showing displeasure. The immortal aperture was the most private area of the Gu Immortal, Fan Xi Liu was infringing on it, Fang Zheng felt a sense of anger.

But immediately, Fang Zheng relaxed his brows, he opened the immortal aperture door and said plainly: "Sure, Fan Xi Liu, please enter."

Fan Xi Liu was surprised, Fang Zheng had just become an immortal, the process was not over yet but he had already changed his manner of speech with such a natural attitude.

"However, Heavenly Court seems be nurturing Fang Zheng greatly for the sake of dealing with Fang Yuan. I am actually quite envious of him."

Several hours later, Fang Zheng's tribulation was passed, Fan Xi Liu's envy rose again.

It was because Fang Zheng's vital Gu was successfully refined into his second blood path Immortal Gu.

Cold blood Immortal Gu!

Several days later, Immortal Crane Sect announced to the Gu Immortal world that Fang Zheng succeeded in his immortal ascension, he was once harmed by the vicious demon Fang Yuan, he was saved luckily and would now become one of the main forces of dealing with the demon Fang Yuan.

Due to Heavenly Court's intentional propagation, news spread throughout the five regions, Fang Yuan's reputation was hit, his situation of being deserted by family and kin was highlighted, while Heavenly Court promoted its own magnanimity.

Several days later.

"Spirit Affinity Fairy, goodbye." Above the clouds, Fan Xi Liu smiled as he spoke to Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun smiled: "Thanks for hosting."

She heard that Fang Zheng succeeded in his tribulation so she came to visit him. Unfortunately, Fang Zheng was not meeting anyone, he was hidden by Immortal Crane Sect.

Fan Xi Liu did not dare to be rude to Zhao Lian Yun, she was the current generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House, even though she had rank six cultivation level, she controlled rank nine love Gu.

Fan Xi Liu assured: "I will definitely pass your gift to Fang Zheng personally."

Zhao Lian Yun nodded as she thanked him and flew away.

Chapter 1647: Joint Suppression

Fang Zheng blessed land.

His space path and time path resources were higher than normal, this was a high grade blessed land.

The terrain of the blessed land was mostly flat, but across some distance, there would be several tall erected mountains.

Fang Zheng's focus was currently fully on a valley.

This valley was covered in weird rugged rocks, it was completely blood red. Upon entering it, one would notice that the valley was filled with blood flower trees.

There were tens of thousands of such trees, they were different from ordinary trees, they bore fruits before flowers. The fruits were the size of a baby's fist, round and smooth. The flowering only took an instant as the fruit shell would explode into a huge flower that was white and red. The flower was white at the base while the core of the flower resembled splattered blood. Each of these blood flowers had different colors and shapes.

In Central Continent, there was once a time where Gu Masters cultivated these blood flower trees on large scales. Each time they bloomed, the scene would be grand. There were even huge ceremonies just to lure these Gu Masters to see them. But later, blood path was created and caused great problems to the world, blood flower trees were a basic Gu material in blood path, they were banned from being planted.

Fang Zheng's blood flower trees were all provided by Immortal Crane Sect, or more accurately, by Fan Xi Liu as a proxy.

This was the trick of the righteous path, Fang Zheng was already used to it, feeling no surprise.

In the current five regions, blood path was outlawed by the righteous path, but ironically, the ones who truly researched blood path were these righteous path forces.

"These blood flower trees are all mortal Gu materials, but as long as their numbers go up, I can use them in huge quantities, they will be equivalent to immortal materials. This is blood path's most unique advantage!"

"These blood flower trees that I have are also a source of immortal materials in a way."

"But now, I already have rank six blood path Immortal Gu Cold Blood and Blood Revenge, they need mortal blood path Gu to supplement them and form immortal killer moves."

Fang Zheng understood that his focus now was to refine blood path mortal Gu and practice the blood path immortal killer move that Fan Xi Liu imparted him.

Because he had just ascended, the immortal aperture was very different from his original aperture, he needed time to adapt to it.

After looking for a while, Fang Zheng retracted his attention to the real world.

The joy and feeling of achievement from looking at his immortal aperture slowly faded, they were replaced by a feeling of pressure in his mind.

"Fang Yuan…" Back in the real world, Fang Zheng could not help but think of his brother.

These last days, he had not only undergone his immortal ascension, he had also obtained information about Fang Yuan from Fan Xi Liu. The information was much more detailed than what circulated in the outside world, it was from Heavenly Court.

Fang Zheng learned about Fang Yuan's situation, as for the fact that Fang Yuan did not die, he had known that when he was saved and returned to Central Continent. But strangely, when he learned the truth, he did not feel any rage from being deceived.

In contrast, the more he learned, the more sadness he felt in his heart.

"It turns out, I have never truly understood you… Fang Yuan."

"Otherworldly demon… Spring Autumn Cicada… rank eight cultivation level…"

The more he knew, the more minuscule he felt, the more he could feel Fang Yuan's terrifying strength!

Thinking that he had to face such a person in the future, he felt a bit of depression and also a hint of despair.

He faced the despair deep in his heart.

He did not deny it or try to avoid it.

Humans often said that a youth knows no fear, when one is young, they fear nothing and have strong drive and motivation. But after a person experiences a lot, they would learn about their own fears. Tigers would eat people, tiger claws would harm people, one's own strength was not as strong as they think.

Imagination was wonderful, but only after facing reality would one feel pain, understanding the world and themselves during this painful process.

"When I was a rank five Gu Master, I was engaged in the hairy man war in Lang Ya blessed land, I lived a difficult life wandering about."

"But now as a Gu Immortal, I am stuck between Fang Yuan and Heavenly Court, becoming a pawn. Even though my strength has grown greatly, my freedom has dwindled, I am facing greater danger now, I can die if any mishaps occur."

Thinking of this, Fang Zheng smiled bitterly to himself.

Even now, he did not know what value he had for Heavenly Court to put so much focus on him.

Soon, he thought of Zhao Lian Yun.

When he ascended, he received some congratulatory gifts. This was the custom of the five regions, whenever a Gu Master becomes an immortal, their friends and family, or even the forces they were friendly with, would send them gifts.

Fang Zheng's gifts mostly came from Immortal Crane Sect, Zhao Lian Yun's one was quite memorable as a result.

From Immortal Crane Sect's information, Fang Zheng gained a deep understanding of Zhao Lian Yun.

"You are also an otherworldly demon, although not completely."

"You looked for me so proactively, I assume you want to join up and deal with Fang Yuan…"

Zhao Lian Yun's gifts included a letter that expressed her goodwill, but she did not say much. Fang Zheng could tell what she wanted from her subtle words.

Zhao Lian Yun gave him one of the cultivation methods for growing a blood type plant resource, it suited Fang Zheng. She even described her own cultivation experiences, Fang Zheng was very mindful of a certain paragraph.

"In Gu Immortal cultivation, combat is the path of domination, while immortal aperture management is the path of supremacy, the two are complementary and necessary. Without enough battle strength and dominance, no matter how well the immortal aperture is developed, one will only get bullied, they will hand over their hard earned spoils to others. But if one has great battle strength and lacking immortal aperture foundation, they will be like a blazing flame, only able to stay lit for some time, when they run out of firewood, they would only end up as smoke."

Fang Zheng nodded to himself, thinking: "Other than this, her descriptions of the calamities and tribulations are also very useful. I can see that this Zhao Lian Yun is very sincere, it is a pity that Immortal Crane Sect is not allowing us to meet, what a pity indeed! Don't you think so, Fang Yuan?"

Saying so, Fang Zheng's gaze froze.

In his early years, he was accompanied by his master Lord Sky Crane, inside Lang Ya blessed land, he was together with Fang Yuan's fake will. But now, in Central Continent, he was alone.

Unknowingly, Fang Zheng had gotten used to accompaniment.

"Without you, I am not used to it…" Fang Zheng shook his head and smiled bitterly, an indescribable sense of loneliness permeated in his heart.

Heavenly Court.

Fairy Zi Wei smiled in joy: "Fang Zheng has become a Gu Immortal, but he needs to raise his cultivation level to become a useful counter against Fang Yuan."

Fairy Zi Wei knew about Zhao Lian Yun's intention. After all, even though Ma Hong Yun died, his soul was still kept by Fang Yuan.

Fairy Zi Wei frowned: "The true problem is still Fang Yuan himself."

Ever since Fang Yuan broke out of the River of Time's encirclement, he had vanished, no longer appearing in public.

Fairy Zi Wei would prefer that he went around scavenging for resources. At least in that case, he would leave behind many traces and she would deduce many useful things, and even find a way to break his wisdom path defenses.

In Fairy Zi Wei's view, Fang Yuan was very strong in battle strength, but the more terrifying thing was his management skills. Every time he stayed secluded for a while, he would experience a huge rise in strength, his speed of progress was simply very shocking.

This was the result of his skillful management.

Because he had such a sturdy foundation, it could support his terrifying growth in battle strength.

"Right now, Spectral Soul is slowly losing his control, we are getting more and more information that is of high importance."

"In the River of Time, the time path Immortal Gu House has been repaired, we have four in total now. The earlier time path formation needs to be modified further."

"At the same time, we cannot let Fang Yuan live comfortably, I should contact Wu Yong."

Some days later.

Intense winds blew.

Fang Yuan pushed forward with his palm, the strong force of the killer move went into the immortal aperture's entrance and permeated Lou Lan blessed land.

Hei Lou Lan's tribulation was destroyed instantly.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes twitched slightly but her expression was unchanging. She stood in her immortal aperture as she thanked Fang Yuan, who was outside.

"No need to thank me." Fang Yuan looked at Lou Lan blessed land, it was quite poor, it could not be compared with the sovereign immortal aperture. Even though Hei Lou Lan had high aptitude, she had never truly developed her immortal aperture properly.

This was what Fang Yuan wanted.

He could give Hei Lou Lan cultivation resources, she had to rely on him for this, it was a form of control over her.

In fact, Ying Wu Xie, Bai Ning Bing, and the rest were all in similar situations.

"Quickly leave, my wisdom path methods can only block them for some time, moreover, each time, the tribulations will greatly influence my methods." Fang Yuan urged.

"Okay." Hei Lou Lan nodded, she did not dare to be careless, quickly storing her immortal aperture and entering the sovereign immortal aperture.

Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel to leave immediately, Wu Yong and the rest who came at full speed failed to catch him.

"Damn it! He escaped again."

"This lingering aura, someone underwent tribulation again…"

The Southern Border Gu Immortals had ugly expressions, some were furious, some were solemn, while some were fearful.

"This is the fourth one… evidently, Fang Yuan is helping his lackeys undergo tribulation to raise their cultivation levels. If this continues, the situation will not be good."

Wu Yong had a grim expression, a cold light flashed in his eyes as he said slowly: "Fang Yuan has Fixed Immortal Travel, he can escape rapidly, we can only set up many Beacon Towers and work together in treasure yellow heaven to restrict his businesses and reduce his profits. Eventually, this will become our advantage."

Jade light flickered in Qi Sea grotto-heaven as Fang Yuan appeared out of nowhere.

"We are safe for now."

"They are starting to target my businesses in treasure yellow heaven…" Fang Yuan snickered.

He did feel pressure, but because he had recently devoured the Five Xiang's public grotto-heaven and Qi Sea grotto-heaven, he gained a vast amount of resources, even if his businesses were suppressed, there was no issue.

But this was obviously Heavenly Court and Southern Border working together, if he allowed them to continue, Fang Yuan would not be able to endure it.

He had obtained a lot of resources from the Southern Border Gu Immortal captives, but precisely because they knew about these resources, they could target these businesses efficiently.

"I need to think of a plan." Fang Yuan gaze flickered with consideration.

Chapter 1648: Conflict Between Miao and Ren

Eastern Sea.

Swish swish swish!

Waves crashed onto the rocks by the island shore, bursting into white bubbles upon impact.

Wicked winds howled, the sky was dark.

This uninhibited island was not eye-catching in the huge Eastern Sea, but it actually hid four Gu Immortals.

"Ren Xiu Ping, you are too much!" Miao Ming Shen shouted angrily with bloodshot eyes, he was injured, expressing intense anger and hatred in his eyes.

He was a famous lone cultivator in Eastern Sea, having rank seven cultivation level and cultivating space path, he had a method to increase the size of immortal apertures. He did that as a way of living, expanding the immortal apertures of many Eastern Sea Gu Immortals, he was quite popular.

Miao Ming Shen was neither tall nor short, neither fat nor thin. In terms of appearance, he looked ordinary, only his flat and wide nose left a heavy impression on others.

In terms of appearance, he was unassuming. But he was an ambitious person, being very good at building relationships, he had a lot of charisma. Three Eastern Sea lone immortals, Immortal Hua Die, Feng Jiang, and Gui Qi Ye all looked to Miao Ming Shen as their leader, the four were a group of Gu Immortals with common interests.

But now, Gui Qi Ye was unconscious, his body was covered in a poisonous purple color, he was in great danger.

Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die who were standing beside Miao Ming Shen were in bad states too, they had evidently gotten injured from a serious battle.

"Lord Miao Ming Shen, what do we do? Gui Qi Ye was hit by the ice poison starfish, we do not have the way to heal him." Immortal Hua Die was very worried.

Not long ago, the four of them had fallen for Ren Xiu Ping's plot.

Ren Xiu Ping had rank seven peak cultivation level and was an enslavement path Gu Immortal, he wanted to assassinate Miao Ming Shen using the ice poison starfish. But at the crucial moment, Gui Qi Ye blocked this fatal attack for Miao Ming Shen.

Miao Ming Shen reacted and quickly brought the unconscious Gui Qi Ye, as well as Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die, out of the trap through a fierce battle.

Feng Jiang's expression was cold as ice: "The ice poison starfish might have a troublesome poison, but I've heard that Su Chen and Fairy Jiu Yue can heal it."

Su Chen was a member of the super force Su clan, he specialized in healing and was famous in Eastern Sea, he was quite a kind person.

Meanwhile, Fairy Jiu Yue was a lone cultivator, she was cold and aloof, the price was high if they wanted to get her help.

Miao Ming Shen shook his head: "I am not going to turn to these two. Su Chen is from Su clan, while Fairy Jiu Yue has some relationship with Ren Xiu Ping, others might not know but I am certain of this. I am highly suspicious that Fairy Jiu Yue might be a trap set by that old scoundrel Ren Xiu Ping!"

"Ah? Then…" Immortal Hua Die did not know what to say.

Miao Ming Shen smiled forcefully: "Have you forgotten? Ice poison starfish's poison can be removed with underworld yellow water."

Feng Jiang stared with wide eyes: "Underworld yellow water is a rank eight immortal material, even in Eastern Sea it is very rare, lord, you have it?"

Miao Ming Shen shook his head: "Of course not, I am going to use the extreme time pole to exchange for it."

Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die understood at once.

Extreme time pole was a rank eight time path immortal material, Miao Ming Shen had obtained it long ago, he could not bear to sell it. Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die knew this.

Immortal Hua Die's expression changed, she said with pity: "Extreme time pole is an extremely rare rank eight time path immortal material, why don't we use other rank eight immortal materials to exchange for the underworld yellow water."

Miao Ming Shen shook his head again: "Rank eight immortal materials are usually exclusively traded with each other. If I use other things to request for the underworld yellow water, others will not want to exchange it for my immortal material, and even if someone wants my rank eight immortal material, they might not have underworld yellow water."

"But now, you all know that Heavenly Court and Southern Border are trying to stop Fang Yuan from doing his business, they are also gathering time path immortal materials and buying them out. Time path immortal materials are now very high in demand, the price is rising sharply. Heavenly Court has a deep foundation, they definitely have underworld yellow water. I will definitely get it if I offer the extreme time pole."

"Lord…" Feng Jiang was hesitant, he remembered that Miao Ming Shen had almost died when he obtained this extreme time pole, he paid a huge price.

Miao Ming Shen laughed loudly, patting Feng Jiang's shoulder: "How can I let him die in front of me? So what if I have to give up the extreme time pole?"

Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die were very moved, they did not follow the wrong leader after all!

As expected, the situation went as Miao Ming Shen predicted, once his extreme time pole appeared, Heavenly Court took notice and the two sides soon traded, Miao Ming Shen obtained a huge amount of underworld yellow water.

He used the underworld yellow water to cleanse Gui Qi Ye's body, he used just the right amount, after all, this water was also corrosive on an undefended Gu Immortal body.

After meticulously cleansing him, the ice poison starfish's poison was fully neutralized.

Not long ago, Gui Qi Ye woke up and opened his eyes.

After learning that Miao Ming Shen had paid such a huge price to save him, he felt extremely moved.

However, he was not an expressive person, he kept his gratitude inside him and said to Miao Ming Shen: "Lord, that old scoundrel Ren Xiu Ping suddenly attacked us, he must be after the blue dragon whale."

Miao Ming Shen sighed: "I think so too, Ren Xiu Ping had always wanted to work together and enter the blue dragon whale to excavate the hidden Paradise Earth true inheritance. But his price is simply not sincere. This time, he actually attacked us, I was truly caught unguarded. What idea do you have, tell me."

Gui Qi Ye nodded: "Lord, you know the blue dragon whale's location, this secret has already been exposed, it is too hard to guard this secret anymore. We should invite people to explore the blue dragon whale instead. When we gain the inheritance inside and increase our strength, we can deal with that Ren Xiu Ping. Otherwise, with our strength now, we cannot defeat that guy. He also has a bunch of lone immortals helping him, as a crafty person, once he senses something amiss, he might spread the news and lure more people to us!"

Miao Ming Shen's gaze flickered: "Instead of waiting for that to happen and letting Ren Xiu Ping gather his people, we should seek reinforcements now. This idea is good, it is our only choice. It is a pity, if I had rank eight cultivation level, we would be able to explore it ourselves."

Gui Qi Ye added: "Lord, we need to choose our reinforcements carefully."

Miao Ming Shen nodded, he looked at the three immortals, asking: "Of course I know, what recommendations do you have?"

The three immortals gave their suggestions.

Miao Ming Shen nodded at times while shaking his head occasionally, he chose a few of them that were suitable, and eliminated some more from among them for safety.

The most important thing was dependability.

But this way, they had few people, even if they worked together, they could not break the first hurdle, they would not be able to enter the blue dragon whale's inner world.

At this time, Immortal Hua Die voiced: "I have a suggestion, does lord remember this person called Chu Ying?"

"Chu Ying." Miao Ming Shen's eyes shined: "Brilliant, this person has rank seven cultivation level and cultivates transformation path, he even has grudges with Ren Xiu Ping. But he is truly too secretive, I have not found any more information on him since then…"

Saying this, he showed hesitation again.

Chapter 1649: Regret

"Paradise Earth's true inheritance?" Within Five Xiang's public grotto-heaven, Fang Yuan received Miao Ming Shen's letter, inviting him to join the exploration of the blue dragon whale.

A light of pondering flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes.

Miao Ming Shen had actually clashed with Ren Xiu Ping, he decided to explore the blue dragon whale ahead of time, this was out of Fang Yuan's expectations.

In the memories of the five hundred years of his previous life, this was too early.

"Maybe it was because of the increasing influence of my rebirth, Miao Ming Shen and Ren Xiu Ping's conflict turned out earlier than expected."

"Maybe the five hundred years of memories were tampered with to begin with. After all, heaven's will was lurking inside Spring Autumn Cicada, it could act very easily if it wanted to."

"There is another possibility, Heavenly Court plotted and deduced my relationship with Miao Ming Shen, so they used this chance to deal with me."

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan calmed his mind and closed his eyes, starting his deduction.

A while later, he opened his eyes, gaining his conclusion: "With all the clues that I have, there is little possibility that Heavenly Court planned this against me, it seems I have to go Eastern Sea now."

Right now in the five regions, Northern Plains and Central Continent had Heavenly Court and Longevity Heaven, they were extremely dangerous for Fang Yuan. For the remaining three regions, Fang Yuan was most familiar with Southern Border. Especially since he had stayed in Wu clan for some time, and had captured many Southern Border Gu Immortals, he knew a lot of information about their super forces.

There was another reason, Shadow Sect's headquarters were set in Southern Border, they had the most operations in Southern Border with many natural immortal formations set up in secret. These were all hidden and unexposed.

With many of the above reasons, Fang Yuan chose to stay in Southern Border.

Even when Hei Lou Lan and the rest underwent tribulation, they were in Southern Border.

Even though the five regions had different heaven and earth qi, forcefully undergoing tribulation outside the home region would harm the immortal aperture, but Fang Yuan did not want them to develop their apertures well anyway. He took care of their cultivation resources, it gave him great control over them.

During this period of time, Fang Yuan had already refined the many Immortal Gu from Qi Sea grotto-heaven, they were usable to him now.

The resources in Qi Sea grotto-heaven and the Five Xiang's public grotto-heaven were also starting to be absorbed.

The remaining rank nine killer move heaven form was very stubborn, it resisted Fang Yuan's refinement. But he was still making progress, in time, he would definitely be able to use it.

Fang Yuan was troubled now because his businesses in treasure yellow heaven were obstructed by Heavenly Court and Southern Border's righteous path, they succeeded in becoming an obstacle for his economic profits.

Fang Yuan thought of many ways to compete with them, but the results were not good.

Be it Central Continent's Heavenly Court or Southern Border's righteous path, they were rich and had deep foundations, Fang Yuan's capital could not match them.

The easiest way to solve this problem was to engage in a monopoly business like guts Gu. But that required countless guts Gu, Fang Yuan lacked souls, even though Dang Hun Mountain was repaired, the production could not be raised.

His plan in green ghost desert had fallen through, if he had succeeded, right now against Southern Border and Central Continent, he would not have any problems.

Qing Chou had gone missing, while the rest of the Western Desert super forces were now finding trouble with Fang clan, they had a hard time raising their statuses.

Fang Yuan had thought of using Fang clan, but he had reservations about this, because his Suan Bu Jin identity was already exposed by Heavenly Court.

His decision to plan for green ghost desert was correct in hindsight. It was a pity that the situation turned out quite different from his expected results.

This way, Fang Yuan's income started to dwindle. And worse was that Central Continent's Heavenly Court was buying all the time path immortal materials they could find.

As long as there were time path immortal materials, Heavenly Court would basically pay them whatever they wanted. During this time in treasure yellow heaven, time path immortal materials were extremely popular.

This was problematic for Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's income had already fallen, he wanted to refine time path Immortal Gu to raise his battle strength in the River of Time, but now, Heavenly Court was oppressively stopping him.

Heavenly Court had been created since the Remote Antiquity Era, after countless years of accumulation, how could Fang Yuan contest them?

Fang Yuan's improvement in time path was very marginal, while Heavenly Court obtained a lot of time path immortal materials, they might even be able to refine a fifth Immortal Gu House.

In this situation, Fang Yuan's hopes of obtaining Red Lotus' true inheritance were dwindling.

"I need a lot of time path immortal materials to refine time path Immortal Gu. Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was an earth path venerable, the Paradise Earth true inheritance inside the blue dragon whale might not have many time path immortal materials. But even so, I must go!"

This was an uncertainty, nobody could say what he would gain.

Even if there were no time path immortal materials, the Paradise Earth true inheritance was definitely going to have some good things.

"Southern Border's rank eight Gu Immortal Lu Wei Yin is the current generation inheritor of Paradise Earth, if I can obtain this Paradise Earth true inheritance, I might gain a way to deal with him."

"The more important thing is that according to my memories, the blue dragon whale seems to contain the rank eight Immortal Gu Regret! In my previous life, Miao Ming Shen explored many times and did not obtain Paradise Earth's true inheritance, but he still gained a lot. Because there were many participating Gu Immortals, rumors of Immortal Gu Regret spread out."

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable used Immortal Gu Regret as the core to create an immortal killer move famous throughout history — Regret and Repent. Using this move, he caused many demonic path Gu Immortals to change sides and realize their mistakes, they turned from evil to kind. This move had incredible achievements.

Immortal Gu Regret was naturally a wisdom path Immortal Gu.

Wisdom path had three elements of thoughts, wills, and emotions. Immortal Gu Regret was part of the emotion branch, because future Gu Immortals created a small path known as emotion path, Immortal Gu Regret was also part of emotion path.

In the long history of humanity, Immortal Gu Regret had appeared many times, sometimes rank six or rank seven, held in the hands of Gu Immortals of the five regions. When it went into Red Lotus Demon Venerable's hands, it seemed to have been refined to rank eight for the first time. Afterwards, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable also obtained rank eight Immortal Gu Regret.

Fang Yuan had investigated deeply into Immortal Gu Regret.

Because he wanted to recreate Regret Pool.

Speaking of which, other than tributaries of the River of Time, Immortal Gu Regret was the core of Immortal Gu House Regret Pool.

But unfortunately, back then in Eastern Sea, the Regret Pool left behind was half-complete, it did not have Immortal Gu Regret.

"If this Paradise Earth true inheritance has rank eight Immortal Gu Regret, with this Gu, I will be able to replicate a portion of Regret Pool's power, it will help in refining Gu!"

This was what moved Fang Yuan the most.

In fact, Regret Pool was part of Fang Yuan's plans. He had extorted Southern Border's righteous path and painstakingly created the incomplete Immortal Gu House, he had some anticipation towards this. Unfortunately, the incomplete Immortal Gu House was destroyed in the River of Time, Fang Yuan could not retrieve any of the Gu worms.

Several days passed in an instant.

Eastern Sea.

Miao Ming Shen looked around, he was surrounded by eight Gu Immortals.

Of course, Fang Yuan was among them.

"Everyone." Miao Ming Shen said solemnly: "I have already explained the details of this expedition, I gave you all some time to consider. This is my first trip too, the risks are unknown, we might possibly die. If anyone wants to give up now, you can leave. I will definitely not stop anyone, I understand from the bottom of my heart."

Sea winds roared by everyone's ears.

Miao Ming Shen looked around again, nobody moved.

Paradise Earth's true inheritance was too valuable, even though there were few earth path Gu Immortals in Eastern Sea, with only one earth path Gu Immortal among everyone here, nobody wanted to give up.

Humans die for wealth and birds die for food.

Furthermore, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was the kindest venerable in history, he had never harmed a single person's life, his immortal inheritances were also known to be safe.

If anyone gave up this chance, they would be a fool!

"Alright, since everyone wants to join, let's make the alliance agreement." Miao Ming Shen was very excited.

For this trip, he had made ample preparations.

"Zeng Luo Zi, please go ahead." Miao Ming Shen cupped his fists as he spoke.

Zeng Luo Zi stepped forward.

He wore a white robe and had a skinny face, he had convex cheekbones and his eye bags were deep, bright light shined in his eyes.

He cultivated information path and was rank seven, Miao Ming Shen had talked to him long ago, he immediately said now: "This is the alliance agreement that we are going to set, everyone, take a look."

Zeng Luo Zi said that as many Gu Immortals shook, looking slightly surprised.

It turned out that the alliance agreement's information appeared in their minds at the same time.

Zeng Luo Zi's action was a show of strength, affirming his superior status among the group.

This Paradise Earth true inheritance expedition had just started but the Gu Immortals were already starting to compete between one another in the dark.

Chapter 1650: Chu Ying's Death

Miao Ming Shen's expression did not change, but his eyes were carefully observing.

Zeng Luo Zi's action was part of his arrangements, he wanted to collect more valuable information.

Zeng Luo Zi's information path attainment was impressive even to Miao Ming Shen. With Zeng Luo Zi's move, Miao Ming Shen observed everyone and gained quite some insight.

"We have eight people, other than myself, Gui Qi Ye, Feng Jiang, and Immortal Hua Die, there are also Zeng Luo Zi, Tu Tou Tuo, Tong Hua, and Chu Ying."

Other than Zeng Luo Zi and Miao Ming Shen, Tong Hua and Tu Tou Tuo were also expressionless.

The rest had some sort of change in their expression at least.

Miao Ming Shen trusted Gui Qi Ye, Feng Jiang, and Immortal Hua Die the most, but in this trip, he did not inform them about this, so their reactions were genuine.

Miao Ming Shen had lots of interaction with Zeng Luo Zi, Tu Tou Tuo, and Tong Hua, he knew about their background, they were all rank seven experts that were rare in Eastern Sea.

In Eastern Sea, there was the highest number of lone immortals who are superior to those of other regions, because Eastern Sea was the most affluent in resources.

Miao Ming Shen's concern was Chu Ying. He had met this secluded cultivator several times, he left a deep impression on Miao Ming Shen. The truth was, Miao Ming Shen did not want to invite Chu Ying. But because Chu Ying and Ren Xiu Ping had a conflict long ago, because he saved the lives of Feng Jiang and Hua Die, and most importantly, because he seemed to have an abundant amount of lifespan Gu, all these reasons made Miao Ming Shen inclined to invite Chu Ying for this trip.

He was the only one who knew the location of the blue dragon whale. Therefore, all of the people he invited owed him a favor.

Miao Ming Shen wanted to cooperate more deeply with Fang Yuan. Forget the rest, just the amount of lifespan Gu that Fang Yuan had was extremely alluring to Miao Ming Shen.

Zeng Luo Zi's action made Chu Ying's expression change too.

As for Tu Tou Tuo and Tong Hua, it was unsure whether they were unaffected or pretending to put up a front.

Miao Ming Shen looked at everyone as he laughed heartily: "Zeng Luo Zi, you have good methods."

Tu Tou Tuo snorted while Tong Hua gave Zeng Luo Zi a cold stare.

Fang Yuan looked at Zeng Luo Zi with a surprised expression, but he was laughing coldly inside.

Zeng Luo Zi's gaze swept past Chu Ying, before meeting with Tu Tou Tuo and Tong Hua's gazes, he laughed heartily as he tossed out some information path mortal Gu.

The information path mortal Gu recorded the fine details of the alliance agreement, after inspecting them, the immortals nodded their heads in agreement, while also suggesting some changes.

Of course, these changes were small and negligible, Miao Ming Shen took charge as the leader and after coming to an agreement, they signed it using Zeng Luo Zi's methods.

Once the alliance agreement was made, everyone laughed as the atmosphere became less tense.

"It is time, let's go." Miao Ming Shen moved at lightning speed as the immortals followed him.

Miao Ming Shen flew in the sky for a while before diving into the sea.

"We can't hide in the sky, it is easy to find us. If Ren Xiu Ping learns of this expedition, he would not wait aimlessly. If we enter the sea, that means we are going to use the undercurrent…"

Fang Yuan speculated inwardly.

As expected, after a while, Miao Ming Shen led everyone to the bottom of the sea, they saw a huge python-like undercurrent crossing the trenches in the sea.

Miao Ming Shen's speed gradually slowed down until he arrived before the undercurrent.

Miao Ming Shen looked at Zeng Luo Zi: "Before entering the undercurrent, for our safety and to ensure we will not be separated, Zeng Luo Zi, I would like you to use that immortal killer move to mark us and allow us to sense each other's location."

This was another way to control them.

But Miao Ming Shen did not say it before the alliance agreement, he had said it before entering the undercurrent, nobody could rebuke his sensible words.

"Miao Ming Shen, are you sure?" Zeng Luo Zi pretended to hesitate.

Miao Ming Shen smiled: "We have already made the agreement, we need to work together sincerely, how can we not trust each other when exploring Paradise Earth's true inheritance?"

He said in a serious tone, Tu Tou Tuo, Tong Hua, and the rest nodded in agreement without objection.

Zeng Luo Zi looked around: "Then everyone, don't be nervous or defensive, my move has no offensive capability."

Fang Yuan mentally rolled his eyes as he said: "Go ahead and do it."

"Let me go first." Feng Jiang stepped forward at once.

Zeng Luo Zi first used the immortal killer move on Feng Jiang before the rest took turns.

After a while, all of the immortals were affected by the information path killer move, they could sense each other's locations.

"It is fine now, please follow me, the undercurrents are extremely fast, if you are slow by a step, you will be thrown far behind." Miao Ming Shen said as he entered the undercurrent.

Fang Yuan and the rest followed after him rapidly.

Eastern Sea's deep sea undercurrents did not have fixed paths, they were always changing and had various lengths, it was a display of the great power of nature.

Moving along the undercurrent, the immortals were faster than some movement immortal killer moves, and most importantly, they saved a lot of energy, only having to put up defenses.

If there were water path Gu Immortals who had methods to move rapidly in the undercurrents, they could even defend themselves while fighting enemies here.

Fang Yuan was towards the rear of the group, he found that this group's formation was quite specific. For example, Immortal Hua Die was right beside him, talking to him constantly.

Fang Yuan entertained her on the surface while secretly inspecting his information path dao marks.

After a while, Fang Yuan relaxed.

These information path dao marks were not hard to get rid of, Fang Yuan had lots of methods. He even had immortal killer moves like self cleansing to resist these information path restrictions.

But now was not the time.

"Everyone, we are about to go out, follow me!" Ahead, Miao Ming Shen suddenly spoke.

After several breaths, he left the undercurrent, the rest followed, nobody was left behind.

After leaving, Fang Yuan found that he was in an ordinary nameless sea area.

In the following journey, the immortals used several undercurrents to travel, if there were no undercurrents, they would travel under the sea as well, being extremely low profile. Even if they met desolate beasts or ancient desolate beasts, they avoided them. If they saw any resources, they would ignore them.

After several days of traveling, the group became more cohesive.

Miao Ming Shen was very skillful in human interaction, he solidified his position as the leader.

He was smiling when he suddenly froze, saying: "We are near!"

The immortals were energized.

Fang Yuan felt a little suspicious, he had used several investigative killer moves but could not sense anything. He could not see what method Miao Ming Shen had used or why he was so confident.

The blue dragon whale's existence was known to everyone. But its exact location was a mystery, Miao Ming Shen must have a unique method to know its location.

Fang Yuan had rank eight cultivation level with immense battle strength, it was possible to kill Miao Ming Shen and search his soul. But there were risks involved, Gu Immortals had all sorts of mysterious methods, if he possessed some strange abilities, there might be mishaps occurring.

Thus, Fang Yuan continued to lurk, it would not be too late if he attacked after getting into the blue dragon whale.

As they got closer, the immortals started to sense the peculiarity.

The seawater became more turbulent ahead, if earlier was a drizzle, it was a storm now, the obstruction was far greater.

Desolate beasts and ancient desolate beasts increased in numbers, they could not help themselves in this huge storm.

Fang Yuan and the rest had to fight while moving, slaughtering a bunch of desolate beasts before they carved out a bloody path to move on.

At this time, everyone's strength was displayed.

Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die had the lowest battle strength, they were soon the ones who needed protection. Miao Ming Shen was leading the group as the vanguard, facing the greatest pressure.

Behind him were Tong Hua and Zeng Luo Zi.

Tu Tou Tuo was an earth path Gu Immortal, his battle strength was greatly restricted in this place.

Next was Fang Yuan, he had already turned into a tiny seahorse that was palm sized, he moved like lightning speed. His strength was only mid-tier in the group, it was nothing impressive.

The journey ahead was getting tougher, from the groups of beasts, figures of immemorial desolate beasts started to appear, the immortals could no longer move forward so casually.

The 'strongest' Miao Ming Shen was merely rank seven.

Following Miao Ming Shen, they flew out of the sea, arriving in the sky.

Rumble!

Intense tornadoes surged in the sky, lightning flashed continuously as thunder rumbled, dark clouds extended to the horizons.

Waves surged from the sea, they were thousands of feet tall.

The situation was just as dangerous as underwater!

Countless flying birds and eagles fought intensely amidst the thunder and lightning.

Blue charm lightning shadows flickered in the dark clouds, they were hunted down by immemorial desolate beast thunder phoenix.

Seeing the tail of the thunder phoenix flash by, Miao Ming Shen and the rest breathed in deeply in shock.

"Quick, follow me!" Miao Ming Shen transmitted, his body was covered in sweat, he flew forward rapidly.

The Gu Immortals all had their hidden methods, but this situation was too chaotic, the safest solution was to get away from this place as quickly as possible.

The thunder phoenix screeched as it discovered Fang Yuan and the rest, diving down.

The seawater erupted as an immemorial octopus large as a mountain moved its countless tentacles, treating Miao Ming Shen and the rest as prey for food.

"Damn it, damn it!" Miao Ming Shen's expression was distorted, he almost broke his teeth from gritting too hard.

Even before meeting the blue dragon whale, they were already in a desperate situation, the aura of death was close.

"Split up and run!" After hesitating for a while, Miao Ming Shen screamed.

The Gu Immortals quickly split up and ran.

Crack!

The thunder phoenix was extremely fast, arriving before Fang Yuan in the blink of an eye.

"Chu Ying!" Immortal Hua Die was dragged along by Gui Qi Ye, upon seeing this, she screamed in fear.

"Save me!" Fang Yuan shouted with a look of despair on his face.

Next, the thunder phoenix arrived in a flash, burning him to a crisp by lightning as he died on the spot.

"Chu Ying…" Seeing this, the remaining seven immortals were shocked, they escaped in an even greater panic.

Chapter 1651: Merit Obelisk

Boom!

A grindstone-sized lightning ball crashed onto Miao Ming Shen's back and exploded intensely.

Guh.

Miao Ming Shen's body shook as he spit out blood, his pale face was even weaker now. He tried to concentrate and use an immortal killer move, vanishing from his spot and appearing several thousand steps away.

But even there, lightning weaved and beasts roared, the situation was truly at its worst.

"To think that I would die here!" Miao Ming Shen was filled with despair.

Wasn't Paradise Earth's true inheritance meant to be mild? Why was it so dangerous here?

These questions were no longer the point, Miao Ming Shen's immortal aperture had run out of immortal essence, even though he had his Immortal Gu left, his escape earlier was the final struggle he could muster.

The roaring of beasts almost burst his eardrums, the immemorial thunder phoenix attacked him again.

Around him, none of the other seven Gu Immortals were left, he had lasted the longest, the rest died one by one earlier.

"If I had known this, I would not have explored Paradise Earth's true inheritance. Dying before even meeting the blue dragon whale, hehehe, Ren Xiu Ping is going to die laughing after hearing this." Miao Ming Shen was filled with regret but he also felt very helpless.

In life, who could predict everything that was going to happen, even if it was a dead end ahead? Even for the great wisdom path Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, could she predict everything?

"Come at me." Miao Ming Shen sighed, straightening his back as he faced the thunder phoenix's sharp claws.

With an intense pain, his vision fell into darkness.

"Did I die…" Miao Ming Shen was quite dazed.

At this time, a voice resounded: "Lord Miao Ming Shen, wake up, quickly wake up."

Miao Ming Shen opened his eyes.

He saw Immortal Hua Die's concerned look, she was standing beside him. Gui Qi Ye, Feng Jiang, and Tu Tou Tuo, even the one who died first, Chu Ying, were all around.

They were all smiling.

"You guys… what happened?" Miao Ming Shen's eyes suddenly flashed: "Wait, is this a test?"

"You are right, we came to that conclusion too." Tu Tou Tuo laughed loudly, replying.

"To think that the first test came before we entered the blue dragon whale, this was simply too dangerous." Miao Ming Shen shook his head, feeling some lingering fear as he inspected his injuries.

But he became stunned immediately.

It turned out that his injuries were all gone, his Gu worms were all intact, even his immortal essence had been restored to its original state.

"This?!" Miao Ming Shen raised his head: "Was it all an illusion?"

"Precisely."

"Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable is truly amazing, we did not notice it at all, we only realized after dying."

"Thinking about it, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was able to create Reincarnation Battlefield, this test was definitely not hard to put up."

"In history, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable created such killer moves to deal with the rank eight expert Combat Demon, Reincarnation Battlefield was the peak of this series, after so many years, Central Continent's ten great ancient sects has nurtured countless Gu Immortal experts using it!"

Miao Ming Shen sighed to himself as his mind got clearer: "I think this is Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's warning, after experiencing death, we can give up many obsessions."

"Lord is right, the feeling of death is truly hard to forget." Feng Jiang sighed.

"At the same time, this is a test of our battle strength. Miao Ming Shen, I have to admit that you are amazing, we saw your performance in the illusion, you lasted the longest among us." Tong Hua smiled.

Miao Ming Shen was joyful but also worried.

Joyful that his great strength had increased his authority in this group, but worried because most of his methods were all exposed. After all, he was facing death, why would he reserve his trump cards?

Miao Ming Shen suddenly thought of Fang Yuan, his gaze flashed: "Chu Ying, to think that I worried and felt aggrieved about you so deeply, yet you were the one who saved the most energy."

His words had deep meaning.

Fang Yuan sighed as he showed a bitter look of shame: "The truth is, I felt horrible when death approached, I was simply too unlucky, why did the immemorial thunder phoenix target me? When I woke up, I was dazed for a long time before gaining clarity."

With attitude Gu, he had sincere and truthful looking acting, Miao Ming Shen stared at Fang Yuan intensely but seeing his expression, his suspicions faded away.

"Then where are we?" Miao Ming Shen looked around, seeing that they were on a nameless island. The island was surrounded by vast blue seawater, extending to the horizons.

There were schools of fish in the sea, waves were moving slowly as winds blew, white seagulls were making sounds, some were flying in the sky while others were flying slightly above the sea level.

"We were about to ask you. We arrived here after waking up, we do not know where to go." Tong Hua said.

Miao Ming Shen nodded: "Everyone, wait a moment."

Next, he shut his eyes, using a mysterious immortal killer move.

This was his unique way of locating the blue dragon whale!

But just on the surface, nobody could decipher his method.

After shutting his eyes, Miao Ming Shen opened it again very quickly, showing shock and joy in his eyes.

"Everyone, as I expected, this is the immortal aperture world of the blue dragon whale!" Miao Ming Shen said some shocking things.

"What?" The immortals were all very surprised.

They more or less knew something about this Paradise Earth true inheritance.

Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable subdued the blue dragon whale and awakened its immortal aperture, he had left behind a Paradise Earth true inheritance in this grotto-heaven.

Years later, many Gu Immortals tried to find the blue dragon whale but could not find anything.

The Gu Immortals were still prepared to see the true appearance of the blue dragon whale, but to think that they would arrive directly inside its immortal aperture.

"Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangements, they are truly something we cannot comprehend fully."

"This means, entering this place has no difficulty?"

"Then why has nobody entered this place before us?"

"Was the blue dragon whale too hard to find…"

"Then what are we going to do now?" Tong Hua asked.

The immortals all focused their attention on Miao Ming Shen.

Miao Ming Shen was quite satisfied with this situation, they had all arrived at the destination without separating, they still wanted to stick together, he did not waste his effort in consolidating his authority as the leader of the group.

"To speak the truth, I am not sure too, but since we are in the grotto-heaven now, we have already succeeded in the first step. Next, we should find the hidden Paradise Earth true inheritance. This is an unknown place that has existed for many years, we do not know what lives here. To be safe, we should travel in a group, even if anything happens, we can take care of each other." Miao Ming Shen's words were acknowledged by everyone.

Fang Yuan spoke at this time: "I have a simple idea, since we entered this place via Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangement, this small island must not be simple, we should search around this island first."

"Nobody explored this place yet?" Miao Ming Shen asked.

The immortals shook their heads, some looked at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled bitterly: "Even though I am the first person who got here and learned of the illusion, I was afraid of the lurking danger here. I have been guarding our current location since then."

"Alright, let's split up and look around this small island." Miao Ming Shen immediately gave them some missions.

This island was small, with so many people around, they soon found clues: "Quickly come to the center of the island, there is a rank eight Immortal Gu House here!"

A moment later, eight Gu Immortals stood in front of the Immortal Gu House.

This Immortal Gu House had a peculiar design, from the outside, it looked like an obelisk made of gold.

The surface of the obelisk had many inscriptions.

Feng Jiang took a few glances and shouted: "So this is Paradise Earth's true inheritance!"

Immortal Hua Die who was beside him frowned: "It is really troublesome to inherit this true inheritance."

The obelisk stated that this rank eight Immortal Gu House was a merit board, it was effective in the entire grotto-heaven world. If outside Gu Immortals wanted to gain Paradise Earth's true inheritance, they would need to do the missions on this obelisk and gain merits after completing them.

The more merits they had, the more valuable things they could exchange for.

If one did not accept this, they could only wait on this island, they could not leave and go to other places in the grotto-heaven world.

"According to the inscription, we can only stay here for three hundred days." Tong Hua said with a regretful tone.

Three hundred days in terms of the dragon whale grotto-heaven's time.

"What missions can we do in three hundred days?" Zeng Luo Zi's eyes flashed with bright light, there were only ten missions on this obelisk, each one was different, it meant that these Gu Immortals were going to engage in competition later.

The others were not stupid, they quickly realized this problem, the atmosphere became heavier all of a sudden.

Miao Ming Shen acutely sensed the change in the atmosphere as he spoke: "Everyone, even though the inscription says that, this is our first time here, we cannot be so sure. In my opinion, we should test if we can leave this island. I hope you can all research on this Immortal Gu House, if you have a way of moving it, we can take it for ourselves, that would be wonderful!"

The immortals were deeply moved, this was a rank eight Immortal Gu House, if they could break it and take parts of it, they would have great gains.

Miao Ming Shen continued: "When we looked around, we found a lot of cultivation resources on this island, they are in huge quantities. We should decide on how to split these resources, what do you think?"

The immortals would only benefit from this, why would they disagree, everyone cheered in acknowledgment.

Chapter 1652: Choosing Mission

The island was small but it contained a lot of cultivation resources.

With this size and amount of resources, they were clearly intentionally arranged.

Fang Yuan and the other Gu Immortals looked around and scavenged for resources before redistributing them. Fang Yuan as Chu Ying was a transformation path Gu Immortal, he obtained a lot of transformation path immortal materials.

But because transformation path projected all paths, these immortal materials were of various types and paths. For example, soul beast cores were soul path immortal materials, but if a transformation path Gu Immortal has a way to transform into soul beasts, then this soul core was also a type of resource for the transformation path Gu Immortal.

Fang Yuan used transformation path as the concealment to pick a lot of time path immortal materials.

Zeng Luo Zi seemingly asked casually: "Friend Chu Ying has a time path transformation? Why didn't you use it when we were in the illusion?"

Fang Yuan laughed: "I am just being greedy, I am sure everyone knows about the demon Fang Yuan. These time path immortal materials can be sold in treasure yellow heaven for many good things. But if I compete with everyone here, it will harm our relationship after all."

"Hahaha, that is a good idea Chu Ying, why didn't I think of it?" Tu Tou Tuo laughed.

Zeng Luo Zi's eyes flashed with bright light, he stopped talking.

After the scare from the illusion, these Gu Immortals finally had a change of mood, these gains were quite valuable after all.

Especially when Miao Ming Shen was not corrupt, he split the gains equally, the atmosphere of the group was quite lively.

Half a day later, the immortals gathered before the rank eight Immortal Gu House Merit Obelisk.

"According to the information on the Merit Obelisk, these resources were all arranged by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable back then, it was to ensure that the Gu Immortals who did not want to accept the missions would still gain some rewards. Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable was truly a kind person!" Tong Hua was in awe.

Gui Qi Ye pondered: "All of us have acted already, we have tried to but this island cannot be broken through forcefully."

"And this Merit Obelisk, we cannot unravel it with our abilities." Feng Jiang added.

The immortals were silent.

How could Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangements be so easily broken? Especially when all these Gu Immortals barring Fang Yuan were rank seven, even though some were elites, against a venerable, they were nothing.

"Miao Ming Shen, I wonder what insight you have?" Tong Hua asked.

Miao Ming Shen shook his head: "I know nothing about Paradise Earth's true inheritance, I am like all of you. In my opinion, since we cannot forcefully unravel Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's arrangements, we only have two options. One is to ignore the obelisk's missions and stay here for three hundred days, once the time is up, we will likely be sent out. The second way is to follow and complete the missions on the obelisk."

The immortals looked at each other.

Undeniably, the resources on the island were all distributed already, who would want to stay here for three hundred days?

The immortals had already gained something, their interest in Paradise Earth's true inheritance grew as well.

In their opinion, the cultivation resources on the island were just the appetizers, Paradise Earth's true inheritance was the true treasure here.

"But to accept missions, we will need to be acknowledged by the Merit Obelisk. The process is like a super clan's life tablet Gu and soul lantern Gu, but more restrictive in nature. If this is a trap…"

"Risk and reward are often interlinked, we came to explore Paradise Earth's true inheritance, weren't we taking a risk? I am going to accept the mission."

"Since this is an arrangement of Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, there must be no problem. The true inheritance is right in front of us, if we stop now, we will regret it for life."

…

After some discussion, none of the eight Gu Immortals wanted to give up.

According to the inscription, the eight immortals went up and placed their palms on the Merit Obelisk.

With a bright flash of light, the eight immortals' names were all displayed on the obelisk, the blank area earlier turned into a list.

Fang Yuan's name was there too, but 'Chu Ying' was written instead.

This made Fang Yuan let out a sigh of relief.

He had inspected this Merit Obelisk already, it mainly comprised earth path and sound path, he could not deduce it. Of course, there was a chance of destroying it with Fang Yuan's battle strength. But the risks were too high, he was better off disguising himself and exploring with the others.

The Gu Immortal world was filled with countless methods, this Merit Obelisk was a rank eight Immortal Gu House made by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable, it had a high possibility of exposing his true name. Thankfully, that did not happen, otherwise, Fang Yuan would have to kill everyone around if he got exposed.

His identity was too important, these people might have some peculiar methods, even if they did not, it would be bad if Heavenly Court was lured over.

"Before I understand the situation, I should not attack them. This is Paradise Earth's true inheritance after all, he emphasized on forgiving people for their mistakes, he was kind and magnanimous, if I kill people randomly, something bad might happen."

The eight immortals were listed on the Merit Obelisk, they started to look at the missions.

There were only ten missions written.

Each mission had a vague description, the Gu Immortal needed to explore it themselves.

For example, the first mission — exterminate the surrounding water monsters around sea eagle city.

Water monsters were similar to soul beasts, they were both dao beasts that had various forms, most of them would dissipate after dying, leaving behind water cores or soul cores. These were immortal materials filled with abundant water path and soul path dao marks.

But what level were these water monsters, were they ancient level water monsters or desolate beast level water monsters, there was no information.

Sea eagle city? What was that? Where was it? There was no information.

There was still some clues regarding exterminating water monsters here, but the remaining missions were weirder.

For example, creating a water well in fish round island, or gathering medicinal herbs for three tattoo tribe, maintaining a spirit spring, protecting the merchant caravan, fixing the formation, and others.

The eight immortals looked at the Merit Obelisk, after thinking for a while, Zeng Luo Zi sighed: "My information path methods are useless against this rank eight Immortal Gu House, whatever mission we choose is based on luck. Let me try first, I will choose the first water monster extermination mission."

The others were silent.

Even though Zeng Luo Zi said that, the missions had differences.

Using logical deduction, the harder the mission, the greater the merits. Water monsters were at least desolate beasts, the mission of eliminating them was naturally difficult, the merit reward should be quite high.

As for maintaining a spirit spring, protecting the merchant caravan, and others, they were mortal level missions, the difficulty was lower than exterminating water monsters.

Zeng Luo Zi's choice was clearly to snatch the best mission, the atmosphere in the group suddenly changed.

Zeng Luo Zi remained silent but he was a little nervous in his heart.

Miao Ming Shen nodded as he agreed and said: "Go ahead, I will be the last one."

Everyone looked at him with a different gaze the moment he said that.

Miao Ming Shen waved his hand, saying: "No need to overthink it, I just feel that Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable created such an arrangement with deeper intentions, how could he not think of balance? These simple missions might not be as easy as they seem."

Everyone nodded upon hearing Miao Ming Shen's words.

Tong Hua spoke: "I choose the second mission."

Tu Tou Tuo made his choice too.

Their decision was the same as Zeng Luo Zi, they evidently chose the harder missions.

After Tu Tou Tuo chose the mission, there was still one seemingly hard one. The rest of the missions were all very ordinary.

There were still three rank sevens left, they were Miao Ming Shen, Fang Yuan, and Gui Qi Ye.

"Next… go ahead and choose, Chu Ying." Miao Ming Shen took a look and smiled.

Feng Jiang and Immortal Hua Die were beside him, they did not speak.

"Wait." Gui Qi Ye suddenly interjected: "Everyone, Lord Miao Ming Shen, to speak the truth, I wanted this mission from the start."

The immortals' expressions all turned weird.

Miao Ming Shen looked at Gui Qi Ye, showing a gaze of shock and criticism.

But Gui Qi Ye ignored him, he looked at Fang Yuan eerily.

"Picking on the weakest person?" Fang Yuan chuckled in his heart, saying: "Gui Qi Ye, since you like it, this means that the mission has an affinity with you, I will not snatch it from you. Hmm… I will choose the seventh mission."

Everyone turned to look, this seventh mission was to collect Earth Trench black oil from the deep sea, it was something that only mortals would do.

Miao Ming Shen quickly added: "Chu Ying…"

"No need to refuse it, I am truly in admiration of Brother Miao for having such a companion. You deserve it, if not for you, how could I have gotten in here?" Fang Yuan laughed heartily.

Gui Qi Ye looked at Fang Yuan with a kinder gaze now.

Indeed, he forcefully chose the mission not for himself, but for Miao Ming Shen.

Like what Fang Yuan had said, everyone could come here due to Miao Ming Shen, he deserved it with his contribution.

Miao Ming Shen refused, but Fang Yuan persisted.

Miao Ming Shen was helpless as he accepted it.

A moment later, everyone made their choice, the Merit Obelisk shot out a pillar of light, the Gu Immortals were all transported away once they stepped inside.

Fang Yuan's field of vision changed, when he blinked, he was on an unknown island.

"I am a rank eight Gu Immortal, but that Merit Obelisk transported me with no effort. It seems to be the core of this entire grotto-heaven, it is truly profound, as expected of Paradise Earth!"

Regarding these missions, he had a similar conjecture to Miao Ming Shen. He gave up that mission earlier not because he was courteous, but because he was probing Miao Ming Shen.

After Fang Yuan left, only Gui Qi Ye and Miao Ming Shen were left.

"Oh you…" Miao Ming Shen sighed.

Gui Qi Ye cupped his fists: "Please forgive me, lord."

"What wrong did you do? It is just that you underestimated Chu Ying. He was the first person to die in the illusion, so you think he is weak." Miao Ming Shen shook his head.

"Lord thinks Chu Ying is hiding his strength?"

Miao Ming Shen shook his head: "I did not detect anything, the possibility of that is small. But in this unknown environment, we should unite instead of having internal conflicts."

"Yes, I understand."

Chapter 1653: Previous Life's Most Beloved

With Fang Yuan's investigative methods, this island was completely transparent in his eyes.

He found that this island that the Merit Obelisk transported him to was very common and ordinary. There were few resources on the island, there was a small fishing village with some people living there.

There was a fishing village, a spirit spring existed as well, of course. Gu Masters existed here too, but in such a poor and desolate place, a rank four Gu Master was the utmost limit.

Fang Yuan had accepted the mission to collect Earth Trench black oil from the deep sea, after he investigated, he soon found that there were traces of black oil oozing out near the fringe of the island.

Other Gu Immortals might go into the sea to collect the black oil already, but Fang Yuan did not do that, the moment he saw the Merit Obelisk, he started to think about Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's intentions.

He concealed himself as he entered the fishing village, it did not have many people living in it, there were only five or six Gu Masters, the highest cultivation was a rank three Gu Master, it could not compare to Gu Yue clan on Qing Mao Mountain. Back then, Gu Yue clan had about ten of such villages under it.

Fang Yuan directly approached the sole rank three Gu Master in the village.

This was an old man with white hair and deep wrinkles, from what others said, he was the village head.

Fang Yuan was quite satisfied.

Having high authority and being old, he naturally knew a lot of things.

Soul search!

Fang Yuan used his immortal method, the old village head's secrets were all exposed.

Instantly, Fang Yuan gained a lot of information that was rather precise. As he expected, this village was very ordinary. There were many of such villages around the island.

"This fishing village doesn't seem to have any trap." Fang Yuan realized this and left the village secretly.

The old village head only felt dazed for a moment, even though it was a bit weird, he went on with his business soon after.

Fang Yuan's soul search method was simply too incredible for mortal Gu Masters to realize.

Fang Yuan left the island and flew to the surrounding islands.

But Fang Yuan experienced what happened on the Merit Obelisk island earlier again.

Even though he could see a small island in the horizon, no matter how he flew, the distance did not shorten.

After using all his methods, Fang Yuan still returned helplessly.

"Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable cultivated sound path in his early years before converting to earth path later, this method of controlling distance is his signature move."

There were many battles in history that showed Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable standing on the spot as his enemies attacked. No matter what they did, their attacks could not reach him, even though the distance was short.

"Other than that, Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable has an extremely alluring method, that was to create paradise."

Paradise…

This was also the reason for Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's title. Nobody knew how a paradise was created, but Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable left behind many paradises in the five regions and two heavens.

A paradise's most distinct trait was the lack of calamities and tribulations!

"This dragon whale grotto-heaven was transformed by Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable into a paradise."

From the old village head's soul, Fang Yuan obtained a lot of information that confirmed this. If there were calamities and tribulations, even if the old man could not feel it, there would be information in the village's historical records, but there was none.

Since he could not go to the other islands, he changed directions and entered the water.

As he got deeper, the water pressure intensified.

This water pressure was a problem for Gu Masters trying to excavate oil, but for rank eight Gu Immortals like Fang Yuan, it was an insignificant problem.

For Gu Masters, the sea was very deep, but for Gu Immortals, the water surrounding the island was still very shallow.

Fang Yuan soon found that a large area of darkness appeared in his vision. It was like a huge seaweed that endlessly extended in all directions.

This Earth Trench under the water was very spectacular, the ordinary island was at the fringe of this Earth Trench. From the information he got from the old village head, the surrounding islands were also connected to the extensions of this Earth Trench.

Earth Trenches produced black oil.

Regardless of ordinary Earth Trenches or deep sea Earth Trenches.

Black oil was an immortal material belonging to food path. The quality was very high and production was abundant, it was easy to excavate.

This was a trait of food path, having high production with cheap costs, it was very economically friendly.

Black oil was extremely helpful to immortal zombies. Spreading the black oil in the dead aperture could slow the speed of the disintegration of the blessed land. In the outside world, or to other Gu Immortals, it was a very useful Gu refinement material that was widely used, it had a huge market.

One of the main business of Zombie Alliance was black oil. This was similar to Fang Yuan's guts Gu, but the scale of black oil sold was much larger than guts Gu.

"There are about three million kilograms of black oil here. I can take them all within half a day if I go all out. But I cannot leave the island after a certain distance, even though black oil can move, it is much slower than water. After I take all the black oil here, it will take too long and be too inefficient to wait for the black oil from the other parts of the Earth Trench to flow here."

Black oil was very easy to collect, but that was for Gu Immortals.

For mortal Gu Masters, it was quite difficult.

There was a special category of oil collecting Gu Masters. They specialized in exploring Earth Trenches to collect black oil, these people were professionals in this business. Oil collecting Gu Masters had their own set of Gu worms specially used to collect a certain amount of black oil.

Even though their battle strength was not high, because they were excavating immortal materials, they had abundant wealth and status, they were quite popular.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, Fang Yuan had once been an oil collecting Gu Master in Eastern Sea. That was his fortuitous encounter, he almost became the son-in-law of a certain oil collecting Gu Master, the collection method was also imparted to Fang Yuan by this old Gu Master.

People lived according to their environment, the Gu Masters on the small island survived mainly by collecting black oil. The old Gu Master that Fang Yuan soul searched was the most impressive oil collecting Gu Master in the village. Even though he was old, he would still enter the water and collect them each year.

Seeing the black oil here, Fang Yuan could not help but recall some of his previous life's memories.

He was once an oil collecting Gu Master, he entered the sea to collect black oil, but it was a dangerous job, he was treading on thin ice. The first problem was oxygen, secondly, he could not go too deeply, the pressure would kill him. And the sea was not peaceful, there were many fierce beasts underneath. And finally, he needed specialized methods for the black oil.

How could mortals not use special methods when collecting immortal materials?

Especially if they did not collect the black oil well, it would pollute their bodies, the Gu Master would be covered in black oil grease, it was hard to remove and carried a disgusting stench, as time passes, it would even corrode the Gu Master's own mortal body.

In his previous life, Fang Yuan had been polluted by this black oil. The old Gu Master who taught him the method purposely did that so that he would be forced to marry his daughter.

He was furious back then and felt like he was plotted against, but thinking about it now, Fang Yuan smiled bitterly.

The teacher had no son or inheritor, he had to do that or he could not impart his family's unique methods to an outsider Gu Master. He had no choice but to use that tactic, what was wrong with playing safe? It was normal!

But back then, Fang Yuan was placed into despair, he had no alternatives.

Without specialized methods, he could not clear the black oil pollution. Even if Fang Yuan knew the method, he needed the Gu worms to do that. These reasons made him relent.

Thinking of this, Fang Yuan felt a sense of his mindset back then.

He was very anxious and in pain, he was greatly attracted to the profits of excavating black oil, he secretly swore that he would change the situation! For example, there were water path Gu worms that could allow him to dive agilely, he could also design some Gu worms to resist the water pressure.

Currently, he could totally refine a bunch of Immortal Gu and create a huge quantity of useful mortal Gu instantly.

But he no longer needed them.

Life often threw you into situations like this. At present, you lack some very crucial things, but when you obtain them, you no longer need them.

That was why getting things when you needed them the most was called a fortuitous encounter, you had to treasure them if it happened.

"Back then when I extracted black oil, I almost died."

"But fortune and calamity come together, I actually met Mo Er when about to die… from that perspective, the old Gu Master did something good after all."

Fang Yuan showed a complex and deep smile on his face.

The white figure appeared in his mind once again.

Her expression was both vague and clear at the same time.

Her name was Xie Han Mo.

Xie Han Mo.

Fang Yuan had never forgotten this name, because she was the person he loved the most in his previous life.

Chapter 1654: Water Shell Gu

Several days later.

Waves ebbed and flowed, crashing into the rocks and creating huge splashes.

Putting it crudely, the unnamed island was poor and had treacherous waters. Firstly, the island was small, and secondly, there was Earth Trench black oil here. Because of the black oil, the resources of other cultivation paths were suppressed, nothing else could exist here.

The greed of humanity was limitless, the concept of human path revolved around reducing deficits and increasing surpluses, the strong grew stronger. Meanwhile, heaven path took away surpluses while replenishing deficits, it emphasized on the balance of all myriad beings.

Precisely due to an immortal material like black oil, the unnamed island had almost no other resources, the size of the fishing village had been like this for centuries, development was slow and they could only nurture single digits of Gu Masters, they were truly few.

Right now, at the center of the fishing village, in the village head's house, Fang Yuan was currently fighting against a rank two Gu Master.

Boom boom boom.

After some clashes, water splashed around, the middle aged rank two Gu Master was drenched, he sprawled on the ground weakly.

Fang Yuan was using Chu Ying's appearance as he stood on the spot, his arms were behind his back as he smiled lightly.

From the start to the finish of this battle, Fang Yuan was standing on the spot, having not moved at all.

The rank two Gu Master stood up weakly as he cupped his fists: "Master Chu has incredible methods, I am in great awe, thank you for the guidance Master Chu."

He was truly in awe.

A few days ago, Fang Yuan disguised as a rank four Gu Master and entered the fishing village openly, he started to interact with the Gu Masters here.

Back then, his appearance caused a commotion. There were usually no outsiders in the fishing village, especially not a solitary visitor.

Fang Yuan's identity was a traveling Gu Master, he managed to make his presence in the fishing village. Undeniably, his appearance completely disrupted the original peaceful life of the villagers.

Even a mortal without any cultivation would know that a strong Gu Master had entered their village.

Traveling Gu Master.

Such Gu Masters traveled the world, they had no home, they were usually alone but some moved in groups of two or three as well.

Traveling Gu Masters normally had great strength and few weaknesses.

It was common sense.

The world outside was not safe, traveling Gu Masters were able to travel around, they naturally had sufficient strength to do so. This was not just in terms of battle strength, they also needed to take care of their accommodation, food, movement, and feeding of Gu worms.

Without enough strength, one could not become a traveling Gu Master.

Thus, when Fang Yuan appeared, the Gu Masters in the fishing village became very alert.

Fang Yuan's rank four Gu Master aura was extremely threatening to them.

The first time they met, Fang Yuan claimed that he needed to feed Gu, he asked for Gu materials from the old village head.

The old village head was the sole rank three Gu Master in the fishing village, Fang Yuan had searched his soul. He did not dare to reject the request, he had to agree.

After the spar, the middle aged rank two Gu Master approached the village head.

Shutting the door and readying their Gu worms in defense, the two started to talk.

The middle aged Gu Master did not speak, he had a bitter and worrying expression. The old village head smiled: "Now you know how strong Master Chu is?"

The middle aged Gu Master nodded: "Master Chu has unfathomable strength, even if we join forces, we will not be his match!"

Saying so, he looked at the village head with an indignant expression: "But why should we give him Gu materials? His Gu worms are hungry, that is his problem, why must we solve it for him? Most importantly, our inventory was stocked up over the last few generations, he used up almost everything in just a few days!"

The old village head was silent for a moment before saying with deep meaning: "Traveling Gu Masters have a certain rule, they usually exchange for Gu materials to feed their Gu worms when they arrive in a new place. These Gu Masters are very strong so local forces would usually not reject them, they would cooperate and improve their relationship. We should treat it as a chance encounter."

The middle aged Gu Master frowned, the anger in his voice became more prominent: "Lord village head, you said it yourself, they exchange! But this Master Chu directly took the materials, he did not exchange anything for them."

"So what do you think? What can we do?" The old village head looked at the middle aged Gu Master.

The middle aged Gu Master was stumped, after a few breaths, his anger dissipated, his back became bent as his face was full of bitterness, pain, and helplessness.

"It is about time." At the other end, Fang Yuan smiled.

The conversation between the middle aged Gu Master and the old village head was under Fang Yuan's supervision. In fact, he knew everything inside this fishing village.

A few days ago, he went into the deep sea and wanted to take some black oil. But afterwards, he had a flash of inspiration, he changed his idea.

Fang Yuan realized: "Collecting black oil is nothing, the true key is Paradise Earth's true inheritance! I should test this situation."

Thus, Fang Yuan changed his method, he disguised as a traveling Gu Master to enter the village.

The next day.

The old village head saw that Fang Yuan had visited him, he was filled with bitterness but still showed a smile on the surface, he bent his back as he said: "Master Chu, do you need more Gu materials?"

Fang Yuan smiled: "Old sir, thank you for the hospitality, I am about to leave."

The old village head was dazed, great joy surged in his heart but he controlled himself, he showed a shocked and sad expression, urging: "Master Chu, you are leaving so soon? Why don't you stay for a few more days, we would like to offer you more of our hospitality."

Fang Yuan shook his head, joking: "Old sir, I have imposed on you for the last few days, if I stay any longer, they might not spar with me anymore, but risk their lives to fight me next."

The old village head was shocked as he smiled bitterly: "So you know about it."

Fang Yuan spoke calmly: "I have traveled for many years, how can I not understand your mindset? I do not like to bully the weak, so before I leave, I will leave some things to you."

The old village head was joyful but also a little suspicious, he waved his hand: "Master Chu, no need for that, you are too kind."

"Call all of the Gu Masters here." Fang Yuan stopped smiling, he spoke plainly.

A moment later, all of the Gu Masters in the village had arrived in the old village head's house, except the middle aged Gu Master who sparred the previous day.

"Unfortunately, he went to the deep sea to collect black oil, he is going to miss out today." The old village head explained.

Fang Yuan looked at him deeply as he smiled: "Village head, you've worried too much. Everyone, look at this Gu worm."

Fang Yuan opened his hand, showing a rank two mortal Gu.

This Gu worm was white and blue, it resembled a seashell and was large as a jade bracelet.

Fang Yuan continued: "This is water shell Gu, it can form a layer of water as a shell on the Gu Master's body to resist the sea's water pressure. Using just this Gu worm, you can go six li deep into the sea."

The Gu Masters in the house went into a commotion.

"Rank two Gu worm that can go six li down into the sea?"

"Water shell Gu, why have I never heard of it?"

Fang Yuan smiled: "Try it."

After trying it for a while, the Gu Masters were overjoyed, they found that this Gu worm had another advantage, it used very little primeval essence.

"This is a really rare and precious rank two Gu!" Someone said with a trembling voice.

"It is a pity there is only one…"

This person immediately got fierce stares from the village head.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily: "Don't worry, everyone will get it." Saying so, he took out more water shell Gu, everyone had their own one.

Almost ten water shell Gu were handed out, only one remained in Fang Yuan's hands. He passed it to the old village head: "Give this to him."

The old village head was very moved, he apologized in a choked up voice: "I was wrong, Master Chu is truly magnanimous!"

Fang Yuan gathered the Gu Masters in the village, the old village head was afraid that Fang Yuan was trying to wipe them out, what should he do?

That was not impossible at all.

People were hard to understand, especially when this was a stranger.

Thus, the old village head placed the middle aged Gu Master, his future successor, in a secret location, he was afraid of Fang Yuan's attack!

Fang Yuan's act of giving the water shell Gu made the old village head extremely happy and also ashamed.

But Fang Yuan had just started.

"This is water shell Gu's recipe, I will give it to you." Fang Yuan gave out ten Gu recipes to the Gu Masters present.

They were all stunned!

Giving Gu worms and giving recipes were two different concepts entirely!

"Master Chu, how can we take it?" The old village head received the recipe with trembling hands.

"No worries, take a look at the content." Fang Yuan waved his hand.

Everyone took a look as someone shouted: "Oh heavens, the core Gu material of this water shell Gu is the spiral seashell on the shore of our island's beach?"

"The Gu materials of this recipe can all be found on our island!!" Immediately after, someone shouted.

Fang Yuan nodded: "I have some insight in Gu refinement, these last days, after sparring with several Gu Masters, I understood your lifestyle and cultivation method, while inspecting this island, I tried to look for useful materials. I created this Gu recipe for your village, you must accept it."

As he said that, Fang Yuan saw that the old village head had knelt down on the ground in an instant.

The old village head kowtowed as he said: "I was too blind to see Mount Tai, I did not know that Master Chu was such a genius in Gu refinement! I am too ashamed, I actually misunderstood Master Chu's kindness…"

Before the old village head finished, Fang Yuan helped him to stand up as he smiled and said: "Old sir, don't say that. I am someone who believes that a droplet received in need will be repaid with a whole spring. The Gu materials I got from you were very helpful for my problem. Our encounter is a type of fortune, we need to treasure it."

"But I have just created this water shell Gu, I am not sure of its exact value in reality. Why don't you select a few people to enter the sea with me? We can collect some black oil and test out its actual effect."

"We will do as you say!"

Chapter 1655: Collecting Black Oil

Vague water ripples were moving before the eyes, in extreme tranquility, a group of Gu Masters dived into the sea.

The light above them became dimmer, the surrounding seawater was emitting greater pressure on them.

Someone started to use water shell Gu.

The water shell Gu that Fang Yuan invented was simply amazing!

Almost the instant it was activated, the fishing village's Gu Masters felt their pressure reducing, their bodies felt relaxed, as if they had discarded a ton of dead weight.

The Gu Masters all showed joyful expressions, even though they had already tested water shell Gu in their village earlier.

But at this time, someone suddenly made an alert signal.

A large number of weaving sea spiders were approaching them.

These sea spiders moved very quickly underwater, they would split up when they encountered prey, shooting out their spider webs that would entangle the prey before they attacked.

Seeing this group of sea spiders, the fishing village's Gu Masters turned pale, even the rank three village head was full of fear, he could not calm down.

The sea spider group was huge, and they were most skilled at fighting with numbers, to defeat a stronger enemy with collective effort. Many sea creatures would often die to them due to a battle of attrition.

Even rank three Gu Masters were not their match in a drawn out fight.

The deep sea had too much danger. On the surface, the sea was calm, but under the sea, undercurrents surged, dangers lurked everywhere.

"No need to worry." Fang Yuan transmitted before waving his hand at the crucial moment.

At the next moment, the Gu Masters of the fishing village were so shocked their eyes almost popped out!

A huge whirlpool formed instantly, it crashed into the sea spiders, it was like a tornado that swept away all of the sea spiders in it.

"Quickly leave, I cannot sustain it for long." Fang Yuan said purposely.

The fishing village's Gu Masters realized at once and quickly dived deeper.

After they got to a safe distance, the Gu Masters turned back to look, the whirlpool had started to dissipate. The sea spiders were completely disoriented, they had low intelligence and moved according to instinct, seeing that the prey vanished, they gathered again and moved away.

The Gu Masters relaxed at long last, their gazes towards Fang Yuan was filled with admiration and reverence.

The Gu Masters who fought against Fang Yuan earlier finally saw how powerful this Master Chu was! And most importantly, his method was very wise.

If they fought in the sea, the blood would attract more problems.

Trapping but not killing, that was the work of an expert.

The group continued to move with Fang Yuan as their guardian, they met with no danger.

Sea spiders were just one of the lurking dangers, oil collecting Gu Masters faced hundreds of types of aquatic beasts, sometimes, they would even get swept into special currents, helplessly moving along with them.

In the following journey, some problems still occurred, but they were not disasters like the sea spiders.

Diving and stopping continuously, after some hard work, they finally reached the Earth Trench.

They did not need to dive into the Earth Trench, because there was a lot of black oil here already. There had been no Gu Immortals who came to excavate them.

The Earth Trench was filled with black oil, at the same time, some gushes of black oil leaked outside. These black oil streams were like octopuses with long tentacles, they also seemed like seaweed, messy and scattered.

The fishing village's Gu Masters quickly used their Gu worms to get close to the leaking black oil.

They started to collect the oil, moving around like worker bees.

Fang Yuan did not act, he watched from afar.

These Gu worms specially used to collect black oil were the core and vital Gu of these Gu Masters, Fang Yuan did not ask them about this in their previous interactions because it was taboo, but with his ability, he could understand everything with just a single look.

His refinement path quasi-supreme grandmaster attainment level was not a joke!

"The number one resource around this unnamed island is black oil. When I use this black oil as material to refine Gu worms for them, their efficiency will increase."

While he was thinking of this, suddenly, a huge group of seashell sharks approached them.

These sharks opened their bloodthirsty mouths, full of shells that were used as sharp teeth.

The seashell sharks were very special.

They began life without teeth, instead, when they grew up, they would choose seashells in the sea and put them in their mouths. As time passed, these seashells would take root and grow, the more years that pass, the whiter and tougher they would become.

The seashell sharks would use the shells as teeth to tear prey that were stronger than seashell sharks apart.

This special relationship made infant seashell sharks very weak, but when they reach adulthood, they would be overlords of the sharks.

This group of sharks were attacking, be it individual or group strength, they far surpassed the sea spiders. But the fishing village Gu Masters were not afraid.

They moved around the black oil terrain with ease and agility. From time to time, they would spray the black oil that they collected as barriers to shield themselves.

Seashell sharks were huge and could not move easily in this black oil area, if the oil stuck to them, they would become slower and even struggle to move as the oil got thicker.

The fishing village Gu Masters used the territory to quickly feed these seashell sharks to the black oil as food.

These seashell sharks struggled until they had no strength left, they were slowly devoured by the black oil.

Normally speaking, the black oil would take a long time to completely corrode these seashell sharks, all of their flesh, bone and blood would turn into new black oil.

Black oil was an immortal material that contained food path dao marks, it was not safe, the Earth Trench filled with black oil was a dangerous area.

Fang Yuan saw this as he sighed in his heart.

He remembered that in the five hundred years of his previous life, he had once seen how the black oil devoured its prey for the first time. From that day on, he had nightmares for several nights, of the black oil sticking onto him and slowly devouring him without any hope of salvation.

Normally speaking, oil collecting Gu Masters would work in groups, they were afraid that the black oil would stick to them and kill them in the process of collection.

But the oil collecting Gu Masters in the fishing village would not form groups, it was too easy for disputes to arise, and encountering dangerous situations might cause everyone to perish.

Right now, everyone grouped together, but it was a special situation.

"I advise that you try to drag out the seashell sharks that are trapped, these are all usable Gu materials." Fang Yuan transmitted.

"Master Chu, these seashell sharks are polluted by the black oil." The old village head hesitated.

"Don't worry, I have a way to remove the black oil. Trust me, these seashell sharks are very useful for you." Fang Yuan smiled.

He had designed a Gu recipe that used these seashell sharks as the main material.

Without water shell Gu, these Gu Masters would not believe him, but after Fang Yuan displayed such strength, the old village head stopped hesitating, he ordered: "You all heard him, hurry up and do it. But be careful, don't let the black oil stick to you, it is too troublesome otherwise."

Not just troublesome, the price would be huge!

Black oil was an immortal material, once it got stuck, the food path dao marks would be carved onto the Gu Master's body. Just the problem of conflicting dao marks would be fatal, and because they had mortal bodies, they could not endure the corrosion of the black oil.

"Don't worry, I can remove the black oil on you even if it sticks to you." Fang Yuan spoke.

His words made the Gu Masters overjoyed, but even with his assurance, the Gu Masters still acted carefully, they were afraid of touching this beloved and accursed black oil.

The seashell sharks were all dragged out.

Most were not dead, they still had some vitality.

Falling into the black oil would not cause suffocation immediately.

At this time, a small surprise occurred.

"Look at what I found? A trapped mermaid." A Gu Master dragged out a mermaid corpse.

Her body was covered in black oil, her appearance could not be seen, but from her build, it seemed to be a girl.

"She has some life force left…" The Gu Master who saved the mermaid said with surprise.

"Let me." Fang Yuan acted.

The Gu Masters were very shocked, because they saw that the black oil moved like an obedient child, getting away from the mermaid and gathering in front of Fang Yuan as a big black ball.

"Master Chu is truly unfathomable!"

"Such methods, how much black oil can he get each time?"

Gu Masters were in admiration and envy, their respect towards Fang Yuan increased again.

"Don't worry, with me around, you will all be safe." Fang Yuan's action was just to reassure these people, but at the next moment, the smile on his face froze.

His sight was stuck on the mermaid's face, he went into a daze.

"Mo Er?!"